By the way, are you free on Sunday?
Yeah.
You said you wanted to eat omelette rice.
I found a good restaurant.
Yeah.
I'll see you then.
What?
Oh, after that.
Where should we go?
Oh.
You like cats, don't you?
How about a cat cafe?
Can I come in?
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh.
Ayako, what's wrong?
What?
I'm just here because I'm free.
Oh, is that so?
What about you?
Oh, I'm on the phone right now.
What about your girlfriend?
Oh, well.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Oh.
Oh, sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no, it's not like that.
Well, yeah.
It's my sister.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's just...
Oh, yeah.
No, it's really nothing.
Oh, wait a minute.
Ayako, what are you doing?
I was wondering what you were talking about.
What are you talking about?
No, it's okay.
I'd like to make a phone call.
I'm sorry, but...
Can you not disturb me?
Quietly?
Oh, well, yeah.
Quietly.
Oh, I see.
Go ahead.
I see.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Can I?
Then, the cat wall.
Yeah.
I wanted to go there, too.
Oh, no.
I've never been there.
I was wondering what it was like.
Oh.
What?
Oh, well.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, yeah.
It's pretty close.
I looked it up.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's kind of like...
It's kind of like it's near the online shop.
Really.
What?
Wait, wait a minute.
What are you doing?
What?
No, nothing.
No, it's really nothing.
Yeah.
I'm totally fine.
Yeah, you're right.
Um, well, I'll call you later.
Yeah, yeah, I'll see you later.
Hey, what are you doing?
What?
Nothing.
I was bored, so I was just playing.
You're always like this.
What do you want to do? Don't bother me.
Why? I'm just trying to communicate with my brother.
This is not communication with your brother.
Is it?
Yes, it is.
What? No?
No.
Why?
It's not why.
It's okay. I'm older than you.
Well, that's...
Right?
A man and a woman of the same age live in the same house.
You suddenly became an older sister.
Don't you have anything else?
What do you mean?
You have, right?
For example, you've been living alone.
You didn't have a family or a brother.
You didn't have a sister, either.
Finally, you have a sister.
Don't you feel nervous?
Don't you feel like you're getting closer to her?
No, I don't.
Well, look at her.
I don't want to say it myself, but...
I think she's a pretty good woman.
What do you think?
Well, I have a girlfriend.
I didn't expect to have a sister so soon.
But this is what Ayako is like.
I'm not used to it.
I see.
I want to make her happy.
I really like her.
So you don't want her to get in the way, do you?
No, I don't.
I support her.
But isn't it more fun to play with me than a cat cafe?
No, it's not fun at all.
That's what I'm saying.
No, it's not.
Let's get to know each other a little more.
Besides,
you've been worried about her, haven't you?
See?
No, I haven't.
You've been looking at her, haven't you?
But you have.
I told you I haven't.
Really?
Yes, I have.
What size is her boobs?
Are they bigger than mine?
Well, they might be a little small, but...
See?
What do you think?
No, that's enough.
Why?
Why don't you come home and play with her boobs?
What are you talking about?
No, no.
If you want to make a girlfriend while she's here, you're cheating.
But she's your sister, so you're not cheating, are you?
Even if you say that,
I'm not cheating.
But you're looking at her, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Stop it, please.
But you're looking at her, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
But you are.
But you're not looking at her, are you?
No, I'm not.
Really?
Yes, I am.
But you're saying,
you're actually looking at her.
It's like an erotic anime.
So stop it, please.
Stop touching her boobs.
Ayako, stop it.
Get out of here.
Why are you so angry?
You don't have to be angry.
I'm angry.
Stop it, please.
Please don't do this again.
What should I do?
Just get out of here.
Ayako, what's wrong with you?
Why are you doing that to me?
Please forgive me.
I'm so angry.
It's so annoying.
I'm going to call Ayumi.
Hello, Ayumi?
Yes, I'm sorry about earlier.
I'm so angry.
I'm going to tell her I'm better than her.
Don't worry.
She won't bother you like before.
She's hiding in her bed.
I'm so sorry.
I know.
But I want to talk to her on the phone.
I want to hear her voice.
Yes, I'm angry, too.
Please touch me.
There's no one here.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Where are you touching?
You're better than her, right?
It's nothing.
You have a big boob, don't you?
If you don't be quiet, she'll find out.
Call her.
Hello?
It's nothing.
I'm talking about the cat's hair.
Tell me then
Nothing. It's OK
Yes, yes. So that's the way
There's nothing in there.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's true.
I'll call you back.
Why did you hang up on me?
You can still do it.
What are you doing?
Why did you hang up on me?
I'm talking about this.
You're so sick.
You're sick.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
If you move your neck, I'll hit you.
Why?
You're out of your mind.
What are you looking at?
What?
What do you mean?
It's a nice underwear, isn't it?
It's cute, isn't it?
I can see it.
Where have you been looking at?
I'm not looking at you.
I'm looking at you, so I'm out of my mind.
You're so sick.
No, I'm not.
Are you sure?
Stop it.
You smelled it.
Do you want to smell it?
What does it smell like?
Tell me.
I don't know.
Don't you smell her?
Answer me.
I don't smell her.
I can't hear you.
What do you think of her?
You don't know her, do you?
I'm sorry.
I am so sick of you.
Look at my results.
Please open the door.
It's in.
Oh no.
You can't take it off.
What?
Why?
Why can't I take it off?
I have a girlfriend.
It's okay.
We're brothers.
What?
It's okay.
What do you think?
I feel better than her, right?
That's...
What?
What do you mean?
Hey.
It feels good.
Oh no.
What do you mean?
What do you think?
I feel better than her, right?
That's...
What?
If you don't say it, I'll take it off.
It feels good.
Which one?
Say it again.
It feels good.
Better than her?
Really?
It feels good.
She won't do this to me, right?
Oh no.
What?
It feels good.
Really?
It feels good?
She grabbed my blanket.
It feels good.
Do you want me to rub your belly?
Why are you so energetic?
Even when you're with your girlfriend,
you're energetic?
You're energetic?
What?
I'm more energetic than her?
Yes.
Really?
I'm going to sleep if you lie to me.
It feels good.
Oh no.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Oh no.
Really?
Which part feels better?
My belly.
Only your belly?
What about this part?
My nipples.
Does this part feel good?
It feels good.
Does your girlfriend
Does your girlfriend rub your nipples
Does your girlfriend rub your nipples all the time?
No, she doesn't.
I see.
Do you?
Are you tired of this?
No, my head is breaking.
What?
It's so tight.
Stop it.
Don't break it.
But...
What?
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
What should I do?
It's in there, right?
If it feels better than that, I'll take it out.
What? No?
Don't you want to take it out?
I want to take it out.
Ah, no.
It's too late to say it, so no.
But...
You can't say no to your brother.
It's communication, right?
Communication.
Right?
You like being patted on the neck like this.
I like it.
What?
You don't want to be my girlfriend?
No, I don't.
No.
I feel sorry for you.
If I were you, I'd do this a lot for you.
Why?
Right?
Yes.
Why?
It feels good.
Wait a minute.
What?
I'll go.
Don't you want to go?
Ouch!
I don't want to.
I'm so nervous.
I'm sweating a lot.
Hey.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sorry.
Do you do this to your girlfriend?
No, I've never done that.
What?
Really?
Yes.
So, you've never done this to me?
No, I've never.
What's the matter?
You're standing up.
You can do this to your girlfriend.
No, I've never done that.
No?
No.
Really?
Then, I'm the only one.
Hey, you're standing up.
You're going to vomit again.
You're going to vomit.
I won't let you vomit.
You do it.
Do it yourself.
Here you are.
You've grown up so much.
I want you to put it in here.
Can I?
Yes, you can.
Here you are.
Can I put it in here?
Yes, you can.
It's too late.
Come on.
Here you are.
It's too late.
What?
Wait a minute.
It's moving.
Then I won't move.
What?
Come on.
Here you are.
Didn't you want to move?
It feels good.
You've grown up so much.
Here you are.
It feels good.
You're still nervous inside.
Yes.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Come on.
You want to stay inside, don't you?
Yes, I want to stay inside.
You have to grow up.
You're in trouble.
I'm in trouble.
I can't move.
It feels good.
It's not enough.
Come on.
Yes.
Shake your hips as much as you want.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
More.
Did you shake your hips like her?
No, I didn't.
What?
Did you shake your hips like her?
No, I didn't.
Yes, I did.
Tell me.
It's amazing.
No.
It feels good.
Go away.
You're in trouble.
It feels good.
Do you want more?
Yes.
More.
Is it enough?
Come on.
Did you shake your hips like her?
It feels good.
What?
Does it feel good?
Did you shake your hips like her?
No.
I don't like a man like you.
You have to shake your hips by yourself.
By myself?
Yes.
It feels good.
No.
Go away.
You're in trouble.
I'm sorry.
Do you want more?
Yes.
It feels good.
Here.
More.
Yes.
It feels good.
Touch my boobs.
Yes.
It feels good.
More.
Shake your hips more.
It feels good.
Yes.
You're in trouble.
Do you shake your hips like her?
No.
I see.
You're in trouble.
It feels good.
No.
You're in trouble.
It feels good.
No.
Go away.
You're in trouble.
More.
Shake your hips more.
Yes.
You're in trouble.
It feels good.
You were making a big noise.
You're in trouble.
It feels good?
It's more pleasant than her, right?
It's true.
No.
It feels good.
You're in trouble.
Go away.
It feels so good.
Do it more.
It's not enough.
Come on.
It feels so good.
Wow.
It's here, right?
You like here, right?
It feels so good.
Wow.
Wait.
It's here.
It's not enough.
Hold your waist more.
Hit it more.
It's not enough.
It's not enough to make you my girlfriend.
Ah.
No.
Don't do that.
It's the best.
No.
It's not enough.
Give me more.
Wow.
Hey.
It's not enough.
Wow.
Why?
It's here.
Come on.
Ah.
It feels so good.
Shake your waist.
Do you always do this with your girlfriend?
What?
Only this time?
Only when you're young?
It's boring.
I have to hit you more.
It feels so good.
No, you can't do that.
More, more, more.
More, properly.
Shake your hips more.
Please shake your hips more.
No, you can't.
Oh, no.
Hey, it feels good.
Oh, no, here.
Here is good.
No, it feels good.
I'm going.
Oh, no.
Hey, why are you taking it off on your own?
You can't take it off.
What?
Take it off.
More.
You can't take it off on your own.
You can't take it off.
Oh, it feels good.
Take it out more.
Put your mind in me.
Take it out more than her.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, no.
I'm going.
Oh, it feels good.
Give me more.
More.
Oh, no.
Give me more.
I'm going.
Why are you doing that?
Oh, my God.
I'm surprised.
I did it.
There's a lot.
It's good.
You have to clean it up.
Oh, my God.
You're getting bigger.
It's good.
I'll put it in for you.
Who is it?
It's my girlfriend.
It's not coming out.
Come on, come on, come on.
I can't get out now.
Hello?
I'm sorry.
I came all of a sudden.
What's wrong?
I can't do this.
I'm coming in.
Are you doing it again?
No, I'm not.
I want to squeeze a little more.
Are you doing this again?
I'll try a lot of things.
I see.
Is it like that?
Your girlfriend?
Do you like someone who has muscles like that?
Well, there's that, too.
I thought I wasn't good enough.
I see.
Is that why you're working out?
Yes.
I haven't done it yet.
I see.
I have to do more.
You're working out.
You and I are brothers.
We don't go out at all.
I don't mind.
Can I squeeze more?
I don't mind if I don't squeeze it.
Let's hang out more.
No, a little more.
What?
We're brothers.
Let's get to know each other better.
I'd like you to squeeze me a little more.
Come on, sit here.
I don't know.
We're brothers.
Don't you have anything you're happy about?
Don't you have a sister you admire?
I did admire her.
I'm your sister, so I'm happy.
I'm happy to have a younger brother.
Are you different?
I'm happy.
Really?
Do you really think so?
I do.
Then why are you working out?
I want to squeeze more.
I told you that you don't have to do it.
I'm happy.
You're happy, aren't you?
Yes.
Let's hang out more.
But I have to squeeze more.
I told you that you don't have to do it.
But...
What?
Don't you like it?
No, I don't.
Are you happy?
I'm happy.
I don't get it.
You have to show me that you're happy.
I'm sorry.
Don't you invite me to hang out?
I want to invite you.
Then invite me.
But I have to squeeze more.
I don't like it.
If you don't like it, I'll work out.
I want to work out my butt and my chest.
I don't mind.
Will you work out with me?
Of course.
You don't play with me.
How do you do this?
Is this right?
That's right.
Like this?
Yes.
How do you do this?
That's right.
Really?
Tell me how to do this.
Stretch your back like this.
Like this?
Is this right?
Are you looking at me?
I'm working out my back.
You're good.
Where are you looking at?
I'm not looking anywhere.
You're lying.
You're looking at me, aren't you?
No.
I'm serious.
You can touch me.
No.
You're my sister.
You can touch me.
I can't.
Why?
You can touch me.
I can't.
I don't mind if you touch me.
But...
You're my sister.
You can touch me.
I can't.
Why?
Why not?
I have a girlfriend.
It doesn't matter. You're my sister.
I don't care.
But...
You're my sister, so I won't cheat on you.
I will.
You want me to touch you, don't you?
You can touch me.
Can I?
Yes, you can.
I can't.
Why not? You're my sister.
What's wrong with you?
Rinka, what's wrong with you?
You're always like this.
You always bother me.
You're always working out with your girlfriend.
I'm doing my best.
But you don't get better at all.
I'll make you like me.
Look at me.
I did 50 push-ups and rollers today.
You, too?
Squats?
I'll do squats, too.
I think I'm not good at it.
Look forward to it.
Where are you going next week?
That's good.
I'll make a reservation.
Let's make it a little higher.
No, it's okay.
Wait a minute.
I'm on the phone with my girlfriend.
Can you answer the phone?
Are you on the phone with your girlfriend?
Yes.
Why are you on the phone?
Answer the phone.
Hello?
It's okay.
Leave it to me.
I'll take care of it.
I'll hang up the phone.
You can call her.
It's okay.
It's really okay.
I'll continue to do muscle training.
You should continue, too.
Let's train together next time.
Let's train together.
Let's do it on our next date.
It's okay.
I know that.
I'm a member, so it's okay.
Yes.
What?
It's okay.
I'm in the middle of training.
Can I call you later?
I'll call you later.
Yes.
I'm in the middle of training.
It's hard.
Yes.
I'll call you later.
See you.
Mom.
What is it?
What is this?
Why is it like this?
I'll touch it.
Will it be like this if I touch it?
It will be like this.
I can't do it.
Look at this.
It's a training wear I bought a long time ago.
It's too big.
Is it a little small?
It's a little small.
How is it?
I think it's really good.
Really?
How is it?
I think it's really good.
Really?
It's too small for a training wear.
I bought it a long time ago.
I see.
How is your butt?
My butt?
How is it?
This is...
Is this really a training wear?
Yes, it is.
It's like a titty bag.
You said you were going to do muscle training.
I thought I'd do it with you because it's a muscle training bag.
It's not a training wear, is it?
It's a training wear.
Really?
How is it?
It's amazing.
This is...
Look at this.
Don't make fun of me.
You're older than me.
I can't.
Why?
Look.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's cute.
You're staring at me.
I think it's good.
Look.
If you make fun of me like that...
If you make fun of me like that, what?
I can't control myself.
It's amazing.
How is it?
Which do you like better, her or me?
Well...
Aren't you older than me?
No, I'm not.
I'm not older than you. I won't make fun of you.
What?
I can't choose.
Which do you like better, her or me?
I don't know.
Come on.
Which do you like better, her or me?
You're older than me, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Come on.
Aren't you older than me?
Which do you like better, her or me?
I don't know.
What?
Come on.
Which do you like better, her or me?
What?
Hey.
Are you still hesitating?
You're beautiful, too.
Come on. Which do you like better?
I don't know.
Come on.
Which do you like better, her or me?
I don't know.
Come on.
Which do you like better, her or me?
I don't know.
Come on.
Aren't you older than me?
No, I'm not.
Come on.
Which do you like better, her or me?
I don't know.
Come on.
Aren't you older than me?
No, I'm not.
Are you older than me?
Come on.
I've never seen such beautiful boobs.
What?
So, you like them better.
Yes.
Come on.
Wow.
They're so slender.
It's hot.
Come on.
They're amazing.
I can tell from your T-shirt.
I know.
You like them better, don't you?
Yes.
I like them.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
They're so slender.
Come on.
Do you want more?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
What's this?
It's hard.
It's always been hard.
I can tell.
It's hot.
What?
Does it feel good?
Come on.
It's hot.
Oh, no.
Rai-kun.
It's a mess.
It's amazing.
What?
It's a mess.
Do you want me to touch you?
It's hot.
It's very hard.
What?
It's a mess.
What? Is it?
Rai-kun, does it feel good?
It's amazing.
It's a mess here.
Does it feel good?
Rai-kun, does it feel good?
Do you want me to touch you?
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
It's always been hard.
It's amazing.
Do you want me to touch you?
Does it feel good?
No, Rai-kun.
Be patient.
It's amazing.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Do you like me?
Does it feel good?
It's amazing.
It's getting harder and harder.
It's hard.
What?
It's amazing.
Do you like me?
It's getting harder and harder.
No, be patient.
It's amazing.
It's hard, isn't it?
Does it feel good?
It's amazing.
I'm going to give you a lot.
What do you think, Rai-kun?
She won't do this to you, will she?
It's amazing.
Do you like me?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
I'm going to give you a lot.
You can give me a lot.
It's amazing.
What is it?
You can't move that much.
I want to eat.
What is it?
Do you want to lick me?
It's okay.
Rai-kun, you love me too much.
It's amazing.
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
I'm full.
Rai-kun, does it feel good?
What's wrong, Rai-kun?
I want to give you a lot.
It's okay.
Is it okay?
Really?
Just give me a lot.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
Maybe she won't let me do it.
Just give me a lot.
It's okay.
Rai-kun, does it feel good?
It feels good.
What's wrong with you?
It's okay.
Rai-kun, does it feel good?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I want to give you more.
Me, too.
It feels good.
That's a lot.
Rai-kun, does it feel good?
It feels good.
What should I do?
Does it feel good?
That's a lot.
It's okay.
Have you ever given it to your girlfriend?
No, I haven't.
It's okay.
That's a lot.
Rai-kun.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's still hard.
It's coming back.
Will it come back?
Yes.
I'll put it in here.
It's in there.
That's a lot.
Rai-kun, does it feel good?
Does it feel good?
That's a lot.
Do you like it?
It feels good.
I want to touch you.
It's okay.
That's a lot.
Rai-kun, does it feel good?
It's okay.
I'll put it on your back.
That's a lot.
I want to do it more.
Rai-kun, does it feel good?
It's okay.
That's a lot.
Rai-kun, does it feel good?
I'm nervous again.
Rai-kun, let me do it again.
That's a lot.
I can't do it anymore.
Rai-kun.
Rai-kun's girlfriend.
Rai-kun and I.
Let's play with the three of us.
The three of us?
Yes, the three of us.
Is it okay?
Don't you like it?
It's okay, right?
Let's play with the three of us.
In front of her.
Rai-kun.
What?
You can do it, right?
Are you almost there?
Yes.
Did you enter the elevator hall?
Do you know the room number?
Yes.
Then...
Just ring the doorbell.
I'm going to pick you up at the entrance.
See you later.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Um...
Is my girlfriend outside?
Your girlfriend?
She's over there.
What?
Um...
Is she not here?
She's not here.
Why?
When I told her that I'm your girlfriend,
she got angry and left.
What?
She's not here.
Why?
Why did you say that?
Because you don't care about me at all.
No...
What?
It's obvious that you don't care about me.
No...
What?
I want you to care about me.
No...
Um...
Why do you always do that?
You don't care about me at all.
As your sister,
you should be nice to her.
You should be nice to her.
Don't do that.
It's obvious that you don't care about me.
I want you to care about me.
No...
Then,
let's play with her.
What?
Look at this.
Wait.
Don't hide it.
Don't you see it?
Look at this.
I saw it.
Don't tease me.
I'm not teasing you.
You are.
Look at this.
Her boobs are small.
What?
I don't like her boobs.
You like me more than her, don't you?
What?
No.
It's not like that.
Anyway,
I'm going to look for her.
Are you going?
No.
I'm going to look for her.
I think I'm better than her.
She's not here.
She must be angry.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
She's not angry.
It's your fault.
Why?
I can't get in touch with her.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Did I do something wrong?
It's not a problem.
I don't talk to you anymore.
Really?
Why do you lie to me?
I'm pretty angry.
I don't know what's going on.
Cheer up.
You're older than her, aren't you?
No?
I'm older than her now.
Come on.
I can't do it this time.
Look at this and cheer up.
Look.
All right.
What do you think? Isn't it cute?
Come on.
It's not like that.
But you always look at it like that.
What do you think?
You can't show it to me.
Isn't it good? Look at this.
Look at this.
What?
You got it from abroad, didn't you?
From abroad?
Isn't it good?
Are you happy?
No, I'm not happy.
I'm angry.
Look at this.
Don't you want to look at it?
You should look at it.
It's bigger than her, isn't it?
Well...
A little.
A little?
She was small.
A little.
You like it, don't you?
Don't touch it.
It's cute.
A little.
What's wrong?
It's hot.
Hey.
What's wrong?
It's hot.
Don't you want to look at it?
Hey.
It's not good.
We're siblings.
Hey.
What's wrong?
What?
It's hot.
We're siblings.
Don't you want to look at it?
No.
Hey.
Do siblings do this?
I don't know.
Don't you want to look at it?
No.
Drink a lot.
Is it big?
It's big.
It's big, isn't it?
You can lick it.
What?
No.
I can't lick it.
You can lick it.
What?
I want you to lick it.
Did you eat?
Have you ever had your girlfriend do this?
No.
No, right?
How's your nipples?
Nipples?
I don't know yet.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
You won't do this to me, will you?
I want you to do this to me.
It's the best.
It's hot.
How do you do it?
I've only done it normally.
What do you mean by normal?
I'll do it.
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear that.
Are you excited?
Yes.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
You're older than your girlfriend, aren't you?
That's...
It's hot.
Hey, Jiro.
Yes?
What do you want me to do?
What?
I want to see your pussy.
Do you want to see it?
Yes.
I'll show you.
Okay.
Wow.
What do you think of my pussy?
Well...
Can you show me more?
Okay.
Wow.
Can you touch me?
Yes.
Wow.
Is it amazing?
Your pussy is beautiful.
Is it beautiful?
Yes.
You can do whatever you want.
Okay.
Wow.
Does it feel good, Jiro?
Really?
Yes.
Can I touch you more?
More?
Yes.
Jiro.
Wow.
Hey.
Yes?
I want to see your pussy.
Okay.
Look at me.
Wow.
Which one do you like more?
Which one?
Well...
I think I like you more.
Really?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Wow.
Can I look at your pussy?
Yes.
It's special, isn't it?
Wow.
Wow, Jiro.
You're good.
Really?
Congratulations.
What?
I'm nervous.
I want to see your pussy.
Wow.
It feels good.
Can I touch you more?
More?
Yes.
Wow.
You didn't care about me until now.
I didn't care about you.
I'm nervous.
Wow, Jiro.
You made me nervous.
Yes.
Wow.
Jiro.
Yes.
Don't you want to touch me?
What?
It feels good.
No, no, no.
What?
I mean...
I have a girlfriend.
I can't touch you.
You can't?
Oh.
Why?
But it feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
More than she does.
It feels good.
Yes.
Oh.
Wow.
You're a big sister after all.
I know.
Oh.
That's...
Hmm.
Oh.
Wow.
It's cold.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Do you want me to pinch your lips?
You don't have to.
I'll do it for you.
Do you want me to do it?
Yes.
I'll do it for you.
Have you ever had a girlfriend like this?
No.
You haven't, have you?
It's cold.
Is it cold?
It feels good.
You look like you're in a good mood.
You're getting bigger.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
You want to have a girlfriend, don't you?
I can't stand it anymore.
Really?
Do you want to have a girlfriend?
I'm glad you chose me.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Is it amazing?
Have you ever gotten a massage like this?
I've never had my hair up.
It feels good.
I'm going to die.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
I'm going to die.
I want to see more.
It feels good.
I'm going to die.
Have you ever been in a relationship with your girlfriend?
No, I haven't.
I'm going to die.
Let me go.
I'm sorry.
I'm not sorry.
It felt good, didn't it?
It felt good.
I'm sorry.
I'll hit you again.
Again?
It's so hot.
I'm going to die.
Can I move?
You can move.
Hang in there.
It's so hot.
I'm going to die.
Are you okay?
Hang in there.
I'm going to die.
Can you open your butt?
It's so hot.
I love you.
Can I do it again?
It's okay.
It's so hot.
I'm going to die.
I slept a lot.
It's so hot.
It felt good, didn't it?
It felt good.
Are you tired?
I'm going to die.
I got a message from her.
Excuse me.
I'll tell her that I want to break up with her.
I'm better than her.
I sent it to her.
It was fun to go on a date with Ichika.
I'll send her a picture.
She's so cute.
Where should I go next time?
You're kissing me.
I was surprised.
Welcome back.
Why did you come in?
There's no one here.
I was waiting for you.
You always tell me not to come in.
Show me the picture.
I don't want to.
Can I go out?
Show me the picture.
I don't want to.
You're going to a fancy cafe.
Give it back to me.
Show me the picture.
Is she called Ichika?
She's so cute.
I like her.
Isn't she cuter than you?
I don't care.
Tell me the truth.
Isn't she cuter than you?
I can't decide.
You can't decide?
But you won't deny it.
I think you're beautiful.
Ichika is cute.
What?
I didn't hear you.
Say it again.
Ichika is better.
What?
Ichika is better?
I won't say it.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
Ichika is cuter than you.
But you like her, don't you?
Why do you think so?
Don't you think so?
You're my family.
I like you.
But I don't like Ichika.
What do you like about her?
I don't know.
Please stay away from me.
Why?
I don't know.
Ichika is...
Ichika is cute, too.
She has beautiful skin.
She is young, but...
What do you think about me?
I'm confident about my legs.
Please put your legs down.
Why?
Please stop.
Please look at my legs.
I won't.
Please put your legs down.
I won't do that.
Do you want to see more?
What are you doing?
What do you think?
I won't touch you.
Please touch me.
I feel good.
I don't know.
Please touch me.
You are soft.
What are you doing?
You are looking at my pants, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
You are weird.
What?
Are you drunk?
No, I'm not.
How do I look?
It's cute, isn't it?
I don't know that.
You don't know?
Please stop.
This string is cute, isn't it?
How do I look?
Do I look like this?
What?
I've never done this before.
Why are you so angry?
I'm not angry.
You are like me.
I'm sorry.
Your pants are not enough.
Please stop.
Do I look like this?
It's cute, isn't it?
It's the same.
Please stop.
Are you angry?
No, I'm not.
What's wrong?
What if my parents see this?
What are you going to do?
You don't have anything, do you?
You are my family.
My family?
I feel like I'm being teased.
I'm not being teased.
I feel like I'm being treated like a child.
I don't like it.
I'm not being treated like a child.
We just became a family.
I feel a little more excited.
I want a man.
I'm excited.
I'm not interested.
Normally, when a man has a younger sister, he is not excited.
I'm excited.
That's the feeling of tension.
Do you want that kind of thing?
No, I think it's only in the world of dramas.
What?
It's not like that at all.
You think of me as a woman, don't you?
When you look at me like this, you get nervous, don't you?
Hey, are you really satisfied with Ichika?
What do you mean?
You get nervous, don't you?
Like this part.
I know because I like it.
Really?
If I were you, I would do everything you want to do.
What?
You're really not satisfied, aren't you?
That's not what I meant.
What?
Well...
Of course not.
You wouldn't do something like this, would you?
What?
Like this.
It's not good.
What's not good?
If I do something like this, you'll find out.
I haven't done anything wrong.
I'm your sister.
I have to do something like this for you.
I have a girlfriend.
But you're not satisfied, are you?
Let me go.
You don't seem to be satisfied.
I don't know what satisfaction is.
You don't know?
It doesn't matter.
I'll make sure you're satisfied.
What are you doing?
You're right.
Would you do something like this for me?
Like this.
I wouldn't do something like this.
It's not normal.
You're really not satisfied.
It tickles.
You're twitching.
Let me go.
You're too close.
What?
Look at me.
What are you doing?
You're playing with me.
I'm tickling you.
You're really not satisfied.
Let me go.
It tickles.
What?
Look at me.
What are you doing?
You're playing with me.
You don't have to tickle me.
You're really happy, aren't you?
What are you going to do if you find out?
Please keep it a secret.
I don't know.
You're not satisfied, are you?
I don't care.
Let me go.
Please keep it a secret.
What should I do?
It tickles.
You're not aware of it.
What should I do?
Tatsuya-kun.
You're looking at me like that.
You're really tickling me.
If I push you a little more, will you be satisfied?
You're cute.
What should I do?
What should I take off today?
I bought a lot of things.
I have a lot of things.
There are a lot of cute actresses.
This is good.
It tickles.
You're really tickling me.
You're looking at me like that.
What are you doing?
You like that kind of thing.
No.
Do you always dress like this?
You don't know, do you?
You told me not to come in.
Please forgive me.
Even if I ask you to come in, you won't come out.
I can't wear it.
Please come out.
I won't.
Tell me what you think.
What do you think?
What do I think?
I don't know. I haven't seen it.
I won't come out unless you tell me what you think.
What is that?
Look at me.
I haven't seen it.
It's pretty close here.
Don't you think it's heavy?
I don't know even if you explain it.
Maybe it's transparent here, too.
What do you think?
I understand, so please come out.
You can't tell unless you look at the whole body, can you?
What do you think?
You have a lot of hair on your butt.
Look closely.
That's enough.
What do you mean, enough?
Ichiko, you can't wear this kind of thing, can you?
I think I look better in this kind of thing.
Look closely.
I think it's good.
I think it's good, but...
I don't know until you tell me clearly.
It's good.
What do you think?
Does it look good on you?
Look closely.
I've already seen it.
You haven't seen it, have you?
What do you think?
What do you like?
I don't know.
Are you excited?
I'm not excited.
You're not excited?
You're standing.
Please stop.
You're standing a lot.
This is the AV I was watching earlier.
The AV you were watching earlier?
How many minutes ago?
You're standing.
No, this has nothing to do with it.
What are you doing?
It's getting harder and harder.
Please stop.
You were really excited to see this, weren't you?
No, I wasn't.
Were you really nervous about your sister?
My legs are a little...
What's wrong with your legs?
This isn't normal.
It's not normal.
But earlier...
What's wrong? Does it feel good here?
No, I don't like it.
You were crying in the AV earlier.
I will.
It's not a bad thing, is it?
You're not satisfied with her, are you?
No, it's not like that.
I'll do anything for you.
Really?
Yes.
I don't like it.
You're saying you don't like it, but you're really excited.
Please stop.
Don't say that.
You're saying you don't like it, but you're so excited.
Are you excited about yourself saying you don't like it?
What's wrong with you?
Are you serious?
What?
It's hard.
It's hard?
Do you want to do something worse?
You're excited, aren't you?
Is it better to do it directly?
Come on.
It's hard.
You're not going to do that, are you?
It's harder than before, isn't it?
This is...
Where are you touching?
With my feet.
Wait a minute.
It's hard.
It's embarrassing.
You don't know what I'm talking about, do you?
Please lick me more.
It's hard.
You're not going to do this, are you?
I'll teach you more.
It's hard.
You can touch me more.
You don't let me touch you so much, do you?
It's hard.
Please lick me more.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm going to satisfy you.
I'm your sister.
You're a good boy.
You've never seen this room before, have you?
Look closely.
You're going to get in there.
You're not going to do this, are you?
I'll teach you a lot of things.
Look closely.
You can touch me or lick me.
It's hard.
Your skin is wet.
It's wet, isn't it?
It's okay.
It's hard.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Please lick me a lot.
It's hard.
I feel good.
I think it'll be over in a minute.
It's hard.
Like this?
It's hard, isn't it?
You look like you're in a good mood, don't you?
You look like you're in a good mood.
Are you always like this?
You're always wet.
It's hard.
No, not again.
I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
You don't want me to do this, do you?
I'm sorry.
It's hard.
You're in a good mood, aren't you?
Can you lick me this much?
I'm...
I'm not...
I'm not dressed like this.
You're more excited to dress like this, aren't you?
It's hard.
Don't hide it.
You're in love.
You don't have to do it yourself.
I'll make you feel better.
It's hard.
How do you feel?
Please stop.
It's hard.
What are you doing?
Can you eat this much?
It's hard.
How do you feel?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Did you feel so good?
It's hard.
It's still hard.
I didn't mean to.
It's true.
It's hard.
You're more excited, aren't you?
What are you doing?
You want to sleep, don't you?
What?
I'm sorry.
It's the only thing I can do.
It's hard.
This is the first time I've heard of it, so I'm not sure if it's true or not.
I'm not sure if it's true or not.