Graduate Student Information
You got tons of homework today...
What can I do for you?
Actually, I'm easy.
I really don't like teacher's homework.
But if you'd like me to, I really want to!
You two get along well even at work, don't you?
Ueda-sensei.
I didn't expect you two to get married.
Are you taking care of the house?
Koichi-kun.
I'm helping.
The life of a couple is helping each other.
Otherwise, Rino-sensei will not be able to finish her work like a cow.
Ueda-sensei.
Please stop.
By the way, Rino-sensei.
What happened to your students after that?
I don't have a class after this, so I'm going to see what's going on.
I have to go back to school, so I can't stay that long.
I see.
Watanabe Shinji-kun, right?
Does he talk to you?
Yeah.
I can talk to him sometimes.
Oh, that's great.
Yes.
But it seems that my parents are not on a business trip, so I hope they can rely on me more.
It's because you're young and difficult.
Yeah.
It's hard to get such an education.
Well, that's interesting, though.
That's true.
Rino-sensei.
It's time to go.
Hello.
Shinji-kun, I'm here to deliver your homework.
Please wait a minute.
Can I come in?
Yes, you can.
Can I sit down?
Did you study?
I'll give you your homework tomorrow.
Yes.
It's until tomorrow, so do it well.
Shinji-kun can do it.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Oh, you're studying hard.
You're almost correct.
That's great.
You can do it.
Shinji-kun, you're really smart.
If there's anything you don't understand, I'll tell you, so tell me.
Yes.
But your room is a little messy.
I'll clean it up.
Rino-sensei.
Yes.
Okay.
I cleaned it up.
It's still a little hot.
I'm going back to school soon, so do your homework.
And I'd be happy if you came to school.
I'll be waiting.
I'm going.
Yes.
Rino-sensei.
Rino, don't be so down.
But Shinji-kun stopped talking to me again.
That's how men in puberty are.
Is that so?
That's right.
Rather, your grades are better.
You can study at home and that's fine.
If you spend so much time with your students, there's no end.
I know, but I want you to experience a lot of things other than studying.
If you say so, I won't object.
Well, I'll try to face Shinji-kun a little more.
Yes.
More than that.
Are you free tonight?
Yes, I'm free.
I love you.
Me too.
Rino, it feels so good.
Rino, you can do it.
No, hang in there a little longer.
No.
Ah.
Did you go already?
I'm sorry.
It's been a while, so it felt really good.
Did you feel good too?
Yes.
But it would have been better if it had been a little longer.
I'm sorry. It felt so good.
Well, I'm going to take a shower first.
Quick-sightedness.
Any woman will feel sick.
Looking for a man.
This is a high-concentration purified liquid.
Well, that's all for today.
Good morning.
Rino.
Yes?
Are you going to see Watanabe again today?
Yes.
He's starting to talk to me like before.
I see.
But I think you're the only one who's amazing.
I don't care.
I'm going to see him again today.
Yes.
See you.
Is it that effective?
Yes.
Shinichi, it's Rino.
Can I come in?
Come in.
I'm sorry.
It took me a long time to gather the materials.
It's still hot.
It was hot outside, wasn't it?
If you don't mind,
this is for you.
For me?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'll take it.
Wait a minute.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Can you teach me how to study?
I don't know how to study.
Of course.
Thank you.
This is it.
Here?
Yes.
This is the formula for the answer.
Let me see.
Yes.
This is the formula for the answer.
In order to get the answer,
do you know the formula here?
P minus 2 plus L.
P minus 2 minus 1 is the whole number.
Yes.
Let's solve this.
Let me see.
X equals 2 times P minus 4 plus minus root.
P minus 4 times 2.
Yes.
It's done.
I don't know why there's a minus here.
If you look here,
you'll know.
If you do it here,
it's done.
Really?
Yes.
I don't know why there's a minus here.
Isn't this room hot?
Really?
I set it to 20 degrees.
Doctor, did you catch a cold?
I don't know.
Are you okay?
Let's study.
But you'll catch a cold.
I'm fine.
I have to study.
No.
You're not well.
Are you okay?
I have to study.
You're out of breath.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
I have to study.
No.
I'm worried about you.
It's not time for that.
Doctor,
you should drink more tea.
Yes.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Are you tired?
I'll give you a massage.
Really?
You have a fever.
Are you tired?
Shinichi, I'm sorry.
I caught a cold.
Doctor, you should go to bed.
No.
I'll go home.
I'm sorry.
I'll go to bed.
It's almost over.
But it's amazing.
The medicine worked.
What's wrong with me?
I have a fever.
I can't stand it.
What's wrong with me?
What did I do?
I can't stand it.
Shinichi.
Hello, Shinichi.
I called you because I was worried about you.
You're breathing.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm fine now.
Doctor.
You look sick.
You have a fever.
I'm worried about you.
I have a fever?
Don't say that.
I see.
Doctor.
I'm grateful to you.
I'll go to school next time.
Really?
I'll try to go to school tomorrow.
Okay.
I'll wait for you.
You're finally here.
Thank you for your hard work.
Doctor.
Watanabe didn't come to the first class.
I see.
I should have picked him up in the morning.
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
Doctor.
I'm sorry.
I...
Shinichi.
Don't worry about it.
No.
If something happens to you...
Doctor.
What's the next class?
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Watanabe is in trouble.
Is he coming?
Shinichi.
Are you okay?
Can I come in?
Yes.
I'm glad.
I was worried about you.
Doctor.
You came.
Yes.
I'm glad you came.
Shinichi.
I was worried about you.
Doctor.
I'm sorry I couldn't go to school.
No.
It's okay.
You're so thin.
You came running.
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
You're kind.
Thank you.
Thank you, Shinichi.
You took care of me.
But I couldn't do anything.
No.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Doctor.
You're sweating.
I'll wipe it off.
Thank you.
It's okay.
I'll wipe it off.
Stop it.
You're sweating.
It's okay.
No.
By the way.
Were you okay?
Yes.
You're the same as before.
Shinichi.
No.
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
I'm trying not to smell like you.
No.
You're out of breath again.
Are you sick again?
I'm fine.
You should sleep more.
Shinichi.
No.
Stop it.
You're out of breath.
You're sweating.
I'll wipe it off.
No.
It's hot, isn't it?
Shinichi, stop it.
I'll wipe it off.
No.
It's hot.
You should sleep more.
Stop it.
It's okay.
I'll wipe it off.
Stop it.
Shinichi, stop it.
It's okay.
You're out of breath.
I'll wipe it off.
I'm glad you're okay.
You're out of breath.
It's hot.
I'll wipe it off.
Stop it.
I'll help you.
I'm here.
It's hot.
I'll help you.
I'll do my best.
I understand.
Handsome Takeru
I don't know what to say
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I'm sorry I held you.
You have beautiful boobs.
Your body is strange.
You care about me so much.
I love you.
You feel good.
I'll do it again.
I love you.
Do you feel good here?
It feels good.
I'll do it again.
I want you to do it more.
Your head is strange.
It feels good here.
It hurts.
It's hot.
Stop it.
You don't want me to stop here, do you?
It's hot.
You're a teacher.
You shouldn't do this to me.
Stop it.
You're a teacher.
Do you feel good rubbing your head?
Stop it.
You're clenching your teeth.
You should do it quickly.
Stop it.
You're a teacher.
I was happy that you were worried about me.
Stop it.
It feels good here, doesn't it?
You're a teacher.
I love you.
I'll make you feel better.
Stop it.
I can't stand it.
You have a headache.
You should see a doctor.
Can I have a doctor?
No.
You want me to have a doctor, don't you?
You should have a doctor.
I can't do this!
Stop it!
Is that so?
You didn't go to school?
Yes.
You haven't come home yet?
I'm in front of your house.
If you're not there,
I'll call you.
Yes.
I understand.
Rino.
What are you doing
in your student's house?
No way.
After that,
Rino came home
very calmly.
I couldn't ask her anything.
Watanabe, who didn't go to school,
gradually started
posting pictures
to persuade Rino.
I thought
I had nothing to worry about.
Teacher.
Come here.
Wait a minute.
Are you sure?
I'll post
the picture
I took at that time
to you.
Teacher, come here.
Wait a minute.
Do you really
want me to delete
this video?
You promised me
you would delete it.
If you really want me
to delete it,
let's
take a bath
together again.
Stop it.
It's okay.
Teacher.
Even if
everyone in the class
finds out about this...
No.
I understand.
What should I do?
I don't know.
Let me know.
Are you done?
No.
I'm scared.
I'm standing here.
Make yourself comfortable.
Ah...
Teacher.
Stop it.
Ah...
I'm going to put some oil on your face.
Your tongue is getting hotter, isn't it?
Do you feel dizzy?
Please erase that picture.
I want you to feel better.
You don't look sick at all.
I'm getting hot.
You can't do what you like.
You are a pervert.
I'm getting hot.
What's wrong with you?
Do you want me to clean your face?
I'm getting hot.
You really wanted to have a baby, didn't you?
Rino.
What?
Are you okay? You seem to be absent-minded recently.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Ueda recommended me to you.
So, I'm going to have an internship.
So, this Saturday...
Rino.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to have an internship at the Education Committee.
I see.
Rino.
Are you really okay?
Yes, I'm sorry.
I'm a little tired.
I think you work too much.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to lie down.
I don't need to eat.
Rino has been acting strange recently.
I remember seeing her on the ground.
Can I find her location with GPS?
Rino.
You are so sexy.
You make me feel good.
Stop it.
Can I say something?
I'm worried that I might break that picture.
Listen to me.
No.
Are you sure?
Open your mouth.
Why?
I wanted to have an internship at the Education Committee.
No.
I don't have the right to refuse you.
I'm being treated badly.
Stop it.
It's okay.
I had a lot of sex.
No.
It doesn't change.
Your breath is getting softer.
Are you okay?
No.
Are you sure?
Let's check your temperature.
You are very nervous.
No, I'm not.
It's dangerous to touch you from the outside.
You might get a fever.
Show me your face.
No.
I'll do it here.
It doesn't move.
You are sensitive.
It's okay.
It's getting softer.
You might go crazy.
No.
I'm just touching you gently.
Where do you think you are?
This is a school.
No.
You got a fever.
What's going on here?
Open your eyes.
You got a fever.
No.
Are you sure?
I want you to touch me.
I'll touch you.
No.
It's okay.
Your cheeks are wet.
Let me give you a hand.
No.
I'll give you a shot.
What's wrong?
No.
Please.
I want to go.
No.
Please.
It feels good.
Let's go.
No.
I want to go.
What's wrong?
I want to touch you.
It feels good.
Do you want to go outside?
No.
Let me in.
You want to go inside.
I can't stand it.
No.
It feels good.
It's cold.
Let's go.
It feels good.
It's cold.
Do you want to feel better?
Yes.
I want you to feel better.
Did you feel better?
Yes.
Let's go.
Did you like my sex before?
I wanted to do this.
I want to do this.
Come on.
You have to eat more.
Your right hand is open.
You have to eat by yourself.
Do you want me to put it in your mouth?
Please put it in your mouth.
You are drunk.
Please spread your legs and wait there.
I won't put it in your mouth unless you open it yourself.
Please put it in your mouth.
Please open your mouth by yourself.
Where do you want me to put it?
Please put it in your stomach.
It's hard and I feel good.
I feel good.
Please put it in your stomach.
Please open your mouth by yourself.
I feel good.
Are you there?
You went to drink with your friends today.
Rino?
Have you forgotten?
It's strange.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Shiichi , I can't go anymore ...
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Oops, why? It seems like I can't satisfy with it
when I wake up.
I guess you couldn't keep up with your family.
I'm home.
Shinichi-kun.
Can you give me a hug?
I'm home.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I'm going.
It feels good.
It's hard.
I'm going.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
ah ah ah ah ah
to
the
new
pocket
I'm home.
Welcome back.
I left your cell phone in the staff room.
I'm sorry.
I forgot to give it to you.
I thought I dropped it somewhere.
Thank you.
Hey, Rino.
I don't have any practice from tomorrow.
How about tonight?
I've been drinking.
It's early tomorrow, isn't it?
I have to prepare for the business trip.
Did you drink?
You don't smell like alcohol at all.
It's true.
It's early tomorrow.
Let's get ready.
I'm sorry.
You don't have any medicine.
You want me so much.
I'm sorry.
Did you like our sex?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
You've been silent for a long time.
You've been like this all day.
You're really a misogynist.
Are you okay?
Do you feel good?
You only have sex, don't you?
I don't feel good.
Please look at me.
Do you feel good?
I don't have any medicine.
I don't give you medicine.
I'm sorry.
Give me hot water, please.
Do you want to be my girlfriend?
Do you want my life that much?
Hurry up.
I'm sorry.
You are disqualified today and tomorrow.
I want to do it again.
How is my life compared to your life?
It's big.
It's delicious.
I'm sorry.
Can I lick you?
Please lick me.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to lick you?
Give me a kiss.
I can't do it with my hands alone.
I'm a pervert teacher.
Give me a kiss.
I feel good.
Do you want me to lick you?
Let me out.
Please.
I want to sleep.
Let me out.
It's a waste.
Let me hit you one more time.
Let me out.
It's a waste.
I feel good.
Let me out one more time.
One more time.
Don't do that.
It's a waste.
How much do you want?
Let me out one more time.
Of course I'll let you out.
Let me out a lot.
It's a waste.
Let me out.
Let me out more.
It's a waste.
Let me out while you're away.
I'll keep doing this forever.
She went to the training with anxiety.
But she noticed something she forgot on the bullet train.
She hurried to get it back.
I forgot it.
I can't get it back.
It feels so good.
She's trying to get it back.
Let me out.
It's a waste.
Let me out a lot.
I have to do more.
It's a waste.