Yes, that's right.
I understand. I'll try to do that.
I'm very happy that my father told me about my job.
I'll do my best from now on.
I'm really looking forward to tomorrow's welcoming party.
My father will come, too.
Yes.
I'll definitely finish my work.
It's okay.
Do you want some alcohol?
I can drink alcohol.
I like alcohol.
So I'm really looking forward to tomorrow.
Yes.
I can't crush it.
It's definitely okay.
Yes.
I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
Thank you for today.
Good night.
Excuse me.
I talked to TSUCHIYA.
I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
What should I do if I get along with TSUCHIYA?
I'm nervous.
But I've never drunk alcohol.
But I can drink.
If I control myself, I'll be fine.
It's not refreshing at all.
I want to have a girlfriend.
I want to have sex.
I can't do it.
I'm thinking about it.
What should I do?
What is it?
I'm going to take a bath.
I don't have anything.
I don't have a job.
I just stay at home.
I don't have a job, but I sweat a lot.
I can take a bath anytime.
Let me take a bath first.
Why?
It's early in the morning because I have a job.
Is it because you have a job?
I don't want to be told by someone who doesn't have a job.
I'll definitely quit my job.
I won't quit.
I'll definitely quit in three years.
I won't quit 100%.
I won't quit.
What are you talking about?
There are various reasons.
I won't quit.
I won't quit 100%.
There are various reasons.
I don't want to be told by someone who doesn't have a job.
I'm going to take a bath.
Why?
He looks very angry.
KOTA.
Do you have anything to do today?
I don't have anything to do.
What are you doing this weekend?
I don't know.
What?
What are you going to do?
I'm looking for a job.
You can quit your job.
I'm looking for a job at home.
Mom.
Let him think about it.
How can I spoil him?
How many months has it been since KOTA quit his job?
That's right.
Let's wait a little longer.
Good morning.
You are late.
Your suit looks good on you.
Is that true?
That's right.
You are a good person.
I'm not used to it yet.
You look good in it.
I'm glad.
By the way, how is the company?
The company?
It's fun.
Is it fun?
Yes.
Everyone is kind.
I'm relieved that you joined such a company.
That's right.
I want you to see it.
It's a rising company.
That's right.
Don't you have a job?
You don't look like that.
You should do it properly.
Mom.
I'm late for the company's welcoming party.
You said that.
Do you want to drink alcohol?
Yes.
Are you okay to drink alcohol?
I'm okay.
You are strong.
I'm sure you can drink alcohol.
You are kind.
I'm kind.
It's just right.
Dad and Mom are going to have dinner with their friends.
Is that so?
Wait a minute.
Where is my meal?
You are not a child anymore.
Make your own food in the refrigerator.
There is only time.
That's right.
I can't live like this.
I feel sorry for you.
I want everyone to see it.
That's right.
I'm running out of time.
I give you this.
I don't need it anymore.
I'm going to the company.
Wait a minute.
Don't you have a towel?
I don't have it.
Be careful not to catch a cold.
You are serious.
Don't be late.
You can make fried rice with leftovers.
If you are good at it.
You often made it for me when I was a child.
I'm here.
Wait a minute.
I open the door.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure someone is here.
What are you doing?
what?
What is it?
It's heavy.
I'm sorry.
Did you get in?
I didn't get in.
It's dirty.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
How much did you drink?
I want to go to the bathroom.
Don't go to the bathroom.
You don't have to go to the bathroom.
This is a liquor store.
Why don't you understand your own conditions?
I'm sorry.
Wake up.
If you touch me, I'll fall in love with you.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
I don't understand at all.
I'm going to sleep in the water.
It's hot.
I know it's hot.
I'm going to sleep.
I feel uncomfortable.
Did you see me?
I didn't see you.
You saw me, didn't you?
I saw you, so I showed you.
I didn't see you.
I saw you, didn't I?
I told you to close your legs.
You're noisy.
I'm annoyed.
What should I do?
My father doesn't know.
Stand up.
I'll carry you to your room.
Tsuchiya-san.
What should I do?
Don't push me.
My butt hurts.
No, it's because you're talking to your panties.
Tsuchiya-san, you're good at rubbing your butt.
No, I'm not.
You're a pervert.
Let's go to your room.
Are you going to take me to my room?
I have to take you to your room.
I have to take a shower.
You'll die in the shower.
I have to take care of myself.
Tsuchiya-san.
Tsuchiya-san, where did you go?
I'll leave the luggage here.
Tsuchiya-san, you came to my room.
You're so rude.
You're dirty.
I'm sorry.
Can you hear me?
I can't hear you.
I can hear you.
Tsuchiya-san.
Tsuchiya-san, I'm full.
What?
I'll touch you.
Stop it.
What?
Can't you touch me?
I won't touch you.
What?
Stop it.
You're not supposed to do that.
Why don't you touch me?
I don't know.
Do you want me to touch you?
Please touch me.
I want you to touch me.
Please touch me more.
You have a big chest.
Tsuchiya-san.
I'm not Tsuchiya-san.
Please touch me more.
Thank you.
Is this okay?
I'm glad you touched me.
I'm tired.
I want to take off my clothes.
I'm going to take off my clothes.
Please go.
Can you hear me?
What?
I can't hear you.
Please touch me more.
You have a good style.
Really?
I'll touch you more.
No, it's okay.
I met Tsuchiya-san for the first time today.
I'm very happy.
Are you done?
What?
I'm done.
No.
Please look at me and touch me.
What?
I really like Tsuchiya-san.
Do you like Tsuchiya-san?
Can I kiss you?
No.
I'm good at kissing.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Tsuchiya-san.
I can't stand it anymore.
Tsuchiya-san is very close to me.
I'm very happy.
You have a very cool smile.
I'm done.
You have a cool smile.
Why are you looking at me?
I'm happy.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I want to look at Tsuchiya-san.
You can't.
I want to look at him.
I'm sorry.
Tsuchiya-san is very big.
It's very hot.
It's cold.
I've never seen such a big Tsuchiya-san.
It's amazing.
It's cold.
Tsuchiya-san is licking me.
It hurts.
It's hot.
It's cold.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
You can go.
What?
It's cold.
You can go.
I want to look at Tsuchiya-san.
I can't.
You can go.
I want to look at you.
You have a lot of hair.
It's cold.
Tsuchiya-san is licking me.
You have a lot of hair.
It's cold.
You're still fine.
It's hot.
You still have a lot of hair.
Of course.
You can go.
It hurts.
It's cold.
You have a lot of hair.
It feels good.
It's cold.
I can't.
You should clean up, too.
You invited me.
It's your fault.
You should tell everyone.
Do you understand?
I understand.
The food was delicious yesterday.
It was really good.
I drank too much.
Good morning.
I'm sorry.
Kota.
What did you do yesterday?
What did I do?
You made something.
I don't remember.
You don't remember?
You're not good.
I'm sorry.
Get a hold of yourself.
There was a lot of food in the refrigerator.
I made something.
I'm sorry I don't remember.
There was no food in the refrigerator.
You made something, didn't you?
Where is Minami today?
Did she go to school?
She hasn't gone to school yet.
She usually wakes up at this time.
That's unusual.
I wonder if she's okay.
Good morning.
You're late.
I drank too much.
Are you okay?
You're not sick, are you?
That's right.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Did you drink a lot?
I drank a lot.
My senior sent me home.
Did he send you home?
Yes.
Didn't he bother you?
I don't know.
He's a good senior.
He's cool.
He teaches me how to work.
We often have lunch together.
Lunch?
I'll introduce him to you next time.
Isn't it too soon?
It's too sudden.
I'll introduce him to you next time.
That's right.
I have to introduce him to you first.
If I do it suddenly, I'll be in trouble.
That's right.
Minami is not young anymore.
I want to drink more.
But you can't drink too much.
Why?
That's right.
Let's go to the restaurant I went with my mother yesterday.
Let's go with my father next time.
I don't want to go with my father.
There is a delicious wine.
Wine?
Let's go with my father.
I think it's good to get stronger.
Is wine delicious?
It's delicious.
I don't know yet.
Don't you remember him?
I don't remember him.
My father was normal.
Was I so drunk?
Hey.
Come to my house.
Why?
I have something to tell you.
I don't want to.
Come to my house.
What?
Hey.
Don't you remember what happened last night?
Last night?
My senior sent me home last night.
After that...
Your senior?
Yes.
He was not sober.
I don't remember him.
Hey.
Yes?
If I bring a man next time, don't bother him.
Yes.
I think there will be more opportunities like that.
I see.
I don't think I was so drunk.
Did he say something to you?
Yes.
What did he say?
He said I was too drunk.
He said I should start drinking again.
He teased me.
Let's practice drinking.
Practice drinking?
Yes.
If you don't practice drinking...
What is it?
You'll get drunk easily.
Okay?
Are you going to drink?
Yes.
Let's drink together.
Did you buy so much?
Sometimes I want to drink with you.
What?
Okay.
You talk fast.
Let's open it.
Cheers.
This is a simple drink.
Try it.
I don't think so.
Thank you for the meal.
Did you drink?
I have one more.
You're drinking a lot.
Do you want to open it?
I can't drink anymore.
What?
You can't drink at once?
I can't drink anymore.
I have a headache.
Isn't it too early to drink at once?
No.
You can't drink at once.
I still have alcohol.
Let's drink.
Are you going to drink?
Yes.
This is delicious.
Are you okay?
I can't drink anymore.
Your face is red.
Don't worry.
You have to drink more.
Let's go to a place where we can go.
It's spilled.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Are you sure?
You don't talk at all.
Yes.
I'll give you this.
It's hot.
If it's hot, take off your clothes.
Okay.
Let's go.
Don't take off your clothes.
Okay.
Do you want to drink?
I'll help you.
You are very cute.
I can't drink anymore.
You can drink at once.
Your face is too red.
It's not red.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
There is a handsome man.
Is he TSUCHIYA?
He is TSUCHIYA.
Why are you here?
I happened to pass by here, so I stopped by.
Really?
Yes.
I didn't know you were here.
I sent you here yesterday.
I see.
Are you okay?
Do you want to drink more?
Let's make a toast.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Let's make a toast.
You didn't drink at all.
Do you want to drink again?
No.
I don't want to drink.
You are a heavy drinker.
What's wrong with you?
I'm not a heavy drinker.
Really?
I'm a heavy drinker.
You are wearing a cute underwear.
I envy you.
Why do you envy me?
We are not that close.
You are right.
Show me your underwear.
What should I do?
Please.
Okay.
Here you are.
You are so cute.
I'm getting drunk.
Really?
Are you drunk?
Yes, I am.
I'm drunk.
You are right.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You are kind today.
Why am I always strict?
I'm sorry.
It's my job.
It's private time now.
Really?
Yes.
Okay.
I'm drunk.
You said you were a heavy drinker.
Yes.
You are a good girl.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Can I kiss you?
What?
Yes, you can.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I want to stop drinking.
I'm leaving.
If you don't stop drinking, I'll come to you.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
It's too hot.
I'm sorry.
You look good.
You are a heavy drinker.
Look at me.
Come here.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's cold.
I'm sorry.
Look at me.
It's your fault.
Rub it on your butt.
It's okay.
I'm done.
You're still in a bad mood.
What are you going to do?
What?
Rub it on your butt.
Okay.
You can't help it.
What?
Is that so?
Yes.
You have a lot of hair.
I always look down on you.
Do you look down on me?
Yes.
You're just like your brother.
Why do you look down on my brother?
I don't know why.
Rub it on your butt.
It feels good.
It feels good when you cry.
Look at me.
I'll give you some sake.
You're good at drinking sake at times like this.
Really?
Yes.
You're good at it.
Drink it.
Do you want more?
You're good at it.
It feels good.
Look at this.
Can you see where you're in?
I can't see.
You're in there.
I'm in there.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay? Your face is red.
Aren't you drunk?
I'm drunk.
You may not remember tomorrow.
I remember.
Really?
Really.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm sorry.
It's the best.
Try moving.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Can you see where I'm in?
I can see.
It feels good.
Push me more.
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm drooling.
I think you can do it.
Put your hand in here.
Like this?
Yes, like this.
I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
You can stand up if you exercise like this.
I don't like anyone.
I'm sorry.
Get up and move.
Turn your butt this way.
I'm sorry.
One more time.
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
I can see.
It's in there.
I'm sorry.
I can see.
One more time.
I'm sorry.
Use your fingers.
You can do it.
I'm fine.
Really?
I'm sorry.
You can do it.
I like you.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
Can I go again?
Let's go together.
Really?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
You can do it.
I can see.
I'm sorry.
I can't forget you.
You can't forget me.
You'll forget me tomorrow.
You're a good girl.
I can't forget you.
It's a gift from God.
I'm so happy.
You're a good girl.
I've cleaned up.
Let's go back to your room.
Okay.
You can sleep over there.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
It's a cute room.
What are you talking about?
You're here.
No, I'm not.
Again?
What are you talking about?
But...
That's not true.
I'm always at work.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I see.
Did you forget me?
Didn't you send me to the welcoming party?
Welcoming party?
I was drunk, so I took a taxi.
No, you sent me home.
Did I?
I was drunk, too.
I think we parted at the taxi stop.
I...
I can't get a job because of you.
What do you mean?
What?
I...
What's wrong?
Can't I?
What?
What are you doing?
You're trying to avoid me.
But...
You're always avoiding me.
Always?
But...
What?
You don't like me?
I don't dislike you.
But...
You always say that.
But you're not a good girl.
But I always say that.
Always?
You mean...
But you touched me.
But...
You're drunk...
I said that after that.
Wait a minute.
Don't you like it?
I don't hate it.
Did you forget?
I made it so much.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I'm doing what I always do.
Do you always do this?
You did it, too.
You're terrible at forgetting.
Do you really do it?
No.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'm scared.
Tsuchiya, have you changed?
I think it's the first time.
Is it weird?
No, it's not weird.
Maybe it's just my imagination.
It was my misunderstanding.
You're good at it.
I can't stand it anymore.
I can't stand it.
It's scary.
I'm going to go.
No, you can't.
I'm really going to go.
Hang in there.
I'll be there soon.
Do you always go so early?
I always go early.
You look very energetic today.
Maybe I am.
I'll be there soon.
Can't you do it?
You are very good at it.
Do you want to do it?
Do you really want to do it?
Don't you want to do it?
Can you do it?
I can't do it.
You are very energetic these days.
I'm always energetic.
You are always energetic.
Please put this in.
You are very brave.
What is this?
Please put this in.
Do I have to use a rubber band?
You don't usually wear a rubber band.
Do I always wear a rubber band?
Yes, you do.
That's amazing.
I'll put this in.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Show me your hand.
What?
Did it come out already?
No.
It felt good.
You just touched it.
I'm sorry.
I'll be there soon.
You don't usually wear a rubber band.
Do I usually wear a rubber band?
I see.
I'm sorry.
I'll be there soon.
Can I use a tissue?
Yes, it's okay.
It was a little sudden.
I don't think so.
It's different from usual.
I was nervous.
What's wrong?
I've been busy lately.
I've been quiet.
I can't help it.
I'll get ready.
Did you get tired of me?
Was it a dream at that time?
I'm sure I had a dream.
It's Sunday.
I'm sleepy.
I'm going to sleep.
Why are you going to sleep?
Are you sleepy?
I'm sleepy.
Is he drunk because it's Sunday?
He's in good shape.
I'm sleepy.
I'm going to have sex today.
He's in good shape.
I like this place.
I'm going to have sex.
What are you doing?
It's okay.
You're not moving, are you?
I'm going to have sex as usual.
What do you want to do?
Do you want to have sex?
Or do you want to tighten your neck?
You can tighten your neck.
What do you want to do?
Was I the only one who had sex?
Are you drunk?
I just had a drink and went to bed.
Really?
Yes.
I thought I was in love with you.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it for you.
I was patient at first.
I'm not bad at all.
Let's keep it in our hearts.
You felt better.
You felt better than Tsuchiya.
It's the worst.
Let me check.
What are you talking about?
Wait a minute.
This is the picture of me and Tsuchiya.
Let me see.
You're really Tsuchiya.
You're looking at me too much.
Let me see.
I'm sorry.
Let's end this.
What?
I don't want you to get drunk.
You're right.
Let's keep it in our hearts.
What?
Minami.
I have a question.
Are you okay?
Wait a minute.
Minami.
Are you okay?
What?
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Is it good?
Are you sure?
Okay.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Does it feel good?
Does it hurt?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I want you to look at me.
No.
I'm sorry.
You are big.
Are you okay?
I'm still standing.
It's hot.
I'll put a blanket on you.
Okay.
It feels good.
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I feel so good.
Let's take a break.
I'm serious.
Don't do that.
It's hot.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it.
It's hot.
I'm back.
She's back.
Wait a minute.
You'll be found out.
Let's stop.
It's hot.