​​​ ​This is his story-​ ​​
​​​ ​Study with Riku Suzuki.​ ​​
​I have met Nakazato as a trustee​ ​​
​and with Koyuki as a roommate,​ ​​
​and with a lot of expectations wherever I go.​ ​​
​​​ ​In the end, I just believed that​ ​​
​​​ ​I had to manage
​​​ ​my own coworkers and myself...​ ​​
​​​ ​I had this reasoning!​ ​​
​​​ ​that I couldn't stop myself​ ​​
I love you so much.
You want to see me soon, don't you?
I'm nervous.
I love you so much.
Do you want this?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Do you want this?
I love you so much.
Does it feel good?
Do you want me to touch you and lick you?
You're not a man who licks.
Do you want me to touch you?
No.
Can I?
I'm embarrassed.
I think it depends on the person.
I'll lick you.
Does it feel good?
What's wrong?
I'm nervous.
Does it feel good?
It's very hot.
Are you okay?
I'll lick you.
It's very hot.
Does it feel good?
I can't drink it yet.
I'll drink it slowly.
It's very hot.
I'll put it in your mouth.
Are you okay?
I can see you.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
It's very hot.
It's amazing.
Nicolas didn't see the daughter but while watching them,
the mother cat came to hear from cats.
Are you okay?
That was close.
That feels good.
Are you okay?
Are you sleepy?
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I brought you a cup of tea.
Why?
Do you want to drink it?
Okay.
Look at me.
Don't look at me.
No?
No.
You're making a lot of noise.
You're sweating.
No.
It feels good.
Don't look at me.
Does it tickle?
It's not my imagination.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I want you to touch me.
I'm stiff.
It's warm.
Does it feel good?
Don't touch me.
You want to sleep.
It's warm.
It feels good.
Do you want me to pet you?
It's warm.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't do this.
It's too much.
You shouldn't do this.
You're lying.
You're so nice.
You haven't slept yet, have you?
What?
You want me to pet you, don't you?
It feels good.
Do you want me to pinch your boobs?
It's warm.
Let's hurry up.
You shouldn't hurry up.
You're so excited.
This is dangerous.
I can't see.
It feels good.
You shouldn't hurry up.
I can't see.
It's warm.
Do you want me to pinch your boobs?
I can't see.
I'm going to put this in.
Here he comes.
This is bad...
It feels good
Hang in there
It feels so good.
I can't move.
Are you okay?
It's hard.
This?
It feels so good.
It's hard.
I made a weird sound.
It feels so good.
It's hard.
This?
It feels so good.
I want to see the inside.
Really?
Like this?
It's hard.
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Here?
Here.
I'm sorry.
Mom will be here soon, so I will explain about the movements of my body.
When there is movement, it means everything goes well and you can sleep well.
Your water just got in here.
What a clever boy you are.
I love you.
I love you too.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Oh, my God.
You can't move yet.
But your hips are moving.
Oh, my God.
What's wrong with you?
Come here.
Everything is wrong with me.
Are you okay?
Oh, my God.
You don't want to eat, do you?
No.
Oh, my God.
You're going to get a stomachache.
No, I'm not.
You can't stop it?
I can't stop it.
Oh, no.
You're going to get a stomachache.
No, I'm not.
Are you going to get a stomachache?
Yes.
You're trembling.
Are you okay?
Oh, my God.
You're trembling.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do it
I feel greedy
I don't know what to do.
I'm going to eat it with the sauce I made earlier.
It's so delicious.
It's a treat by two though...
But...
I gave up...
It's hot, it's pretty hot, so let's just break it into several pieces.
I'll cool it down and finish it 1 minute later.
Can you hear the chicken being cut?
The chicken is completely done.
أ decree
Amber that, when it is cooked today, tastes delicious!
…
Hello,
Ah...
Hmm...
Enpuff!
Ah...
Do you want to eat?
I can't believe I'm doing this for the first time in a while.
I'm so happy.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Uh
Oh
Hmm
RE
Hmmm
Now we're gonna go to the massage hall to see what he's doing.
He's so pretty.
Help me!
H... Help...
Help!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
!
Oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh,
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
Here you are.
If you have a coach, write it down.
Yes.
If you write it down, you'll know.
How long have you been doing this?
I'm sorry.
What?
Here you are.
What are you doing?
Would you like to play with me?
Hey.
Wait a minute.
I'm not ignoring you.
Would you like to play with me?
It's a summer memory.
What are you going to do?
Fireworks.
Fireworks?
That's great.
Let's go to see fireworks.
Let's go.
It's hot.
That's good.
Let me explain.
There are a lot of fireworks.
Let's do it all.
Oh, no.
Isn't it hot?
No, it's not.
Oh, no.
It's on fire.
That's good.
It might be long.
It's very thick.
That's great.
It's pretty fast.
Look at this.
Fireworks.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Me?
I'm free.
Free?
You're the same as me.
I'm not the same as you.
I'm free no matter where I go.
I'm just playing with firecrackers.
We're the same, aren't we?
No, we're not.
We're definitely not.
Hey.
Do you want to go to the hotel?
What?
You want to go, don't you?
Yes.
Let's go.
It's open.
Ta-da.
Wow.
Awesome.
It's awesome.
Is it?
Let's get started.
Let's go.
I'll send you home.
Where is your home?
I don't have a home.
How far should I send you?
So, send me to your home.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
If you don't send me to your home,
I'll call the police.
I'm sorry.
I don't have a home.
I know.
I'm serious.
Yuki.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
It's dirty.
What?
It's really dirty.
It's clean.
Why don't you throw this away?
I'll throw them away together.
You're separating them.
You're great.
This is a magazine.
It's dangerous.
It's garbage.
There's nothing in it.
It's dangerous over there.
It's hot.
I told you.
It's good.
It's cooked well.
It's really good.
It's good.
You eat a lot.
Do I?
I'm happy.
There's a lot in it.
I heard you like it, so I bought a lot.
Did you eat it?
Yes.
I'll eat it.
Here you are.
You should eat vegetables, too.
No.
You have to eat them.
I can't eat vegetables.
What?
I'll take them.
It's really good.
You're getting tired of it.
You didn't see it, did you?
You're crying.
It's in the way.
It's really in the way.
You're fast.
I'm a professional.
It's really in the way.
I did it.
I can't win at all.
You're weak.
What's the last one?
I want to eat it.
Is it really your first time?
Yes, it is.
You can eat it.
Can I?
Put an egg in it.
Do I?
It's good.
There is a timing to put an egg in it.
There is a timing to put an egg in it?
Now?
I'll say it.
I have to say it.
Now.
It's amazing.
I'll enjoy it.
Well...
Is there a white part?
I'll enjoy it.
Do I have to mix it?
You can mix it.
It looks good.
I'll enjoy it.
Is it hot?
I want to eat it without an egg at first.
Well...
It's hard to eat it.
It's good even if it's hard.
Is it hard?
Yes.
I can eat it.
You can eat it every day.
Every day.
I can eat it every day.
I can eat it.
What are you doing?
I have nothing to do.
So, I tried to suck your boobs.
You have nothing to do.
So, you tried to suck my boobs?
Yes.
I'll enjoy it.
Is it hot?
It's good.
I'll enjoy it.
Hey.
Yes?
You're going to quit sucking my boobs, aren't you?
Yes.
I'm going to work seriously.
I'll go to an interview tomorrow.
I'll wear a suit.
Yes.
It's my responsibility.
I have to pay the tax soon.
It's normal for a man.
It's a shame that I don't work for the woman I like.
I'm such a bad man.
So, I decided to do my best.
I'll enjoy it.
The noodles are good.
I'll go to an interview.
Yes.
I'll enjoy it.
See you.
Were you here?
What are you doing here?
I'm alive.
It was hard for you to leave the restaurant suddenly.
The manager was worried about you.
I was worried about you, too.
I'm glad that I'm alive.
Is he your boyfriend?
I don't know.
You said that again.
What are you?
I just want to be free.
You don't know anything about the society.
We all want to be free.
That's why we sold our bodies instead of working.
It's a delusion of freedom.
I still want to be free until I'm satisfied.
That's enough.
I was worried about you.
You should live like that.
I hope you can live like that.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
You should clean up.
It's a mess.
Right?
You can clean up when you want to.
It's too late to clean up when you want to.
Do you wash this?
Yes, I do.
Hey.
Yes?
If you're at home all the time, make me a meal.
It's delicious.
It's not like that.
What?
It looks delicious.
Oh.
Do you want to eat something?
No, I don't.
Do you want to eat this?
You can eat this.
Really?
Welcome home.
It's hot.
What are you doing?
Don't you want to play?
Don't be sad.
Let's play.
It's the last summer.
It's nice.
What are you doing?
I'm playing.
It's the last summer.
Let's go see fireworks.
Let's say goodbye.
Yes.
What are you going to do after this?
Let's have sex for the last time.
Yes.
It's hot.
What do you do?
Me?
I'm a freelancer.
A freelancer?
You're the same age as me.
No, I'm not.
I'm free to go anywhere.
I only play pachinko.
We're the same age, aren't we?
No, we're not.
Definitely not.
The last summer.
Hello.
This is a special video.
A new special video has been completed.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Yasuna Kawai, a freelance actress.
How many years have you been in the industry?
I've been in the industry for 5 years.
Do you have any memories?
I've been in the industry for 6 years.
You've been in the industry for 5 years.
I've been in the industry for 5 years.
You've been in the industry for 6 years.
That's a long time.
Not yet.
Do you remember the interview you did when you debuted?
I remember where it was.
It was raining in the park.
Did you ask how many people were there?
I did.
I wonder how many people answered.
How many people were there at that time?
There were about 3 or 4 people.
By the way, how many people are there now?
I don't know.
That's amazing.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
Do you do it a lot?
No, no, no.
I've met a lot of actors.
I don't do it in private.
But everyone does it.
Don't you do it?
I don't.
Do you swear?
Do you swear to God?
I swear to God.
I...
In private...
I know. Let's discuss it.
What?
What does it mean to have sex in private?
What does it mean?
Isn't it difficult?
Is it better to have sex in private or not?
It's better to have sex in private.
Is it better to have sex in private?
Why?
Well...
It's the job of an AV actress, isn't it?
All the men in the world are dreaming, aren't they?
AV actresses are erotic.
So I want them to have sex at any time.
I see.
It's impossible.
Pro-wrestlers...
I want them to have sex at any time.
It's impossible.
Pro-wrestlers are strong.
AV actresses are erotic.
Actors are funny.
I don't want them to have such fantasies.
I see.
I think it depends on each person.
Let's do our best.
Do we have to do our best?
No, no, no.
No, it's dangerous.
It's dangerous.
How can we...
How can we be friends?
Well...
Do you have a dog?
Do I have a dog?
Well...
It's quite hard.
It takes a long time to get there.
Do you wear iron panties?
Yes, I do.
What do you decide to do?
What do I decide to do?
Well...
I might go out with her.
Go out with her?
Not going out with her?
Going out with her.
Going out with her is...
She's very clean and smells good.
Why are you laughing?
She might be there.
What?
I'm not good at smelling.
Perfume?
Perfume and other things.
What's your favorite perfume?
My favorite perfume is...
Well...
Doja Cat?
Jo Malone.
Do you wear that perfume to your next event?
There are many kinds.
I find my favorite scent.
There are so many kinds.
I find my favorite scent and wear it.
That's good.
If you wear that, you're done?
If I wear that, I'm a bad person.
There are some conditions.
She smells good.
She's clean.
Does that mean you can take a bath, shave, and have a hair cut?
Yes.
And dental care. That's the most important.
Go to the dentist.
If you clear these three, you're done.
It depends on my mood at that time.
Your face doesn't matter.
My face?
I haven't decided what kind of face I like.
That's what I think.
If I think it's good...
If you think it's good, does that mean you're good-looking?
No, no, no.
As long as you have a face.
As long as I have a face, I'm good.
That's enough for now, right?
That's enough.
Let's all go to the dentist.
That's a great idea, isn't it?
Let's all put on perfume.
Let's all clean up.
Let's all go to the event.
Let's all be popular.
Let's all have a chance.
I'm going to say it quickly, but is that okay?
I don't like people who say they want to do it directly.
It's difficult.
If a woman says she wants to do it, wouldn't you be surprised?
I'd be surprised.
Really?
Even if it's not your favorite girl?
That's okay.
Really?
Even if it's not your favorite girl?
That's okay.
You can have sex with her.
I just realized the sad reality.
That's right.
It's not a big deal.
You don't like people who smell, do you?
But it's different.
It's different.
Have you ever done it while looking at the ceiling?
That's amazing.
It was too smelly.
What kind of smell is that?
I don't know. It smelled like fish.
It's definitely not good.
It happens.
That's why it happens when you do it with a lot of people.
Oh, I have to check my genitalia.
I have to check my genitalia.
I have to check my genitalia for a week.
This is...
What should I do with the person who cleared it?
I'll wait for you here.
Is that okay?
Where should I send it?
It's coming out here.
To the play stage?
That's really good.
There's an amateur project.
Oh, yeah?
Let's send it there.
That's great.
Now that we've decided where to recruit.
Some people may be watching for the first time.
I have to make them think that I want to recruit them.
To the owner who invites me to recruit.
You want to have sex with me, don't you?
Is that okay?
I don't have any small tools.
Do you have any small tools?
I think I'll bring some small tools.
Do you want anything?
Do you want a robot man?
I want it.
Then wait a minute.
I'm sorry.