Please take a look at this and sign here if you don't mind.
Thank you very much.
I'm relieved from today.
This time, I lost to Kimura's enthusiasm.
When I was on vacation, my wife came to my company.
She gave me a tissue and a calendar.
I always refused because I didn't think about insurance.
Thank you very much.
I will deliver the insurance certificate later.
Isn't it okay to deliver the certificate?
I'm in charge of this area and I go around every day.
I will deliver it by hand.
Is that so?
Thank you very much.
It was cold.
Is that so?
I think it's sex.
It can't be once every three months.
I think it's about once a month.
It can't be once every two or three months.
I don't know.
But that's not the desire of a man.
I can do it every day.
There are many men.
Who is it?
Yes.
May I come in?
I came to deliver the insurance certificate.
Please come in.
Thank you very much.
Who is it?
This is my best friend, Hidemi.
I went to my husband's insurance the other day.
Kimura is in charge of the insurance business.
Thank you very much.
I'm leaving now.
We are free.
Would you like some tea?
I'm leaving now.
This is the insurance certificate.
Thank you very much.
I'm leaving now.
When I went to Hidemi,
Kimura invited me.
That's not good.
Hidemi and her husband are there.
I'm not satisfied with my desire.
You're not satisfied with your desire?
You should talk to your husband about it.
But women can't say that.
That's strange.
You're married.
That's right.
I'm going on a business trip again next week.
A business trip again?
I don't have enough people.
I'm leaving.
I see.
I'm leaving tomorrow morning.
Good night.
I'm leaving now.
Hello?
Did Kimura come?
No.
He sent me the certificate.
I don't think he's coming.
Please find a reason to invite him.
Please.
Hidemi,
it's not good for your husband.
It's okay.
My husband is cheating on me.
Is that true?
He can't stand it for three months.
How can he cheat on you?
It's okay.
You have to enjoy life only once.
Only once?
Please.
Okay.
I'll ask him next time.
Thank you.
Bye.
Hi.
Please come in.
Thank you.
I'm sorry to bother you.
It's okay.
Today,
I brought a pension insurance pamphlet.
Here it is.
Thank you.
Kimura.
Yes.
Do you remember my best friend, Hidemi?
Hidemi?
Yes.
I remember.
Actually,
she's married and has a husband.
She wants to know more about you.
What do you mean?
She wants to be sexless with her husband.
Sexless?
Yes.
How about your wife?
Me?
You can't answer right away.
No.
Please stop.
Kimura.
Please let me go.
No.
No, Kimura.
Ma'am.
Please.
Don't forget about your wife.
What are you talking about?
Kimura.
I have a husband.
You're a sexless woman.
You have a husband.
What are you talking about?
It's okay.
No.
Kimura.
Please let me go.
Please stop.
It's okay.
It's a secret.
No.
Kimura.
What are you talking about?
It's okay.
Please let me go.
Please stop.
It's my house.
It's okay.
Ma'am.
I'll let you go.
I won't let you regret it.
What are you talking about?
You won't do this, will you?
It's okay.
Please stop.
Please let me go.
You have such a nice boobs.
It's okay.
Kimura.
Please let me go.
It's okay.
Please stop.
Wait.
Please let me go.
It's okay.
You can feel it.
Please let me go.
It's okay.
Please stop.
Wait.
Don't touch me.
Ma'am.
It's getting hot here.
Do you know what I'm doing?
It's okay.
It's a secret.
You need to let me go.
It's okay.
Ma'am.
Please stop.
It's okay.
What are you doing?
Kimura.
Please stop.
Please let me go.
It's okay.
No.
I'm a smart person.
Please stop.
Ma'am.
Kimura.
It's okay.
Please let me go.
Kimura.
It's okay.
Please.
Please stop.
You're really tired.
Please.
No.
I'm going to fall.
Be careful.
Please be careful.
Please don't say that.
It feels good.
Please stop.
Please let me go.
It's okay.
Please stop.
You look beautiful.
You're really...
How can you be sexist?
You're too much.
Madam.
It's in your anus.
Stop it.
It's warm.
Wait a minute.
Let go of me.
It's okay.
Please let go of me.
Let's feel good together.
Please stop it.
Don't do this.
Stop talking nonsense.
Please stop it.
It's in your anus.
You're wearing a heavy anus.
No.
It's in your anus.
It's torn to the inside.
No.
How do you feel?
It's not like that!
Here?
Stop it!
Do you really feel it?
I don't feel it!
Stop it!
Please stop it!
Do you feel it?
I don't feel it!
Stop it!
Please stop it!
Do you feel it?
It's not like that!
Stop it!
Please stop it!
I don't feel it!
Stop it!
Please stop it!
Imura-san!
I can do it!
Stop it!
Please stop it!
Imura-san!
I can do it!
I can't do this!
It feels good, right?
Imura-san!
Please stop it!
I can feel your body!
Imura-san!
No...
Against the joiner...
Forbidden shrine
Madam...
You feel really어
Without mission...
Ah...
No...
Oh, please...
Please stop...
Oh...
Oh, Kiki...
You're very strong...
Oh...
Sounds good.
I can't do it.
Why?
You're doing well.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Your body is the best.
I can't do it.
Your voice is beautiful.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
What happened to your story?
Did you give up?
I think I gave up.
I see.
That's better.
You can't cheat.
I can't do it.
Ano M어주
What did you think?
What did you think of me?
Did you think of me?
I can't answer right away.
Why is it you?
Hi!
Kibara-san...
Yes?
That makes me sad.
I help him finish her bunk.
Mr. Imura...
My back...
Isn't that a bit of an nicest baby?
How did your mother spend her whole life?
We got married.
Have you had a lot of children?
I haven't.
But...
It's okay, it's okay.
You want to be healthy, don't you?
Tell me the truth.
I don't want to hear it from you.
Please don't tell me the truth.
It's okay.
I'll do it.
I didn't know you were wearing such a sexy dress.
It's not.
You wanted to do it, didn't you?
You showed me such a sexy dress.
I'm sorry.
I think you're very lonely.
It's okay.
I didn't know you were wearing such a sexy dress.
It's not okay.
It's okay.
Move your hands.
You can feel it here, too.
You can feel it, right?
It's getting better.
What?
It's okay.
It's not okay.
What's wrong?
I can't see
You like inside?
I'll open it for you
It's in
You can't see
Do you feel better?
No, no
Wife
Do you feel better?
No, no
This?
Don't move
No, no
She's gone
Let's enjoy
Show me your hips
You love your hips
Yappa, let's stop
Don't do that
You can't feel your body
Wife, you can't do that
Don't do that
This is not good
Don't look at me
You love your hips
This is not good
Wife
No, no
She's gone
This is not good
Wife
Please check me
What?
You love me
Let's stop
Wife, you wanted to do a lot of things, didn't you?
I will
Come here
Wife's favorite house
Make yourself comfortable
You're quiet, aren't you?
You don't answer the phone
No, no
Wife
Please stop
Don't do that
With your mouth
You want to lick, don't you?
Wife
It feels good
It feels really good
Wife
Great
Show me your face
It feels good
Do you understand?
You're getting bigger
Wife
It feels really good
Wife, it feels good
Wife
Lick a lot
You're talking deliciously
It feels good
Wife
If you talk so much, I want you
You want this, don't you?
I can't do it anymore
Wife
You can't wait anymore, can you?
I'll put it in
Slowly
Wife is sleeping
Do you understand?
Please let her sleep
Wife is sleeping
It's beautiful
It's wonderful
Wife is sleeping
I can't do it anymore
No, no
No
Wife is sleeping
No, no
You want to feel better, don't you?
You want to sleep, don't you?
I can't do it anymore
Wife is sleeping
It feels good
I can't do it anymore
You can put that beautiful face on
I'll put it on
It feels good
I can't do it anymore
Clean it up
Wife is sleeping
I can't do it anymore
It feels good
Wife is sleeping
I can't do it anymore
It feels good
Please
I can't do it anymore
Clean it up
Wife is sleeping
I can't do it anymore
It feels good
Wife is sleeping
I can't do it anymore
It feels good
Clean it up
More
It feels good
Wife, it feels good
Wife is sleeping
It feels good
I can't do it anymore
Wife is sleeping
Yuri, you should get dressed up too
Do you remember Sayori from high school?
Sayori who had good grades
Yes, we met at the station the other day
We had tea together
I see
Then we are going to date
It's only been 3 months since we got married
I'm surprised
It's amazing
It's already this time
We are going to the beauty salon
Tomorrow we are going to date
Bye
Wife
What do you think?
You won't do this for me, will you?
You are tied up
You are excited
Because you are poor
I'm sorry
Wife
You are excited because you are told like this?
Because
Wife
Wife is sleeping
Don't say
Really?
What?
Wife, will you do this for me?
It's already been so long
I'm so scared.
You're so scared.
Don't say that.
I'm scared.
I'm so scared.
You're so scared.
You can't resist.
I'm so scared.
Don't be so surprised.
I know you're shaking because you don't have any underwear.
I'm so scared.
You can't resist.
I can't resist.
I'm so scared.
What is it?
I want you to stop.
But...
Don't cry.
I'm so embarrassed.
I can't resist.
I'm so scared.
It's hot.
I can't resist.
Here?
I'm so scared.
I can't resist.
Wait.
I'm so scared.
Please make me feel better.
You like me, don't you?
It feels so good.
It really does taste good.
Don't worry about it.
Hey, wifey.
Which do you like more, your baby or mine?
Which do you like more?
Kiyohara-san...
Oh, that's right.
Lick it.
Madam,
you can't take it anymore, can you?
Yes.
Do you want it?
I want it.
Then, please.
Mr. Kimura's.
Please put it in.
Yes.
Please put it in for me.
Okay.
Push it out.
Don't let go of your hand yet.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It's hot.
It's getting hot.
It's hard.
It's hot.
It's hitting the inside.
Oh, no.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I'll release it.
It's hot.
It's so hot.
Are you okay?
Go, go, go.
It's hot.
Okay, take this.
Be careful.
Are you okay?
It's hot.
I'm here.
Help me.
You're excited, aren't you?
Wait.
It's hot.
Where are you?
Go, go, go.
Turn around.
It's hot.
It's hard.
Where am I?
It's hot.
Me too.
It's okay.
It's hot.
Look at me.
It feels good.
Does it feel good inside me?
It feels good inside you.
Madam.
Which one feels better?
Mr. Kimura.
It's Mr. Kimura.
It's hot.
Go, go, go.
You went again.
It's hot.
It feels good.
There, there.
There.
It's hot.
Go, go.
Go away.
Ha!
Where did it go?
and thank you for respecting our community.
So please take this opportunity to share this with your loved ones.
I...
don't need this.
I know.
Come meet me here.
Okay.
When will we see her?
Maybe the day after tomorrow.
I'm very nervous, so I'll be back later.
Yep.
Now thank you.
You look quite happy.
I just can't put myself into this.
You just scornfully do things well.
And I can't help but think...
I always think that I need to learn from you.
That's right. You also need to learn from Mr. Kimura.
That's right.
Thank you very much for your help.
You're welcome.
I look forward to working with you from now on.
I'm leaving now.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.