I'm sorry. I'll have the same one, please.
Yes.
Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
Well, but is there any evidence that the husband is cheating?
There is evidence.
There was a girl's name card in the back pocket.
It was fun today.
Come again.
It's a heart.
Oh, it's not cheating.
What?
It's cheating.
It's a divorce.
Divorce.
I'm really sorry.
So, what did you do with this girl?
No, I didn't do it.
It's a soft shop.
So, what?
No, so...
With my hands and mouth...
Say it properly.
So...
You touched me with your hands and...
Say it properly.
Everything.
So...
I had a handkerchief, a Ferrachio, and a lotion.
I'm really sorry.
On the way home from the party with my juniors,
I just...
Hmm...
You're cheating on me.
No, so...
It's not cheating.
No, it's the same.
And we haven't done it recently.
Even if I invite him, he's old.
He said he lost his sexual desire.
No, no, he has a lot of sexual desire.
Well, men are like that.
So you did it at home.
Yes.
Let's do it tonight.
No, I can't.
My husband is neurotic.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hey, mister.
She doesn't have a place to stay tonight.
So, I'll take care of her for a night.
Stop it.
Take your time.
Excuse me.
What?
Are you stupid?
I'm not stupid.
Well, sometimes it's good.
You can have sex with someone other than your husband.
I see.
Are you doing it?
Of course.
If I don't enjoy it, I can't be a housewife.
No, no, no.
Why don't you do it?
You can forgive your husband's sexual desire in a second.
He has a lot of sexual applications.
No, no, no.
What?
Are you on his side?
Mai.
Don't drink too much.
Shut up.
Oh, I see.
Have you been there?
Oh, no.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Excuse me.
Damn it.
Where did she go?
Answer the phone.
Are you awake?
Yes.
It's already closed.
I'm sorry.
Where is Ruka?
She went home.
She said she would take care of you.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I'm going home.
What?
Are you okay?
This way.
I'm sorry.
I'm okay.
I'm not okay.
Do you want to take a break somewhere?
Where?
Hotel.
What?
I can't.
But...
What's wrong?
Get out.
I'm sorry.
Mai.
Is it your husband?
Please hang up.
I can't enjoy it.
Well...
I'm going home.
Don't do that.
But...
I'm sorry.
Just for one night.
You can forget it when it's over.
How about this?
This is a dream.
It's a dream that I'm watching.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
You're soaked.
This way.
You don't have to be embarrassed.
This is a dream.
You have to do what you want.
I'm sorry.
Please close your eyes.
It's okay.
It's a little dark.
It's a dream.
You can forget it when you wake up.
It's beautiful.
Please show me.
Don't be embarrassed.
It's beautiful.
I can't.
Your nipples are up.
No.
It's beautiful.
Do you like it here?
No.
It's beautiful.
Please show me more.
No.
You can't see it because you're wearing clothes.
It's very hot.
It's difficult.
How about inside?
No.
You're very sleepy.
It's hot.
Your buttocks are beautiful.
This is beautiful, too.
It's hot.
You have a beautiful body.
Are you embarrassed?
Yes.
It's hot.
No.
It's very wet here.
It's hot.
Please show me more.
Can you hear me?
No.
It's hot.
Did you feel good?
Yes.
It's hot.
No.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Please move a lot.
It feels very good.
Yes.
Let's touch.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's getting wet.
It's hot.
Please move a lot.
Did you feel good?
Yes.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Please move a lot.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
No.
It's hot.
It's a dream.
No.
It's hot.
It's a dream.
Please move a lot.
No.
It's itchy.
It feels good.
It's a round shape.
No.
It feels good.
It's itchy.
No.
It feels good.
It's itchy.
No.
Do you like this?
It's itchy.
No.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's cold.
Let me do it.
There's a lot.
It's cold.
You're sweating a lot.
I'll wash your hair.
What was that?
Was that a dream?
It's delicious.
I have to go home.
I saw this on the vending machine.
I'm not riding the train.
I'm going home by taxi.
I bought this.
Let me use it.
You can't.
Does it feel good?
You seem to feel good.
Do you feel good?
NANDO DOES THE LIFTING ONLY IN JUST ONE OCCASION
What's the matter?
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
You're holding back your tears.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
Hey.
Are you going to wear it?
I'm going to take it off.
I don't need clothes.
We still have time until the departure.
Let's go home by taxi.
It costs money to take a taxi.
Your neck reacts like this.
Which do you like better?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Your neck is like this.
You're touching your nipples.
Don't do that.
Touch my nipples.
I'm sorry.
Let me touch your nipples.
Don't do that.
It feels good.
There are a lot of pimples on your nipples.
Hey.
Do you want to drool?
Try it.
Just a little.
It feels good.
Do you want to drool?
Try it.
It feels good.
Look at me.
You're so cute.
It feels good.
Do you want to go inside?
I'm sorry.
What did you say?
I couldn't hear you.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Hey.
I want to lick you.
I want to take a shower.
It's good, isn't it?
You can take a shower again.
Look at me.
It's amazing.
I'm pulling your hair.
I'm sleepy.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It's ticklish.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
If it's so ticklish,
Don't you feel pain?
It's okay.
I'm dirty.
Do you want to wipe it with this?
I don't have a towel.
Do you have a rubber band?
Rubber band?
I used up all the rubber bands in the hotel.
That's not good.
I'll take it out at the end.
That's not a problem.
I can't.
Doesn't it feel good?
Do you want to stop?
Do you want to take it out?
I'll take it out.
I can't.
Do you want to use this?
Do you like this?
I can't.
You like toys.
I like it.
You like it, don't you?
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't.
My legs and butt.
I like your butt.
I can't.
It feels good.
Show me your butt.
I can't.
It feels good.
Damn it.
I can't.
You look embarrassed.
I don't.
I can't.
It feels good.
I want to get up.
I can't.
It feels good.
I'm hungry.
I can't.
It hurts.
Does it hurt?
No.
I can't.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I can't.
It feels good.
Did you really lose it here?
Yes, I think I lost it around here.
Oh, I found it.
What?
I'm glad.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Please come again.
No.
I won't come again.
I just had a dream last night.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
Mai, where are you now?
Where?
I'm staying at Ikanchi.
I see.
Mai, it's my fault.
I won't come to your house anymore.
So, please come back.
Okay.
I won't forgive you next time.
Wait a minute.
Mai, what's wrong?
Is someone there?
No, it's nothing.
Mika played a prank on me.
I'll hang up now.
Please don't.
I have to go home.
It's time to say goodbye.
Don't say that.
Hey, Mai.
Mai.
Let me see your tongue.
More.
I have to go home.
I know.
Mai, what are you doing?
Mai.
Kiss me.
Does it feel good?
There was my face
.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Let's go home.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's getting late.
It's okay.
Don't worry about time.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Let's go.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Let's go.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It tickles.
Let's go.
It feels good.
It tickles.
What's wrong?
It's ticklish.
It's ticklish, isn't it?
It tickles.
It's ticklish.
ah
ahh
hee
ah
this feels good
ooh
aah
ahh
crazy
ring
jump
ahh
ooh
puh
ahh
whoa
huh
ahhh
I want to go this way, too.
I'm sorry. I'll be right back.