I’m okay, you’re going to make breakfast.
Then I will go.
Come to go.
It is hot.
I am so hard working.
Sorry to
Oh, my dear, I will take care.
Oh, I was careful.
Where is the bed?
Che, a little bit
Is it okay now?
and sleep.
No more, no more.
Thanks to.
Oh no.
The beginning of the rope.
I want to let you meet with your mother.
Yes, I did not know.
Yes, I introduced my friend to me a half year ago.
I drank with my friend today.
meet for a long time, so have fun.
It seems to have drunk too much.
It’s too late, but is it okay?
Oh is?
Would you stay?
I have a job, so stay quiet.
I felt well.
He had a boyfriend, and he didn’t tell his sister.
When we started dating, my sister broke up with her boyfriend who had been with us all the time.
So I cannot tell.
Oh, and so
This Saturday is my birthday, so we’ll celebrate it together.
Oh yeah yeah.
Yes to.
Please
So I am out.
Come to me.
Yes to.
I did I did.
Yes this.
Yes to.
thanks to.
If you suddenly get a case,
I told you to come.
I cannot train on Sundays.
Oh yeah yeah.
Sorry, I can’t celebrate my birthday.
Yes, it is okay
Hi to
Congratulations on your birthday.
thanks to
Why is?
It was my sister’s birthday.
Because I miss you.
Then again
Wait a little.
I drink alone.
What if I am good?
Are you hungry?
Oh yeah
It’s my birthday, so let me do it.
Please sit down sister.
thanks to
You are good at cooking.
Oh is?
Oh oh oh oh
They are cooking themselves.
As much as this.
I have come.
Sit down.
Thanks to you.
Can you beer?
Of course entirely.
I love beer.
Good to.
Will you follow me?
OK is.
Thanks to.
Oh awesome.
Good to Camper.
It is delicious, you are good at first.
No, I’t be able to compliment you, I did it.
At high school, I was a little bit responsible for making such a cultural festival.
If it was done at home, it would have been better.
Okay okay okay.
Not cool.
No, please do not say that.
Not cool, otherwise.
Red is happy.
Is it fine with red?
It is difficult to be a child.
well
But
My sister, you are well done, right?
The sister?
I called you.
Can you be a spy?
I am a younger girl, so I’m just a little bit careful.
No to?
Because I am not capable.
Work or man is not good at all.
If I can be like a cowboy, I’ll be easier.
It is gone.
Is it okay?
No problem, I’ll drink another.
Oh, you drink too much now.
I just drank a little too much.
Sorry to
Drink another?
Yes
That is
My sister is inviting you.
Not bothered at all.
Oh yeah
First Mr.
No, if you do that.
My sister always.
About me.
I will look at it that way.
Let me see.
Really not like it.
You don’t hate it at all, right?
I say I hate.
Really?
I hate it.
No to no.
Why do you want it, really?
How do not do.
I cannot endure.
Then I understood.
I am attacking my sister like this.
My sister is just being attacked.
Because I did nothing.
I am drunk and my sweetness is attacked.
Did you miss me today?
Oh, it is cold.
Cold, cold and no.
I must not be lost.
Your sister wanted that, right?
I do not want.
How can you be lost?
Saying no to.
No to
No to no.
So here is
No, this is the best.
The most not.
After licking it.
Judge if not.
No is not.
Stop it.
Can’t really?
He said he did not take a bath.
After taking a bath.
What after you entered?
Not after I entered.
What since you entered?
No to no.
My sister, it smells bad, but it’s okay.
No, I have to go to the bathroom.
You don’t hate it at all.
No to no.
It is hit.
Are you hit?
The first Mr.
What is mine?
Because I touched you there.
I did not touch.
It would be crazy if you did that.
It feels bad if you touch it.
The back is moving.
not moving.
Yes
No to no.
OK is OK.
See also
I must be caught.
It will fall.
Sit down in danger.
See also
You are kind.
It is dangerous to fall.
I don’t like his face at all.
It means not to be, right?
My birthday is missing.
Why do you eat sharks?
I will bury your loneliness.
If so, I wish.
No to
I haven’t been crawling here all the time.
not do it.
really
No to
It is hot here.
not hot
The Lie.
Can I verify it?
Let us sit in the gap.
I will sit right.
You can’t be ashamed.
Shame on you.
You asked me to do that, you want it.
No, I did not invite.
I will also take it off.
Is this OK?
I have more of it taken off.
No is not.
Oh a little.
Do you mean touching your ass?
You don’t close your leg at all.
What happened to you?
You wanted to be like this from the beginning, right?
What happened?
and kiss.
Clean it out.
You didn’t like it, right?
Do you want more?
Yes, more of
More of
So, this will extend.
A little before.
It is ERO.
Not a shameless?
Is it not a trophy?
I have no power to say no.
Can’t drink yet?
I drank it.
Did you want to drink?
The wicked closes his feet.
It feels good.
Is it difficult to sleep?
I was excited too, I was excited too.
Not so big though.
I am a bit bit biting.
I was scared of mango, what happened?
Do you want to put this in?
I want to enter.
You want to get in first, right?
Yes, I want to enter.
I want to go in first, but you can go in.
I say I want to go in.
No to no.
Which is it?
Can you use your fingers?
You want to get in.
I am already very tight on my fingers.
Can I just one side?
Do not be upset.
Just a little.
Because I don’t have it all in.
You will not enter.
This is fine, right?
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Because it is my fault.
Yes
Is it my fault?
Oh yeah
You did it yourself.
I helped myself.
Oh yeah
No – very sharp.
No to
Oh yeah yeah yeah
It feels good.
Yes
No to
Oh is
You wanted to do this.
You wanted to do it.
Oh is
Do you want to do it?
Oh yeah
No to
It might be more confusing.
You wanted to do it.
The wind is closing.
It is Gorgon.
Feel good
I say.
Sleeping on foot.
I want to sleep and find 10,000 colors.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Did you miss anything?
The ghost...
The blood is hot!
Let’s go quickly!
The tears...
Sorry to
I put it inside.
No is not.
yet another time.
Tired
Tired of
cannot move
It was the worst.
No longer a dick.
Tired really
He came home.
If if
Ended is
home now
Super tired.
It was hard.
opened quickly.
Yes
When is it? when is it?
Is it really meat?
Please, can you give me a meal?
I did, have fun.
Really, a lot of things.
Go to Go.
Oh thank you.
I am am amusing.
Yes, sooner
I want to see Gigi soon.
Yes, yes, no
Thanks to you.
Eat it...
It was so beautiful, I made it.
It looks very tasty.
Oh, you are celebrating this.
You are happy.
Super happy.
It smells like pizza now.
So then, is it so?
Congratulations on your birthday!
Thanks to!
What to drink?
How about it?
Or do it to me.
No, I will follow you.
I will follow you.
Because it is birthday.
thanks to
Yes, then seriously
It tastes.
Okay okay.
Close it inside?
I will fill it, so it is okay.
Yes please please.
A little bit, I will crumble.
Wait, wait, stop and stop
Did he seem to enter?
No, no, I can’t get in that.
Oh no, yes yes yes
Okay, so let’s take a picture.
Oh my sister, my sister.
What to dress?
Guey
Laugh at me.
Great, you will follow me.
Because I want to bear.
Because it is birthday.
Is it filmed?
Was it filmed?
See and see.
Very cute is.
Send it later?
I will wait for you two.
Okay okay okay.
The Birthday of Money.
It is written.
Is it okay?
Did you drink too much?
I drank a lot.
It is Beronberon.
Not so strong.
What to do.
A little more.
I want to drink.
I go to sleep.
I borrow it.
Yes, and well.
It was fun.
Forget about me.
You will have money.
You are very important to you.
Sorry to
Because he is a more convenient man.
You are very important about the ZTE.
Because I do not want that.
Our relationship is over.
Please do not say that.
Stop to
Can’t really?
It is over.
Just a kiss.
Then I will do it to you.
Take me apart.
Are you waiting?
I think that would use that.
If you like, show me the title.
Take it off yourself.
Take it all off.
to excite?
It is
rather than the sick.
Eating
be more proper.
rather than the sick.
I will eat.
I am
I feel good about yours too.
Then do it.
More than in the eyes.
Money is not enough.
go to
Yes is
Oh yeah
by Kay
Just like Mai-san.
You will not eat.
rather than the sick.
It is Kizai.
So let me lick.
I think so, a little.
I want to lick.
Please please.
Hills is
Then I cannot get money either.
It looks poor.
I want to enter.
I am sorry to want to enter.
He was so angry.
Can I enter?
I want to get in.
Sorry to sorry.
What happened?
Feels too good.
I feel good now.
Let me go, let me go.
It feels too much.
cannot move.
cannot be
I will go inside.
This is
So that
What happened.
Oh, this is not.
Our relationship is over.
Can I finish?
I don’t want to finish, but I’ll leave.
No to no.
You will go out.
If you are going to be so full of stuff, you feel.
I was so interested in doing that before.
I’ll go out and say it’s red, what if I’m out?
You can say nothing.
Oh yeah
Let me tell you about me.
Oh is bad.
The stomach hurts.
My stomach hurt.
Sister is
No to
I thought my stomach hurt.
It is limit.
Go to sleep?
My stomach hurt.
Oh go go
No longer go out.
Do not go out.
Oh, I went out.
I’ll go shopping a little.
Come to go.
I will go.
Yes, no no
Out of devastated.
Go home to.
Oh yeah no no.
MILLY
The Land
laying
Oh, oh oh
On the way home, I have a new cake shop, so it looks so cute and delicious.
I will leave your department.
thanks to
What is good?
Short cake and chocolate.
And I also love your brother’s moon.
Next is delicious.
Oh, what can I do.
There are a lot of things, don’t get lost.
I think it’s a good Mont Blanc, my sister.
Go to Mont Blanc.
Yes, but by Viber.
become a job.
What happened?
What do I do sister?
It seems to have gone.
sweetly
You are watching great.
I liked it very much. thanks.
Generally done.
If you are getting rid of it now, it is not good for the baby.
After entering the stabilizer.
I thought he moved.
Yes to?
Sorry, I have to move.
Is the rent okay?
Yes
Do not worry about me.
Oh yeah
Is it okay?
Better to sleep.
Sorry to
Why apologize?
It was good.
Please do not be angry.
I am not angry at all.
Also by Mr.
You wanted to.
Stop it.
Sorry to
He looked angry, right?
not angry.
It is also important for your dog.
Do not say good things about summer.
When the money comes up, I don’t know.
It is your fault.
It is because of me.
I just want to see.
No to
You are you.
The least
You want to wait.
I am interested in Miyamoto.
Be more and more important.
Sorry to
Lie to me.
A great medicine.
Because they beat faith.
Really my feeling.
You do not know.
Shit
Oh to!
No more no more.
by
Oh yeah
Dare to lose.
This is finished.
It tastes.
It looks delicious.
I will have.
thanks to
I did all the laundry, too.
Thanks to.
My sister.
Because there is a test.
I will go to the hospital.
Is it okay alone?
Yes
No to sister.
Something happened in the beginning.
What is something?
Nothing is anything.
I will go.
Acorn
They seem to doubt us.
That is so.
No longer
Should I better finish it?
If you are sad about money.
I will not forgive.
1 is
2nd
No to
Put it in.
Feel good
Wait a little.
It feels good.
Only her sister.
I too
Feel good
5 days of good night.
Bookbuck
Here is Oh.
sharply
It has nothing to do with the eggs.
by Nayem
No to
Oh well 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂
Oh well...
by ATA
Walked by Walked
by
Oh oh oh oh oh oh.
Oh yeah
Yes is
Oh the Nemo.
Oh yeah
Oh he
ICO is