I'm going to take a break and go to the hospital.
I do not hit...
She is a lady.
Mr.Jr. loves her.
Okay, I'll wait for you on the team.
Oh, yes, please.
Oh, well, is there anything for Ruka-san, who is in charge of Kansai?
Can I present it a little?
Oh, sorry.
There is a place in Kyoto that has become quite a hot topic in this season.
Oh, I know.
Oh, do you know?
This is like a pilgrimage, and it seems that many people are going there.
If there are people who are interested in Kyoto, I recommend this package of Kyoto.
Can I ask for Kyushu next?
Yes.
Hey, what are you shooting?
I'm shooting.
No, you can't.
It's a meeting.
It will be exposed.
I'm doing my best.
You can't take it.
You can't.
It's a meeting.
Mr. Wakita, where are you going?
Yes.
Oh, what is it?
The plan for Kyushu.
Oh, I see.
It would be nice if I could go around Kyushu.
Did you listen to me?
Yes, I did.
Kyushu, right?
Yes.
I'm going to be asked again.
I couldn't see it earlier.
I saw it.
Every time.
It will be exposed.
It's not.
I see.
We can propose it together.
We can do that, too.
That's all for today.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Mr. Wakita, I'm sorry.
Could you clean up the materials here?
Yes.
Thank you.
Could you help me?
I asked you to correct it last week, but it hasn't been fixed at all.
Is that so?
Look, the numbers are completely different.
You know the deadline for this is over, right?
I'm sorry.
If you don't do it in a hurry, it will take a lot of time.
Thank you.
Be sure to do it.
I'm angry.
It's cute.
Please do it today.
I see.
Thank you.
I'm angry.
I'm not angry.
Hey.
I'm angry.
Do you want to do it?
No.
No?
Why are you angry?
I'm angry.
Ms. Furukawa.
Yes.
Are you free now?
I'm free.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Yes.
I heard that there were many complaints from customers the other day.
Is that so?
I think you should change the bus company.
If you don't change it, you won't be able to continue that plan.
I see.
Thank you.
Please do it.
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm angry.
I'm angry, too.
I made a mistake.
I helped you to make the documents.
Again?
I helped you before.
I helped you before, too.
I brought you a meal.
What are you going to make this time?
YAKITORI.
YAKITORI?
Is that okay?
Yes.
Okay.
I'll send you an e-mail.
Please do only half of it.
What?
Half of it?
Yes.
That's fine.
Is that okay?
I just sent you an e-mail.
Yes.
I received it.
I haven't done it at all.
I'll send you an e-mail.
Hey.
What?
Give me back my cell phone.
I'm angry.
RUKA, can I talk to you for a moment?
Yes.
You may be angry again.
Last year, you had a good reputation.
I have a question.
What are you going to do this year?
I think it's important to listen to the local people.
I see.
I'll keep this.
I want to drink tea.
Do you want to drink tea?
Yes.
Are you making a document?
What?
I'm taking a break.
Are you making a document?
I'm making a document.
You're not making a document.
Again?
Yes.
You're being spoiled.
I can work.
I think so.
You can work.
You're right.
I've been working for a long time.
You're a slacker.
I'm a slacker.
You're good at it.
I have to take a break.
I can't do it easily.
You take too many breaks.
It's hard.
Why are you taking a break?
I came to drink tea.
I just came to drink tea.
Hey.
I can't do it.
Someone will come.
I'm taking a break.
I can hear your voice.
You can hide it.
Just a little.
I'm scared.
Everyone in my company works.
Hey.
I can't do it.
Just a little.
You said you wanted me to touch you.
You said it.
You didn't say it.
I didn't say it.
You said it.
It's dangerous.
If it's dangerous, you can hide it.
I can't do it.
I can hear your voice.
Are you having fun?
I don't know.
Aren't you having fun?
I'm having fun.
I can't do it.
I don't want to show you.
Are you okay?
I can hear your voice.
You can hide it.
I can't do it.
You said you wanted me to touch you.
You said you wanted me to touch your neck.
Just a little.
I can't do it.
You said you wanted me to touch you.
You said you wanted me to touch you all the time.
It's dangerous.
You didn't have a ribbon.
I did.
Can I kiss you?
I can't do it.
Are you okay?
I'm not okay at all.
If you go there with this, you'll be in trouble.
I can't do it.
They were both angry today.
Look at me.
I'm embarrassed.
Do you want me to do it?
I made a mistake.
I'm embarrassed.
Me, too.
I can't do it.
I want to lick you.
Do you hate it?
I like that.
I don't like it.
I want to kill you.
Do you want me to kill you?
I'll hide your butt.
I want to lick you.
Can I lick you?
I was patient.
I'm embarrassed.
I want to kill you.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
I'm excited.
I'm nervous.
I made you nervous.
What are you going to do if someone comes?
I'll kill you.
Will you be angry with me?
Will you kill me?
I'll kill you.
I don't care.
I want to lick you.
You had a lot of work, didn't you?
I have a lot of work to do.
You don't have to come.
I'll go back after I lick you.
I want to lick you.
I can't help it.
I love you.
You're taking a lot of pictures.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you excited?
I'm excited.
You're excited, aren't you?
Why do you like licking?
I don't know.
Because I like to fall.
Is it weird?
Is it delicious?
You've grown up a lot.
When did you start licking me?
I want to lick you all the time.
When you're angry.
When you're angry?
What do you mean?
I really wanted to lick you.
You've changed.
I was angry a while ago.
I was angry.
I was angry, but I thought I'd get angry if I licked you.
I'm angry.
I can't stand up.
You can't stand up even if you lick me?
I'm standing up now.
I feel good.
Look at me.
Where?
Office.
I can't go to the office.
Everyone is there.
I can't go.
I'm a little angry.
Thank you very much.
It's dangerous.
It's dirty.
Yes, it is.
I'm sorry.
You can't do that.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Just a little bit.
Keep your eyes on it.
It's dangerous.
You can see it.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I'll call you by your cell phone.
I want to put it in.
It's dirty.
Oh, no.
I'll go first.
Thank you.
Mr. Okita.
Yes?
It's almost time for the meeting.
Oh, I see.
Yes.
Shall we go?
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Shall we go?
Yes, let's go.
I'm going to the meeting.
Are they all gone?
What are they doing?
Hey, are you still recording?
What?
Are you recording?
Yes, I am.
Why?
The meeting is about to start.
Yes.
I want to do it.
What?
The meeting is about to start.
I want to do it.
What?
Sex.
The meeting is about to start.
I don't want to do it.
Why?
I said I don't want to do it.
I'll be scolded again.
What?
Why?
I said I don't want to do it.
What are you going to do if someone comes in?
I have to open the door.
What?
It's dangerous.
I might stop.
I want to do it.
Don't you want to go to the meeting?
Don't you want to do it?
I want to do it.
Do you want to have sex or not?
I want to have sex.
I don't want to have sex.
Really?
I see.
I'm getting used to it.
I'm taking a break.
Thank you for your patience.
Sorry for not coming.
Sorry.
I'm writing a document.
I see.
Yes.
It's an international betting series.
The percentage of betting winning is 40%.
We have a condition for this choice.
This will be changed to 20% after January 10th next year.
There are three ways to apply for a lease.
1. Apply from a travel agency.
2. Apply from a hotel booking site.
3. Apply from a hotel booking site.
4. Apply from a hotel booking site.
I would like to explain where you can apply for a lease.
If you have any questions, please feel free to ask.
There is a special page on the booking site.
Please apply for a lease from the special page.
This is the explanation in the government page.
Let's compare the three major companies.
There is a difference between the two companies.
However, the percentage of each company is almost the same.
If you look at it in detail, you can see that there is only one change.
This is my personal opinion.
However, I don't think it's a big difference.
Let's make a decision here.
We will make a decision until the next meeting.
We will let you know when we make a decision.
This is the travel agency in Hokkaido.
We will make a decision here.
We will make a decision until the next meeting.
We will let you know when we make a decision.
I will organize the documents.
We will make a decision here.
Can you help me?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
She hasn't come back yet.
What?
I don't think she will come back.
I don't know.
I can hear her footsteps.
She left.
Why did she leave?
Because it was an accident.
An accident?
Yes, an accident.
Why did she leave?
It was just an accident.
Pants can be torn easily.
You don't have to lock the door.
I will lock the door.
Did you lock the door?
I have to clean up.
You can clean up soon.
Clean up my bed.
Clean up your bed?
Why did you climb on my bed?
You can't climb on my bed.
You can't.
I'm filming you.
What will you do if your bed is broken?
I will lie on your bed.
Do you want to lie on my bed?
How do you feel?
I'm excited.
Let's take a picture.
Do you want to take a picture?
I'm embarrassed.
I will lie down.
I want to open the door.
I'm happy.
What will you do if you take a picture?
I will save it.
I'm happy.
Are you happy?
What makes you happy?
I'm happy.
You hit me.
Are you angry?
It hurt.
Did it hurt?
I'll pat you.
I just want to pat you.
I want to pat you.
Don't you want to be patted?
I'm happy.
How do you feel?
I want you to be happier.
I'm happy.
It's dangerous here.
Can I stop?
No.
You're mean.
Sit down.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
I know.
I'm scared.
I'm sorry.
You'll be in trouble if the doctor sees you.
I'm worried.
You look like you've been to the doctor.
Again, in a place like this.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm going to do it.
You're going to do it?
Yeah.
Isn't it crazy?
Really?
Yeah.
A little more.
I'm scared.
Isn't this place dangerous?
Let's go to the bathroom.
Bathroom?
Are you going to use the bathroom?
By car.
Yeah.
Are you sleeping?
I'm going to sleep.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
You're sweating a lot.
It feels good.
Open your eyes.
I'll take a picture of you.
I'm embarrassed.
What are you going to do?
It's over.
Is it over?
Let's finish it together.
Can you finish it with me?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I love you.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm embarrassed.
This rug is...
sometimes too mid, but it's still better than nothing ever.
But we got rid of this one, so it should be fine.
Because...
The snake is gonna be my accomplice.
Don't swing your head too much.
I'm going to sleep.
It feels good.
You're doing great.
Let's continue.
I'm going to sleep.
Where did you go?
Hurry up.
I'm going to sleep.
Do you want me to sleep?
You got 87 points.
I got 100 points.
I'm going to sleep.
It's cool and fun.
I got 100 points.
I'm going to sleep.
It feels good.
Where are you going?
I'm going to sleep.
It feels good.
You're soaked.
I'm going to sleep.
Can I hug you?
It feels good.
It's fun.
I'm going to sleep.
Are you watching me?
Can I hug you more?
I don't want you to find out.
I'm going to sleep.
It's embarrassing.
It feels good.
Can you move?
I'm going to sleep.
Are you watching me?
dabbing
Start here
Done...
no no no
Oppa, you alright!?
Just what should I...
O-okay
What should I do?
Wh-what should I do?
Just what should I do?
Hey, you're mean.
Look at me.
I feel sick.
My voice is gone.
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
Can I move more?
Can you move?
Can I move?
I'll show you how to move.
I feel sick.
I'm fine.
I'm so scared.
I feel sick.
Can I move more?
I can't move.
I feel sick.
Can I move more?
I'll clean up.
I feel sick.
I can't move.
I might have a lot.
Do you want me to clean you up?
It hurts.
That feels good.
Do you feel better now?
Yes.
It's good for your face, isn't it?
Here I go.
That feels good.
You ate too much, didn't you?
You ate too much.
That tickles.
That feels good.
Your face.
Are you okay?
I need to fix your makeup.
I'll fix your makeup.
I hope you didn't notice.
I have to go out later.
Are you okay?
What about you, Rio?
I'm going to make medicine.
Good luck with that.
See you later.
I'm going to make medicine.
I found a nice restaurant near the station.
Do you want to go there?
Yes, I do.
What kind of restaurant is it?
It's a restaurant that's good for dinner.
Do you like wine?
Yes, I do.
You like women, don't you?
There are wines from different countries.
You can taste them.
That's great.
I'm sorry, Kogure.
I'm sorry.
Did you go to that restaurant?
I don't know.
What's the name of the restaurant?
I've seen a new restaurant near the station.
It's called Higashiguchi.
Higashiguchi.
Do you want to go there with me?
Yes, I do.
When do you want to go?
When I get my salary.
When do you get your salary?
I don't have money.
You don't have to.
I have a lot of money.
I'd like to ask you to summarize the information of the restaurant.
I'll do it until next week.
Then, I'd like to ask you to summarize it.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'd like to ask you to explain the data.
Anzai.
Yes.
Can you come here for a moment?
Okay.
I got an e-mail from you.
The number you gave me the other day has changed.
Oh, that number.
I see.
The number has been changed.
Okay.
I don't know if you can see it.
He's taking a picture again.
The number you gave me has changed.
What are you doing?
It's still cold.
I was reading an e-mail.
An e-mail?
Yes.
Did you make the data?
Yes, I did.
Okay.
I'll make it in the middle of the week.
You should go home early.
What?
I can't.
You should go home early.
Why?
He's looking at me.
I can't.
Someone is coming.
It's dangerous.
I can't.
It's over.
Someone is coming.
I can't.
I'm scared.
He's looking at me.
It's dangerous.
The manager is looking at me.
I can't.
He's working.
What?
He's not working.
It's OK.
Today?
It's not late.
It's late.
Late?
Late.
I'm going to have lunch.
It's dangerous.
Can't you have lunch today?
I'm working.
I can't go home because I'm slacking off.
Because I'm slacking off.
Do you want to eat?
I want to eat.
No one is here.
Take a good look.
It's the same.
Are you two slacking off?
It's dangerous.
I'm hungry.
Are you okay?
He's coming to eat.
I can't.
I can't today.
Why?
I can't go home today.
I'm lonely.
Can you stay a little longer?
Is there a good thing?
What good thing?
Can you stay a little longer?
Can you help me with my work?
I don't want to.
What's a bad thing?
Is there a good thing?
Is there?
Then, I'm going to leave.
I'm going to leave.
Are you okay?
I'm hungry.
Thank you for your hard work.
Excuse me.
Everyone left.
Are you going to finish early?
No, I'm not.
Then, I'm going to leave.
Thank you.
I'm not good at giving presents.
It's difficult.
Hey.
What?
Do you want to say something?
I finished collecting the presents.
When will you finish?
Tomorrow.
It's before the end of the year.
Does it take that long?
It's still June.
Is it that long?
Do you want to do it now?
It's past the end of the year.
Do you want to do it tomorrow?
No, I don't want to do it.
You don't want to do it, do you?
I don't want to do it.
You don't want to do it?
What are you going to do?
Are you taking pictures again?
What?
You've been taking pictures all the time.
I'm not taking pictures.
You're taking pictures.
Are you working?
Yes, I am.
Let's do something good soon.
Hey.
Don't push me.
I want to do something good.
Okay?
Do you want to do something good?
Just a little.
Just a little?
Five minutes.
Five minutes?
Do you want to do it for five minutes?
What are you going to do for five minutes?
I want to lick you.
Okay?
Okay.
I'll lick you.
No one else is here.
What are you going to do when you get home?
I don't want to be forced to do it.
You're the worst.
Do you want to do it for five minutes?
Five minutes may be too long.
Okay.
Can I lick you?
I can't do it.
I want to lick you.
I'm excited at night.
You're doing something nasty in the dark.
I'm excited.
It's okay.
Just a little.
I just want to work.
Do you want to do something nice while you're working?
I don't want to work.
Try it.
Do you want to work?
I don't want to work.
Make a good feed.
If I make a weird feed, you'll get angry.
Then we'll get angry together again.
I'm the only one who can get angry.
It's good.
Make a good feed.
You can't go home if you skip a meal.
You're the worst.
Do you hate me?
I like you.
You like me, don't you?
I want to work.
I'm getting dizzy.
I think it's been about a minute.
I haven't made any progress yet.
About a minute?
You said you wanted to do something nice for five minutes.
Do you want to stop?
You'll get angry.
I want to work.
Don't you want to work?
I don't want to work.
I've been filming you all the time.
Why have you been filming me all the time?
I thought you'd get angry.
What should I do if someone comes?
Is it a security guard?
I'm going to be fired.
I'm going to work.
I'm nervous because I'm at work.
I'll help you.
I feel good.
I want to feel better.
I'm going to be fired.
I don't want anyone to come.
I'm hungry.
I feel good.
I'm going to be fired.
I'm nervous because I'm at work.
I feel good.
I want to feel better.
I want to have sex.
What?
You want to have sex.
No.
I want to have sex.
Are you wet?
I feel good.
Why are you so wet?
If I were here, I would have had sex.
I feel good.
You move a lot.
I want to have sex.
Do you want to have sex?
You're in the way of my work.
I can't?
You can't.
You're mean.
I'm going to sleep.
I want to sleep.
Do you want to have sex?
I want to have sex.
I feel good.
Why are you so wet?
I'm going to sleep.
I feel good.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
Let's see your belly.
Can you see my belly?
Look at me.
Raise your arms.
Can you see my belly?
I can see your belly.
I feel good.
I'm hot.
Come here.
I feel good.
I'm sleepy.
It's fun, isn't it?
Yes.
I can have sex because no one is here.
I feel good.
I'm going to run away.
I'm used to it.
You like it, don't you?
I feel good.
I was surprised.
Do you feel good?
It's getting hard.
I feel good.
I can't see anything.
I'm used to it.
I'm used to it because I feel good.
I feel good.
You like it, don't you?
I can't do it anymore.
I feel good.
Can I move a lot?
Can you bear it?
Can I bear it?
Yes.
Look at me.
I feel good.
I can't do it anymore.
I want to go out.
Do you want to go out?
Yes.
Can you go out a lot?
Where should I go out?
Where do you want to go out?
Anywhere is fine.
Right?
Yes.
Anywhere is fine.
Can you bear it?
Yes.
I feel good.
I can't do it anymore.
I want to go out.
Do you want to go out?
Yes.
I feel good.
I can't do it anymore.
You can't do it anymore.
Do you want to continue your work?
I'm going to finish my work.
See you tomorrow.
You're naked.
I'm embarrassed.
How do you feel?
You're naked.
Go back to your seat.
Where are your panties?
Panties?
You tore your panties.
Let's get back to work.
When does the meeting start?
The meeting will start soon.
Soon?
Yes.
Let's go.
It's a long meeting.
I'm going to the meeting.
I'm going to be late.
It's a long meeting.
I understand.
Let's go.
It's a long meeting.
I can't do this.
What?
I don't want to do this.
Do you want to fly?
I want to fly.
No, you can't.
You'll catch a cold.
Thank you for the meal.
How far are you going?
This is the summary of the travel support of each company.
It's on the third page of the document.
It's the summary of the three companies.
It's calculated according to the annual rate in 2022.
We don't have the data yet.
I'm going to make a mistake in the summary.
I'll make a new one and put it together again.
I'm sorry I'm late.
It's okay.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I see.
I'll review the data again and put it together.
It's okay.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Thank you very much.
We always clean up.
What?
I'm happy.
What's that?
Really?
Yes.
Are you filming today, too?
Are you addicted to filming?
No, I'm not.
It's fun.
Why don't you do it at work?
What?
I'm a little nervous.
It's exciting.
Is it exciting?
How is it?
It's exciting.
Is it exciting?
Yes.
It's good, isn't it?
You're motivated today, aren't you?
Well...
It's hot in this room.
I'm on a business trip.
Really?
Yes.
Where are you going?
Osaka.
For how many days?
I'll be back on the weekend.
It's a long time.
I don't know.
It may be only today.
I'll see you again.
It's hot.
You're going to do a lot today.
I'll do a lot.
What are you doing?
I'm going to do a lot.
Are you going to do a lot?
You're going to do a lot.
No.
I like talking to you, but...
I want to make you feel better.
It feels good.
What are you going to do until the weekend?
Are you going to put up with it?
I'm going to do a lot today.
It feels good.
I'm getting used to it.
I'm listening to you.
I'm going to make you work with this.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm getting used to it.
Did you find out?
I'm listening to you.
It feels good.
You're rubbing me a lot.
I'm rubbing you.
It feels good.
Morito dares not eat the food he eats.
Tickling
I want to cry when I think of how much I thank her for everything.
I feel so sad.
But I can't help taking a break.
Oh, it hurts.
It hurts.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
Oh, that's great.
I'm out of breath.
You're not here anymore, are you?
I'm not here anymore.
Are you lonely?
I'm lonely, so be strong.
I'm not lonely.
It feels good.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to be fired.
But it feels good and I can't stop.
My legs are moving.
I'm going to be fired if I keep doing this.
I want to lick you.
It's okay, right?
I want you to poop.
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
You remember a lot, don't you?
What's wrong?
I want to poop.
You're shaking a lot.
It feels good.
I want to poop.
Come here.
Why are you pooping here?
I want to poop.
Put it in your mouth.
No.
Okay.
I want to poop.
Mari who only holds a toy and does not administrator in a room ...
Manbo has a lot ofthers in the room.
Then he has power in his hands ...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You are hitting me a lot.
Maybe.
Then, go to bed early.
Let me remember.
I don't want to.
You are hitting me a lot.
You are saying you want to go to bed.
It feels good.
You are hitting me a lot.
I don't want to.
I won't forget your shape.
I can't stop it.
It feels good.
You are hitting my head a lot.
What?
Stop it.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Wow.
You do not seem to mind if I smoke a crown.
There's a lot.
Wow.
I had a hard time.
Do you mind if I close my eyes for a minute?
Yes.
Oh.
You just had to tell him that, Ono?
You already cried a lot yesterday.
I don't know who you are.
You're suspicious.
Oh!
Oh, I'm so tired.
It's so hot.
It's so cool.
Do you have Rion's phone?
Rion's phone?
I don't have it.
What?
Do you have Rion's phone?
I don't have it.
I'm just licking it.
It's cool.
I don't like it.
I'm just licking it.
Whose manko and chinchin are these?
Rion's manko and Okuta's chinchin.
You've got a lot of sweat.
Oh, it's cool.
Why are you so serious?
It's embarrassing.
It's so sexy.
You're enjoying yourself, aren't you?
It tickles.
I've got a lot of sweat.
You've got a lot of sweat.
It tickles.
I'm getting a lot of sweat.
Are you?
You're getting more and more sweaty.
My butt is shaking.
Your butt is shaking.
It tickles.
I've got a lot of sweat.
Can you look at me?
I wonder if someone is there.
With this?
I'm in trouble.
No one is there.
What should I do if someone is there?
Can you bring my clothes?
It tickles.
What time is it?
It's 5 o'clock.
It tickles.
Does it tickle?
It feels really good.
I can't do it anymore.
It's okay.
I think I'm used to it today.
Really?
Yes.
Why?
I don't know.
It feels good.
Really?
Does it feel better than usual?
It feels good.
It hurts.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
Not yet?
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
You're used to it, aren't you?
Yes.
It feels good.
Take as much as you can.
Does it feel good?
Can you see well?
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Let me see your face.
It hurts.
It feels good.
What are you doing in the video I just took?
Let's clean up.