Indifference
I'm sick of it.
This is so disgustingly disgusting.
It came through.
Another faulting walker...
A walking vampire was here!
It's really awful!
It's disgusting...
eriotic
Put her down.
I hate that thing.
She'll be fine.
Hey, sleep.
I'm going to tell you why I'm doing this.
Good morning, Ms. Miyoka.
Good morning. You're early today.
Yes, I am.
I have a souvenir for you.
Would you like to have it?
Yes, is it okay?
It's a famous sake in my hometown.
Please drink it.
Thank you very much.
Don't worry about it.
I'll take this.
Thank you very much.
My family will be happy, too.
Don't worry about it.
Thank you very much.
Good morning.
Would you like something to drink?
Would you like coffee?
Yes, please.
Here you are.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Oh, I see.
My neighbor, Hosoda-san, asked me to drink with you.
It's sake.
It looks good.
It's local sake.
I see.
I've just received it.
Please tell him that I'll have it for dinner next time.
I see.
Chika, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Thank you very much.
Where are you going to have dinner?
I'll have dinner at home.
I see.
Take care.
I'll be back soon.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done that.
You don't have to apologize.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
My husband was a good man.
He was a good man.
But he was a bad husband.
Until that happened,
We were a peaceful and normal married couple.
Cheers.
It's delicious.
Thank you for inviting me today.
Don't mention it.
I'm sorry that I always receive food from you.
It's okay.
Your wife's cooking is delicious.
I'm sorry that I can't cook well.
It's enough.
It's so delicious.
There's more.
Take your time.
Thank you.
Your wife's cooking is delicious.
It's delicious.
It's so delicious.
I'm so happy.
Can I have more?
Eat more.
You like this, don't you?
I love it.
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
It's good for your health.
Eat more.
I will.
Did you have fun?
Did you drink too much?
I had fun drinking with you.
I'm glad.
I had fun, too.
I'll clean up.
I'll help you.
It's okay.
I'll help you, too.
You gave me a delicious meal.
Is it hot?
It was really delicious.
I'm full.
It's okay.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Don't do that.
Don't make her hate you.
I won't.
Miyoko.
I'm sorry.
The storeroom.
Second floor.
Yes, sir!
I can handle it.
Let's go to bed early.
That's right.
It's not good to be late the next day.
I have to get up early tomorrow.
I overslept.
What do you think of this?
I think it's good.
Really?
I'm glad.
I'll do it for you.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I can't do it.
You feel sorry for me, don't you?
What?
I don't feel sorry for you.
I was looking at you the other day.
What were you looking at?
You were hugged by Hosoda.
What?
No.
It's okay.
What?
Satomi.
I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
Can you hug me again?
What?
What do you mean?
Can you show me that you're having sex with him?
What are you talking about?
I know I'm saying something strange.
But I stood up when I saw you.
Maybe it'll get better.
That's why I...
You love me, don't you?
What?
Yes.
Then, please.
Please, Satomi.
Yes.
Welcome.
Please come in.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
This is boring, but I hope you'll like it.
Thank you.
Can you hug me?
What?
Miyoko.
Wait.
What's wrong?
Please don't say anything.
Miyoko.
I'm sorry.
You're beautiful.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
You're beautiful.
Miyoko.
I'm sorry.
I'm so wet.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm sorry.
You're beautiful.
Does it feel good?
This bag is very beautiful.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
I love you.
I'm so jealous of you.
You're so cute.
Can I kiss you from behind?
From behind?
I love you.
You're so beautiful.
Please wait.
I love you.
No, I won't.
What?
Oh, god...
Stop.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh
I
Oh oh
I'll go...
I don't know what to do with myself.
JIGO
7 days later
I don't know what to do with myself.
Then I'll enjoy the meal today too!
Thank you for the meal.
First of all, I'll try the soup first.
It's a little spicy and delicious.
It's not as spicy as I thought it would be, but it's delicious.
The soup is delicious, but I think the spicy taste is a little strong.
It's a little spicy, but it's delicious.
It was
You know
Honey
It's okay.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
It gets cold.
Let's go inside the room.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
OK.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Here's a present.
What?
What is this?
I brought it.
You like flowers, right?
Yeah.
I don't know if you'll like it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I like this color.
It's cute.
I'm sorry.
I don't think I can do it.
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
It won't heal that easily.
I'm sorry.
Do you want another cup of coffee?
I'll take it.
Hey.
You have a day off tomorrow.
Can you go shopping instead of me?
Tomorrow?
I don't mind.
I'll text you later.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'm glad you called me.
I'm sorry.
Ah, how disgusting.
Oh, it's hot.
It's hot.
It's so hard.
Welcome.
Oh, it's hot.
It's so hard.
Please lick it first.
Oh, it feels so good.
It feels so good in my mouth.
May I?
I'm so used to it.
It feels so good.
It's been a while since I felt this good.
I'll make you feel better.
What's that?
Can I move too?
I want you to move.
What's that?
Wow.
I feel sick.
What's that?
I want you to move.
I feel sick.
Does this feel good?
This?
Wow.
I feel sick.
I want you to touch my butt.
Wow.
I feel sick.
It's been a long time since I've been this high.
I want to jump higher.
I feel sick.
I can't stand it.
Come on.
Lick me.
Wow.
I feel sick.
I'll come again.
Yes.
Darling.
You are very hard.
It's been a long time.
I'm happy.
I'm very happy.
I love you.
Are you angry?
I'm not angry.
You hugged me for me.
I want you to be happy.
I want you to hug me strongly.
I love you.
I'm happy.
Thank you.
I love you.