I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first
time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time, and I'm going to draw a picture
of a cat that I met for the first time in a long time.
Who?
Unknown person?
Business?
Ah, that...
Ah, I'm finally back.
Ah, don't you know me?
Wait a minute.
Ah, old lady.
Long time no see.
I'm sorry.
It's been a while.
Yeah, it's been a while.
Onee-chan asked me to make sure that Dai-kun is able to live on his own.
Oh, I see.
That's amazing.
I didn't know that.
It's been a while.
Are you able to drink alcohol now?
Yeah, a little bit.
You know, I have a lot of friends.
It's good that Onee-chan is strong.
I couldn't drink alcohol in the past.
You're strong.
That's right.
I'm getting better now.
It's been a while since I drank alcohol.
Don't I look red?
You're still fine.
Really?
You look like a family.
But Onee-chan can drink a lot.
I'm fine.
You're drinking too much.
I'm sorry.
Dai-kun, you're going to be a college student soon, right?
You're going to have a drinking party soon.
You should be able to drink alcohol.
You're right.
I don't drink much.
Really?
Dai-kun is similar to me.
I'm not good at drinking.
I'm not good at drinking, either.
That's right.
Don't overdo it.
Okay.
But today is a special day.
It's good for you, isn't it?
You're right.
It's delicious.
I feel like I'm going to drink alcohol today.
Are you in a good mood?
I'm in a good mood.
Are you sure?
Are you okay?
Why?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
So...
She was not good at drinking.
I'm fine.
I'm not drunk.
I can still drink.
You're too excited.
I want water.
Give me water.
I want to drink something more delicious.
I want to drink sake.
You should go to bed.
I don't want to sleep.
Where are you going?
I want to drink sake.
I want to drink with you, ma'am.
Don't drink too much.
Drink sake.
You can't be a fine person in this situation.
Drinking sake with you is delicious, isn't it?
Why?
I'm going to drink it.
Hey, sister.
Oh, stop it.
I'm going to drink it.
Oh, she ran away.
She ran away.
I'm sad.
What is it?
Hey, hey.
Let's open the bottle.
No, Mahiro.
I want to drink it.
Oh, it looks delicious.
I'm fine.
Don't say that.
I was asked to do it.
Put it in the bottle.
I'm going to drink it.
Excuse me.
It's dirty.
This is what a man's private life is like.
I haven't washed it yet.
I have to do this often.
I'll do it later.
You should do it.
I don't often do it.
There's a little bit of the tea, so I have to do it soon.
If you don't wash it, it will be difficult to take it out.
I wonder how old you will be.
But you are still in good shape.
All right.
Well, that's it.
Thank you.
You are welcome.
What did you buy?
I bought this.
You drink this in the daytime.
You are a good boy.
Thank you.
It's nice to be able to drink freely.
He is noisy at home.
So I can't drink with him.
This looks delicious.
It's nice.
He is drinking.
This is delicious.
You can drink a little.
You drink this.
Are you serious?
I'm tired.
I'm not good at this.
DAI-KUN.
What are you doing?
I told you not to go to the toilet.
You didn't go to the toilet.
I went to the bathroom.
This is DAI-KUN's room.
This is a man's room.
Don't throw away the garbage.
Please leave it alone.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
Show me your face.
I want to talk to you.
Don't do that.
You are cute.
Show me your face.
DAI-KUN.
Do you have a favorite girl?
I don't have a favorite girl.
Are you sure?
Are you not interested in girls?
I'm not interested.
You are cute.
Then.
How about this?
I'm not interested.
Can you say that you are not interested in this?
Don't say that.
You are lying.
I'm kidding.
You are cute.
Then.
I can smell alcohol from Iroha's lips.
I feel good.
You shouldn't drink so much.
I'm fine.
I can drink a lot even if I look like this.
You can't drink.
That's not true.
I've been drinking a lot lately.
Is that true?
That's true.
Where is your uncle?
He was supposed to come with me today.
But he went on a business trip.
I see.
He seems to be busy lately.
This is really delicious.
I'll buy it next time.
This is easy to drink.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'm glad to hear that.
You are not strong.
You don't want me to drink.
You don't have to worry about that.
I'll put this on you.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
But it looks delicious.
Yes, it is.
Do you have any other food?
No.
You look tired.
I'm getting hungry.
Can you take my bag?
Yes.
Thank you.
Can you buy me some food and alcohol?
I'll use this.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Go ahead.
I'll be right back.
Thank you.
See you.
Drinking alcohol in the afternoon is the best.
I'm hungry.
What's going on?
Thank you for waiting.
It looks delicious.
I'm glad to hear that.
Why?
You should move because you're young.
I'll drink this.
Go ahead.
Wait a minute.
It's too sudden.
I'll drink it slowly.
I see.
I can drink it at once.
Let's do it.
Wait a minute.
I'll drink it slowly.
Are you sure?
I can't drink it at once.
Don't worry.
I've never been drunk.
That's what people who are drunk say.
That's not true.
You're drunk.
Is this it?
I can't drink it.
Wait a minute.
You're not used to it, are you?
Did you find out?
It's what students do.
That's right.
I wanted to try it.
You should do it like this.
Wait a minute.
It's fun to drink with a young person.
You're drinking at a fast pace.
I want to drink more.
Give it to me.
I'll wrap it.
Dai-kun.
You're late.
I'm late.
Thank you.
Come here.
Dai-kun.
Do girls come to this room?
No.
I've never been here.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
What about your girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
Are you sure?
You don't have a girlfriend now?
No, I don't.
It's been a long time.
I've never had a girlfriend here.
Are you sure?
You told me that.
You asked me if I brought a girlfriend.
I told you I don't have a girlfriend.
I've never had a girlfriend.
Don't you have a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
I don't have a girlfriend now.
Do you want to go on a date with a girl?
I don't have a girlfriend.
You should go on a date with a young man like Dai-kun.
When I was young, I was very popular.
Are you sure?
It's a secret.
I understand.
I don't have a chance.
You should make a chance for yourself.
Let's practice here.
I'm a cute girl.
Dai-kun invites me.
Let's practice.
How should I invite you?
I'll go on a date with you.
Let's practice.
I don't have a girlfriend.
You should talk to her.
Why are you hesitating?
It's difficult.
It's not difficult.
Recently, girls are more active.
What should I do if a girl comes to me?
Dai-kun, you are wonderful.
You are wonderful.
What should I do if a girl comes to me?
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect you to kiss me.
I told you to practice.
That's right.
I didn't expect you to kiss me.
I'm sorry.
You are beautiful.
I didn't expect you to kiss me.
I'll go over there.
I'm sorry.
Let's drink again.
That's right.
Yeah.
I'll have a girlfriend soon.
Let's play a game.
A game?
Yes.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
The loser drinks a little.
Okay.
Let's play a game.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
I won't lose.
Let's play a game.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
I lost.
I'll drink.
Don't overdo it.
Let's play a game again.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
I lost again.
You are strong.
I'll drink more.
Please drink more.
I'll drink.
It's getting more interesting.
Do you want to drink more?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Do you want to drink more?
I'll drink more.
Look.
You lost.
I'm not good at drinking.
You are lying.
You don't drink at all.
I always lose.
I'm not that strong.
You are strong.
You are my sister's daughter.
It's been a long time since I had fun like this.
It's fun to drink with you.
It's really fun.
You have grown up.
I changed your diaper.
I can't believe it.
Really?
Of course.
It's embarrassing.
You changed your diaper.
You were cute.
You are still cute.
You are an adult.
Do you want to change your diaper?
My lips are soft.
Are you sure?
Are you okay?
Do you want to change your diaper?
It's good to change your diaper.
Let me wipe your tears.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you okay?
I love you.
My butt.
My butt is beautiful.
I can't touch you.
I'm sorry.
I was surprised.
You're a grown-up.
I'm sorry.
I made you so hard.
Did you make me so hard?
Yes.
That's great.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
You're cute.
Your lips are hard.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
Don't do that.
I'm going to cry.
I'm going to go crazy.
I don't want to.
It's hot.
Give it to me.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
I'm going to go crazy.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
I'm tired.
No, no, no.
It's hot.
Do you want me to do it from behind?
Please.
It's hot.
I'm sweating.
I can do it.
It's hot.
I'm sweating.
It feels good.
I did it.
Let's drink together tomorrow.
Yes.
Thank you for watching.
I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I think it's true.
I think it's true.
Oh, no.
I love you so much.
I love you.
I'm so bored.
Where are you?
Hey.
Please.
More.
That's it.
That's amazing.
No.
I'm scared.
I feel great, too.
I feel great.
Move.
That's amazing.
It's hard.
I feel great.
Is this okay?
That's it.
Sit down.
I feel great.
I'm going to die.
It's okay.
Hey, Dai-kun.
Can I come here again tomorrow?
I have an appointment with my friend tomorrow.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
So, you'd better not come here tomorrow.
I see.
A few days later.
You've been having a hard time lately.
What's wrong with you?
It's because of my mom.
What do you mean?
She's my mom's sister.
I see.
She's really noisy.
That's tough.
I told her not to come here today.
I see.
I want to hang out with her.
You're great.
Cheers.
I want more snacks.
You've only bought a pack of snacks.
I forgot the snacks.
Don't you have any snacks?
I don't have any snacks.
You should have brought more snacks.
Don't you have any snacks?
I don't have any snacks.
Wait a minute.
I'm coming.
Hello.
Mom.
You told me not to come here today.
I did.
You said you had a friend coming today.
I don't drink.
I want to drink with you.
Let's drink together.
I don't want to.
Excuse me.
Are you serious?
You're drinking, aren't you?
I'm looking forward to it.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'm Iroha.
Who is she?
She's an old lady.
I'm an old lady.
What?
Is an old lady this young?
She's young.
She's a good girl.
She's young, but she's an old lady.
I thought she was older because she called me an old lady.
She's a good girl.
She has a good friend.
You're drinking, aren't you?
Yes.
I want to drink, too.
Let's drink.
I like this.
Don't drink too much.
I'm fine.
Let's toast.
She always complains to me.
I thought she was a scary person.
She always says strange things.
I'm worried about her.
She's cute.
It's fun, isn't it?
Yes.
I can't believe I can drink with such a beautiful person.
It's delicious.
She's an old lady.
Why?
She's not a scary person.
I'm not a scary person.
I'm fine.
I don't change even if I drink.
I'm not a strange person.
She's strong.
That's right.
I'm not strong, but I'm fine.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Isn't it strange?
You look more beautiful when you drink.
No way.
I'm not an alcoholic.
Why do you get drunk suddenly?
Because I'm a good person.
You're a good person.
We're different.
Don't drink too much.
I'm fine.
Can I take a picture of you?
What's wrong?
Are you done?
You're my sister's child.
I won't let you get drunk.
Are you serious?
Are you okay?
You're here.
I came to pick you up.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
That's not good.
It's not bad.
Don't push me.
Why?
He's here.
He's sleeping.
Don't you feel hot when you drink?
Don't you feel stuffy?
No, I don't.
You're not an adult.
No, I'm not.
No, you're not.
You're saying yes.
I'll leave it to you.
Hey.
Have you ever had an operation?
No.
I'll do it for you.
What?
It's a secret.
Okay.
Don't you feel stuffy when you drink?
Don't you want to do this?
You're getting bigger.
He's sleeping.
He won't wake up if he sleeps.
I'm sorry.
I've only touched the tip of your nose yet.
You have a pimple on your nose.
You're cute.
Do you want me to put it in your nose?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's really good.
I'm sorry.
Tell me it's no good.
I didn't say it's no good here.
It's delicious.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's hot.
It's no good.
Do you want to touch it?
I want to touch it.
It's no good.
I'll do it for you.
Is it hot?
A little.
A little?
You're so cute.
It's hot.
Do you feel the softness of my breast?
Yes.
It's very soft.
It's hot.
It's delicious.
It's going to come out.
Let's go together.
Put it in your mouth.
It's hot.
It's delicious.
Let's drink again.
You're not awake, are you?
I'm going home today.
See you.
Are you going home?
Excuse me.
It's okay.
Let's drink again.
Okay.
It's hot.
I'm going home.
I'll come back tomorrow.
See you.
Cheers.
I drink alcohol every day.
It's the most fun to drink with you.
I'm glad.
I feel happy every day when I drink with you.
Really?
Yes.
You're happy to hear that.
Dai-kun.
What?
Come here.
Aren't you drunk?
What?
I'm not drunk yet.
I just started drinking.
You seem to be in a good mood today.
I'm having fun.
I'm glad.
Come here.
Why are you embarrassed?
It's hot.
It's too late.
Hey.
It's good to drink at home.
Yes.
Why don't we go out sometimes?
That's a good idea.
Let's change the place.
Is there a good restaurant?
There is a good restaurant in my neighborhood.
What kind of restaurant is it?
The food is good.
And there are many kinds of alcohol.
Do you know any good lemon tea?
Yes.
Let's go.
You like lemon tea, don't you?
Yes.
It's good.
Let's go after drinking this.
Okay.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Again?
Let's do it.
Rock-paper-scissors.
I won this time.
How was it?
It was very good.
It's a good restaurant, isn't it?
I've never drunk such good lemon tea.
I heard you like lemon tea.
Yes.
The frozen lemon was good.
It was good.
I'll go over there.
Wait a minute.
It's close to my house.
Would you like to go there?
Is it okay?
Yes.
Let's drink at my house.
Okay.
Let's go.
Come in.
It's a little messy.
Please wear these slippers.
Thank you.
Please sit over there.
Okay.
I'll make sake and bring it to you.
Thank you.
Please wait a minute.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'll make good sake.
Okay.
Please wait a minute.
Thank you.
I'll make good sake.
Please wait a minute.
Thank you.
Cheers.
How is it?
It's much better than the one I usually buy.
I'm glad.
It's handmade.
Isn't it?
My lemon soba is good, isn't it?
Yes.
I'll drink a lot.
I still have a lot of soba.
You can drink as much as you want.
By the way, where is your husband?
He is on a business trip again.
He said he had a problem at the company.
Is that so?
He is in trouble.
You're on a business trip, too, aren't you?
Yes.
I've been on a lot of business trips lately.
You've been on a business trip for a long time.
My living room is spacious, isn't it?
I feel lonely when I live alone.
I agree.
So, I'm glad you came here.
I'm embarrassed.
You're shy.
I can't help it.
Can I stay here until late?
Yes, you can.
I drank a lot.
That's right.
You can take your time.
I agree.
I'm sorry.
I smell the scent of lemon on yellowfish's lips.
This is a typhoon.
Thank yougod for sending a weight holding video
We have a bigish notification
So check it out
I'm really happy to hear that
I'm really happy to see you guys
It's spunking time
It's super sorry
I just found a language broken
Is there any translator coming with me
I'm scared
What in the world
I don't know if it's because I'm deaf or because I don't know how to read or sign.
I'm not sure.
Riku is quiet because he is a good boy.
Good morning.
Thank you.
I feel so good.
Okay, I'll do it.
I'll do it.
Ouch!
It feels so good.
You're good.
You're very good.
Ouch!
Don't cry.
It feels so good.
I'll show it to you.
I'll do it.
Ouch!
It feels so good.
I'll show it to you.
I'm crying.
It feels so good.
No!
I slept a lot this morning.
I'll make you feel better.
It feels so good.
Does it feel good here?
No!
Don't do that.
It feels so good.
This...
I can't stand it anymore.
Can I put this in your mouth?
Yes.
I want it, too.
It feels so good.
I feel so good, too.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
This time, this side.
Again?
It hurts.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
It's amazing.
I'll do it.
I can't do it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
I can't do it.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Give me a kiss.
Please call me Iroha.
Okay.
It's hot.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'll do it.