This man who puts me behind is not my husband, I will tell you why this happened.
Good morning.
Sorry, it was too early.
I woke up early, I was at work.
Yes is it.
Please enter the coffee.
Oh thank you.
Yes
I got okay.
thanks to
You seem busy lately.
Oh yeah
It is time for the seasons to change.
I have to think about the new menu.
Oh so is.
But
Being busy is good.
Yes, but it is not until the store is open.
Yes, I have to get the reader.
Yes, yes, I call Rick and tell him I want to stay here for a while.
Is that Mr. Rick?
Yes Yes
meet for a long time.
Since when is it.
Okay of course.
thanks to
Sorry for suddenly.
is OK.
thanks to
It was a long time ago that I met Rick.
No to
What are you doing now?
You can only talk about something.
Yes is.
I think it’s a new menu, but I think it’s a tart.
I love the Talmud.
I like it, you know.
It will be popular.
But what kind of tarot do you want to do?
Or is it season fruit, right?
Or even exist.
It is difficult, that is.
It feels great, Wave.
really is?
Good was?
Because it looks good.
Can I try to put it in?
Yes
Then
Sorry to
I want to eat.
by Nay
No apologies, it is okay.
My husband had a dream, and he just started a coffee shop.
Because I am busy every day.
I wanted a child.
Sex was like that.
Oh yeah
Mr. Nami, I am trying to get you.
meet for a long time.
Come in and come in.
Yes I will hinder you.
Please Please Please
It was far away.
No, so much
Oh is?
All part of it?
Sorry for the hand.
It is totally OK.
Okay please.
Thanks to.
Yet yet
You never look at the face at all.
Is it?
Is that praise?
I love you, it will be exciting forever.
Is it really?
If Nami says, I believe it.
indeed if
Oh, so, why did you come here?
Did you hear from Mr. Hart?
Yes, I did not hear.
Mr. Harper, you have been doing this for a long time.
Sorry, I haven’t talked about anything lately.
Sorry, but I said something strange.
Yes, well
I came for training work.
If you tell Mr. Hart, you can use it.
So, it was so.
Sorry for being in a hurry, I will bother you.
It’s not a problem, so you think it’s your home.
Thank you, I will try hard today.
I went home and had eggs.
That was a junkie, the boss is doing it.
It is lying, right?
Really said
Satoshi is you.
The Satoshi?
The President?
Is it not great?
No, I do not believe.
It is a lie.
I am surprised too.
Just now
You go home.
Mr. Harvey go home.
I am hindering you.
meet for a long time.
They are already very friendly.
Yes to?
Yes, it is an old face.
Yes, I don’t know, we are not together.
I know that you both do not say that.
Yes is it.
What are you dinner?
I ate it, it is okay.
Can I just get a coffee?
Oh, I understand
thanks to
for a long time.
Was he well?
Sorry, but I’m so narrow.
It’s not so bad, if you accuse me, beat me.
So do it.
Then I shut off the electricity.
Good night to you.
Good night, well
So I will go.
Yes, come to me.
Nelly, I am going to go.
Something I am glad.
Go to come.
What are you saying.
Go to.
Yes is
Be careful.
Go to.
by Nami
Rick, you are too early today.
I was just doing business today, so it was quick.
It will fall.
thanks to
Is it a little okay?
Let us go.
What happened to Rick? – We have no food yet.
Yes, I will also get a drink.
Okay, because it’s in the kitchen refrigerator.
Thanks, I will get you.
Yes, yes, it is late.
Oh yeah, yeah, I understand it.
Be careful, no.
Is it Mr. Hart?
It seems like there was a problem with the farm.
It is going to be late.
Yes is it.
The shop is difficult.
than that.
Rick is not used to the environment, right?
No, it is not that difficult at all.
Is it not more difficult to do home work or a place to work?
No, no, if I say so.
Do this you do.
Oh, I will do it now.
I will help you here.
Yes, is it okay?
Yes, I think it will look like an iron.
Yes, it is awesome.
Please please please.
Yes, let me take care of it.
there
Is it okay?
Did not burn?
Mr Rick
Rick is...
What happened?
From before...
I always... liked it.
Even if they are eaten, they are refused.
I must like it.
Wait to
by Smear
Not to break.
Even if Mr. Hart is there.
I am...
2nd
Hyun is
I am tired.
Oh...
No to...
Stop it...
No to
No to no.
I cannot, I cannot stop.
No to
is beautiful.
Everything is beautiful.
Tears are
Or go away.
See also
I am tired.
It is in tears.
The year 2016.”
hurtly
Sit on it.
Yippidy yi yippity yay.
Oh yeah yeah
It ended early today.
well
Yippidy yi yippity yay.
Oh yeah yeah
Good morning
No to?
It is quiet tonight.
Has something happened?
Oh is?
No so does.
go to
by
Rick is okay.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
If you have any trouble, tell me.
Oh yeah yeah
It’s early today, so I’m going.
Now I go.
Okay, okay, I am going to go.
Go to Mr.
Go to.
I call my friend and I go.
If you stay here, I cannot hold your feelings back.
Sorry to.
Oh Mr Hart.
Training is far away.
Nearby friend’s house.
I had to get to stay.
Oh yeah yeah
No, absolutely absolutely
Thanks for doing well.
Oh yeah yeah
Please be kind again.
Sorry to.
well
Sorry to
I know
Who is like.
Sorry to
is okay.
You are poor.
About me.
The bad guy.
You are poor.
It is not so, you.
is lying.
Really is
When I was Rick.
They grew up so.
Did you know?
I saw it.
Sorry, this is
Okay is.
Go to
by Naomi
I have a request.
that
Can you hold me?
Being hugged?
to someone.
Can you show me?
What do you mean?
So is
With someone other than me.
They are having sex.
Can you show me?
You say something unusual, I know.
But
That is why I am excited.
With Rick
You love me.
So please please.
Please please.
Yes
Mr. Hart is worried too.
and also
I also want Rick.
I want to meet.
Yes to.
thanks to.
Then then.
I will hinder you.
Leech is up.
I leave when I am not there.
Sorry to.
Sorry Mr Hart.
Oh go in.
Where did you go?
It is hindering.
You drank a lot.
You are drinking too much, right?
Yes is.
Is it okay?
Yes to.
Okay okay okay okay.
I will clean it up.
Thanks, I want to.
I am thankful.
Yes to.
Thanks to you, Mr Rick.
It is totally good.
Mr. Harper is too drunk.
Nami, what happened to you?
I can’t forget the warmth of Rick.
So Mr. Hart is there.
He is drunk and okay.
said that.
It is bad.
How can I do.
Let’s stop it.
Let us stop.
Is it okay?
Concentrate to.
Because it is okay.
Feels good?
It feels good.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
No to
Oh yeah
Not with you.
That is bad.
I am sleeping, okay.
No to no.
Put it in.
by
Jake, my body is
Jake is okay.
Yippidy yi yippity yay.
Oh yeah
I am late home today.
Please drink.
by
Oh yes yes
Come to go.
Then
Chouchou
Touch me too.