Itadakimasu!
Yum!
Is it good?
It's really good!
Really?
The saltiness is perfect!
What's this?
What's in it?
This?
It's a secret.
I added a secret ingredient.
It's love, right?
Yes, love.
Eat this too.
Let me eat it.
Do you want to eat it?
Can't you eat it by yourself?
I can't.
It can't be helped.
How is it?
It's melting.
Are you sure it's okay?
It's okay.
Do you want to eat this too?
I'll eat it.
I aged it for a long time.
It's good, right?
It's good.
I'll eat it all.
Did it have a strong taste?
Not at all.
It's good.
That's good.
You haven't eaten recently, have you?
Is that so?
Are you sick?
No, I'm not.
Masae.
I'm lonely because my husband is on a business trip.
Please understand me.
I see.
I'm sorry.
No, it's not like that.
The rice is delicious.
It's really good.
It's good, isn't it?
It's good.
Masae.
Futo.
How long are you going to stay at my house?
I'm sorry.
Please stay a little longer.
It's been about a year since I said that.
Don't say that.
We're sisters.
That's right.
But...
Did my brother say something to you?
No.
He said I could stay here until he calmed down.
That's good.
Please stay a little longer.
Futo.
We'll find a room soon.
Okay?
That's right.
Shinjuku is good.
It's good.
Let's stay in front of the station.
It's good to stay in front of the station.
It's convenient.
That's good.
Let's do that.
How about a bath?
That's good.
It's good to have a bath.
I agree.
Let's take a bath every day.
I'm going to take a bath.
What's wrong?
I haven't taken a bath since I came back from work.
I want to take a bath.
Why?
You said you wanted to eat rice, so I made it for you.
I just came back from work.
I'm hungry.
Then, you should have made it for me.
I want to eat your cooking.
You always say that.
You're a child.
Masai.
You should say that to me.
I'll make it.
Thank you.
I'm going to take a bath.
I'm going to eat rice.
Can you leave it here?
I'll leave it on the table.
Thank you.
I'm going to take a bath.
See you.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
I don't know what to do when you're gone.
What's wrong?
Can you take a bath for me?
What?
I'm so excited today.
Can you do that to me?
What's wrong?
Are you angry?
Yuri.
Why are you angry?
Because I did it with my sister yesterday?
That's not what I mean.
Don't call me by my name.
I'm sorry.
I'll listen to you.
I'm counting on you.
You're the worst man.
But my sister seems to like me.
Why do you depend on Yuri?
That's the problem.
You're the worst.
You're in the middle of your husband's business trip, aren't you?
Here.
It's just right.
So.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
Look.
I was looking at the reaction.
Wait a minute.
It's okay, right?
Here.
What?
You don't like it?
Here you are.
I don't like it.
It's okay.
It feels good.
You feel good.
I'm sorry to show you my vulgar appearance.
I lived with my husband in this house.
My sister got married there.
But she didn't have a place to live.
So I moved to this house.
My husband was on a business trip.
So I agreed to live with him.
But the problem was my sister's husband.
Sit down.
What?
You can tell me now.
Here you are.
Masaya is here.
You don't have to tell me.
I can't.
You are wet.
You can hear me.
Masaya.
This man is my ex-husband.
Of course, my husband and my sister don't know that.
I was young.
My parents died early.
I met him when I was playing.
Of course, I'm calm now.
I'm living a normal life.
But this man who knew me in the past.
He wanted me for a reason.
I don't want to deny it.
But I don't want my husband and my sister to know my past.
So I listened to him.
You can hear me.
What?
You want something from me?
No.
Hey.
I don't have a hair tie.
Where is my hair tie?
I'm sorry.
Give it to me.
I left it outside.
Wait a minute.
I'll bring it right away.
I'm sorry.
You always say that.
Thank you.
What?
It's a hair tie.
I'm sorry.
I'll bring it right away.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Where is your work tonight?
Well, today's evening.
Come here and wear your shirt.
Sooner or later.
You have a bad relationship with me.
Do you have a bad relationship with my sexuality?
No.
But, wait a minute.
What is it?
You were peeping yesterday.
No, I wasn't.
I see.
Hey!
What is it?
Hey, stop it.
You are soaking wet.
No, I'm not.
You are always peeping.
What are you talking about?
I wasn't.
What?
You are soaking wet.
No, I'm not.
I'm going to pee.
You are soaking wet.
No, I'm not.
Look here.
You are soaking wet.
You are always peeping.
No, I'm not.
Look here.
Look.
You were peeping.
No, I'm not.
I'm going to pee.
Masaya, it feels good.
Do it more.
More?
Oh, no.
It feels good.
My stomach is growling.
I'm going to pee.
At the same time she took pleasure in her uncle's pain.
Ah, I see.
Hey, what should I do?
I can't stand it.
You can't stand it?
No.
You can't stand it.
I can't stand it.
You are sweating a lot.
Because it feels good.
Ah, it feels good.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Ah, it feels good.
I can't stand it.
It feels good.
You like it here, don't you?
I can't stand it.
I know.
Let's sleep.
I can't stand it.
I like it.
I like it, too.
I can't stand it.
Ah, it feels good.
It feels good.
I can't stand it.
I like it.
It feels good.
I can't stand it.
It's very tight.
What?
Don't you want to sleep?
This.
I want to sleep.
Really?
Let me ask you.
Did you say something?
You did.
You are smiling a lot.
No I'm not.
Really?
Wait a minute.
What if I hold you like this?
You want to look like that old man?
Hold that way!
No...
I know you're kickin' ass.
Nuh-uh...
Didn't we just break up?
Stop it!
Yuri, you've always liked to cry out loud, haven't you?
Don't talk about the past.
It's different now.
It's different now, isn't it?
What?
No, it's different now.
You don't have to be so hard on me.
It's different now, isn't it?
Hey, don't be so hard on me.
Stop it.
You can't do that.
Don't do that.
I'm not pretending.
You can't do that. Stop it.
Okay, okay. I'll do it outside.
Don't do that.
I said, don't do that.
Okay.
I'm going to work now.
Sister.
Yeah.
I'm going to work now.
It's okay.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's nothing.
Yeah.
Come back soon.
Okay.
I'll wait for you.
Hey.
What's up?
Brother.
Yeah.
What?
You're going on a long business trip?
I think so.
It's hard.
I'm going on a business trip as soon as I get back.
Masaya is busy these days.
You're doing your best at work.
That's right.
But I'm not satisfied.
What are you talking about?
Maybe he's doing well over there.
That's not true.
Hey.
What?
Masaya is not on leave today.
Let's have fun.
What do you mean?
Do you want to have sex?
No.
Why?
Let me go.
Let's have fun today.
No.
Stop it.
What?
Let's have fun.
No.
Don't touch me.
Don't you want to have sex?
I don't want to.
Okay.
Let's have fun.
What?
Like we used to do.
What are you talking about?
What?
You're not on leave today.
I'm not on leave today.
What?
I don't want to have sex.
So...
It's okay.
I'm not on leave today.
I'll be satisfied if I have sex.
You're not on leave today.
That's right.
I don't understand.
If I have sex, will I go home?
Yes, you will.
Okay?
Okay.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Hurry up.
Okay.
I want to have sex.
What are you talking about?
Okay.
It feels good.
You're so eager to have sex.
Shut up.
Okay.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
What are you doing?
Look at me.
Oh, no.
I get more excited when I look at your face.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
I want to lick you.
Hey.
Can I lick you?
What?
It's okay.
Hurry up.
Don't say that.
Don't move.
You're my sister.
Please lie down.
Oh, no.
Look at me.
Relax.
Okay.
I'm going to lick you.
It's okay. I'm going to lick you, too.
It's okay.
Look at me.
It's not good for you to be one-sided.
So, don't be shy.
Look at me.
You're not satisfied, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Look at me.
Oh, no.
What?
You're pulling a string.
I'm not.
You're not?
What?
Don't do that.
She wants to be licked, too.
Wow.
It's sour.
No, no, no.
You're really weak.
Look at me.
Okay.
It's sour.
You're really weak to be licked, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
It's okay, isn't it?
Look at me.
No, no.
No, no, no.
Look at me.
I'm not.
You're not?
No, I'm not.
Then, you can continue.
Hey.
Can I put this in your mouth?
No, you can't.
I'll put this in your mouth.
I'm begging you.
No, I can't.
Can I put this in your mouth?
No, you can't.
I'll put this in your mouth.
It's the same as a vial.
Is that so?
No, no, no.
What are you talking about?
I'm begging you.
You're my sister.
I want to do it, too.
He's been busy lately.
I'm lonely, too.
I know how you feel.
I'm not cheating on you.
We'd like to help each other.
I don't cheat on you.
Do you cheat on me, too?
No, I don't.
So, you should consider this a favor.
Look at me.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'll put a bomb on you.
You already did.
It doesn't matter.
Look at me.
I'll put a bomb on you.
You can think of me as a vibrator.
What are you talking about?
Look at me.
Think of me as a vibrating vibrator.
We have a lot of time.
Let's solve the problem.
But I'm not good at baseball.
Don't be silly.
People who say that don't feel like that.
Look at me.
What?
Are you done?
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Why?
It's getting harder.
What should I do?
It doesn't matter.
Do you want me to do more?
No.
Are you sure?
What are you going to do?
I won't do it.
Do you want me to do more?
No.
Look at me.
What?
You're just moving slowly.
You're moving slowly.
Why?
You're not good at this.
You're just pushing me.
I'm not pushing you.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's dangerous.
You're not moving.
You're just pushing me.
I'm not pushing you.
It's hot.
It's dangerous.
You said it yourself.
It's painful.
Why are you moving slowly?
I'm not moving.
You're not moving?
Do you want me to do more?
No.
I'm just pushing you.
Do you want me to do more?
No.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Did you really want me to do more?
I can't do this.
Why can't you do this?
Tell me honestly.
I can't do this.
What's this?
You can't do this?
No.
No?
Why are you so scared?
I don't know.
Why can't you do this?
I can't do this.
What's wrong?
Don't you want to go?
You want to go, right?
Look.
I can't do this.
You're shaking a lot.
You can lie down on the bed.
You always do push-ups.
I can't do this.
Why?
I'll move slowly.
I can't do this.
Taste it.
You can't do this.
I can't do this.
You can do this.
You like to do push-ups.
No.
I can't do this.
I'll tickle your ears.
Your ears.
Why are you running away?
My ears.
I'll tickle your ears.
Your ears are dirty.
What is this?
I can't do this.
Do you want to go further?
No.
I can't do this.
Wait.
You can't do this.
I can't do this.
Wait.
I'll tickle your ears.
No.
I can't do this.
What is this?
You are amazing.
Is this your favorite sound?
I can't do this.
I'm tickling your ears.
I'll tickle your ears.
I can't do this.
What is this?
Why are you saying that?
I can't do this.
What is this?
Don't say that.
I can't do this.
Why?
Is it because it's too hot?
No.
I can't do this.
Can you do this?
You can't do this.
I can't do this.
You can move, right?
It's hot.
Take a break.
I can't do this.
Why don't you do what you feel?
You're running away.
I'm not running away.
Why don't you do what you feel?
I can't do this.
Go deeper.
Don't move.
I can't do this.
Really?
Then I'll do what I feel.
I'll do what I feel.
I can't do this.
That's good.
Keep going.
I can't do this.
I want you to move.
Look at what's in there.
I can't do this.
Look at what you feel.
I won't stop you.
Put your hand there.
I can't do this.
Rubber takes time.
Stop it.
You are erotic.
I don't know.
Rubber takes time.
I was addicted to his pace.
It was true that I was not greedy.
I was using him conveniently.
I was making use of him.
I made use of him.
He even told me that if I clothed myself with rubber, I wouldn't cheat.
Wait.
I beg you.
No!
Searching for Kurokawa
Yes, Sasahara's speaking.
What about Sachiko?
How is she?
Is she okay?
Yes, she's fine.
Your husband is on a business trip, isn't he?
Yes.
He went on a business trip the other day.
I see.
Yes.
What about it?
Well...
What is it?
I saw your husband and his sister walking together the other day.
When?
The other Sunday.
Sunday?
You know, there is a department store in the neighborhood.
I think he went shopping there.
Don't tell me...
My husband and...
His...
His sister?
It can't be...
Really?
I see.
I think it's great.
Yes.
I think so, too.
I think he likes it.
Yes, I think so, too.
Yes.
I think it's great.
I think it's more fun to be with my brother.
Yes.
I think it's great.
It's more fun to be with my brother.
You know that, don't you?
Well, I'll call you later.
It's early.
Yes, I think so.
Are you his friend?
Yes, I'm his friend.
Can I talk to him on the phone?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm going to take a shower.
It's hot.
Hey.
Aren't you a little violent today?
No, I'm not.
No.
What are you doing?
It's okay to say that.
Let's get it over with.
I don't feel good.
I'm going to bed.
You know what?
what?
is there something wrong?
Nothing.
nothing.
What?
Really?
Okay, I'm going to put it on now.
I put it on.
What?
This way.
Wait a minute.
Am I going to move?
What?
You can't put it on, can you?
Here you are.
You can use it as you like.
It feels good.
Look, your back is moving a lot.
I'm sorry.
I can't tell you about other people, but my husband has a younger sister.
I want to ask you, but I can't.
What if it's true?
I was so angry that I forgave him.
What?
Wait a minute.
For some reason, when I had sex with him, I felt like I was out of my mind.
What?
You can't go home?
Why?
Nagabiku?
You didn't say that the other day.
Why?
Come to think of it...
Yes.
No.
It's nothing.
I said it's nothing.
Yuri.
What's wrong?
Your brother?
Yes.
He can't come back until tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Yes.
Tomorrow is Yuri's birthday.
Do you remember?
Of course I remember.
What's this?
It's not expensive at all.
It's not a big deal.
But it's a birthday present.
For me?
Yes.
It's really not a big deal.
I'll give it to you later.
Okay?
Okay.
I'm glad.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Where's my sister today?
She's late for overtime again.
What?
Do you want to do it now?
Okay.
Don't you want to do it?
No way.
Oh.
We could have done it.
My husband and my sister.
Of course.
We've been doing it for a long time.
But I don't know why.
I don't want to lose to my husband and my sister.
What's wrong?
You're so serious today.
I want to do it now.
Do you like me?
No.
I like this bed.
I like your body.
Where's my body?
Your pussy.
Touch me.
I'm embarrassed.
Hurry up.
Are you embarrassed?
Sorry.
Don't touch me.
I gave it to you.
I know I'm weak when I'm tired.
I'm sorry.
You're getting bigger.
I'm enjoying it.
You're squeezing it in there.
You like this, don't you?
Yes.
My hips are shaking.
It's hot.
I'm scared.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'll make you feel better.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
You like to be petted, don't you?
Yes.
It's hot.
Let me do it.
I'll do it.
No.
Is it hot?
It's hot.
I'm going to cry.
I'm so excited today.
It's amazing.
Come on.
It's hot.
Can I do it, too?
Yes.
I love you.
It's hot.
No.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
You're the best.
You're tickling yourself.
You're mean.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
Come on.
You're tickling yourself.
You're mean.
Let me do it.
Come on.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
You're tickling yourself.
You're mean.
Let me do it.
Do you want to do it?
It's amazing.
Yes.
Let me do it.
What are you doing?
Do you want to do it?
Yes.
What?
I haven't erased it yet.
It's raw.
Can I do it?
I'll put it in your bowl.
I don't have to erase it.
Can I do it?
What?
Don't you have to do it?
I put it in your bowl.
Can I put it in your bowl?
Wait.
Oh, my God.
Ah, ah, ah, ah
Say, ah, ah, ah.
Nama is yourself.
I'm already in trouble!
Say, ah
The only one in trouble is you, Nama.
Na, na, natomiast.
Yeah
Ah
Oh, it's so hot.
Wait, wait.
I'm so thirsty.
I'm so wet inside.
I'm too old, aren't I?
Wait a minute.
It's not good.
I'm putting it in my sister's body.
Wait, wait.
It's really not good.
Wait.
It's not good.
Wait, I'm...
Wait.
Your grandpa is trembling.
You're going to be wet soon.
Wait a minute.
It's not good.
Wait.
It's really not good.
You're trembling.
Wait, wait.
You feel good, don't you?
It's not good.
Come on, come on.
What?
It's not good, isn't it?
It's not good.
It's coming out.
Come on, come on.
Oh, my God.
It's messed up.
Did you take it out?
I'll clean it up for you.
Oh, my stomach hurts.
Oh, there's a lot.
You're drooling.
Because...
You're drooling when you're naked.
Let's touch it.
Come on, come on, come on.
Oh, my God.
What?
No, that's...
You're suddenly attacked and you're naked.
That's what happens.
It's not all of a sudden, it's always like that.
It's always Zako and Chinchin.
When you're naked.
You're Zako, too.
Come on.
Then don't do it in the basement.
Why?
Come on.
Can I put in a manko again?
What do you want me to do?
I'll do it for you.
No.
Next.
Then it's my turn.
Wait a minute.
Next time, I'll do it at my own pace.
You're going to do it again, aren't you?
Wait a minute.
I'll do a lot of things you like.
It's not intense.
It's intense from the beginning.
Why?
You like it intense, don't you?
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
I just switched on.
I can't do it.
Oh, my God.
What's wrong with you?
I can't do it anymore.
I want to rest.
Do you want to rest?
Do you want to rest here?
I want to rest.
I'm weak.
It hurts.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I sometimes try to exterminate you.
Sorry.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I want you to do your best.
I can't. I can't move.
I'll move. I'll move for you.
I want you to move.
I'll push you down.
No, no.
I won't move.
I don't want to move.
Look, Haruka.
I'm not moving.
I'm just pushing you down.
You're hitting your uvula, though.
Hey.
Don't touch me anymore.
Why?
Don't move.
I can't play with you.
I don't want to play with you.
Don't move.
I want to move.
Which one do you like?
I like this one.
Be honest.
I'm happy.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
I like this one.
I'm happy.
You're sweating.
It hurts.
Don't move.
Let's take a break.
I'm tired.
Do you have a sore spot?
No.
I have a sore spot.
Where?
No.
I can't get out.
Come here.
Who is it?
You have a sore spot.
I have a sore spot.
You can do it.
Wait.
I'm tired.
I love you.
You have a sore spot.
Why are you looking down?
I want to rest.
You can't get out.
Why do you say that?
So
I'm
going
to
I feel sick.
You are crying.
You have a very erotic face.
I feel sick.
It hurts.
What are you saying?
It hurts inside.
This is bad!
It hurts!
Really?
I didn't know
It hurts!
Move
It really feels good
You are doing something really gross
It feels good
I want to do it too
No
Why?
Can't I do it too?
No
You can do it!
Wow
You are doing something really gross
It feels good
Wow
Don't stop
It hurts!
It feels really good
It feels good
I'll do it from tomorrow
No
I want to do it slowly
It hurts!
I can't do it anymore
It feels good
Put your butt on the floor
More
Wow
No, don't stop
It hurts!
Please
That's you, right?
Um..
It's probably fine, right?
Hey, wait.
What about my octopus wahoo?
You've been quiet a few times, haven't you?
I think I've been quiet enough.
But you did it.
No, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
Yes, yes, yes.
See?
You've been standing for a long time, haven't you?
I won't let you go.
Ah!
There, there.
You can't go there.
I know.
I'm sorry.
You can't.
I'm going.
Let's go this way.
I feel so bad.
I'm sorry.
Tickling!
It tickles and I hate it!
I hate it.
I'll...
toss you again
I'm scared
Hey, wake up Okay.
Okay, go, go, go....
Thank you very much.
I'm not going to do it.
Why?
I want to go home.
It feels good.
What do you think if I do it hard?
I want to go home.
I'll make it slow.
It feels good.
I want to go home.
It's slow.
What do you think if I do it fast?
It hurts.
You can't do it.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
You can't do it.
You're persistent.
It's broken.
Wait a minute.
Please stop.
You can't...
I can't...
You can't?
Are you in trouble if I go in now?
I can't, I can't...
Please...
PLEASE!!
AHHHHHHHH!!
I can't...
AI!
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no.
Why?
Baby is coming.
No, no, no, no.
Are you okay?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll get you out.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
No, I can't.
My head...
I can't get the face to cover it up.
I'm sorry.
I think you're a little excited because you're a big sister.
No, I'm not.
Really?
Yes.
But...
I don't think it's good to have a baby.
I've had a lot of babies.
I've had a lot of babies, so I'm sure it's a boy.
Do you think it's over?
Are you still sick?
It's not over yet, is it?
Let's take a shower and take a break.
No.
Turn your butt this way.
I'm saying this because I'm relaxed.
You've said it a few times, haven't you?
Absolutely.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you so scared?
You want to have a baby, don't you?
No.
You really want to have a baby, don't you?
Let me go.
It's okay.
Because...
I chose it with my brother.
Yes.
But...
I can't give it to my brother directly.
I'll give it to him.
It's okay.
Yes.
Leave it to me.
Me?
It's okay.
I love you.
But...
When you come back,
you have to take care of me.
You can't do that.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Good luck with your work.
Excuse me.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I said I'd be late.
But it's okay.
What should I eat for dinner tonight?
I'll buy you a birthday present.
Will you be happy?
Let me go.
I can't.