The next day
Are you feeling good?
Yuma-chan
It's no good
Oh, right
You're going to the dance party, right?
Yeah
Take your time
No, I want to go home early
Because, Yuma-chan
You don't really go out to drink, do you?
Well, yeah
Somehow
It's a hassle to go out
Well
If you stay at home
It will melt
What?
Are you making fun of me?
No, it's not that
It's not that, but look
As a man
I want to show you what I can do
What?
Why?
No, because
In the world
It seems that couples who say that they shouldn't go to the dance party
Is that so?
Why?
No
Well
You know
People who used to date
They come
Right?
What?
Is that what happens when you go to the dance party?
No, no
It's not that
Sachiko-chan and the others
They think it's good
Why do you come up with Sachiko's name?
No, no
Look
Well
My best friend
You're familiar with her, aren't you?
What?
You like Sachiko?
No way
That's not the case
Because
I
know
I love you
Don't you?
Well
You're right
Come on
Take it easy
Say something nice
What's that?
Well
You can be late
Take it slowly
Well, as long as you're in the mood.
Well, let's go to bed.
What's wrong?
Well, don't you want to do it again?
Well, I've been getting along with you a lot lately.
No, it's not like that.
Is that so?
Well, when I go on a business trip, I get tired.
Well, you have a lot of business trips, so you should do your best when you go on a business trip.
I'm trying my best.
Well, I can't do it anymore.
Well, let's try again when you're in a good mood.
I met my husband at the company I was working for, and we got married because of our love in the company.
He was a very nice person from the beginning, and he always listened to my wishes.
Even now, three years later, we get along very well, and we spend very happy days together.
And recently, for the first time in decades, I was invited to a reunion when I was a student, and I'm going there tomorrow.
I was able to marry a really nice person, so I didn't have any worries about cheating, as my husband thought.
Until I reunited with him...
Hey, Saki.
Oh, Hayashi.
Well, he's gone.
Yeah, I was thinking of going home today.
You still have time, so go out with me just once.
Well, but...
Just once, okay?
I was thinking of going home today.
Well, just once, okay?
Come on, let's go.
Well, just once.
Okay, let's go.
Hey, hurry up.
No, I can walk by myself.
Oh, I see.
This way.
The next day
I was really surprised that Suzuki was riding on such a rough road.
Yeah, I was surprised.
Suzuki was much thinner.
You used to get along well with him, right?
Yeah.
Oh, did you keep in touch with him?
No, I haven't been in touch with him recently.
Oh, I see.
That was amazing.
Yeah.
On the other hand, Yabana was so fat that I was surprised.
I didn't know who he was.
Well, it's been a while since we last met, and everyone has changed a little.
Yeah.
It's hard to stay the same as before.
That's true.
Are you drinking?
Yeah.
Drink more.
It's been a long time.
Yeah.
You don't usually drink, do you?
Yeah, I don't drink much.
I don't drink that much.
It's been a long time since I've had a chance to drink.
It's a waste to go home with just one glass.
I'm pretty drunk with just one glass.
Really?
This is easy to drink, but isn't it strong?
Did you notice?
But it's delicious.
Yeah, it's easy to drink.
I drink this a lot.
It looks really delicious.
Was it that weak?
Yeah.
I see.
It's fine.
On this day, my best friend's child suddenly got a fever and came home early, so I tried to go home early, too.
However, my ex-boyfriend called me after a long time, and because of the restlessness, I finally got on the invitation.
I got on his pace and drank too much.
Excuse me.
SACHIKO'S MOTHER
I can't think of anything.
I thought he wasn't the type to get married.
Really?
He used to play a lot.
Isn't Hayashi the one who played the most?
Me?
Really?
I don't think so.
You used to play a lot.
No, I didn't.
I did have a lot of relationships with him.
But he dumped me right away.
If you had married a girl, you would have been dumped right away.
Well, that's true.
But I had a lot of relationships with him.
Really?
Of course.
But you know him the best.
Really?
I don't think I've ever had a relationship with him.
You don't remember a lot of things?
Well, I remember a lot of things.
Right?
I remember a lot of things too.
Well, Hayashi hasn't changed much.
Really?
People say he's calmed down since he got married.
He looks different though.
What's inside?
I'm more surprised that Hayashi got married before Sachiko.
Really?
Well, I've been with her for a long time.
So I'm not sure.
You're not sure?
You don't seem to have changed much.
I see.
What is it?
Well, Taki has become more attractive since he got married.
What's that?
It's been a while since we met.
What?
Are you drunk?
I'll go home if you're drunk.
Wait a minute.
It's been a while since we met.
Well, you're right.
What's wrong with you?
We're a bit close.
Let's go back.
We were this close before.
That's when we were dating.
We were so close.
It's been a while since we met.
Taki told me to look this way.
I did.
We were so close.
It's been a while since we met.
I thought Taki was still beautiful.
I'm happy about that.
What's wrong with you?
We were so close.
I'm drunk.
Let's kiss here.
What are you talking about?
It's impossible.
We were so close.
I'm married.
I know.
But isn't it different to kiss when you're married?
If you do that, you'll never stop.
I won't stop.
I'll be fine.
I can't.
I'll go home.
It's okay.
Are you serious?
Wait a minute.
It's impossible.
It's okay.
There's no one here.
We're the only ones here.
Are you serious?
We can only kiss once.
Then we can go away.
Okay.
Are you serious?
Yes.
Look at me.
I miss you.
You're cute.
Yes, he's cute.
It could be because I drank for the first time in a while.
It might be because I'm soft-hearted.
I knew this would happen, so I didn't approach him.
What if someone comes?
It's okay. This is a private room.
But...
It's okay.
It's no good.
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
I can hear you.
Look this way.
It's okay.
It's okay to touch his head, but he's in a sleepwalk.
It's very wet here.
If you say so, I will go home.
I want to touch the back of your head.
Wait a minute.
It's very wet here.
It's embarrassing.
Don't do it.
Don't make a sound.
It's embarrassing.
Don't do it.
It's very wet here.
I want to touch your back.
What are you talking about?
Don't do it.
I don't know.
It's been a long time.
That's right.
It's bigger than before.
I don't know.
I want to lick this.
What are you talking about?
It's okay.
I don't know.
Don't lick it.
Don't do it.
I can't get used to it.
I really liked your licking.
I don't know.
Don't do it.
I told you not to do it.
If I kiss you, the switch will turn on.
Don't do it.
I'm telling you the truth.
You need to defense.
Let's practice again
That's okay.
Just lick it.
What?
It's okay.
Okay.
Just lick it.
What?
It's okay.
It's really wet.
Hey, Taki.
Don't you want to put it in?
No.
What are you saying?
It's okay.
No.
I won't put it in.
It's okay.
It's not good.
Come on.
Let me see.
I can't.
I can't put it in.
Come on.
Wow.
Your hips are great.
Wait a minute.
It's the best.
It's not good.
It's really not good.
Are you okay?
It's not good.
What are you doing?
Hey.
Don't make that sound.
What are you going to do if you get caught?
It's not good.
Please calm down.
No.
Seriously, Taki.
What are you going to do?
Huh?
Are you going home?
Yeah.
Are you sure you can go home?
Yeah, But can you go home...?
Aren't you going to stay a little longer?
Where?
You can't chase me like this.
I can.
It hurts a little more.
I'm going home.
Do you really think so?
Look at me.
It hurts a little more.
What?
Do you still want to do it?
I can't stop it.
I really didn't want this to happen.
I felt a lot of guilt against my husband.
But when I realized that my husband was in a place where I couldn't reach, I opened my eyes.
I was embarrassed, but I felt a lot of guilt.
I can't stop it.
Nata?
Yes?
I see.
What did you say?
I didn't really contact you.
I'm fine.
You're trusted.
Well,
I'm a good husband.
By the way,
why were you wearing clothes the other day?
I thought I had to wear clothes.
I see.
You still feel this place, don't you?
No, I don't.
It's not easier to feel than before.
Maybe it's just a misunderstanding.
No, it's not.
Didn't you do it with your husband?
No, I didn't.
You're right.
If you don't want to go home, let's do it again.
What?
I was drunk earlier.
If you're not drunk, let's do it again.
No way.
It's okay.
Don't you want to hug me?
Just for today.
Just for today?
Let's hug each other.
Just for today.
Without being followed.
Well,
just for today.
You like it, don't you?
It's embarrassing.
You like being embarrassed, don't you?
No, stop it.
You like it, don't you?
I like it.
I like the way you look.
No.
Be careful.
Oh, no.
Which one do you like more?
I like both.
Which one?
No.
I like it.
You have to hit harder.
Your face is so wet.
Your face is so dirty.
I like it.
No.
Wait.
I like it.
I want to put it in.
Can I put it in like this?
It's okay.
I'm scared.
I used it earlier.
Put it outside.
I got it.
I want you to put it outside.
It's okay.
I like it from the back.
I'm just rubbing it.
Put it in.
I'm scared.
What is it?
Amazing.
Here.
It's a little bit.
It's not moving at all.
It's so painful.
You really like me.
I really like you.
Here.
It's painful.
No.
You really like me.
It's painful.
No.
It's ok.
I can't watch.
OMG!
Hot, hot!
You like it hot, do you?
Ah, that's...
Ah!
Oh, no!
I'm sorry!
It hurts!
Oh, no!
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
I was surprised!
Ah!
It feels good.
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
It hurts!
Will you go out?
I'm sorry!
Ah, you're crying a lot.
Ah!
It hurts!
Ah, it hurts!
Oh, no!
Ah!
I am sorry.
Almost hit one...
Sorry....
Noooooooooooo
Don't put me down.
We had chance to move back to corelly but I resisted to hit with a bat...
I an't move to ducks So sorry.
I m not good at it.
I'm going too far.
It feels good.
Amazing.
You're getting better.
What do you want to do next?
Behind.
Behind?
Do you want to see me from behind?
Yes.
You're getting better.
Come here.
What did you do?
Don't do that.
You're moving.
You're moving too much.
I can't do it.
It hurts.
You still want to have sex, right?
I want to have sex.
I want to hug you.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I want to have sex.
It hurts.
Let's go for a walk.
I can't do it.
It hurts.
HA UGH
landed
huh
no no no
it hurts
my heart throbbing
I'm scared.
I'll move to another place.
Dancing
It was a lot.
Sorry I beat you
Did you feel any pain there
Your shoulder
It hurts!
I can't breathe!
No!
How bad this is!
It's dangerous!
I can't breathe...
It hurts!
One more time, one more time, one more time
Ah, it feels good
Ah, it hurts
It hurts
Ah, it feels good
Ah, this is bad
Ah, I'm about to cry
Ah, it hurts
Something is coming out
Ah, I'm sorry
Ah, I'm about to cry
I'm sorry
Ah, it hurts
Did it feel good?
It felt really good
Really?
Mom, let's go back
Okay
What should I do?
I like the back
Okay
Ah, it hurts
My body is in good condition
Even after a few years
Everything I felt
I felt it all
I don't know how many years
I've been screaming like this
It hurts
Ah, it's the best
Ah, I'm
I'm feeling
It's strange
It's hard
It feels good
Taki
From now on
Let's meet sometimes
No
It's okay
My body is in good condition
Taki, from now on
Let's meet sometimes
No
It hurts
Let's go inside
It's okay
Nevertheless
I felt guilty
But
His place
No matter what
It hit the place where the master couldn't reach
I realized
We were shaking our backs again
Let's wash
Ayashi-kun is standing
He stood up
I want to wash
Ayashi-kun
He stood up
I can't stand
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
If I continue to have a relationship with him regularly,
if I do something like that,
I'm sure I'll fall in love with him.
If I don't refuse,
even though I know it in my head,
I couldn't speak a word.
However, my body is in search of him.
Until this morning,
I had sex with him
so that my memories with him became vague.
It's impossible for a main character to do such a thing.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for making you cry.
I want to go home before my husband wakes up.
I see.
Hey, Taki.
Come here.
What?
I'm sorry.
Hey, Taki.
Let's meet again.
But I don't want to have an affair.
It's not an affair.
Let's meet and have sex.
What do you mean?
It's not an affair.
It's like a sport.
No way.
Taki,
didn't you feel good about having sex with me?
I felt good.
Then it's okay.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I thought it was a trap
to have sex with him.
I accidentally thought so.
I was so happy that
I could have sex with him
and that he wanted me
so much more than anything else.
I'm sorry.
It feels so good.
I love my husband.
He seems to be very satisfied with me,
but since that day,
I've been comparing myself to him
and I can't feel anything at all.
Today, while remembering my sex with him,
I feel sorry for my husband,
but I still love him.
I'm sorry.
That's it.
Don't worry.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I've been seeing him a lot since then.
I've been having sex for a few hours.
I'm really excited and excited.
I love you.
You're still standing even though you've been there so many times.
I'm cold.
I was really scared the other day.
Were you okay that day?
Did you get caught by your fiancee?
I was fine, but I was scared if I used a bamboo stick for five minutes.
I'm scared, so I'll stop.
That's good.
You were excited, weren't you?
That's right, but I'm going to stop.
I see.
I'm going to stop seeing you.
Why?
The hotel is expensive, so I can't come often.
That's right.
I'll see you sometimes.
Let me see you again before you go back to work.
Come here.
What's wrong with you?
You're really wet.
What's wrong?
I don't want to see you.
I agree, but think about it.
Yuna, I'm sorry.
What do you mean?
Please concentrate from tomorrow.
Don't worry about it.
I know what I can say.
Thank you.
But I haven't invited you recently.
What?
You're satisfied with me, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
I'm glad to hear that.
I agree.
Did you go to see everyone?
Yes, I did.
Yes.
It's time to sleep.
Really?
Good night.
I love my husband.
But I really want to have sex with him.
I used to be very depressed when my husband's business trip came,
but I didn't expect my husband's business trip to be so long.
I didn't expect my husband's business trip to be so long.
Yes, that's right.
Please take care of Sachiko.
Sachiko said she wanted to go to lunch with me.
Let's go together next time.
I'll thank you.
See you tomorrow.
What did you say to Sachiko?
What?
I made an alibi.
You made an alibi?
Is it okay for me to have sex with you?
It's okay.
I've known my husband since yesterday.
Really?
Yes.
Then you can do it.
That's right.
If you have such a good point, say it quickly.
My husband is not here until the day after tomorrow.
Really?
Yes.
Then you can do it.
Don't you want to do it?
Can you say you don't want to do it?
I can't.
Taki and Sachiko are amazing.
That's right.
Everyone is relaxed because of that video.
Sachiko has been training Kawasaki for such a short time.
I was really surprised.
Did Hayashi aim for Sachiko?
No.
I was aiming for Taki from the beginning.
Really?
Yes.
I'm serious.
Are you happy?
I'm happy, too.
I wanted to be like this with Taki.
I wanted to be like Hayashi.
Me too.
Taki is eating.
Taki wanted to be like this with Taki, right?
Really?
Yes.
Do you usually do this with your husband?
It's a secret.
No.
You are very relaxed.
Already.
Taki.
You are already shaking here.
No.
It's embarrassing.
Taki is really great.
It's Hayashi's fault.
Touch more.
You are sweating too much.
It's embarrassing.
It feels good there.
Taki.
Oh, no.
Hold on.
It's okay.
Is it okay?
Taki.
Taki is very relaxed today.
Really?
Do you always do this?
Maybe only today.
Taki.
Touch more.
It's amazing.
It's really good.
No, no.
No.
Your hips are moving.
They are moving.
It feels good.
It feels good there.
I want you to touch here.
It's stained.
It's not that bad.
Show me.
Why are you licking me?
What do you want me to do?
I want you to lick me.
It feels good.
It's really good.
Let's touch.
It feels good.
I feel like I'm going to fall asleep.
Ah...
I'm going to fall asleep.
I feel like I'm going to fall asleep.
I already said it, but.
I'm going to fall asleep.
I'm gonna fall asleep.
Tell me.
If it's Hayashi-kun, he'll get wet all over.
I just feel the pain of spots attached to the skin.
Piss off
I'm sorry
Calm down
You are such a pervert
Can I lick here?
No one can lick such a place
It's dangerous
I'm sorry
Please pat my butt
You like to fight
More
It's dangerous
I'm sorry
Please relax
Do you want me to hug you?
Wow
I'm sorry
Your room is very comfortable
Really?
My girlfriend is very comfortable
I'm sorry
It's very comfortable
I love you
I'm sorry
What do you want to do?
I want to put it in
Do you want to put it in?
I want you to put it in
Here?
I'll put it in
Don't tease me
Does this feel good?
It feels good
Look at the back
I like it
It feels good
I'm sorry
I love you
It's big
It feels good
I'm sorry
I love you
It feels good
I'm sorry
I love you
Look
It's so good
It feels good
So it's like this
Do you want me to put it in the bath?
I want you to put it in the water
I'm going to put it in
Oh, no
I'm going to hit something
You can move as you like
I'm going to move
Oh, my God
It feels good
I'm sorry
Oh, no
It feels good
I'm running fast
I'm sorry
It hurts
I'm going
I'm sorry
It feels good
It hurts
Oh, no
It feels good
It hurts
Oh, no
It feels good
It hurts
I'm sweating
It feels good
Oh, no
It hurts
It feels good
What's next?
Behind
You want me to do it from behind?
Yes
I did it
Don't spread your hips
It's hard
What's this?
With both hands
That's right
I want you to do it
You want me to do it?
Yes
What should I do?
Spread your hips
Please
It feels good
It hurts
No way
I don't think I'm having sex
No
I can't sleep
It hurts
It feels good
I want to do it more
It hurts
One more
Ah!
Ahaha!
This is a long one...
Ah!
Ahh!
Ah, I can't do it!
I just did it once!
Ah!
Ahhhhh!
Eh?
Ah!
Want it?
Want it...
Ah...
I can't see anything.
Oh, no.
Ah, it hurts so much.
This is bad.
It feels so good.
Ah, ah, ah.
Ah, I'm embarrassed.
I'm sweating.
I want to sit down.
I want to sit down too.
I'm going to eat a lot.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Ouch, ouch.
Shhh, don't cry.
Don't cry, don't cry.
Ouch, ouch.
Oh, no.
I'm going to die.
Can I lie down here?
No, you can lie down here.
I'm going to die.
Ouch, ouch.
Don't cry, don't cry.
I'm going to die.
Ouch, ouch.
Don't cry, don't cry.
Are you okay with the phone?
What?
It's ringing a lot.
Really?
It's okay.
I think it's like I just got here.
Really?
Yeah.
I'll call you later, so it's okay.
It's okay.
Let's do it again.
Let's do it.
I'm going to laugh.
It's okay.
It feels good.
Show me.
Taki.
What?
I'm going to stop getting married.
Let's get married.
Why?
If we get married, we can have sex every day.
I want to do that every day, but...
It's suspicious.
What?
If I marry Taki, I won't cheat on you.
You're lying.
It's true.
Let's get married.
No.
We're not in a relationship right now.
But...
Do you love your husband?
Yeah.
I knew it when I saw you.
I love you more and more.
Then what am I?
What?
That's all.
Is that all you think?
That's right.
What?
Okay.
We can have sex like this from now on.
We have a good physical relationship.
I want to do that until my husband comes home today.
Let's do it every day.
I'm going to stop.
Yeah.
What?
I can't.
Yuna, I'm sorry.
I sent you an e-mail earlier.
I arrived at the station early today.
Shall I make your favorite macaron?
If you like anything else, please reply.
I can't.