I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Yes, hello.
Oh, hello.
Yes.
What?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm in my late 20s.
It's irregular.
My practice is below average.
I'm sorry.
I'm not that busy.
I'm always tired.
I don't think I'm working properly.
Sometimes I feel like I don't want to work at all.
But there's a reason why I can do my best.
That is...
Welcome back, brother.
Thank you for your hard work.
Mei-chan.
Do you want to hug me?
Yes.
This is Mei-chan, a female student who lives next door.
We share a lot of things.
She helps me with my housework every day.
Today, Mei-chan made dinner and waited for me to come home.
She's younger, but she's so kind.
She's like a mother.
Thank you for your hard work.
Brother.
It's time for dinner.
Let's eat together.
Yes.
I'll eat.
Thank you for the meal.
Brother.
You're so kind.
There's dessert for you.
Yay!
Dessert?
What is it?
Wait a minute.
Ta-da!
I made pudding.
It's pudding!
I love pudding.
Thank you, Mei-chan.
Mei-chan.
Yes?
I want you to
give me a hug.
You're so sweet.
Can't I?
You can.
Really?
Give me a hug.
It's good.
Is it good?
Do you want more?
Yes.
Give me a hug.
Is it good?
Eat more.
It's good.
Is it good?
You're a good boy.
Give me a hug.
Mei-chan's pudding is really good.
Really?
Do you want me to make it again?
Yes, please.
I'll make it for you.
Really?
Thank you, Mei-chan.
You're so kind.
Thank you.
I can't sleep if I eat everything.
Mei-chan.
The pudding was really good.
Really?
I want to eat it again, so make it for me.
Thank you.
I'll make it for you again tomorrow.
Really?
I'll do my best tomorrow.
Okay.
What's wrong?
I got sleepy after eating.
Do you want to sleep?
Yes.
I'll make you a pillow.
Come here.
Can I?
Yes.
Good boy.
You did a good job.
Thank you.
I'm sleepy.
Do you want to sleep?
Yes.
Good boy.
Do you want to sleep?
Yes.
You must be tired from work.
I was scolded a lot.
You were scolded?
Yes.
I'm doing my best.
Good boy.
You smell good.
Did you hear that?
Yes.
I didn't hear that.
I know.
You feel bad.
No.
I want you to call me more.
Call me more.
Louder.
What?
Can I call you mom?
Yes.
Call me a lot.
Mom.
Good boy.
I wanted to call you mom.
You can call me a lot.
Thank you.
You don't have to call me sister.
You can call me mom.
Mom.
Cute.
Good boy.
Let's sleep on my lap.
OK.
Come here.
You like here.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
What's wrong?
It smells good here.
Does it smell good?
What's wrong?
It smells like pudding.
What?
Does it smell like pudding?
It's sweet.
Do you feel good?
You can call me more.
Good boy.
Hey.
Chinchin.
You are stiff.
What's wrong?
Mom.
What should I do?
Touch me more.
More?
More.
Like this?
Good boy.
Chinchin.
How do you feel?
Good.
Mom.
What?
I want to see your boobs.
You are a spoiled child.
Can I?
Yes.
Mom's boobs.
Touch me.
How do you feel?
You are cute.
Am I cute?
Can I kiss you more?
Good boy.
How do you feel?
Can I do it?
You're good at it.
You're really good at it.
I feel good, too.
Mama.
You're still a baby.
I want you to be gentle.
You've grown a lot bigger than before.
Mama's boobs.
How is it?
You're good at it.
You're really good at it.
Give me a kiss.
Let me do it.
Hey, Mamma.
What is it?
This time,
pat me.
Pat you?
Yes, pat me.
Okay.
How is it?
It's so soft.
Is it soft?
It tickles.
You can keep patting me.
You pat me so much.
Because
you've grown up so much.
I have to pat you a lot.
Okay, okay.
What is it?
You can keep patting me.
Okay.
Can I hold this?
Of course you can.
How is it?
It tickles.
It tickles my boobs.
Can I touch you more?
More?
Can I pat you more?
It tickles.
You're so good.
More?
Yes.
Can I hug you with my boobs?
Like this?
You're so good.
I feel good, too.
Really?
Okay, okay.
Are you okay?
I feel so good.
You're so good.
I kissed you.
One more time.
Okay.
How do you feel?
I feel so good.
I want to hug you directly.
Do you want to hug me?
Yes.
Okay.
Can I go home?
Yes, you can.
How do you feel?
I'm sleepy.
Are you sleepy?
Yes, I'm sleepy.
I'm embarrassed.
You're so good.
I can't hug you.
Really?
I'm kidding.
You're a good boy.
Thank you.
Now, let me see your butt.
My butt?
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
I'm going to lick you again.
You're so cute.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
You're so cute.
I'm so happy.
Are you happy?
Yes.
What should I do?
Let me see your butt.
I'll do something for you, okay?
Really?
How is it?
I don't feel anything.
You don't feel anything?
How is it?
I don't feel anything.
Doesn't it hurt?
No.
It feels so good.
Leave it to me.
You can use this.
How is it?
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
More?
How is it?
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels so good.
How is it?
I'm about to puke.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
What is it?
My boobs.
You love boobs, don't you?
I love my boobs.
That's good.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Do you feel better?
How is it?
It feels so good.
Can you feel my boobs?
Yes.
You're spitting on my boobs.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
Yes.
It's coming out.
What's coming out?
Your white boobs.
Do you want to show them?
I do.
But I don't like your boobs.
What should I do?
I want to see your boobs.
Do you want to see my boobs?
Yes.
Ow!
Wait, what if Big Bro does it?
Shall I do it?
But I hate doing this.
Can I hold you?
Yes.
Give me your hand.
It feels good.
It feels good?
Yes.
It feels good.
You're a good boy.
Give me your hand.
Okay.
It feels good.
You're a good boy.
Really?
Give me your hand.
It feels good.
Look at me.
Does it feel good?
You can move more.
Can I move more?
Yes.
It feels good.
I'm going to go.
You're a good boy.
Give me your hand.
It feels good.
I'm going to go.
How are you?
Are you okay?
Here you go.
I'll scratch your back.
Does it feel good?
Do you want me to do more?
I love you.
I feel good, too.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
You love my boobs, don't you?
Do you want me to do more?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Give me everything.
You're strong.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
You love my boobs, don't you?
Does it feel good?
You're getting bigger.
What's wrong?
It's okay.
Give me a lot.
You're sweating a lot.
You've got a lot.
I've put up with it.
You did a great job.
You're sweating.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to take a bath with me?
Does it feel good?
You did a great job.
I'm tired today, too.
Are you tired?
I wanted to take a bath with you.
Did you?
You should have told me earlier.
I wanted to go home early.
I don't want to see you anymore.
Why?
Every time I see you, I get angry.
I'm not angry.
Don't cry.
Are you calm?
It's hard work, isn't it?
I want to quit.
Do you want to quit?
But I'll go home.
I'll do my best.
You're great.
You're cute.
You're tired from work.
Wash your body.
I'll wash your body.
You're sweating a lot.
You're sexy.
Am I sexy?
How is it?
You're mischievous.
You're selfish.
I forgive you.
Do you want a nose job?
I'll do a noose job for you.
You're prepared.
You like buttocks, don't you?
I like it.
Give me a hug.
I love you.
How do you feel?
Good.
I love you.
You are cute.
Your buttocks are cute.
Really?
Your buttocks are very cute.
I'll wash your buttocks more.
Give me a hug.
I love you.
Can I give you a hug?
I want to give you a hug.
Give me a hug.
Can I give you a hug?
You are a pervert.
I don't know your boobs anymore.
You don't know?
No.
But...
This is your boobs.
You are right.
Do you feel good?
You are good at washing.
I feel good.
Really?
Do you feel good?
There?
Yes.
Do you feel good?
There?
I'll wash your buttocks.
Do you feel good?
Really?
I'll wash your buttocks.
I washed your buttocks.
Can't I?
You have a lot of bubbles.
You are fine.
For I am the bread of heaven
and the bread that is your own
Bread of heaven
Do you think so?
Grrrrrr...
Umph!
Grrrrr...
It's true, it's so fluffy.
Do you like this?
Yes.
Can you hold the bubbles?
Bubbles?
It's so fluffy.
Does it feel good?
You're so weak.
You're so cute.
How is it?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Do you want to feel better?
It's so fluffy.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
What is it?
What?
I want you to do something with my mouth.
Your mouth?
Okay.
Are you going to play a prank on me?
Because I love your butt.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
It's so fluffy.
Hurry up.
What is it?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Do you want more?
Yes.
It's so fluffy.
You're so cute.
You'll have a lot of milk.
Will I?
Yes.
Really?
Give me milk.
Okay.
Can I put it in your mouth?
Yes.
It's so fluffy.
I'm scared.
It's amazing.
You put it in my nose again.
Your milk is so delicious.
Really?
You put it in my nose again.
You can put out a lot of milk.
Good morning.
What's wrong?
Let me see.
Did you put on make-up?
What's wrong?
You don't want to put on make-up when you grow up, do you?
No, I don't.
I can't control myself while I'm sleeping.
I'm fine.
Really?
Yes.
But I have one more thing to tell you.
One more thing?
Yes.
Well...
It's time for you to grow up.
Growing up is a sign of your health.
Really?
Yes.
And you can be proud of it.
Can I be proud of it?
Yes.
But I can't go to work like this.
You're right.
Are you suffering now?
Yes, I'm suffering a lot.
I'll do something for you.
Really?
Yes.
I love you.
You love my boobs, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Oh, my boobs.
How do you feel?
They're soft and comfortable.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Do you want to lick my boobs?
Yes, I do.
Come here.
It's time for breakfast.
Good boy.
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
You can drink more.
One, two, three.
Oh.
It feels good.
Yes, it does.
Really?
Let's feel good together.
Do you want to feel good with me?
You're getting bigger.
Yes, I am.
Are you happy to see me?
You're honest and cute.
Good boy.
Oh, my boobs.
What's wrong?
Do you feel good?
Yes, I do.
It's good.
I can smell milk from here.
I'll put a lot of milk.
You're cute.
Give me a kiss.
A kiss?
A kiss.
Oh, my boobs.
I'll take off the button.
The button?
Ta-da.
I found your nipples.
Is it good?
How do you feel?
Oh, my boobs.
You're trembling.
It's painful.
Is it still painful?
You have to do something.
Oh, my boobs.
It's slimy.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I do.
You can feel better.
I'll put a lot of milk.
Okay.
Are you going to put a lot of milk?
I'm full.
Okay.
I'll put a lot of milk.
Give me your boobs.
Oh, my boobs.
What?
It's okay.
Give me your boobs.
Oh, my boobs.
You're still sleeping.
Do you feel ticklish?
You put a lot of milk.
You made me feel better.
Are you okay now?
I'm glad.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Good luck with your work.
Mom.
Yes.
When I come home from work,
don't leave me at home.
Don't worry.
I'll be with you forever.
Really?
Absolutely?
Absolutely.
Okay.
Good luck with your work.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
Good night.
Mom.
I don't want to go home.
I know.
Then, let's take a rest today.
Okay.
You are good at being honest.
Do you want to drink my breast as a reward?
Yes.
Come here.
Do you want to drink my breast?
You are a good boy.
You can stay here forever.
Come here.
You are a good boy.
Do you want to stay here forever?
Does it hurt?
You can do whatever you want.
There, there.
I have a lot of breast.
Does it taste good?
There, there.
Do you want to see more?
You are a good boy.
There, there.
Does it taste good?
Does it feel good?
You are cute.
There, there.
Drink a lot.
You are getting bigger.
There, there.
Drink more.
Does it taste good?
There, there.
Good.
Show it to me.
It's getting bigger.
How do you feel?
Give it to me.
Leave it to me.
What's wrong?
Do you have more milk?
Give it to me.
Drink more milk.
Is it good?
I hope it gets bigger.
Drink more milk.
It's getting bigger.
It feels good.
What are you doing?
It's getting bigger.
Drink more milk.
Is it good?
It's getting bigger.
You can do everything you want.
You're the only one.
Drink more milk.
It feels good.
It's getting bigger.
Does it feel good?
Do you like my boobs?
What's wrong?
Do you want this?
It's open.
How do you feel?
Does it feel good?
Can you see?
Touch me more.
It hurts.
Does it feel good?
What's wrong?
There's a lot.
I'm your sister.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
Touch me.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
Do whatever you want.
Ah!
Ahhh!
Oh!
I'm sorry.
Ah!
Oh!
Eh?!
Ah?!
Hah!!
Oh!
Hahhhh
Ahhh
Hahhh
Hah....
Hahh...
Ah
Haah
Time's up
It feels nice!
Over Egg
Feels good
Good boy.
You'll be with me forever.
Thank you for watching.