Mazinger Z beat upierst Maizen Sisters
Every single day ...
Yes, thank you for your hard work.
Yes.
What?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yes.
Well, I can't go back to the office today.
In his late 20s, he works non-stop.
He practices less than average.
Yes.
He's not that busy, but he's always tired.
Excuse me.
I don't think his work suits him.
Sometimes I feel like I don't want to work at all.
But I have a reason to work hard.
That is...
I'm home.
What?
Welcome home, brother.
Thank you for your hard work.
I made dinner for you today.
Really?
Yes.
Let's eat together.
Yes, yes, I'll eat.
Come on up.
Yes.
Let's go.
This is Lena, a girl student who lives next door.
She has a lot of reasons to help me with my housework every day.
Today, Lena made dinner and waited for me to come home.
She's younger than me, but she's really nice.
She's like a mother.
Don't say that.
I can't eat by myself.
Then I'll let you eat.
Really?
Open your mouth more.
How is it?
Is it good?
It's not good.
But you ate it.
That's great.
Give me a kiss.
That's great?
Yes.
If you eat another one, I'll give you a big one.
I can't help it.
Then eat it properly.
Yes.
Here you go.
Did you eat it?
Yes.
That's great.
I ate it.
That's great?
What should I do?
Give me a kiss.
You did a good job.
That's great.
You did a good job today.
You were able to eat what you didn't like.
That's great.
By the way, you haven't cleaned your ears lately, have you?
Yes.
Do you want me to do it for you?
Yes, please.
Yes.
Come here.
Do you want me to do it for you?
Yes.
I'll clean your ears.
I think it's fun.
Yes.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
You don't have much earwax.
Do you want me to do it for you?
Yes.
It feels good.
Did you call me mama?
No.
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
Call me mama.
Can I call you mama?
But I'm older than you.
I don't feel good when I call you mama.
No.
When you call me next time, say it louder.
Can I call you mama?
Yes.
Call me mama.
Mama.
It's cute.
Mama?
Yes.
I'll call you mama.
You can be more spoiled.
Really?
Yes.
Mama.
You must be tired from work.
I'm very tired.
I'll heal you.
Mama.
Can you do me a favor?
I'll do anything for you.
Really?
I want to drink your boobs.
Do you want to drink my boobs?
Yes.
It's time to drink my boobs.
Let's drink a lot.
Okay.
Here you are.
Did you sleep well?
It's hot.
Let's drink a lot.
Do you want to drink a lot?
How is it?
It's delicious.
How did you learn that word?
Do you want more?
It's hot.
Can I kiss you more?
Really?
My boobs are hot.
What's wrong?
It hurts.
I'll look at you.
I can't look at you.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Your boobs are getting bigger.
Do you want me to kiss you more?
It hurts.
It's hot.
Do you want me to kiss you more?
Is it hot?
It's hot.
Yes.
How about your boobs?
It's hot.
What about you?
Ah...
I don't know.
I'll do my best until you get better.
I'll do my best.
You have to say it properly.
I'll kiss you.
I'll do my best.
I feel good.
How do you feel?
I'll do my best.
I'll make you comfortable.
Are you okay?
It's a little painful.
Does it hurt?
Come here.
Are you okay?
Do you want me to kiss you?
Behind you.
I did it.
I'll lick you.
Do you want me to lick you?
Do you like this?
Do you want me to kiss you?
Is it good?
It's good.
Do you want me to kiss you?
It hurts.
It's painful.
It's not painful.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to kiss you?
Do you like this?
You must be tired.
Can I kiss you a lot?
It's white.
I'll look at you.
I'm going to sleep.
You're a good boy.
Are you okay now?
You're dirty.
You need to clean up.
Do you want to take a bath together?
I'll take a bath with you.
I'll give you a bath.
Why?
Because I'm tired
Come here
Are you tired?
Yes
Is it warm?
Yes, it's warm
Are you tired from work today?
Yes, I'm very tired
I'm tired
I see
I'm not tired
Really?
Yes
I'm not tired
You can be more spoiled
Can I?
Come here
I want to see your teeth
Do you want to see them?
Yes
Come here
Do you want to see them?
No
Can I?
Come here
Yes
Is it hard?
I'm going to brush your teeth
You are so cute
I'm going to brush more
Do you want to kiss me?
Yes
Kiss me
You are good
I'm going to brush more
Are you cold?
No
Really?
I'm warm
Are you warm?
I'm going to brush more
More?
More
Can you do it?
Yes
Do you want more?
More
I'm going to brush more
Mochi showed up
I hope Mom only kisses you
Hey Mochi
It's getting harder and harder.
It's getting harder and harder, isn't it?
Yeah.
Do you want me to give you a blowjob?
It hurts.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Do you want me to fix it?
Yeah.
How do you feel?
It's a little swollen.
Is it swollen already?
No, not yet.
What?
I have to make it clean here, too.
Yeah, I've got a lot of sweat and it's dirty.
I'll wash it for you later.
Yeah.
It feels good.
What?
It feels good when I do it.
When you do it?
Yeah.
Does it feel good when I do it?
Yeah, it feels good when it's soft.
Yeah.
You've done a lot of work.
It's sour, isn't it?
Yeah.
Is it sour?
Is it good?
It's good.
I'll do it all for you.
It's hot.
It doesn't fly at all.
Yeah, it doesn't fly at all.
What should I do?
It's hot.
It tickles.
It tickles, doesn't it?
Yeah.
You've done a lot of work.
I'll do it for you.
What?
Oh.
Oh, Mom.
What?
I'm going out.
No.
I can't.
Oh.
I'll do it for you.
No, I'll do it for you.
I'll do it until you wash it.
Yeah.
Oh.
I'll do it until you wash it.
It's hot.
Yeah.
I'm going to change my clothes.
Okay.
Are you going to change?
I'm going to change my clothes.
Okay.
Is it warm?
Yes.
I'm going to change my clothes.
You haven't changed your clothes yet.
What are you doing?
I'm going to change my clothes.
Mom, wash your face.
Where?
I don't know until you tell me.
Your body.
Wash your body.
My body?
Yes.
I'm going to change my clothes.
Wash your boobs.
Do you want to wash your boobs?
Can you wash your boobs?
Okay.
I'm going to make it foamy.
I'm going to make it clean.
Stand up.
Can you do it?
I'm going to make it clean.
You have to do it.
I can't wash this.
I can't wash it because it's too big.
I can't wash it.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Are you scared?
No, I'm not.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
I'll wash your butt, too.
I'll be right back.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'll be right back.
Are you going to wash my butt?
Yeah.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Can you wash your butt by yourself?
Yeah.
What?
This.
You did a good job.
Can you wash your butt by yourself?
I'll clean your butt.
It's cold.
Oh.
I'll clean your butt.
It feels good.
Oh.
I'll wash your butt, too.
It's cold.
I'll wash your feet.
I washed your feet.
Did you wash your feet?
You did a good job.
I washed your feet.
You're feeling good.
You did a good job.
I'll wash your feet.
Okay, let's start the massage.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Okay, let's start the massage.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Let's start the massage.
Okay, let's start the massage.
You are good at it.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you for washing me.
You are welcome.
You don't have to be scared.
Okay.
Does it feel good?
I'll give you a massage.
Yes, it feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'll give you a massage.
Yes, it feels good.
Does it feel good?
I like you.
Really?
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
I'll give you a massage.
Okay.
You have a lot of bubbles.
You like bubbles, don't you?
Did it hurt?
I'll give you a massage.
I like you.
Thank you.
Does it hurt?
I'll give you a massage.
How's your butt?
Show me your butt.
Did you wash your butt?
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
My butt is warm.
It's fun.
Let me massage your buttocks.
I'm done with the bubbles.
Are you tired?
Does it feel good?
Are you done with the bubbles?
You look beautiful.
Do I?
You had a lot of work today.
Let me massage your buttocks.
Does it feel good?
More?
You like my boobs, don't you?
Kiss me.
What should I do?
I want to put you in my belly.
Do you want to?
Please. I want to see it.
I know.
May I?
Sure.
What should I do?
The back.
The back?
Yes.
Like this?
Then, try it.
Ah.
Are you tired?
Yes.
Please, give me your leg.
Ah.
There.
There, right?
Yes.
Ah.
Are you okay?
Yes.
You're good.
Really?
Yes.
Can you move?
I'll do my best.
Ah.
You're good.
Yes.
Ah.
I'll do my best.
Yes.
Ah.
I'm going to sleep.
That's amazing.
You moved a lot.
I'm tired.
Then I'll move.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm tired.
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
That's amazing.
Does it feel good?
Do you know it's in your stomach?
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
That's amazing.
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
That's amazing.
You're getting better.
I'm going to put you in my arms.
Did you get it out?
You're amazing.
Did it hurt?
I'm going home.
I'll see you tomorrow.
I don't want to.
I can't sleep.
I know.
I'll stay with you for a while.
I don't want to.
I can't sleep.
I have to stay with you longer.
I'll sing you a lullaby.
Good morning.
What's wrong?
Breakfast is ready.
Are you still sleeping?
I don't want to go to work.
I see.
You don't have to go to work.
You're not sleeping, right?
I'm fine.
You're not sleeping, are you?
Will I be angry if I don't go to work?
I don't know.
Take your time.
It's okay if I hang out with my mother at home.
It's okay.
It's okay?
Yeah.
Then...
I'm going home.
Do you want a drink?
No, breakfast.
Breakfast?
Yeah, breakfast.
Do you want to sleep?
Yeah.
Then...
There, there.
That's not your boob.
Your boob is here.
Yeah.
I'm sleepy.
Do you want to get some air?
It's hard.
There, there.
Does it hurt?
This isn't hard, is it?
Yeah.
There, there.
Does your boob feel good?
My boob feels good.
There, there.
Can I kiss you?
Kiss.
You can roll your eyes.
Can I give you a kiss?
Can't you?
You don't listen to me.
I have to make you a good boy.
Can I give you a kiss?
My hands are getting hot.
I'll give you a lot more.
Can I give you a kiss?
No.
Do you like this?
Can I give you a kiss?
You're good.
Do you like this?
Can I give you a kiss?
I'll give you a lot more.
Do you like this?
Can I give you a kiss?
It hurts again.
I'll give you a kiss.
I'll be nice to you.
Can I give you a kiss?
It's hard.
Do you want me to give you a kiss?
Can I give you a kiss?
Do you like this?
It hurts.
I'll give you a lot more.
Can I give you a kiss?
Do you like this?
It hurts.
Do you feel better?
Can I give you a kiss?
I'll make you feel better.
It hurts.
It's moving.
Can I give you a kiss?
It hurts.
You're getting better.
It feels good.
Can I give you a kiss?
You're getting better.
Can you be more comfortable with me?
Hang on.
You're getting better.
I'll hold you tighter.
It feels good.
You're getting better.
Are you tired?
It feels good.
Are you sleepy?
I'll put you on my chest.
Can you see me?
Do you want to move more?
You can move a lot.
Can you move more?
I'll try to move.
I don't feel good.
I love you.
I fell asleep.
I failed.
Come here.
I love you.