It's a taste like a horse, but it's not good for the world, so I want to use it for a long time, isn't it?
Isn't there anything else?
Oh?
What?
I want you to be a maid of a high school girl.
There are various courses. The longest course is a 10-day stay course?
Hey, are you serious?
No, wait a minute.
There is no such a delicious story.
Isn't it better to be a maid of a high school girl?
It's a little shocking that more than 50 people came.
Well, when the old woman came, it changed immediately.
No, I don't want to be a maid of a high school girl for 10 days.
But it's interesting, so I think it's okay to call it a maid of a high school girl.
When the old woman comes, I want to talk to her.
I want you to be a maid of a high school girl.
First of all, choose a course by application.
Of course, it's the best course.
Wait a minute. I'm looking forward to it.
I'll have a drink and get excited.
All right, let's go.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Good morning.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Erika, and I'll be your maid today.
What's the matter?
Oh, you're a maid.
Yes.
Oh, I see. I was surprised.
You really come.
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, it's not like that.
I didn't expect such a beautiful person to come, so I was just surprised.
Is that so?
I've just started this job, so I'm sure there are some things I'm not good at.
I'll do my best, so please let me know if you need anything.
Oh, yes.
You don't have to bother me anymore.
What?
Oh, are you inside?
Yes, I want to change my clothes right away.
Oh, is that so?
Was it Erika?
Yes.
I'm a little embarrassed to be in Erika's room.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Oh, but the room is really dirty.
What should I do?
It's okay.
Can you clean it up?
Yes, I can.
I'm a maid who will take care of you from today, so please call me Erika, not Erika.
Master.
Then I'll go out right away.
Yes.
Wow, isn't it beautiful?
Oh.
It's sunny, too.
She's a real maid.
What?
You called me master, didn't you?
You mean me, don't you?
I'm so excited to be called master by such a beautiful girl.
I'm so excited.
Wait a minute.
I've been doing that for 10 days.
What if I make a mistake?
I'm so excited.
Can I call you Erika?
Is it okay?
Won't she get angry?
Erika, you can change your clothes in that room.
Yes, master.
Isn't she coming soon?
Oh.
But she looks black.
She hasn't changed at all.
Sorry to keep you waiting, master.
What?
How is it?
What's wrong with my clothes?
No, no, Erika.
This is my mentofuku.
Did you hate it?
Or doesn't it suit you?
What?
No, no, no.
How is it?
Doesn't it suit you?
No, it doesn't suit me.
It's not that.
I mean...
I can see it.
What?
Where?
It's hidden.
I can't see it.
No, I mean overall.
Or do you want to see it?
What are you talking about?
I was just surprised.
You want to see it, don't you?
Master, you're so cute when you're embarrassed.
Well, I'm going to clean up.
Master, please relax.
Yes.
It looks great.
I'm going to clean up.
There's a lot of garbage on the floor.
I have to clean up.
Master, what are you looking at?
Well, it's...
I'm worried.
What are you talking about?
That's what I'm looking at.
I can't do it.
I can't stand it anymore.
Master, what are you doing?
Please calm down.
Please leave me alone.
Please sit down here.
Master, I can't stand it anymore.
I can't help it.
This is a job for a maid.
But there's only one thing.
I'm not Erica.
I'm Erica.
Erica.
You're Erica, not Erica.
I'll make you feel better.
Don't you want me to feel better?
Erica.
But this is...
Master, don't you want me to do it?
I don't want to do it.
I can't believe it.
This is also a job for a maid.
Master's house is very big.
Can I come in?
Are you serious?
I can't believe it.
Erica.
It's dirty.
You can't do that.
It's okay.
This is a job for a maid.
I can't believe it.
Is this really okay?
This is a job for a maid.
You can't do that.
Yeah.
Does it headaches?
It seems very bad.
I'm sorry.
No, you can't.
I'll make you feel better.
More?
It's hot.
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
Do you like it?
I love it.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can't.
What's wrong?
It feels good.
It's hot.
I can't.
I'm leaving.
I'm happy.
I can't.
I'm leaving.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
It's hot.
I slept a lot.
You slept a lot.
I'm sorry.
I'll make you feel better.
What are you doing?
Take off your pants.
Is that so?
It's okay.
It's not good.
It's part of the job.
Can I take it off?
I love it.
It's part of the job.
It's not good.
Mika.
What are you doing?
Don't you want to be a master?
But I don't think it's part of the job.
I'm sorry.
Mika.
Master, you have a big body.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
No, no.
This is...
It feels good.
Master, please touch my chest.
I'm sorry.
Erika, don't cry.
I'm going to sleep.
You're going to sleep?
Please sleep well.
I'm going to sleep.
It's okay.
But...
No, no, no.
My hands are going to fall out.
It's really bad.
Is it bad?
It's okay.
Is it okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm glad I called you.
Don't smell my armpits.
I'm sorry.
Are you really going to sleep?
Please let me sleep.
I'm sorry.
You're sweating a lot.
But you're still standing.
It feels so good.
I'll make you feel better.
Erica.
Can you still do it?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
It's deep inside.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels so good.
I can't do it.
Look at her butt.
It feels so good.
It's deep inside.
I'm sorry.
It's like a smell.
It feels so good.
I can't do it.
Can I go again?
You can't.
I'm sorry.
Please bear with me a little longer.
Master, I may be able to have a baby.
No, I'm sorry.
It's not over yet.
I want to go to Helica too.
Please put a lot of energy into it.
No, if I beg any longer, I may really be able to have a baby.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, Master.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
You have a lot of feces again.
Yes.
Did you feel good?
I'm sorry.
Please feel better and better.
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Master is still sleeping.
I want to sleep.
I feel strange.
What time is it now?
What?
Good morning.
What are you doing?
Good morning. It's already noon.
Please wash your face.
What?
Before that, say good morning.
Good morning.
You don't have to do that.
Do you hate good morning?
No.
It's not like that.
Or don't you want to be licked by Erica?
No.
I want to be licked.
I really want to be licked.
That's why I couldn't stand it yesterday.
I'm glad you're happy.
No.
I haven't showered yet.
I'm still dirty.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm really dirty.
I'm sorry.
I'm really happy.
Is this true?
What are you doing?
Don't you hate me?
No.
Please understand me.
It's hot.
It's so hot.
I'm going to die.
My husband is going to die soon.
I'll make you feel better.
I'm going to die.
This way of eating is the best.
It's hot.
I can't do it.
I'll get my mouth dirty again.
Drink a lot.
But...
I can't do it anymore.
I'm going to fall asleep.
Are you sure?
I'm sorry.
I'll get my mouth dirty.
It's hot.
I'm going to die.
My husband has a lot of urine in the morning.
I'm sorry.
You have a lot of urine.
It feels good.
I'm glad you're happy.
Are you going to get up?
Yes.
I made breakfast.
Please get up.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to die.
I can't do it anymore.
Can I do it?
If you do that, I'll die.
I'm going to die.
My husband is very hard.
Don't do that.
I'm going to die.
It feels good.
I wonder if I can do it today.
I'm looking forward to it.
The food is delicious.
It's cute.
It's art.
What are you doing?
I'm back.
Welcome back.
What are you doing?
I was cleaning the bath.
Is that so?
I was surprised.
I'm going to take a bath.
Do you want to take a bath together?
I don't want to take a bath together.
Why?
Let's take a bath together.
I'm embarrassed.
It's okay.
I don't want to take a bath.
I'm embarrassed to take a bath.
Do you really want to take a bath?
Hurry up.
I'm embarrassed to take a bath.
Are you sure?
Please wait.
Why are you embarrassed?
The bath is different.
You've taken a bath many times.
That's right.
I'll take a bath with you.
But...
I'll wash you.
Don't worry.
Please sit down.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you sure?
I'll wash you.
Okay.
I'll wash your stomach.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
I'm sorry.
Well...
What?
What do you mean?
Am I right?
No.
I'm washing your boobs.
What?
Are you serious?
Don't you feel good?
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
I've never washed my boobs like this before.
I feel good.
It's the best.
I'm glad.
I'm embarrassed.
Erika-san.
I'm okay now.
I'm clean.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'll do it myself.
Erika-san.
You've grown up.
No.
You've become very hard.
I'm embarrassed.
I used to feel good.
I'll do it myself.
I'll do it.
No.
I'll do it myself.
I'm okay.
I'll clean your boobs and shoes.
Erika-san.
I'll clean your boobs.
Boobs?
No.
It's too hard.
I feel good.
It's very soft.
I feel like I'm going to die.
No.
I'll make you feel better.
Come here.
Erika-san.
I'll give you a massage.
Okay.
I feel good.
Are you okay?
It still hurts a lot.
Thank you.
I'll clean your mouth.
Erika-san.
You cleaned my mouth.
I'll make you feel better.
Thank you.
I'll give you a massage.
I feel good.
You know I'll be gone soon, right?
Yeah, I know.
It feels good.
I want you to do that.
You used to do that with your mouth.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's so good.
It feels good.
Can I take a deep breath?
Here I go.
It's hot.
You're full again.
It feels good.
I'm happy.
Thank you for coming.
It's so soft.
Would you like to take a bath together?
Here I go.
I'm happy.
Are you still standing?
You just went.
It's hot.
Here I go.
It's the last one tomorrow.
It was fun.
It was the best I've ever had.
I wanted to be with you more.
I wonder if my husband thinks so.
It's cool.
It's hot.
I wanted to take a bath together.
I'm going to take a bath.
I'm going.
It's hot.
I'm going to take a bath.
I love you, Master.
Erika...
No...
For the past few days,
I've been having a great time.
Thank you for being so kind to me.
Um...
This is from me.
I don't mean to brag, but...
I want you to take this.
For me?
I'm so happy!
Can I open it?
Not here.
There's some clothes in here.
Can you change?
I'll go change.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll be waiting.
Okay.
I changed, Master.
It looks great on you.
Erika, it looks great on you.
Erika...
It looks great on you.
It's really great.
Really?
I don't want to say goodbye to you.
Today is the last day.
I don't want it to be the last, either.
I love you, Master.
Erika...
It's the last day.
I love you, Master.
I love you, too.
I don't want to see you.
Erika...
It's the best.
I love you.
I don't want to forget you.
I love you, too.
I didn't want to touch you.
You were so gentle.
You were so kind.
I loved you.
I love you, too.
I had a good dream.
I love you, Master.
I love you, too.
I hate this bed.
I slept with my knees on the pillow.
I love this beautiful bed.
I love everything.
I hate this bed.
I can't sleep alone.
I'm so sad.
I hate this bed.
I want to touch you more.
Can I have a last drink?
It's hot.
I'm surprised when I feel it.
I love you.
Can I have a last drink?
I hate this bed.
It's hot.
It's very hot.
I want to have a last drink.
I want to drink more.
It's very hot.
Will you make me feel better?
I'll make you feel better.
It feels good.
I want you to make me feel better.
I'm very lonely.
I want to have a last drink.
I want you to make me feel better.
I love you.
I can rub your butt.
I want you to rub my butt.
Ah...
I'm so drunk.
Please, quickly...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
n't
be
If there is no
Oh, it feels nice
I'm going. Hurry
I want to find a bunch of more
favorites
Oh, it feels nice
re
Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
It's so good.
You won't be too hot.
I'm gonna take off your shoes.
You're in there.
I can't carry you anymore.
I carried you a lot.
I'm going.
I'm happy.
I feel good.
I hope you feel good.
It's the best.
It feels good.
I can't carry you anymore.
I'm going.
I feel good.
Can I hug you?
Yes.
I'm going.
I'm happy.
Thank you for always supporting me.
I want to see you more.
Slowly.
Can you move a lot?
Ouch!
It's the best.
Come here.
Stretch your legs.
I can't.
Ouch!
It's the best.
Keep running.
Get up.
It's the best.
Show me a lot.
You look so warm.
Hold my feet.
With your hands.
Hold me like this.
It's the best.
I'm sorry.
Let's go back to bed!
Let's go again.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
Master.
I was a good maid for you.
I want you to make me feel better.
I want you to make me cry more.
I love you.
Let's go.