I take back what I once said
When I got transferred to a branch school of a regional and tertiary school.
I decided to live alone in the countryside.
It's heavy.
It's heavier than I thought.
It's the worst.
It started to rain as soon as I passed the tunnel.
I don't know what to do.
It smells like mold.
Is it true?
I'll clean up.
At first...
I'm relieved.
It's not bad to take a break in the countryside for a while.
When I started living alone, I noticed that there was a young couple living in the house below.
The wife was beautiful.
I'm relieved.
The weather in the countryside changes easily.
Excuse me.
Did you move to the second floor?
Yes.
I didn't know that.
I'm sorry.
It's raining.
Did you move to the second floor?
He's coming.
He moved to the second floor.
Nice to meet you.
There's nothing around here, is there?
Yes.
You can rely on me anytime.
Nice to meet you.
I work at a farm over there.
Is that so?
My husband runs a farm there.
It's close to here.
You can rely on me.
Thank you.
I didn't know that such a beautiful woman lived there.
I'm relieved.
The weather is bad, but I have to clean up.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
Are you going out?
Yes.
It's raining so hard, isn't it?
It's a little rainy.
Be careful.
Yes.
I'm leaving.
Have a good day.
This is Junguuji.
In the countryside, people's wives serve their husbands to protect them.
You don't care much about that, do you?
The seduction of a beautiful country wife.
It's so far from the country life I imagined.
I'm so busy that I don't have time to go to work.
Why do I have to get up early?
I don't have a convenience store.
I can't even buy alcohol.
I only have two TV shows.
Country life is more free than I imagined.
I don't have time to have fun.
What are the locals doing?
I don't see any young people.
Are they going somewhere?
I'm so tired.
What are they doing?
Are they sleeping?
That's boring.
I have no choice but to sleep.
I don't have time to sleep.
I spend my days at home.
I don't have time to go out.
I realize that I have time to sleep.
I can't sleep.
What?
Did you fall asleep?
I can't sleep.
What are they doing?
I hear a loud moan from below.
Wait a minute.
It's early in the morning.
I can't sleep.
I have to make breakfast.
I hear that at noon and at night.
I can't sleep.
The weather is bad.
I don't want to go to work.
I can't sleep.
Do you want me to do it again?
You've been fine since this morning.
I can't sleep.
My desire grew.
I noticed that I heard a loud moan every day.
I wonder if she's doing well.
I heard a loud moan.
I hear a loud moan every day.
I wonder if she's doing well.
I'm embarrassed.
I was about to go to the field.
I see.
I'm always dirty when I go to the field.
I don't think there's anyone in Tokyo who wears clothes like this.
I don't think so.
Really?
I think it suits you.
This is the easiest.
You don't have to be dirty.
This is surprisingly cool.
I see.
This is a rural area.
There are only old people here.
This is the best.
I think I understand.
There are no young people here.
I think so.
Do you have any friends here?
I have a co-worker.
You're an old man, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
I see.
There are no shops around here.
I don't think so.
I don't think there are any big shops around here.
I see.
The shop over there closes soon.
It closes at 4 o'clock, doesn't it?
It's a little early.
It's too early.
I think so.
Is it different from the urban area?
I think it's a little different from the urban area.
But it's a city if you live in it.
I think there are many department stores.
I think so.
But I didn't go there much.
You're right.
There is a famous coffee shop.
There is a famous coffee shop, isn't it?
There are many chain stores.
I see.
I want to go there.
Do you like coffee?
Yes, but I don't have a chance to go there.
I'm a little nervous to talk to a man from the city.
I didn't live in a big city.
I only get information from magazines.
Isn't your make-up strange?
No, it's not strange at all.
Really?
I hate it.
Wouldn't you be bullied if you went to a city like this?
I've never been so scared.
Cheers!
The weather has been bad recently.
Yes.
It's been bad all week.
Don't you have to go to the field?
It's going to be dark in the afternoon.
It's fine now.
Is it okay to go to see the tractor?
It's okay.
I cleaned it up yesterday.
I see.
Did you take a day off today?
Yes, I did.
I think it's better to take a day off.
It's okay.
It's over.
Don't take a video of me.
I'm going.
Where are you going?
To the field.
I'm going shopping.
Let's go shopping together.
You go to the field and I go shopping.
Let's go together.
No, let's go together.
What?
It's not good.
What's not good?
Get ready.
I'm ready.
Get out of the car.
What are you doing in the morning?
It's not good.
It's a little low.
What are you talking about?
I'm going.
Where are you touching?
It's not good.
Don't touch me.
It's okay.
Show me your skirt.
It's not good.
Like this?
Yes.
Show me more.
More?
Yes.
It's not good, isn't it?
It's not good.
I don't know what will happen if I try to go out.
Should I take it off?
Yes.
It's not good.
Should I take it off?
Go away.
I don't know if I can touch that part.
I want to touch your boobs.
Like this.
Like this?
Yes.
Can you show me your private part?
Private part?
You don't touch my boobs?
I want to touch your boobs.
I don't want to.
I miss you.
Why?
Like this?
Yes.
I want to touch your boobs.
Like this?
You don't want to touch my boobs?
I want to touch your boobs.
Like this?
Yes.
I want to touch your boobs.
Are you ready?
I want to touch your boobs and i want you to touch my boobs.
It's hot.
It's raining continuously.
It looks like peanut rainforest.
It's so hot. I can't even dry my laundry.
It's so hot. I wish the wind would blow a little more.
I wonder how hot it will be this year.
Excuse me.
Huh?
Is he not here?
Excuse me.
I'm here to return the meat and potatoes.
I wonder who he is.
Mr. Mizuki?
He's sleeping.
I didn't know he was this cold.
If he's this cold, I wonder if his husband is also cold.
It's so hot.
It's so soft.
Give me a brush.
Mr. Mizuki?
You're sweating a lot.
You'll catch a cold.
It's so hot.
Yesterday...
Just a little.
It's so hot.
Mr. Mizuki?
You're back.
Welcome back.
It's so hot.
I've come this far.
It's so white.
Forgive me.
It's so hot.
I can't stop.
Please be careful.
Slowly.
I have to be careful.
You're not hurt, are you?
It hurts.
It's so hot.
It's overflowing.
Are you having a bad dream?
It's so hot.
It's so great.
I can't do this.
No.
What are you doing?
I can't do this.
No.
Please calm down.
What are you doing?
I can't do this.
My wife is in this state.
No.
I can't do this.
Are you okay?
I'll be back soon.
Calm down.
I can't calm down if you keep looking at me like that.
Don't touch me.
No, no, no.
Let me go.
I don't want to.
Don't do that.
Calm down.
I'm really sorry.
Don't do that.
You'll be crazy if you hear your disgusting voice.
But I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
Calm down.
Let's stop.
I'm really sorry.
Don't do that.
Let me go.
I don't want to.
I saw you the other day.
You were doing something nice with your husband here.
You noticed that I was peeping, didn't you?
I couldn't help it at that time.
You were peeping at me, weren't you?
I didn't mean to do that.
I can't help it.
You can't help it?
Wait a minute.
If you do that, I'll go crazy.
I can't help it.
My big toe.
It's very hard here.
I can't help it.
Don't say that.
It's very hard here.
I can't help it.
Don't say that.
Wait a minute.
I can't help it.
It's my fault.
Wait a minute, please leave me alone.
I can't do this.
Calm down.
Wait a minute, please leave me alone.
I can't do this.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Please leave me alone.
I'll be back.
I'll be back soon.
Wait.
No.
Please wait.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
No.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Please wait.
Please leave me alone.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no!
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Please don't cry.
I love you!
Misaki?
Oh, my God, are you crying?
It's okay.
Don't.
Please, don't.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh, oh, oh, yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh , oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh
I can't do it.
I want to go deeper.
Don't push me so hard.
I can't do it.
What?
Did you do something to me?
What are you going to do if I do something to you?
No.
I'm sorry.
My head is white.
No.
I'm sorry.
No?
No.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
Did I tell my husband?
I have to apologize to him.
It's hard to say.
I have a girlfriend.
I have to apologize to her.
No.
Thank you.
Please sit down.
Were you going to help your husband?
I'm fine.
I'm going to apologize.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Please raise your head.
I couldn't get my voice out of my head at night.
I forgot what I was saying.
I'm so sorry.
Please raise your head.
I'm sorry.
Did you hear me?
Every day?
I'm so sorry.
I'm so embarrassed.
I know.
You're worried about me, aren't you?
I didn't think about it at all.
We're in the countryside, aren't we?
We have nothing else to do.
It's been raining a lot lately.
My husband is coming to see me.
That's the only thing I can do.
It was noisy, wasn't it?
I'm sorry.
No.
I should have covered my ears.
But I couldn't help it.
Did your husband tell you about yesterday?
No, he didn't.
Don't worry.
I won't tell you.
But...
You're worried about me, aren't you?
I'm sorry I wasn't considerate.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I didn't notice that a single man was upstairs.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I hit you yesterday.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
It's my fault.
Don't worry about it.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's my fault.
I'm sorry.
It must have hurt.
It's my fault.
I was a little happy.
I grew up here.
I've never been with anyone other than my husband.
I don't have much experience with other men.
So it was new to me.
I was more excited than usual.
I'm not as attractive as a city girl.
But I'm glad you saw me as a woman.
No, I'm not.
I'm not as attractive as a city girl.
Is it just me?
Or am I not good at kissing?
No, it's not that.
I'm sorry.
Should I put my tongue in your mouth?
Even a country boy can do this much.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good here?
Yes.
Here, too.
Doesn't it hurt?
It feels good.
Really?
I'm glad.
You made me bigger.
Can I help you?
I can do other things, too.
But...
Is it okay to do this?
No, it's not.
Don't you want to be a country girl?
No, I don't.
I couldn't see you yesterday.
You look different from your husband.
How can I say?
Are you big?
Can I see you again?
Yes.
But is it okay to do this?
But it feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
I want you to tell me how you feel.
This way.
Or this way.
Both feel good.
Both?
It's hard.
Can I lick you?
Yes.
Are you okay?
I'm not good at this.
No, it feels good.
I've never licked you before.
You're so big.
Don't you feel like a country girl?
No.
But it feels good.
It's hard.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
I'll be suspicious if you don't go to the field after this.
You can put it in your mouth.
Can I lick you?
I can't.
I'm so full.
I'm so happy that you're so excited.
I'm a little embarrassed.
It's not like I'm strong because I live in the country.
This is a return for being attacked by Tatsuya yesterday.
I'm sorry.
Mizuki.
I'm watching a baseball broadcast.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't stand it, so I came here.
I can't stand it, either.
Can I come in?
Yes.
Were you surprised?
Was I too aggressive?
No, I'm happy.
Are you happy?
Yes.
I'm glad.
I couldn't stand it.
I've been thinking about Tatsuya all the time.
I'm also worried about you.
I'm sorry.
What have you been doing since then?
I've been doing a lot.
Did you feel good?
Yes.
You're cute, Tatsuya.
I'm sorry.
You've grown up.
If you were thinking about me so much, touch me.
Let's touch each other.
You have bigger boobs than girls in the city, don't you?
Yes.
Here.
I can't do it.
It's painful, isn't it?
It's painful.
You have bigger boobs than girls in the city, don't you?
I can't do it.
It's hot.
I don't need this anymore.
You have bigger boobs than girls in the city, don't you?
Do you like me?
It's hot.
Do you like being touched here?
I like it.
You have bigger boobs than girls in the city, don't you?
You are too sexy.
You still have big boobs here.
It's hot.
I want you to feel good.
Do you feel good in my mouth?
Yes.
My boss taught me how to do it.
Like this.
Put your tongue between your back teeth.
It's hot.
When you touched me, you put your tongue between your back teeth.
Do you like it?
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Do you?
It's hot.
It tickles.
Do you feel good?
I feel good, too.
Do you feel good when I pinch your boobs?
Girls in Tokyo do this, don't they?
It tickles.
I've never been pinched like this.
Really?
I'll be the first.
Okay.
It tickles.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
It tickles.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
It tickles.
I'm going to do something painful, so come here.
I'm honest, so I'll do anything you want me to do.
Really?
What do you want me to do?
I want to be your pillow.
Pillow?
Can you lick here?
Yes.
Here you are.
It tickles.
Can I lie down?
It's hard to lick, isn't it?
I'll make it easier for you to lick.
Okay.
Is it easier to lick now?
It tickles.
Can you lick me more?
I have a lot of food.
It tickles.
You have a lot of food here.
I'm happy.
Which one do you like?
Hands, mouth, or boobs?
I like all of them.
Boobs?
Do you like boobs?
It tickles.
I like it, too.
Come here.
Did you feel good to be pinched by my boobs?
It tickles.
It's getting bigger.
Do you want to be pinched here?
It tickles.
Do you like to be pinched here?
I like it.
It's the first time for me.
It tickles.
You have a lot of food in your boobs.
I'll make your boobs wet.
I'll pinch you.
It tickles.
Do you feel good?
I'll pinch you at the deepest point.
It tickles.
It's getting bigger.
Do you feel good?
It tickles.
I'll make your boobs wet.
Do you like to be pinched here?
It tickles.
I'll make your boobs wet.
It's getting bigger.
It's okay.
You can let it out.
I'll make your boobs wet.
It tickles.
It's okay.
Let it out.
It tickles.
You're amazing.
You're full of energy.
Did you feel good to be pinched so much?
It tickles.
I'm glad.
You're full of energy.
What?
I can't do it.
Do you feel good?
You're a warrior, aren't you?
Your boobs are dirty.
What?
Do you feel good?
Can't I do it?
Yes.
I can't do it.
I'll do my best.
The game is over.
It tickles.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's getting hotter.
Make it hotter.
It tickles.
Sit down.
It's sour, isn't it?
Because you're sweating.
It tickles.
Wet me.
Make me wet.
It tickles.
I'm getting wet.
Make me feel good.
It tickles.
Make me wet.
It's hot.
You're sweating.
It tickles.
I'm sweating a lot.
Make me wet.
It tickles.
I want you to touch me more.
Make me feel good.
It tickles.
I can't go back to the city.
Let's stay here and make me feel good every day.
It tickles.
I can't live the next week.
Think about me more.
It tickles.
I'm glad you always make me feel good.
I'm soaked.
I smell sweat.
It tickles.
I'm soaked.
Let me lick you more.
I'll lick you.
I'm glad.
It tickles.
You don't like it, do you?
I'll lick you.
I'll take care of you so that you can't go home forever.
It tickles.
I'm soaked.
Do you feel good?
Can I talk to you more?
It tickles.
I'm sorry.
I can't stand it.
I'll move.
Can I have this?
It tickles.
You're so big that I feel good.
I feel good.
It tickles.
I want to touch you more.
I feel good.
It tickles.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
It tickles.
Don't do that.
If I were you, I wouldn't complain.
Let's feel good together.
It tickles.
I feel good.
Give it to me.
It tickles.
My legs are shaking.
You can sleep a lot.
It tickles.
I'll clean your ears.
It's still hard.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It tickles.
If I rub your ears with my boobs, you'll feel sick again.
I think you'll feel better.
You're full of energy again.
You can use my body to rub your ears.
My legs are shaking.
It tickles.
Do you want to do it more?
Yes, I want to do it more.
You'll feel better.
Come here.
It tickles.
I did it earlier, but it's still hard.
Give me more.
It tickles.
My legs are shaking.
No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
It tickles.
No, no, no.
Do you still have energy here?
Yes.
I want to do it more and more.
Do you feel like you're about to throw up?
I feel the same.
It tickles.
No, no, no.
Give me more.
It tickles.
No, no, no.
I'm kidding.
It tickles.
Do you want to clean my ears?
No, no, no.
Don't be so mean.
I'm still not comfortable here.
I still have a long way to go.
I want to do it more.
Do you want to do it more?
Give me more.
It tickles.
I still have a long way to go.
Don't do that.
It tickles.
My ears are being tickled.
Don't do that.
It tickles.
Can I use my bed now?
Oh, it feels good.
I can't do it anymore.
My boobs.
I want to do whatever I want.
I can't do it anymore.
Ah!
Ah ah ...
Wow ...
You put a lot again ...
Tatsuya
Yes
It's not bad to live in the countryside, is it?
eh
Hey, do you want to do it again?
Are you sure?
I can't do it anymore.
I have to do it again.
Can you do it?
It's a home run.
I did it.
I think I can do it today.
By the way, Mizuki went shopping.
She is late.
Where did she go?
Never mind.
Please subscribe to my channel.