I'm glad it's sunny.
Yeah, you're right.
I thought it was going to rain a little.
Are you a sunny guy?
What?
You're a sunny girl, aren't you?
I'm a rainy girl.
You're a rainy girl?
Yeah.
I heard you're my favorite sunny guy.
I'm glad it's sunny.
You're a sunny guy.
It's a little cold.
It's cold because it's in the middle of the mountain.
I gave birth to Chosuke when I was 19 years old.
My husband was my second senior in college.
I grew up in a girls' high school and had never dated a man.
As soon as I entered college, I fell in love with my husband, who was my second senior.
I fell in love with my husband, who was my second senior.
I didn't have the immunity to men.
I learned the joy of sex.
I spent every day with him.
I was pregnant.
The people around us were against it, but we decided to have a baby.
That was Chosuke.
Hey, there's a suspension bridge on the tourist map.
Do you want to go there?
But I'm not good at high places.
It's okay.
But I might not be able to walk.
Why?
It's okay.
If you're scared, I'll leave you alone.
Don't leave me alone.
Do you like high places?
You used to be good at high places.
I was good at high places.
When my husband graduated from college and entered society,
my life changed.
Gradually, there was a difference between the two of us.
In the meantime, I was pregnant with my second child.
My husband prioritized drinking at the company on the day of his birth.
I decided to get a divorce.
The newborn baby was going to be adopted by my sister and her husband.
I decided to raise Chosuke as a woman.
I raised Chosuke strictly as a father.
And Chosuke grew up to be a strong child with a sense of justice.
The high school teacher said,
It's a waste not to go to college with this grade.
Chosuke became a police officer after graduating from high school.
Chosuke made his way with his own ideas.
I was proud of Chosuke who realized it.
But there was a clue.
Chosuke, wait a minute.
That's why I told you not to be afraid.
I'm sorry.
Hold my hand.
I'm hungry.
Chosuke, let's take a commemorative photo.
Chosuke, come here.
Let's take another picture.
Chosuke, look at me.
Chosuke was a little nervous.
Chosuke, let's go back.
I was worried about Chosuke.
So I invited Chosuke on a trip.
But Chosuke couldn't see Chosuke's girlfriend or his girlfriend's shadow.
And one more thing.
Chosuke, don't you go on a trip with your friends?
No, I don't.
When I go on a trip with my friends,
I need a delivery service outside the prefecture.
I see.
It's hard.
Did you get a delivery service this time?
No, I didn't.
When I asked a friend who lives far away,
he said,
I can't be found out, so I'll go by bus.
I see.
It's hard to get a delivery service every time.
But it's hard.
It's bad if something happens.
So I don't go on a trip on my day off.
I see.
If you have a girlfriend,
I think you'll go on a trip.
I don't have a girlfriend.
It's time to check in at the inn.
Shall we go?
It's a beautiful room.
It's spacious.
I think so, too.
It's good.
I'm tired.
I think so, too.
What's this?
Oh, it's tea.
Let's make tea.
I'm thirsty.
I'll make it for you.
Thank you.
It's done.
It's hot.
It's warm.
It was cold outside.
It's cold.
But it's warm.
It's a Japanese-style room, so it's calm.
It's good.
I like Japanese-style rooms.
Is that so?
It's cold.
It's calm.
I'm sleepy.
Can I sleep a little?
It's okay.
I'll take a break.
I'm tired.
I'm sleepy.
Another worry was the prank I did when I was sleeping.
It was only once, but Chosuke touched my sleeping body.
I was surprised and confused, so I pretended to sleep without knowing what to do.
Just before Chosuke entered the dormitory of the police school.
It was the last night with Chosuke as a parent and child.
I'm sleepy.
It's night now.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Chosuke.
Are you awake?
Of course I'm awake.
If you do this.
I can't sleep.
Terrible.
I was pretending to sleep.
Which is worse?
Why are you doing this?
Because I love my mother.
I couldn't stand it.
Since I was a kid.
I loved my young and beautiful mother.
I loved her.
No way.
We are parents.
I know.
So I was trying to suppress this feeling.
I've been holding it in.
So.
I've never come back since I joined the police.
But.
I was looking at my sleeping mother.
I couldn't stand it.
So.
But.
It's okay if it's not like that, right?
That's not what I mean.
Because.
You were awake.
You were accepting it.
That's not what I mean.
Mother.
No.
You were accepting it.
Mother.
I want to see your underwear.
No.
Wait a minute.
Stop it.
I won't hide it.
Show me more.
But.
Wait a minute.
That's enough.
Stop it.
I can't stand it.
Look.
Mother.
Stop it.
I'll take a closer look.
Look.
When you were little.
I told you to take a bath.
Stop it.
Just a little more.
Look.
Mother's nipples are like this.
Stop it.
Mother.
Do you like here?
Look.
Stop it.
Wait a minute.
Mother's nipples are delicious.
Stop it.
That's enough.
Look.
Stop it.
Wait a minute.
Look.
Mother's nipples are delicious.
Just a little more.
Look.
That's enough.
Stop it.
Ah
Hmm
Oh, it feels good
Ah
Ah, it feels good
I'm sorry.
Do you want more?
Yes, please.
Your mouth feels good.
Please give me more.
Yes, that's good.
That's good.
I can't stand it anymore.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
I want to put it in my mouth.
No, you can't.
It's a drug.
Please sleep here.
That's good.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm going to sleep.
Are you okay?
Let's take a bath.
This is fun.
Yes, it is.
Can I go in here?
Go ahead.
That's good.
It's been a while since we've been in the bath together.
I wanted to be in the bath with you.
What are you talking about?
You're funny.
Someone might come.
It's okay.
You don't have to worry.
I'm fine.
I love you.
You're getting stronger.
A little.
Are you having fun?
I'm going to cry.
If you cry...
If you cry, it's not good.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I want to go this way.
This way?
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Help me.
Don't look at me.
I'm sorry.
Be gentle.
I don't want to.
I'll give you a massage.
It's embarrassing.
I don't want to.
Just a little?
Just a little.
You can't stand it.
I don't want to.
You can't.
You can't do this in the hot spring.
I don't want to.
You can't.
It's a hot spring.
You can do this.
I'm fine because there are only two of us.
You're the only one.
Just a little.
I don't want to.
I'm tired of standing, so I'm going to sit here.
I want you to sit here.
It's just a little bit.
It's a little bit.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You like it while you sleep, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Over there.
Over there, too.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
It's warm.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
It's warm.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's warm.
It's hard to take off your clothes, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
But it feels good.
It feels good.
It's hard to take off your clothes, isn't it?
You're a troublesome boy.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
It's warm.
Do you want to take a bath here?
There is no one here.
This is a hot spring.
It's a little hot here, too.
But...
Please bear with me.
There is no one here.
I can't take a bath here.
Wait.
I see.
I'll just rub your body.
Do you understand?
If I rub your body,
Yes, I understand.
I can't rub your body.
I don't know.
You cannot go far.
I already know that.
You already know that?
wait.
Please wait.
Please don't go far.
No way.
Come here.
I said No way.
No! No!
Please don't
Don't put your feet in it yet
I told you that's enough
Really?
Are you a questioner?
I'm a questioner
Sorry I should have done it quickly
I'm sorry.
You tried to run away, didn't you?
I won't let you escape.
I'm sorry.
Try again.
That's it.
That's all.
I'm sorry.
I won't let you escape.
Hang in there.
You're a rabbit, aren't you?
I'm sorry.
I feel so good.
I won't let you escape.
I'm sorry.
Hang in there.
I feel so good.
I won't let you escape.
I'm sorry.
Hang in there.
I won't let you escape.
I'm sorry.
Hang in there.
I almost made it.
Mom.
Do you want me to get angry?
No.
Hang in there.
I can't sleep at all.
I'm sorry.
I want to sleep a little.
Hang in there.
I feel so good.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to get angry?
No.
Hang in there.
I feel so good.
But I don't have much time.
Someone might come.
Hang in there.
I feel so good.
I'm sorry.
Hang in there.
It's been a long time since I lashed out last.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm coming, mom.
It's okay.
Why did you leave me?
Because I couldn't stand it.
I'm hungry.
I'm sorry, mom.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to wash your body?
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
I have to clean your body.
It's a little weak there.
Do you feel good?
Wash your body a lot.
You've grown up.
You were small.
It's been a long time since I washed my body.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
Look at me.
It's okay.
It's amazing.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
I'm going to wash my hands, too.
Sit in front of me.
You're getting warmer.
I don't like the way I wash my hands.
It's amazing.
It's cold.
What should I do?
Tell me.
It's intense.
More?
Harder?
Your face?
Yes.
Is it warm?
It's warm.
Oh, it feels good.
It feels good.
You accept everything with your boobs.
Oh, it's amazing.
It smells good.
It's alive.
Let me see.
It's scary, isn't it?
Oh, it's amazing.
It flew over there.
It's amazing.
Oh, it came out a lot.
It's scary.
It's amazing.
Hey, I want to be with my mom again.
Yeah, let's do it once or twice.
But I don't know what will happen.
I'll love my mom for the rest of my life.
I love you.
Can I love you, too?
Yes.
I'll love you as a man.
Okay.
I love you.
I love your mom's yukata.
Do you want me to touch you?
Yes.
I love you.
It's beautiful.
It's my favorite place.
Do you like it here?
Yes.
Then I'll touch you a lot.
Is it still not enough?
It's hot.
It's amazing.
You like boobs, don't you?
Your boobs are beautiful.
Are you happy?
I'm not going to touch you anymore.
Your boobs are soft and comfortable.
I love you.
It's amazing.
It's comfortable.
Your boobs are soft and comfortable.
It's amazing.
I'll show you a lot.
I'll show you where your mom feels good.
It's amazing.
I'll touch you a lot.
Do you like this sound?
No.
It's amazing.
It's beautiful.
You feel good, don't you?
You can feel good a lot.
It's amazing.
I'm breathing.
I put a lot of water in it.
Do you care about it?
I care about it.
I'm happy.
It's amazing.
You're good.
I'll make you feel good.
It's amazing.
Don't tease me.
You can see it, can't you?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Do you let me go?
It's okay.
Pull me.
Am I the only one who is naked?
I'll give you this gadget.
I'm nervous.
Your neck is cute.
It's hard.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's getting hard.
It's sensitive.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
You're hyperactive.
It's because you're licking me like that.
It's really hard.
You almost peed all over.
Ah, it came out.
It's difficult, mom.
Hide it.
Does it feel good?
Wait.
You are amazing. You are energetic.
You have grown up so much.
You are amazing.
You are not supposed to do that on my panties.
I'm going to hide it.
No, that's...
It looks like it's going to break.
Are you going to take it out from here?
Boys take it out from here, right?
It feels good, mom.
It's good.
You are amazing.
It feels good.
It feels good?
It feels good, mom.
It's good.
Mom, can I lie down here?
Of course.
Look at me.
You are amazing.
I want to show it to you.
I can see it well.
Can you see it?
Yes.
I'm going to open it.
You are amazing.
It's embarrassing.
You have grown up so much.
I was more excited when I saw it.
You are amazing.
Can I touch you?
Of course.
You are amazing.
Let me take it out a lot.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
You are amazing.
Let me lick you.
Let me kiss you.
Your face is wet.
You are amazing.
Do you want me to kiss you?
I want you to kiss me more.
I want you to lick me.
You are amazing.
Does it feel good?
Let me kiss you.
Do you feel good?
I feel good when you lick me.
You like this, don't you?
Doesn't it feel good to kiss you like this?
But I want to put you in my mouth.
If you can stand it, I'll put it in your mouth.
Please bear with it.
Do you want to vomit?
No, I don't want to.
You want to vomit, don't you?
You want to vomit?
No, I don't want to.
You bullied me because I was cute.
Do you want to vomit that much?
I want to be one with you.
Do you?
Yes.
Do you want me to wipe your pussy?
Your pussy is very soft.
You licked my pussy a lot.
Do you want me to put it in your mouth?
Yes, I want you to put it in my mouth.
I want to put it in your mouth very much.
Your pussy looks very comfortable.
Do you want me to wipe your pussy?
Yes.
Do you want me to put it in your mouth?
Your pussy looks very comfortable.
It feels good.
Your pussy is very soft.
Let's clean your pussy.
You want to be one with me, don't you?
I want to be one with you.
That's enough, isn't it?
What do you want me to do?
Don't you want to be one with me?
It's okay.
I feel good here.
Akari, I feel good here.
I'm nervous.
Do you want to go deeper?
I want to go deeper.
Say it once.
I won't let you go deeper.
I want to go deeper, mom.
What should I do?
Please, mom.
I'm going to go deeper.
I went deeper.
I feel good here.
I want to go deeper.
I can't go deeper.
I'll hold it.
I feel good here.
I can't hold it.
Are you sick?
I'm not sick.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Do you feel good?
It's hard.
You love me, don't you?
I love you, mom.
I'll do my best.
You can do it.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
It's hard, isn't it?
Can you see it?
I can't hold it.
I feel good.
It's hard.
Do your best next time.
I can do it, mom.
It's hard.
You're moving by yourself.
I'm moving, aren't I?
I feel good.
It's hard.
Do your best.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's hard.
What do you want to do?
I want to hug you.
I'll do it.
Come here.
Can you see me?
I can see you well.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's amazing.
I'm so surprised.
Do you want to follow me?
Move your body.
Good job.
You can do it, right?
You can do it slowly.
Good job.
It feels good, doesn't it?
My neck is stiff.
It hurts.
It's in a good place.
Do you understand?
Do you remember where you feel good?
It's in a good place.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Can you move your body?
It's in a good place.
More.
Do you want to hug me?
It's okay.
Come here.
It's in a good place.
It feels good.
It's very wet.
It's amazing.
You can do whatever you want today.
Can I do it?
You can do it.
You can't do it yet.
Why?
Because it feels good.
It's intense.
It's a good place.
You can do whatever you want today.
It feels good.
I felt good, too.
I feel good, too.
It's refreshing.
I'm glad I was able to take a walk in the park with my family.
But they watch you and run away.
I hope this lawmakers plan can be that.
people help change Japan.
I hope this legislators plan can be that.
I'd like to stay one more night.
The police's delivery is today, right?
I won't be found out.
No, you're serious, right?
That's right.
Let's go home.
Let's go home and flirt.
I don't know if this is good.
But I've been pranked by Chosuke and pretended to sleep.
I may have wanted this to happen.
From now on, I will live as Chosuke and as a man and a woman.
Thank you for watching.