Next, I'm going to show you how to make a water gun.
First of all, I'm going to make a water gun.
I'm going to make a water gun.
First of all, I birthed a water gun.
Second, I'm going to make a water gun!
I made it in two steps!
It was made of screaming vodbie game.
Next, I'm going to make a water gun.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
What's your name?
My name is Abe.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Thank you very much.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Well...
I'd like to talk to you on the phone.
What should I do?
I'm sorry.
I can't talk to you on the phone.
I see.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
I didn't expect you to come.
I just wanted to talk to you.
That's right.
By the way...
We're really close.
I'm usually close to my part-time job.
It's like a business relationship.
But we're really close.
I see.
If you're a man, you'll understand.
But...
I'm sorry.
You know, there's a sense of distance.
Yes.
I see.
It's like an office.
That's right.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
I heard that you have a girlfriend.
No, I don't.
What kind of girl is she?
I haven't heard anything about her.
Is she a hairdresser?
No, she's just a part-time job.
She's a professional hairdresser.
I see.
It's been about two years.
Are you about 20 years old now?
Do you have a picture of her?
Do you want to see it?
Yes, I do.
If you have a picture of her, please show it to me.
Can I take a picture of you?
No, it's okay.
She's cute.
She looks modern.
By the way, what's her name?
Her name is Minami.
I see.
She looks like a modern girl.
That's right.
What kind of girl is she?
She's serious.
She's going to a vocational school in the future.
That's right.
She wants to be a professional hairdresser.
She's a professional hairdresser.
She's serious.
I see.
Is she a professional hairdresser?
No, she isn't.
I see.
She's a professional hairdresser, but she's still a professional hairdresser.
She's still a professional hairdresser.
I see.
Are you okay with that?
I think it's okay.
I think she's good at it.
I think she can do it.
I see.
Do you have a good relationship with her?
Yes, I do.
It's hard to do business alone.
I'm careful about it.
I'm also a manager and a part-time worker.
I think it's not bad to do business with her.
I see.
By the way, do you usually work with her?
She's here today.
I'll ask her later.
I don't want the camera to be exposed.
I'll ask her about herself.
Of course.
I think it's better for you to ask her before she comes.
I'll check the schedule and contact her later.
I'll check the schedule and contact her.
Are you going to do business with her?
Yes, I am.
Can I ask you a favor?
What do you want to do?
A haircut.
A haircut?
Yes.
Is a perm okay?
Yes, it's okay.
Thank you.
I've known her for a long time.
I see.
I'll ask her later.
Thank you.
I hope it goes well.
I'm looking forward to it.
She's coming.
Excuse me.
I'm Abe, a reserved customer.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Here you are.
Is this the place?
Yes, it is.
What should I do with the jacket?
Oh, I see.
Please put your luggage here.
Okay.
Thank you.
Please wait a moment.
Okay.
I'm going to change my clothes.
See you.
I'm ready.
How do I look?
I'm going to put a mask on your face.
You look cute.
I do.
This is the atmosphere.
Yes.
I'm going to take your jacket off.
Okay.
Thank you.
You look stylish.
Yes, I do.
Thank you.
Oh, as expected of Iwazutama.
I'm Minami, a part-time worker.
Yes, I'm Minami.
Nice to meet you.
Your hat is cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
Are you a part-time worker?
Yes, I'm a part-time worker.
I thought you were a hairdresser.
Is it long?
But I just got in.
Oh, really?
I just got in, but it's much tighter than the guy behind me.
Manager.
Aren't you a part-time worker?
No, I'm definitely not.
You're not a part-time worker, are you?
Are you okay?
Yes.
Cute, cute.
You have to take good care of it.
You're taking too good care of it.
That's right.
Are you a student now?
Yes, I'm going to a beauty school.
Oh, I see.
What about in the future?
I want to be a hairdresser in the future.
Do you want to get a job here?
Yes.
Oh, oh, oh.
I wonder if he'll go somewhere else.
Are you going somewhere else?
It's a little further away.
I see.
But the manager is handsome, too.
Oh, that's right.
Are you in Tokyo?
That's what it looks like.
I'm going to go home in time.
Oh, I see.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Is your job fun?
It's fun.
I'm pretty used to it.
Oh, I see.
Let's buy a small one for Yami-chan.
That's right.
It's a little rattling.
Hold it down a little more.
You're holding it down a lot.
Yami-chan, I'd like to ask you a favor.
Could you prepare a plate?
Yes, I did.
I want to make it a little thicker.
I think it's about 27 and 15.
Yes, please.
But if you're a student, you know how to do it to some extent, so it's easy and easy.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
It's fast to learn a job.
Hmm.
It's a little natural, but it's time to get a job.
Oh, I see.
This is good, too.
Hmm.
It's not perfect.
It's cute, so I think a lot of customers will come.
What do you think?
I can talk to you sometimes.
Oh, really?
Yes.
When I first came, you were a little bit of a fruit, weren't you?
I'm talking to you a little bit at the entrance.
You look popular.
It's fashionable.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No, I don't.
Oh, is that so?
Yes.
Is that okay?
Can I talk to the manager for a moment?
Do you have a boyfriend?
A little bit.
Oh, that's good.
You two get along well.
But it's really good.
If you have a cute voice, the atmosphere of the store will be brighter.
That's right.
What do you think, Mr. Abe?
Can I come here often?
Yes.
I always double the points.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Yes.
I'm going to record your face, so please take a look at that, too.
Thank you.
That's good.
That's really good.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes.
Can I put a hidden camera in the store later?
That's right.
I'm going to be under surveillance.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
That's good.
You two get along well.
You're teasing me.
You're cute.
I'll come here often.
Yes.
I'll be waiting for you.
Thank you very much.
Yes.
Shirakawa-san.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Yes.
Thank you for talking to me at my compliment.
Thank you very much.
What is it?
I'm sorry I met you today.
Here?
At this time?
I'm sorry I met you today.
You forget too much.
I'm sorry I met you.
Did you not like me?
I'm sorry to meet you.
Did you not use to hate me?
I didn't hate you.
I'm sorry I met you.
Where are you now?
This is the office.
Seriously?
I'm sorry.
Okay, I'll cut it off.
Let's meet again another time.
Great.
Who do I contact?
I'm sorry, I have to go.
I'll see you in my room.
Thank you for your hard work.
You wipe your hair with your clothes.
It feels so good.
Really?
Yes.
Isn't it fast?
It's fast, isn't it?
When you put your mouth in, it's like eating.
Maybe.
You look cool.
Thank you.
You look cute today.
Is my hair smooth?
Yes, it is.
Your hair is young.
I think you look young this morning.
Thank you.
Please turn around.
You look like a child.
You look like a child in a store.
Sound separate concierge
Purring
I sniff the pet ×1
I smell the pet ×2
I sniff the pet ×3
Danchu, it's time to kiss
lol
Do you like kisses?
yeah
Yeah? What else do you like?
All
lol
Who is it?
It's a secret.
I see.
It's a little hard.
Is it?
It's a secret, isn't it?
Yes.
It's hard.
I've closed it.
It's okay.
You've never done this before, have you?
No, I haven't.
It's a secret.
point key
It was okay
It's different from the video
Foot
I love you.
I love you, too.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
I'm embarrassed to do it.
This way.
Which way?
I'm embarrassed.
Why?
Do you feel embarrassed?
I'm embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed of you, too.
It's a little hard to see, but it looks like this.
I'm tired.
What should I do?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm hungry.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You look shy.
Do you want me to cover your face?
I'm okay.
Are you okay?
Let me see your face.
I'm okay.
You look shy.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Wait a minute.
Are you okay?
Are you fine?
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
Do you feel okay?
PUFF
It feels good
I'm sorry.
Do you have a cup of coffee?
What?
She has a little lip glow.
Don't you get it?
When I put on make-up,
You should put on a glass lipstick as well.
If I put on a lipstick as well,
Yes.
But it turned red in a minute.
It was a pleasant time.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Can I put it on?
Yes.
Do you like it from the back?
I don't think you put it on from the back.
Put it on.
Can you see it?
Do you like it?
Yes.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Is this OK?
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do with myself.
In this way, you can get rid of the tension in your muscles.
You can get rid of the tension in your muscles.
My head.
Feels good.
Why don't you show wonderful ability?
That's good.
You are singing so well.
Good boy.
Which one do you like?
This one.
Are you happy?
You are always cute.
You are hiding your eyes.
You are a good boy.
Excuse me.
Are you okay?
This is my first time.
Please sit here.
Thank you.
Are you done?
Yes, thank you.
I'm going to do something else today.
Is that so?
Is it okay if I cut your hair today?
Yes, please.
I'm going to make it look like a block.
You are going to make it look like a block?
Yes, I am.
Are you going to cut my hair?
Is the manager here?
Yes, he is.
Are you busy today?
Yes, I am.
I'm sorry.
Are you going to make a reservation?
I'm an assistant.
I can't cut your hair.
Is that so?
What do you do?
I wash my hair.
Do you shampoo your hair?
Yes, I do.
You are cute.
Thank you.
I'm going to call the manager.
Yes, please.
Nami.
Yes?
I'm in trouble.
I need you to stay close to me.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to call the manager.
You are cute.
You are cool.
What do you want?
I don't want anything.
You don't want anything?
I want you.
You are cute.
I'm happy.
You don't have to wait for me.
I don't have to wait for you.
I'll wait for you.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I want you to stay close to me.
You are cool.
It feels good just to stand in front of you.
You like my neck.
I'm sorry.
What are you using it for?
What are you going to do?
I'm embarrassed.
You are so cute.
Am I cute?
Yes, you are.
You don't let me go.
You will be a good wife.
Let me help you.
How far do you want me to help you?
All of them.
You used to do this when you were a student, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
I've never done this.
Really?
Okay.
I'm going to cut it with my left hand.
Dr. Anzai said so, didn't he?
Yes.
Okay.
Look at me.
I'm going to take care of your jaw.
Turn your head.
Okay.
Are you embarrassed?
Yes, I am.
You are embarrassed,
but you don't let me go.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Okay.
You are cute.
It feels so good.
You look good.
Are you embarrassed?
No, I'm not.
It feels so good.
Are you embarrassed?
No, I'm not.
I'm going to cut your mouth.
Are you okay?
Okay.
Are you tired?
I'm not just talking to you.
I'm licking your nipples.
Okay.
It feels so good.
I'm licking your nipples.
You are sexy.
I'm going to lick your lips.
It feels so good.
I'm licking your lips gently.
Tell me you like my nipples.
Tell me you like my nipples more than my manager.
You like my nipples.
Do you like my nipples?
Okay.
The sofa was made by the cafe, very beautiful.
The silk of the rug is adorable.
He talks in a rude tone.
If you make a mistake with soft wood, Mоны would be angry too,
so I appreciate being transparent till the end,
She had never wet her wand on icaid before this session.
And..
She has an amazing sense of smell.
Mom, is slipper rubber?
What?
How do you wear a skirt?
Button?
I want you to take off half of your skirt and wear it with your butt out.
Huh? Isn't it too much?
One eye
Only the butt
There
You look like you want to fight today.
Good
You can do it with your mouth only.
Oh, good.
Back view
Good
Very good
Oh
It's a little uncomfortable.
I'm going to lie down.
Oh, no.
I'm going to throw up.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
I put it out of my mouth.
Oh, my God.
I'll do it for you.
I have to go to the bathroom.
I'm in trouble.
I'm not listening.
Can I clean up the rest?
Yes
Oh, my God.
I'm in a lot of pain.
Are you in a hurry?
No, I'm not.
I want you to do it.
I'll do it.
Oh, my God.
Good morning.
The manager is not here.
He's on a break.
I'll do it.
Can I wait?
Yes, please wait a minute.
I'll do it.
Oh, my God.
It's been a while.
I didn't expect to see you here.
Do you also use this place?
Yes, I do.
Really?
It's been a while.
Are you wearing makeup?
Yes, I am.
You look cute today.
You look fashionable today.
Are you going on a date?
No, I'm not.
I bought a new dress.
You look fashionable.
How are you today?
I'm fine.
You look fashionable.
I'm wearing makeup.
Did you have a boyfriend?
No, I didn't.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No, I don't.
I'm sad to hear that you have a boyfriend.
You are popular, aren't you?
I don't know.
I see.
Did you have a boyfriend?
No, I didn't.
Really?
Do you have a problem at work?
No, I don't.
You look fine.
I have a secret hobby.
Do you live with your boss?
No, I don't.
Do you have a boyfriend?
You look like a good friend.
I thought you had a boyfriend.
You look popular.
What kind of person are you?
You look like a playful person.
You have a lot of people.
I have a lot of people.
You look depressed.
You have a lot of people.
You are like that?
I am like that.
I don't know whether you were like that before or not.
I see.
I think you like him, don't you?
You look depressed.
She is popular. She is popular.
She has a beauty salon with that look.
Well, well, well, well.
She said yes.
I was too sure.
Is it okay as usual today?
Yes.
Please tell her that.
I have a day off today.
Oh, you have a day off.
Oh, that's why you are not energetic.
I'm sorry.
It's okay because you have a job.
Thank you very much.
She was listening to me a lot.
I think she can go home soon.
Let's push her.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
What do you do on your day off?
I sleep on my day off.
I get tired.
I see.
Do you practice after that?
I practice and go home, so I sleep.
I'm relaxing.
I see.
Is it here?
Yes.
It's raining.
Thank you very much.
May I sit here?
Yes, please.
Thank you.
6th day
Thank you
So cute
I think we should bring down the temperature
Are you concerning...?
I'm going to add a little bit of red food coloring to make it look like a real flower.
Nothing to do here?
No
Nothing to do...
Then I'm leaving
No
Ok
I can't believe I'm doing this.
I'm saying this.
I can't do it...
It feels so good...
Do you know where the manager is?
Huh?
That's not good...
I can't do it...
It feels so good...
My hands are shaking...
I can't do it...
Can I do it one more time?
It feels so good...
I'm fine.
You're wet.
Do you care about the shower?
I do.
Do you?
Do you like the shower?
Yes, I do.
I'm fine.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or a bad idea, but I think it's a good idea.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or a bad idea.
I don't think it's a good idea.
Can I take this?
You are taking a video, aren't you?
What are you going to do?
I'll show you later.
You are so dirty.
You've been left behind by the manager.
You are moving a lot.
You are cute.
By the way,
Could you wear this hood?
You are moving a lot.
More ...
Put it on.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
Your body is soft.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry..
I'm sorry.
Wow...
She starts to run.
I don't know what to do with myself, but I can't help but cry when I think about it.
I don't know what to do with myself, but I can't help but cry when I think about it!
I don't know what to say.
Because I was going to eventually put videos on.
So I'm pretty confident with mine but I was still seem to doubt myself
until I saw that others were putting up video but it was hilarious.
It was really funny and I'm proud of you.
Oh, my God.
Coco, let's give this to the manager.