8 years after Oस
Lately, most of our songs are released
Is it like a resale?
It's like...
What's this called?
Hommage?
Hey, Yashino!
Yes?
Do you have any taping?
I'm sorry.
I don't have any.
See? You have to go buy it.
You can ask your manager.
But you can't make Takeuchi worry.
Huh? Who's going to worry about you?
Shut up.
Don't be late.
Yes, sir.
Takeuchi-senpai, huh?
I'm sorry, Kebuno-senpai.
Do you...
have sex, too?
I...
I'm pretty confident about it.
Do you want to try it?
No...
If you do it now,
I don't think anyone will come.
What are you talking about?
No, I'm serious.
I'm sure it'll feel good.
It's close.
Let's calm down.
Are you...
a virgin?
Huh?
You're interested...
in sex, right?
Do you...
masturbate?
I'll make your pussy...
really soft.
Ah...
Touch me.
Please.
Takeuchi-senpai.
You're cute.
It's hot.
It's sour.
I'll make you feel good.
It's hot.
It's okay.
Do you feel good?
No.
It's hot.
You feel good, right?
You're weak.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
You're amazing.
You're big.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
You're amazing.
Senpai.
You're sweating a lot.
I could feel it.
You don't have to put up with it.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
You're sweating a lot.
It's hot.
You don't have to put up with it.
Senpai.
Please wait.
It's hot.
I was just doing my club activities.
It's dirty.
It's not dirty.
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
Please sit here.
It's hot.
Senpai.
I'll take off your bra.
Senpai's manko.
It's overflowing.
It's hot.
It's okay.
I'll make you feel better.
It's hot.
Please wait.
Please hold my legs.
I can't.
It's overflowing.
It's hot.
I can't.
I'll put it in.
Wait.
This is...
I think it's better to date properly.
I...
I've always...
I've always liked you.
Now...
Even if I say this...
You might not believe me.
But I really...
I really like you.
If you don't mind...
Would you go out with me?
Really?
I did it.
Cheers.
Then...
I'll put it in.
Hey, Miyashiro.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
How's your cramp?
Sweat...
What? Were you sleeping?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Hey, did you see Takeuchi?
No.
Takeuchi, Takeuchi...
Kato, you don't like Takeuchi, do you?
No.
Yoshino, prepare for the morning exercise.
Yes.
Do it properly.
Yes, I'll do it.
Let's go.
Yes.
I'll put it in.
What's wrong?
Didn't you hear a voice?
A voice? Whose voice?
Takeuchi's voice.
Hey, hey.
Shut up.
I felt like I heard something.
Let's go.
I'm tired.
Ah...
Your cramp...
It feels so good.
Ah...
I'm sorry.
I'm happy to be with you.
Do you feel good here?
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
Come here.
Hang in there.
I told you I'd make you feel good.
Do you feel good here?
I feel good.
Hang in there.
I told you I'd make you feel good.
I can't.
What's wrong?
Hang in there.
I can't.
I sweat a lot and eat pork.
You do.
It's not salty enough.
That's why I feel so good.
I see.
What's going on?
Who are you?
I'm from the baseball club.
Something's fishy.
What is?
I don't know.
It's not easy.
The class is about to start.
Hey, Kato.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
Okay.
Excuse me.
I'm going to buy something to drink.
It's a lab.
There are a lot of labs around here.
Do those couples go to the lab?
It's nice.
Takeuchi?
Who is the man next to you?
What are you talking about?
Sorry.
Again?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Let's go over there.
Why?
There was something.
Hey.
Kato.
I'm sorry.
I want to go to another place.
May I?
What?
I want to go to another place.
It's about five minutes from here.
Okay.
Let's go.
There are good things here.
It feels good.
Here.
It's good.
It's great that you are my girlfriend.
You know where I'm weak.
I'm weak there.
Eat more.
Here?
Yes.
Try to lick it.
Like this?
Yes.
It's good.
It feels good.
Do you want to talk that much?
No.
It's good.
Try to lick it.
It's cold.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's great.
It's good.
It's cold.
Take it off.
Then.
Push it up.
Like this?
Yes.
It's brown.
Do what you want to do.
What's that?
Try to lick it.
I've never done that.
It's good.
You have a lot of experience.
What's wrong?
It's cold.
Kimchi?
Give me a kiss.
Give me a lot.
Like this.
Ah.
Try to put it on your chest.
Like this?
Does it feel good?
You feel good, too.
Yes.
You can use it as much as you want.
What's that?
You can't put it on your chest.
I can't.
Ah.
Try to put it on your chest.
What?
There?
There.
Ah.
If you have a big boob, you can put it on your chest.
Like this?
Yes.
And?
Like this.
Move it as you hold it.
Like this?
Yes.
You're good.
Ah.
Does it really fit?
It fits.
Ah.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Does it feel good on your boobs, too?
Ah.
Can I lick it at the same time?
What's that?
I'll try it.
This is crazy.
How is it?
This feels really good.
Really?
Ah.
You're crazy.
Eh?
Is this crazy?
Ah.
This feels so good.
I'm going to puke.
Ah.
Eh?
Can you hold still?
I feel like I'm going to puke.
Really?
Ah.
Keep going.
This feels good.
Ah.
You're getting big.
This feels good.
Ah.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
It's getting really hard.
I think I can do it.
You can do it?
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
You're so surprised.
You're so cute.
Oh, my God.
Let's do a lot more.
But
You made me feel so good.
I'll do it for you this time.
What?
You like it, don't you?
Yeah.
Oh.
That
Oh, my god.
Ah!
Does it feel good?
Is there anything you want me to lick?
Ah!
I'm
embarrassed.
If you don't tell me,
I'll keep licking your neck.
Ah!
Is it painful?
I want you to
lick my neck
and
touch my
lower body.
Ah!
It's okay, it's okay.
Put your finger inside.
It's hot.
Do you want more?
It feels good.
It's hot.
I love you.
How about this?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Help me.
It's amazing.
You're frowning.
What is this?
You liked this when you first touched it.
It feels good.
What is this?
Do you want to drink this?
It's amazing.
What should I do?
Look over there.
I'm going to lick you.
Lean on me.
Lick me.
It's amazing.
I can't lick you.
I'm going to lick you.
It's amazing.
You really like physical things.
What is that?
You can do anything I tell you to do.
You really want to do a lot of things, don't you?
How is it?
I'm going to lie on you.
It feels good.
You're frowning.
I can't do this.
I can't do this anymore.
You're frowning.
What do you want me to do?
What should I do?
If you don't tell me what you want me to do, I won't do it.
I want you to do it.
Where do you want me to do it?
I want you to do it here.
Here?
Spread your legs.
I can't do this.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm going to do it.
You're frowning.
I'm embarrassed.
I can't do this.
Spread your legs.
It feels good.
It's connected.
I can't do this.
You're frowning.
It feels good.
I'm embarrassed.
Let's rub our backs together.
I can't do this.
I'm embarrassed.
It feels good.
I can't do this.
Can I rub your back?
Senpai.
I like you.
Can you rub my back?
Don't tease me.
Don't do that.
It feels good.
I can't do this.
I'm embarrassed.
Wait a minute.
I found a good point.
You're lying.
It feels good.
I can't do this.
You're my junior.
You have to rub my back.
It feels good.
I can't do this.
I found a good point.
Senpai.
You're a sensitive girl.
I'm not.
Why don't you apologize to me?
I don't want to.
Don't tease me.
I'll rub your back again.
I can't do this.
It feels good.
Don't rub my back.
I can't do this.
It feels good.
I'm glad I'm with you.
It's hot.
I like it here.
I can't do this.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can't do this.
It's the best.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Are you going to lick me?
Will you lick me?
I can't do this.
You were very sexy.
I have an idea.
Let's do this at school.
What?
At school?
Will you give me a arm pillow?
Come here.
Sit here.
What's wrong with this?
I brought this from the club room.
It's noisy on the desk.
Is it noisy?
I can't do this.
What if someone comes here?
Don't worry.
It's past school time.
What if the teacher comes here?
The classroom door is closed.
No one will come here.
In this classroom?
I can't do this.
You are cute.
Don't worry.
Isn't it exciting to do this in the classroom?
What if someone comes here?
I can't do this.
But...
Let's do this together.
I can't see anything.
What if someone sees us?
I can't do this.
You are looking forward to it, aren't you?
I don't care.
I can't do this.
I'm nervous.
What if someone comes here?
I can hear your heart beating.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to sleep.
I can't do this.
Don't worry.
If someone comes here, I'll take responsibility.
I can't do this.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm embarrassed.
I can't do this.
You are cute.
What if someone comes here?
I'm embarrassed.
I can't do this.
You are cute.
You are a senior.
You can feel it.
What is this?
That's...
I can't do this.
If you don't like it, you can't do this.
You are a senior.
You can feel it.
I can't do this.
Let me see.
Let me open your legs.
I can't do this.
Don't look at me.
Do you feel good here?
I can't do this.
This is school.
It's messy.
I'll clean it up.
I can't do this.
Are you still embarrassed?
I'm excited.
I can't do this.
You wanted to do this, didn't you?
No.
I licked you.
I can't do this.
Do you like this?
This is your breast.
You can do this.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I can't do this.
Let's do it in the classroom.
It's okay.
I can't do this.
I'm locking the door.
If someone comes, let's do it.
We're doing something bad.
I can't do this.
You can move as you like.
You like this, don't you?
I can't do this.
You can move as you like.
Let's move together.
I can't do this.
Your hands are wet.
Let's do something thrilling.
Something thrilling?
Stand up.
I can't do this.
Stand over there.
I can't see anything.
The people on the ground are running over there.
They might see us.
That's interesting.
I can't do this.
My hands are cold.
Ouch!
I'm sorry. I was too violent.
Senpai, can you be more violent?
I can't speak.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
I can't speak.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
You like me, don't you?
Look at me.
I can't speak.
Can I hug you?
Yes.
Hug me.
I'll hug you.
What?
What's this?
Senpai.
This is your salt.
Don't look at me.
You can hear me, can't you?
I'm sorry.
I can't speak.
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-
huh,
uh,
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
how can R
our
huh
how
Uh
I don't feel good.
Scared.
I can't do this.
I don't feel good.
I'm feeling sick.
I can't feel...
Oh, dear.
It was her fault!
It was all Maria Kira's fault.
Nobody blamed me...
I was an ignorant daughter.
I was so young, I had no merit...
but to do something like this...
Ah, it's so hot.
Ah, I see.
Ah, it feels so good.
It's the best.
Niiyama, Iida, and Takeuchi-senpai.
Ah, it's the best.
Oh, it's just a dream.
Oh, you're up.
Good morning.
You slept too much.
I was hungry.
What did you eat?
Did you eat something?
You were shaking a lot just now.
Did you have a dream?
Ah, I had a dream when I was a student.
My memory was messed up.
I don't like it when you sleep on your own.
That's right.
Make yourself comfortable.
It's the best.