I'm sorry for the sudden business trip.
No, no.
It's a big contract, so I have to go right away.
It's your long-cherished dream of opening a small business.
Congratulations.
No, I can't let my guard down until the end.
As expected, it's good that you don't let your guard down.
I'm sorry.
You should learn from Yuki.
Yes.
Well, I'm going.
See you later.
Yuki, don't pull my leg.
Yes.
I can't rely on you.
I'm going.
See you later.
Thank you for your time today.
Thank you for your perfect guidance.
You don't have to thank me.
I'll sign any contract with you.
No, no.
You have a good personality.
Thank you very much.
Can you go this way?
Yes, I'll stop.
Then, enjoy Osaka.
Thank you very much.
Then, we'll go.
Take care.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
See you later.
Take care.
It's over.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's over earlier than I expected.
Yes.
What time is the check-in?
It's at 6 p.m.
It's early.
It's 6 p.m.
I have some time.
I want to drink beer.
Do you want to have dinner?
Okay.
Let's have dinner.
Did you get a room today?
I'm fine.
You're making fun of me.
I can't hear you.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Then, let's drink beer.
Okay.
Cheers!
You're a heavy drinker.
I'm sad.
You don't drink much, do you?
I get sick easily.
What are you talking about?
I want you to go out with me today.
Okay.
What do you do when you get drunk?
When I get drunk...
I lose my memory.
Well, I get cheerful.
Drink up.
I'm going to order some more.
Isn't it too early?
Are you okay?
I did my best.
You did.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
You can't go in there.
Go in there by yourself.
Are you okay?
No, you can't go in there.
You can't go in there.
It's dangerous.
Please open the door.
Kiss me.
Are you really okay?
It's dangerous.
What are you doing?
You can't go in there.
Are you okay?
Get up.
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
You can't go in there.
Double means two rooms.
I'm sorry.
You idiot.
It's dangerous.
Are you okay?
You idiot.
Double means one room.
You're weird.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Senpai.
Senpai, you can't go in there.
You can't go in there.
You wanted to share a room with me, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
You're lying again.
I'm not lying.
You're lying.
It's delicious.
Tell me the truth.
No, I can't.
I can't.
Then tell me the truth.
No, I can't.
I can't.
Tell me the truth.
What did you think?
No, not that.
I thought it was 2 rooms.
Are you trying to lie again?
I thought it was 2, so I was wrong.
You're lying.
I made a mistake. I have to clean up.
Um, um, it's okay. I'll do it myself.
Why?
I knew it. You're up to something.
Do you want to play with me?
What's that?
Meow.
Do you want to play with me?
What's that?
If you keep talking, I'll break your teeth.
I'm sorry.
Can you be quiet and look at me?
Can I?
Yes, yes, yes.
Meow, meow.
Kiss, kiss.
Meow.
How many bottles of beer did I drink?
I don't remember.
You don't remember?
No.
There's too much alcohol in the first place.
I can't drink it all.
Did you drink it all?
No, it's over there.
It's going to fall. It's going to fall.
It's dangerous.
Help me.
I'm sleepy.
It's hot, isn't it?
I understand.
I'll take it off.
Yes, yes, yes.
When did you start planning to share a room with me?
No, it's really different.
What?
It's really different.
Then try it.
What?
Meow.
There's only 2,000 bottles left.
There's no more.
I'm sorry.
I don't usually reserve a hotel room.
Your lips are soft and pleasant.
Is that so?
Yes.
It's sour.
I can't do it anymore.
It's coming to an end.
What should I do?
I can't do it anymore.
My lips feel good, don't they?
Let's go to hell.
It's getting hot.
Why are you saying it's getting hot?
Yukiko.
Yes, yes.
Yukiko is getting hot, too.
It's hot.
That's not good.
You did your best.
I'm sorry.
Your body is hot.
No, it's not.
It's hot.
You don't like it?
I don't like it.
It's not that I don't like it.
It's a problem.
You have a beautiful body.
That's not true.
Well, then...
It's hot.
It's not that I don't like it.
What is it?
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
Do you feel it?
It's cute.
No, it's not that I don't like it.
It's hot.
Be honest.
Yukiko.
I'm sorry.
You did your best.
It's not that I don't like it.
Be honest.
You did your best at work.
You were going to pretend to be a doll, weren't you?
No, I wasn't.
It's a misunderstanding.
Why are you reacting like this?
I can't do that.
Come on.
Wait a minute.
How are you feeling?
How am I feeling?
What is it, Yukiko?
You're acting strange.
I'm not.
It's hot, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
Let me hug you seriously.
Thank you so much.
It's hot, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
What's the matter?
Let me sleep.
Can't you hear me?
That's not fair.
It's hot, isn't it?
Let me sleep.
I understand.
It's hot, isn't it?
I took off your clothes.
What's wrong with you?
I have to take off your clothes.
I understand.
How do you feel?
You were imagining that you would sleep with me, weren't you?
No, I wasn't.
Then, do as you imagined.
Kiss me.
Kimchi?
Do you feel good?
You feel good, don't you?
You're cute.
Then, I'll sleep more.
I'm sweating.
You don't have to act like that anymore.
You're so honest.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you so stiff?
That's because you're sitting there.
You're so stubborn.
You're cute.
Let me see.
You're so manly.
It's dangerous.
Nice to meet you.
How do you feel now?
It's dangerous to touch you.
Do you feel good?
Let me kiss you.
Do you feel better?
I'm going to die.
I'm sorry.
I want to do it more.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's dangerous.
Do you feel good?
Your hips are moving.
You're so energetic.
You don't like me that much.
Do you feel good?
I'm sorry.
You should eat something.
Am I a bad person?
You wanted to eat, didn't you?
You don't like me that much.
I'm sorry.
You have to make me feel better.
Here?
More.
Move this.
Yes.
I want to sing more manly.
You can't?
I'm sorry.
You're cute when you're like this.
That's how you do it.
Are you more embarrassed because I'm not your senpai?
I don't know.
I'm sleepy.
Lick me.
Here, too.
Yes.
Lick me.
Like this?
More.
More?
It's hot.
It tickles.
You...
Was that okay?
Here.
Did I do a good job?
Um...
Look at me.
Okay.
It's dangerous.
It's going in.
It's going in?
Wait.
Senpai.
It's going in.
Um...
I didn't put on any rubber.
Shut up.
It's dangerous.
It's going in.
Senpai.
It tickles.
I didn't put on any rubber.
Senpai.
It tickles.
Um...
Can you listen to me?
If you make a noise, I'll kiss you.
It's tickling, isn't it?
That's true.
I didn't put on any rubber.
Senpai, can you listen to me?
It tickles.
Wait.
I didn't put on any rubber.
Senpai.
It tickles.
Wait.
It tickles and it feels good.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, right?
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't do that.
Give me a pat.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's getting harder and harder.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I'm here.
It's hot.
Hey, hey.
Stop it.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I'll give you a special massage.
Look at me.
It feels good.
You said you wanted to give me a massage.
It's amazing.
It's hard.
Make it harder.
It feels good.
Here.
You said you wanted to give me a massage.
It's hot.
Did you drink it?
I drank it.
You drank it.
I'll give you another one.
It feels good.
Make it harder.
Don't move.
It feels good.
It's hard.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's hard.
What's wrong?
Senpai.
I'm so hot.
I feel sick.
Senpai.
I want to go out.
What do you want to do?
What should I do?
Please tell me the truth.
Te-chan!
Te-chan, it's me, Sora.
I'm so tired.
Te-chan...
Can I go to sleep?
Let me out.
What?
No, Te-chan.
Let me out.
I'm so tired.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
Let me out.
I feel like I'm sleeping.
It's warm, isn't it, Te-chan?
Yes.
Did you let me out?
I'm sorry.
Did it feel that good?
Yes, very.
Let's do it again.
What?
One more time.
Let me out.
I want to...
I want to shower.
Let me get some rest.
Rest?
Yes, shower.
Let me rest.
Let's take a shower.
Shower?
Let's pee in the shower.
Let's pee.
Let's take a shower first.
Hmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
It's early morning, but I wonder if Haru-chan is awake...
What?
bad feeling
What was?
I feel sick
What?
Let me dance
I'm shy
It's embarrassing.
I'm taking a bath.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No, I don't.
What kind of girl do you like?
Do you have a girlfriend?
No, I don't.
I can see it on your face.
What is it?
You're drunk.
You're drunk, so you're not drunk at all.
Are you sick?
No, I'm not.
Are you drunk, so you're not drunk at all.
I bought a glass of sake.
Do you still drink?
Are you okay?
I'm still very drunk.
Yes.
I'm very drunk.
I want to go home.
Are you really drunk?
No, I'm not.
Then why are you so drunk?
I'm not drunk.
You are drunk.
You are very drunk.
I tell you, I'm very drunk.
I've told you, senpai.
See what you've done.
You are very drunk.
Oh, it hurts.
It's still warm.
Thank you.
Do you like bigger boobs?
What do you think?
Well...
What do you think of my boobs?
I like them very much.
Do you like them?
Yes.
Open your butt.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
When do you cry?
What?
Do you cry a lot?
No, I don't.
What?
I've never seen you cry.
I'll wipe your butt.
Yes.
Let's eat.
Wow.
You've got a pimple in your butt.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
What?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's hot.
You don't think about it, do you?
No, I don't.
I don't think you think about it.
I'm sorry.
Do you keep it a secret?
No, I don't.
What?
I don't.
You don't, do you?
No, I don't.
It's hot.
You're getting better.
More.
What?
Wow.
It's hot.
Doesn't it feel good?
Let me wipe it for you.
Yes, please.
No.
Let me wipe your butt.
Wow.
It's coming out.
Ouch.
You are funny.
I don't like it.
I don't like it at all.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
You said you didn't like it.
I feel good.
You're bad.
Can you eat it?
Yes, I can.
My nose is cold.
I'm sorry.
You're bad.
I don't like it.
You like them so much.
It's 6 p.m.
Because of you.
If you make me a senpai, I'm going to cry.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
Ouch!
You're annoying.
Are you okay?
It feels good.
What are you talking about?
You're annoying.
Ouch!
What are you doing?
Oh!
Oh, excuse me.
Let me go now!
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
So much.
I told you not to do it.
I've been doing it for a long time.
What?
It's disgusting.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Ouch!
It's hot, isn't it?
What?
Have you cut the hair?
I haven't.
I'm sorry.
Is it heavy?
It's light.
You're lying.
No, it's really light.
Really?
Is it light?
Yes, it is.
I can't see anything.
Are you okay?
Really?
It's heavy, isn't it?
Stop it.
Are you okay to drink that much?
Are you okay?
It's boring.
I can't drink that much.
You're a normal person.
Don't you feel like that?
I don't drink that much.
You'll feel sick.
That's right.
You're cute.
Don't you feel sick?
I'll feel sick before that.
Then you should feel sick today.
See?
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
Do you like sweets?
Yes, I do.
Do you want to eat chocolate?
I don't care.
I can't help it.
You're cute.
Here you are.
I'll eat it.
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
You have chocolate on your face.
You have a thick chocolate.
Do you think so?
Do you feel sick?
Yes, I do.
I feel sick.
Have you ever played a party game?
No, it's my first time.
It wasn't a game at all.
Thank you.
You seem to feel better soon.
I am regretful to see that.
It's good that you feel better
You're right.
I've been doing this for a long time.
Did you notice?
I noticed.
Yes.
Are you really okay?
When was the last time you had a girlfriend?
Well...
It was a long time ago.
What?
Why did you break up?
I don't know why.
You have to be more manly.
I'm sorry.
You are more manly than I thought.
What is this?
It's so tight.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
How many times did you take a bath?
I didn't take a bath.
I told you not to take a bath.
Why are you so attractive?
You are very beautiful.
Really?
Yes.
I'm scared.
I don't think you noticed.
Is that so?
I don't know.
You get better quickly.
Is that so?
You are attractive.
Your body is smooth.
I don't have enough alcohol.
Are you really okay?
You can be more manly.
Really?
Do you mean me?
Yes.
I don't remember you.
You can be more honest.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
You look cold.
No, I'm not.
You keep saying no.
I feel good.
You are happy.
Yes.
You can be happier.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I do.
You are still fine even though I gave you a bath.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
I'm embarrassed.
Why?
I saw your cuteness.
I'm sorry.
I want to give you a kiss.
Wait a minute.
Have you ever been licked?
No, I haven't.
I'll give you a kiss.
I feel good.
Say it again.
You feel good?
Yes.
I feel good.
You look relaxed.
Did you feel good?
Yes.
I feel good.
You are a technician.
Yes, I am.
I'm happy that you feel good.
I feel good.
Touch there.
Okay.
I feel good.
Touch there.
You are very relaxed.
I feel good.
I want to be more relaxed.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
I want to be more relaxed.
I feel good.
It hurts.
I can't bear it.
You can't bear it?
I can't bear it, but I want to have one more bite.
Is it good?
I think you are drunk.
Maybe.
I can't bear it.
I feel good.
Don't move.
Don't move?
Did you move?
Don't move.
Does it hurt?
I feel good.
I can't bear it.
It hurts.
I feel good.
I can't bear it.
Here.
It hurts.
I feel good.
I can't bear it.
Next.
I'll drink this and move.
Drink it?
I feel like a spiderman.
You're like a spiderman.
I'll put it in your mouth.
Look.
I'll look at your butt closely.
I feel good.
It's harder than before, isn't it?
Do you like my butt?
Senpai.
Don't hit me.
I'm not a spiderman.
Senpai's butt is beautiful.
I feel good.
Can I hit you harder?
Oh, no.
I feel good.
It hurts.
I'll do it.
I feel good.
I can't stop.
What?
I feel good.
Senpai.
I'll do it.
I'll do it again.
I feel good.
Oh, no.
Bye.
Matsui Yuki, you are amazing.
I feel good.
What's wrong?
Look at this!
You got all over me.
How many times did you do it today?
How many times?
I told you not to tell me.
You did it too much.
You did it too much?
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
You did it too much.
Drink it after you do it.
You're getting harder.
I got it.
You should drink it too.
Can I?
Use your strength.
You're getting harder.
You can do it, right?
Not yet.
Not yet?
You did a good job.
You can do it.
This is a peach cookie.
Peach cookie.
It's getting bigger.
You can still do it.
You did a good job.
It's hard.
It's hot.
You're getting a massage.
I'm sorry if you get a massage on your butt.
I can't.
I'm sensitive.
I can't get down even if I want to.
Slowly.
It feels good.
Can I do it more?
You're getting harder.
Does it hurt?
It feels good, right?
It feels good.
Here.
It feels good here.
It feels good.
It hurts here.
Let's go.
Over there.
What?
It feels good.
Stand up properly.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It hurts here.
I'm sorry.
I can't. It feels good.
It'll come out.
It feels good here.
I can't.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Wait.
Yusuke-kun.
Yes?
You drank all the alcohol.
I'm sorry.
I didn't say it's okay.
You drank too much.
It's my fault.
No, it's not.
It's not my fault, is it?
No.
How many shots did you take today?
I don't know.
That's amazing.
But you can still do it.
You can do it.
You're amazing.
You're still so energetic.
You're amazing, Yusuke-kun.
You're tired from standing, aren't you?
Yes.
I'm going to sleep.
I can't.
I'm tired.
I'm going to sleep.
Don't move.
Don't move until I say it's okay.
But I don't know if I can bear it.
Bear it.
It feels so good.
Don't move.
Don't move until I say it's okay.
Okay?
Okay.
It feels so good.
I have to bear it.
I can't.
I'm going to go.
I'm stronger than a plastic surgery.
I can move my hips only.
It feels so good.
Yuki's favorite butt.
You like it, don't you?
Yes.
Which one do you like?
I like both.
I'm greedy, too.
I'm sorry.
It feels so good.
I can't decide.
I can't decide which one I like.
It feels so good.
I can't decide.
Yuki.
Don't do that.
Okay.
It feels so good.
It hurts.
I can't drink it.
It feels so good.
I've done it so many times.
I'm so tired.
I can't drink it.
It feels so good.
I can't move my legs.
Don't do that.
It feels so good.
I can't move my legs.
I can't drink it.
It hurts.
Yuki.
Yes?
You've stopped drinking, haven't you?
I don't think so.
Does that mean you can drink more?
No, I don't think so.
But I think I can drink with you.
I'm sweating.
It's hard again.
I think I'm going to get serious.
Are you serious?
I don't think I can drink that much.
Don't do that.
It's harder than before.
It feels so good.
Don't do that.
I can't do that.
I'm sweating.
It feels so good.
I can't do that.
cold
At 5th floor
there is all
not here
You do not want me
5th floor
Ouch!
It's so hot.
I'm sweating a lot.
Please wait a minute.
It's time to check out.
Check out?
Don't say that.
It's not over yet.
I have to do it.
Don't say that.
What time is it?
It's morning.
Is it over?
I have to do it.
It's cold.
You can't do it anymore?
Tell me which one is which.
Which one?
Can you do it if you have time?
That's not fair.
I can't cheer you up forever.
Are you really drunk?
I'm drunk.
You're so energetic.
If you do this to me, I'll be energetic.
You'll be energetic?
If I do this to you?
You don't care about time, do you?
It's not over yet.
You're amazing.
I'm drunk.
Are you okay?
Are you really okay?
You're doing it again.
You still want to do it, don't you?
Yes, I do.
You're amazing.
You're my senior.
You're getting bigger.
Will you leave me alone?
I'll be your senior.
I'm sorry.
I'm not good enough yet.
Kiku.
Yes?
This isn't a morning exercise, is it?
No, it isn't.
Which one is it?
Tell me.
You're my senior.
You're amazing.
I'm getting bigger every time I exercise.
I don't know.
Stop it.
I don't know anymore.
It's your fault.
Yes.
Stop it.
It feels good.
I'm going to do it.
Stop it.
It feels good.
My waist is moving.
Stop it.
It feels good.
I'm getting bigger.
I'm going to do it again.
Stop it.
I'm getting full.
You're going to check out, right?
Yes.
It's over.
Are you still going to do it?
I'm getting bigger again.
It feels good.
What's wrong?
I'm getting bigger.
I'm going to check out when I'm done.
I'm not going to do it.
It's over.
It feels good.
I'm getting full.
It's over.
Stop it.
I'm getting bigger.
It's over.
I'm going to check out when I'm done.
You were crying.
I was.
You've been crying.
Yes.
It's over.
It's not over yet.
I'm getting bigger again.
It's over.
Please sit down.
I'm getting bigger.
It's over.
It feels good.
I can't stop it.
Stop it.
It's over.
It's not over yet.
Stop it.
It's over.
It's not over yet.
I'm getting bigger.
Stop it.
It feels good.
It's over.
It's not over yet.
Stop it.
It's not over yet?
It's not over yet.
More.
More?
Please subscribe to my channel.