My name is Takeshi. I'm a 20-year-old college student.
And this beautiful lady is my mother.
Why do we have to go on a trip together?
I can't help it. My father suddenly got a job.
I hope I can get along with Takeshi a little bit on this trip.
My father got married to this woman who is 15 years older than me.
I can't call this woman who is older than me as my mother.
Takeshi.
My father is a very busy man.
That's why I feel lonely.
Look at this.
Oh, I touched it.
I didn't know there was such a power spot.
What is she thinking about last night?
Do you want me to kiss you?
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
Let's go on a trip together when my father is gone.
A few days later.
My name is Takeshi. I'm a 20-year-old college student.
And this beautiful lady is my mother.
Why do we have to go on a trip together?
I can't help it. My father suddenly got a job.
Takeshi's father is a very busy man.
Then you should change your mind.
It's a waste of money to cancel it.
My father got married to this woman who is 15 years older than me.
I can't call this woman who is older than me as my mother.
But mom, I'm glad I had time alone with Takeshi.
I don't think it's possible to feel like a real mother all of a sudden.
I hope I can get along with Takeshi on this trip.
A few days later.
It's a big place.
I'm sorry for the luggage.
The weather was nice today.
I wish my father could come.
I know.
It's a hot spring town, so the air is nice here.
It was a hot spring town, so the air was nice here.
Let's buy some hot spring buns.
Don't you have any souvenirs for your friends?
Let's buy some.
That's fine.
Let's buy some hot spring buns and key chains.
Do you want to go buy some tea?
Let's go buy some drinks.
Let's go to the hot spring.
Now?
I'm a little thirsty.
I'm going.
See you later.
A few days later.
Welcome back.
It was nice.
Did you feel good?
You were in the hot spring for a long time.
There were many kinds of hot springs.
The hot spring was amazing.
Was there a big round bath in the hot spring bath?
Yes, there was.
It's a men's bath today.
It's a women's bath tomorrow.
It's a one-day bath.
There were many other baths.
There was a wine bath.
What else was there?
Can you hear me?
Yes, I can hear you.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Did you get a little drunk?
I drank too much.
I'm glad you enjoyed the hot spring.
I like hot springs, too.
I'm glad.
What else was there?
There was a small bath inside.
It's like a hot spring bath.
Did you go into the Goemon bath?
Yes, I did.
I'm glad.
I couldn't go into the Goemon bath because there were so many people.
It was good.
I'm glad.
Did you like the men's bath?
Yes, I did.
I think I went into the men's bath too much.
It's hot.
It's been hot all the time.
I heard from the shop assistant that there is a good sake.
I'm thinking of buying it as a souvenir for my dad.
But I like sweets, so I think manju is better.
Which do you think is better?
If I were to buy a lot, it would be sake.
But it's not good to drink too much.
Did you hear that?
A souvenir?
I heard from the shop assistant that there is a good sake.
But my dad doesn't like sweets.
Let's buy a souvenir first tomorrow.
That's easier.
Are you okay? Are you tired?
I got a little drunk.
Let's have tea tomorrow.
Are you going to sleep today?
Yes.
There are two beds lined up.
I'm going to bed soon, so I'll sleep in the bedroom.
Really?
Good night.
The next morning.
I'm tired.
I'm sleepy.
I can't.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Takeshi.
You're here, right?
I've noticed you.
Come here.
Hurry up.
Yes.
My father is very busy.
So I'm lonely.
Come here.
I'll teach you.
Look closer.
Do you know what I'm doing?
Yes.
My mother was a housewife.
Like this.
Can you hear me?
Yes.
Look at me.
Great.
It hurts.
It made a great noise, didn't it?
Do you know what I'm doing?
If you don't touch me, you won't know.
I'm getting used to it.
You can't tell from my panties, can you?
Touch me.
You're trying to do it again.
It hurts.
It's very wet.
Bend your fingers.
That's right.
It feels good.
What?
You're doing a great job.
Takeshi's fingers are getting wet.
It feels good.
You're doing a great job.
Takeshi's fingers are getting wet.
It feels good.
You want to do something better, don't you?
You want to, don't you?
I have a good one.
Have you ever used it?
Do you look at me with a dirty look?
Have you ever seen this?
Have you ever used it?
Is this your first time?
What?
Do you have a toy in here?
There's something hard in there.
What kind of toy is this?
Why is it so hard?
Let's learn how to use this first.
Then I'll let you use a lot of toys.
Next.
What's wrong?
It feels good.
It hurts.
Next.
Do you know where you hit me?
It's so comfortable here.
I'll hold you up from below.
Just a little bit more...
I'm sorry...
It feels so good...
Aiki...
I'm tired...
It feels so good...
How's your neck?
It's hard...
Which one is harder?
I'll use this too.
With this much vibration...
It feels good, right?
You have to know what you're doing to a girl.
Okay?
This is how good it feels.
Next...
How good is this?
Wait a minute...
I haven't touched you yet.
I touched you.
On the tip of your nose?
Here?
How good does it feel?
How about here?
It feels good.
I'll make it stronger.
A little more...
It feels good, right?
It feels good.
It looks so hard.
I'll let it go.
Right?
It's amazing.
You're shaking.
What's wrong?
Are you excited to see your mom?
Are you excited?
You're both shaking.
I don't know which one is harder.
Which one is harder?
Which one?
Not this one?
This one?
Which one?
You're shaking a lot.
How does it feel?
Oh, my God.
It's amazing.
You're all wet.
I'll put it on your hand.
I'll help you.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
I can't help it.
It's cold.
You're shaking a lot.
You're sweating a lot.
You're still sweating.
The waterfall was amazing today.
It was my first time to see it so close.
It was very powerful.
The air was clean.
I want to come here every year.
It was a great spot.
I spent a day in a normal way.
I don't know what this person is thinking.
Let's drink together.
I'm weak.
Are you weak?
You're cute.
You're often told that I'm cute, aren't you?
I'm not told that.
Really?
Is it from a senior?
You're often told that I'm cute, aren't you?
Sometimes.
Sometimes?
Which do you like better?
Older or younger?
Older.
Do you like older people?
You won't refuse my invitation, will you?
Really?
Let's have a drink.
Cheers!
Do you have a girlfriend?
What?
I don't have one.
You don't have one?
Do you have a crush on someone?
I don't have one.
I'm just curious.
You don't have a girlfriend?
No.
Then, you don't mind if I kiss you, do you?
What?
You don't have a girlfriend, do you?
I don't have one.
Do you want me to kiss you?
No.
Then, I'll kiss you.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I was surprised.
Were you surprised?
If I kiss you many times, you won't be surprised.
Are you sure?
Why?
If my friends find out, I'll be in trouble.
Why will they find out?
You won't be found out, will you?
Then, I'll kiss you.
Is it delicious?
You're so cute.
Do you like to be blamed?
Or do you like to be blamed?
I like to be blamed.
Do you like to be blamed?
Then, I'll do my best to get along with you.
We're going on a trip alone.
So, I want to get along with you.
What's wrong with this?
This?
What's this?
What's in it?
I stood up.
Did you stand up?
I'll kiss you.
Did you just kiss me?
You're so cute.
Let me see.
Don't move your hand.
What do you think will happen to your mother's hand in the bath?
Where are you going to touch?
You're amazing.
You have a lot of gold balls.
Don't you have a lot of gold balls?
How many gold balls do you have?
Don't lie to me.
What are you doing?
I do this five times a day.
What do you do when you have a lot of gold balls?
You're amazing.
You can do it five times.
You're touching your nipples, aren't you?
You have a lot of gold balls.
How do you know?
You have a lot of gold balls like a girl.
Don't hide it.
Show me everything.
You're amazing.
You're touching your nipples, aren't you?
What's wrong?
Are you expecting something?
I want you to lick me.
Do you want me to lick you?
What should I do?
I want you to lick me.
Look at me.
You're a bunny.
I was surprised.
I'm just licking your nipples.
You have a weak nipple.
I'm sorry.
You're wet.
What do you want me to do?
I'm sorry.
This trip is...
A trip to get along with me.
I want you to do what I want you to do.
I want you to lick me.
You have to tell me.
I want you to praise me.
I can't help it.
It's so big.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
Let's just do this.
I want you to lick me.
Do you want me to lick you?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm going to fall asleep.
No, no, no.
Hang in there.
Bye.
You're so energetic.
It's amazing.
You have a cute face.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
It's amazing.
You're blushing.
I'll lick you more gently.
It's amazing.
How do you think I'll get more excited?
How do you think?
I think I'll get more excited when I see my mom's boobs.
I'm excited.
Are you excited?
My hands are so soft.
Do you know what I mean?
I know what you mean.
You're so cute.
It's delicious.
You have a sexy face.
What do you want me to do next?
You're a boy, so you have to say it yourself.
If you don't know, I'll break it.
I want to lick you.
What do you want me to do next?
You said it well.
I'll let you lick my boobs.
Come here.
You're so excited.
You've got a lot on your face.
You're so cute.
Come here.
It felt so good.
I'll give this back to you.
Do you want this?
Open your mouth.
I'll give this back to you.
I'm getting tired.
Give me your hand.
How do you do it?
Tell me.
Is this how you do it?
Give me your hand.
I'll give you a hand.
You're acting like a girl.
You're so shy.
What happened to you when you took a bath?
Don't say that.
You're so shy.
You're so sensitive like a girl.
I can't help it.
Be careful of your mother.
Next.
Give me a hug.
Do you understand?
I want to sleep.
I want to sleep, too.
I want to sleep tightly like a baby.
I want to sleep.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I haven't put it in yet.
It's so slimy.
I want to put it in.
It's amazing.
Do you want to put it in?
There's a lot in there.
I want to put it in.
Do you want me to put it all in?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'm going to put it in.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Mom.
It feels good.
Did you just call me mom?
You called me mom for the first time.
I'm glad.
Mom was so happy.
I'll make you feel better.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
This?
It's amazing.
I'll make you feel better.
Mom, it hurts.
It's amazing.
It hurts.
It didn't work.
Next, you move.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Mom, it feels good.
There.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
There.
Kiss me.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
You like milk.
Can I make you stronger?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'm going again.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Give me a kiss.
It's cold.
It feels good.
I'm going.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I want to go.
Let me go.
It's cold.
It feels good.
It's growing.
It's growing, right?
I just went out.
You just went out?
It's soft.
It's growing, right?
It's wrinkled.
It's cute.
Look at this.
It has an edgy face.
It hurts.
I have to do this three times.
Really?
You can't do it anymore?
Call me again.
Thank you.
She called me mom.
I got along well with Takeshi.
I was happy.
I got along well with him.
It's cold.
It's lonely to finish the trip.
It's lonely.
I don't want to leave yet.
Give me a kiss.
It's cold.
Takeshi.
Give me a kiss.
I'll give you a kiss.
It's cold.
Give me a kiss.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to hurt you.
It's only a small injury.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to hurt you..
I'm sorry...
I don't know what to do
Next...
It hurts...
Okay
Does it feel good, mom?
It feels good
Tickle, tickle, tickle
It's so hot.
It's so comfortable here, isn't it?
It's so comfortable.
I can't get it off.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
I can't get it off.
It hurts.
Takeshi.
I want to lick you.
Please.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
Stop it.
Don't put it in your mouth.
I can't stand it.
Do you want to sleep?
I want to sleep.
You have a lot of eggs.
I'll suck them out.
I can't stand it.
You can't suck them out yet.
I'll give you a lot of eggs.
I can't stand it.
Did you put it in your mouth?
Stop it.
I can't stand it.
It feels good.
Your butthole is twitching.
You licked your mother's butthole, so I licked it for you.
Where do you want me to put your butthole?
Tell me.
I want to put it in my mother's butthole.
That's right.
You want to put your butthole in your mother's butthole, don't you?
Yes.
I want you to put your butthole in your mother's butthole, too.
Just by licking Takeshi's butthole, it's messed up.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Mother.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Ouch!
It hurts!
I'm hungry.
I'll tiptoe
No way
The sky above is so red
Wait, wait
No, no
Systems warning
What are you doing Omonare?
That's not good
What are you doing?
Who is hitting me?
I'll go
This feeling...
It feels good, doesn't it?
I like this.
Over there.
Do that.
I'm going.
Why?
What are you doing?
I'm going.
It's deep.
Over there.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Do that.
I'm going.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
I'm going.
It's deep.
Whee, whee~~
Poop?
Hey, wheeeee, whee, wheeeeee
Wha pelapap
Wwwwheee
Help!!!!!!!!
oh!
Ohoorigous
Wselvis
Haha!
Ohodors
Ohhohdors
Ta
Oh, ahh
a
wi
No. No. No.
No. I beg you.
Stop, please.
Ah, it feels so good.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Oh, it's very rough.
I can see that it's hitting your muscles.
Oh, it's going to be crushed.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's going to come off.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it's full of your sweat.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh...
Pant! Pant!
Oh oh...
Oh...
Pant! Pant!
Oh!
Feels so good.
Oh...
Oh!
Mokuma sui-
Mo-
Ah!
Eh?
Ahhehehehe
Ah!
??
Ah~!
Ah!
It feels good
Wow, sounds so good
Sounds so good
Over there
Ah!
Ah, that's
What's that?
Gah!
What's tais..
Oh, my God!
Let's play with your father after you go home.
Let's go together.
Oh, my God!
Let me go!
Let me go to Mom!
Really?
Give it to me!
Oh no...
Oh, that felt good!
Let's go on a trip together when my dad is not here.