Hi to.
Please be kind today.
Please be kind.
Can I change your name, can I ask your name?
It is Kugari.
Mr Kugary.
How many times will this be filmed?
Today for the fifth time.
Are you no longer stressed?
Just a little.
I have been photographed by a professional in this past.
This is a photo, but you have asked me something before.
Yes, I’ve been going on this way so far.
This time I lead myself.
Feel like you are driving.
Yes is
All the men are in the same house today.
I am waiting for you in the next room.
Everyone looks nervous and is waiting.
Has Lissa ever been confronted with a virgin in the past?
Have you ever been the first woman?
not is
Lola has her first experience today.
Will you try hard?
I will strive.
Soon, I will be able to get to the virgins.
Can I call you?
Please please.
Please be kind to me today.
Lisa was in the house with three of her friends.
These guys seem to be very nervous.
Let me introduce myself from behind.
I am glad to say white.
Please please.
I am a craftsman.
I like to hold.
Please please.
Yes, thank you very much.
by Ms. Lisa
How about?
Or want to hear something.
Do you have questions or so?
Which is
Oh is me.
It is O.
I am a little rural.
There was no population around the girls.
So, if you go out to vote, there are girls, and if you think you have a chance, you can’t talk to girls at all.
Hope it goes well.
Welcome to.
Yes, please be kind.
Please be kind.
I actually met a woman.
I have never fought or compared so much.
Looks like it is big.
The first time she came out, she was the only one.
The moment I showed.
I was surprised.
A little
It feels like this.
I said I could do nothing.
The background
Then a little.
I am afraid to show.
to women.
I am scared to show my penis.
I have not met with women since then.
It feels like there is no such thing.
Is it a female organism?
In the female instrument.
I think I can’t get in all my life.
I feel like I want to get in once.
Please please.
Why did you get hand?
I have always been studying what I call Galileo.
She had no friends, of course.
I don’t have any friends, but at this age, I’m a friend of 30 too.
I thought it was bad.
I tried a lot to make her.
Not very visible.
But I want to experience it once.
I have added a little.
Yes is.
Unlike the other side.
I have not experienced any women at all.
I’m used to kissing, kissing, or something like that.
If it works, yes, I think I want to try it.
How many questions, from the blue shutter one.
I am the person in charge, right?
I think it is what we all think.
Are you over 30 years old and you feel uncomfortable?
Not at all that.
Do not listen?
In a totally place.
I just get a little disagreement.
Is there any more?
Tell me about the situation I left my daughter.
I don’t know how to throw it away, I don’t know how to throw it away.
So much
I met him when I was a student.
meet for the first time.
How many students?
Not a high school student, but a high school student.
High school student.
The same person.
Enjoy it.
Please please.
In turn, I will buy some land with Lisa.
Move from the back to another room.
Please please.
Then Mrs. Lisa
Is Mrs. Leah nervous?
I am a little nervous.
Are you nervous with each other?
Yes, each other
Of course, let’s talk a little bit more and think that it’s just the world of you two, please.
Please please.
It is awesome.
Thanks to.
I really have less girls than I have.
So I came to Tokyo,
I don’t know how to deal with women.
What is meant to be done.
I watched the video of the edge and thought there was any clue.
I was just watching that,
Yes
There is no such thing at all.
Something that.
You are doing it, just watch.
Yes is it.
Yes is
Then
today is
Yes is
Full of
Oh yeah
Let me do.
What can I do?
Would you like to try.
The first time I did.
The first time
Yes is
It happened.
Can I drink with both hands?
It is so soft.
is soft?
Yes is
Have you never drank?
not is
Can I say a lot?
Tell me a lot.
A little
I want to see.
Do you want to see?
Then flow it.
Do you not know?
Do not know?
It is completely different to touch it.
No to?
Yes is
How is it?
It became softer.
Has it become soft?
I will do it this way.
Do you do it this way?
Yes is
Does it not hurt?
It does not hurt.
I want to see what kind of bracelet you wear.
really is?
Yes is
is happy.
and happy?
Try putting your hands in.
Is it here?
not entered
I have never seen it in any video.
Is it so?
Yes is
This is the first time.
Was it there?
No, a little
Try to lick.
Yes is
I am on.
Yes
Very big here.
Is it true?
Feel good
Always licking it.
I have never seen it.
Do you want to see?
I want to see.
There is always something in the mosaic.
by
Yes is
Yes is it.
Today is the first time.
Yes is
Should I better take it off?
Yes is.
Oh yeah
Let’s try to take it off.
I want to take it off.
Yes is.
It feels good.
Feels good?
Yes is
Happy is
greatly
by  M  M  M  M  M  M  M  M  M  M
there
Do it yourself?
I want to see.
not see
Please show me.
greatly
Can I get near?
to approach?
It is very wet.
Can I lick?
Try to lick.
Great first time.
But only for the first time.
Is it true?
Yes
Maybe it is already going.
by
Are they left?
Oh, I want to come.
I have been.
greatly
Oh is?
The first time.
Oh thank you.
It hurts, it’s the first time I’ve been touched.
Do you feel too much touching?
This is the first time I can be beaten.
I will fill you a lot.
It feels good.
Feels good?
Yes to.
Because I never did it myself.
You are licking yourself and people, which one do you like?
It is better to lick it.
It is completely different feeling.
What a feeling?
I have a nice hand for such a beautiful person.
Yes
greatly
It is delicious.
Oh yeah
That will be so disrupted.
I want to be more engaged.
Want to be more engaged?
Oh yeah
Maybe you want to go in.
Want to enter?
entered in.
Yes is
So, this too is worth.
thanks to
Can you enter.
OK is OK.
is here.
greatly
Feel good
It feels good.
I feel good too.
WAN
4 is
Yes is
is
Are you moving, you are underground?
Ivas is
with such feelings.
It seems to be down.
Can I get up?
It will be up.
is okay.
Feel good
Feel badly
I have gone out.
is big
touch it.
Okay is it?
A lot of touch.
be big.
It is awesome.
is great?
Yes is
Oh to?
It feels good.
Feels good to be?
Yes is
I will fill you a lot.
We are moving around America.
Are you moving on your own?
Feels good.
Go to?
Maybe I want to try it from behind.
Let’s try it from behind.
Shamefully
Pull your ass out and show me.
It moved again.
I have moved.
Feeling badly
It moved.
It became very hard.
It feels good.
I don’t know why it’s the first time I’ve been on my back.
It feels great, I don’t think it’s the first time.
It feels bad.
Feel badly
My sister is lying.
Dangerously
I want to sleep others.
yet another time.
Let us sleep together.
Feel good
I feel good too.
I got a break.
pleased
It feels bad.
Feel badly
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAby
Tagged as Acheering
I went out.
Oh yeah,
Oh yes yes
Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha
Great, great
Thanks already.
Did you get it well, I?
Because it was good.
Not to think they are completely gay.
Great instruction for you.
Thanks to.
I will be the second man.
Time is free.
Men are more nervous.
I think he is being made by Tito.
I thought we were just two again.
Please have a fun time.
What should I do?
Let’s talk to them and avoid tension.
I have never compared much.
You say that the chicken is big.
I say I can’t, as if I could.
You can’t let me do it.
For women, it is big, full of people they like.
Do you hate it? – Do you hate it?
Maybe it feels like that.
If it is okay, I would like to ask for a little bit.
What should I do?
To take off?
If you want to see your face.
Then I am
Okay yes yes
Okay okay.
Can I sit?
Oh yes yes
I too, okay?
I want to look at it a little, and I want to see it.
Can I see you?
difficult is?
Oh is
Very cute stuff.
Is it true?
It is awesome.
It is really big.
It is big.
But entirely
The complimentary word.
But it is.
Usually is
Hungry is big.
Is it the first time you can lick?
Yes, I can’t lick it at all.
Yes is.
The cane is out.
Certainly
cannot be.
Warmly
It tastes good.
Feel badly
Feels bad?
Please make it delicious.
It feels good.
by O!
Sorry to!
Oh oh oh!
Sorry to
Yes to!
Oh oh oh!
A bit of distance.
I became worse.
Because there is nothing wrong.
Sorry to
It is OK.
Sorry, this is really so.
Give it out.
is OK.
Because there is nothing wrong.
Sorry to
You said.
Yes is
by Mr.
Finally, it is the third.
Now get them both.
I am still a little nervous.
Because I was still starting.
I have a little free time again.
I think it’s nervous, because the tension has risen.
A little bit of tension.
Can you please tell me.
Yes, are you nervous?
I am nervous, it is great.
You are nervous, right?
No, I will do it.
I hardly even talk to women in this way.
It is so.
I have something to ask, but can you?
Ok to.
Key, I have talked about it.
I am studying, and I have no friends.
Of course, I think friends come, for example, if you have friends, how they play, or where they are going, or a little bit.
Still go out to eat, talk, go shopping together, sometimes take colours or go drink.
Looks like fun.
That for example.
Not just women.
Are you even with a man’s friend?
Inside is
It is such thing.
Which of your friends do you want?
No more
You say both?
Men and women, too.
Of course yes.
For example, in the relationship with his friend.
Maybe it will develop?
Yes, maybe there are times like that.
I mean, I am talking about the first.
And then, how to meet her.
If there is anything I can ask?
What, a hobby.
If you have a hobby or a hobby.
Take your hand out, or...
I do not know.
Oh well well.
Sorry, I hear a lot.
Thanks to.
Are you nervous?
No, of course yes
So go down.
Are we together?
I am very nervous, really.
Are you nervous?
There is a cold woman in her eyes.
Okay, you are very nervous.
You are nervous.
Yes is
I don’t know if I’ll go somewhere to see it.
What to do at least?
At least then.
Yes is
Give out warm water.
Oh well okay.
Okay okay is.
Sorry, I am being puzzled.
I can’t wash it, sorry, what do I do?
Oh well, then then then.
Here and here?
Sorry, I’ve grown up a little.
Sorry to sorry.
What happened to you?
I will drink.
Will you come to drink?
Will you come and drink?
Feel badly.
I will go out.
I went out.
Sorry, I just left.
Is it okay?
Very bad feeling.
But I can’t give up a little.
Can I try again?
Can you?
I will try hard.
So really great dress.
This is?
It is awesome.
Fuck it sexy.
thanks to
Is it OK?
I can’t endure a little.
Can I tick it anymore?
here here?
Yes is
I didn’t touch you, too.
I will pick up.
sweetly
is soft?
Have you ever touched?
Not of course.
Is not?
Let’s try to touch it a lot.
Can I chew?
Yes
I want to touch.
How to touch?
So touch it.
Put it in.
Try to touch the cock.
Okay, touch it though.
Try to touch.
Yes, it feels good.
This is difficult.
It feels good, it has become hard.
pleased
Try to lick.
Does it not hurt?
Feel good
The stomach is full.
Yes is
I want to lick a lot of places.
Lying and Lying in a lot.
It looks great.
Shamefully
It becomes this way.
Don’t look at your face, you’re ashamed.
It is time to look at it.
It smells great in your mouth.
Can I lick it too?
Try to lick.
Feel good
Is it here?
Yes, it feels so good.
Yes
Oh well well
Oh, and a whimper.
Be kindly
It is very delicious.
Oh yeah
Oh so so so.
It is harsh.
Oh yeah
has been
It felt good.
More and more.
I want to.
Are you uncomfortable?
Is it unfair?
What is
Then a little.
on the money.
Take it around.
well is
Do you want to take it off?
by Pants
Sorry to
I want you to turn here from now on.
Turn to me?
Yes is
there to there.
I just got away, so I’m sensitive.
Is it something like that?
Yes, because of it.
It hurts, it hurts.
It was very good.
Feels good?
I am a breastfeeding too.
Can I touch my breast while I am in the breast?
It feels great.
Yes
Can I get a lot of stuff moving?
really is?
I can’t get a go, okay?
OK is.
Is it OK?
I was crying.
Feel good
Very good feeling.
A year is good.
Because he is alive.
It is awesome.
Come out on your stomach.
Feel good
Oh, it feels good.
Good morning.
Oh is
Did you go?
I went away.
Okay well well.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
half of
The IPSA
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Evening
Can I let him sleep?
OK is
Feel good
Yes
Oh yeah
Oh is
No to
Oh yeah
Feel good
and AR
It is a great nail.
Yes is
It feels good.
Coin is
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Can I move more?
Move again.
Oh yeah yeah
It feels good.
Feel badly
I had to sleep.
Raise it up.
Feel good
hurtly
Do not do that.
Feel good
I feel so good about it.
Oh, it was great, oh, it was bad.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I will go.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Any great feeling.
Try it next side.
Is this?
Yes is
4 days
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Co
Loan
Oh good boy.
Good boy
I am glad.
It is already very painful, painful.
Yes
I want more.
Full of.
Oh well feel.
Feel good
It feels good.
Very good feeling.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
mother
by dee
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Sorry, I felt too good to leave.
You have gone out.
is OK.
Is it true?
really is.
Thank you for really doing this today.
This is.
I felt very good.
I felt good too.
I am pleased.
I was tired.
All the filming is over.
This time for the first time.
confronting the virgin.
It was filmed.
How was it.
It was the first time.
At first I was very nervous.
While I do.
gradually a little.
I was excited.
It has become fun.
Maybe I can ask you again next time.
So, last but if you have a message to the fans, Mr. Leia, I would like to say one last word.
I’ll be doing a lot of things for the first time, so look at my body and be excited.
Thanks for today.
Thanks to.