Mom
What's the matter?
It didn't work this month either.
I see.
Hey, why are you talking like a stranger?
Your parents want to see their grandchild.
It can't be helped. Ignore it.
I'm busy with my wife and my work.
That's why you're in a hurry because you can't make such an opportunity, right?
I want a child, too.
I've been dating my husband since high school, and it's been two years since we got married.
The husband of a working person is not very cooperative in making a child.
He's not very cooperative in making a child.
Make a body that is easy to pregnant.
Effective massage.
Free of charge?
What's wrong?
This is...
Massage that is effective for pregnancy.
He said he'd come to my house.
I can do it while I'm doing telework.
You don't have to make a baby.
Your father and mother don't have to put pressure on you.
It's free, so you can try it once.
I think it's okay if it's free.
My father and mother are noisy.
I've been working for two days, so I'm a little tired.
It's free for the first time, but if you do it twice or three times, it'll cost you money, so be careful.
I know.
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Yamamoto.
I heard it's effective for pregnancy.
I'm going to give you a massage that will make you feel better.
Thank you.
Please come in.
Excuse me.
I was wondering if there were any women in this kind of massage.
Don't worry.
I've been doing this massage for a long time.
Thank you.
I'm going to ask you a lot of questions.
You're pregnant.
How long can't you have a baby?
I can't have a baby for about six months.
I see.
When do you want a baby?
I want a baby as soon as possible.
My parents want me to have a baby as soon as possible.
I see.
Does your husband help you?
My husband...
He doesn't help me as much as I do.
I see.
Yes.
How many times does he help you?
Does he help you?
He doesn't help me as much as I do.
He doesn't help you as much as I do.
Yes.
Sometimes he helps me.
I see.
I'm going to give you a massage so that you can have a baby.
Is facial massage really effective?
It's very effective.
99% of the people who use facial massage are women.
Really?
I'm relieved.
I'm glad.
I'll leave it to you.
I'm going to give you a massage so that you can have a baby.
Yes.
Please change your clothes.
Okay.
Please come here.
I'm going to take a seat.
Are you going to change your clothes?
Please take off your underwear.
Take off my underwear?
I'll give you a massage so that you can have a baby.
I see.
I understand.
I'll leave it to you.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Yes?
It's quite transparent.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
I understand.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
I've finished changing my clothes.
Okay.
Thank you.
I see.
Please take a seat.
Okay.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Okay.
I'm going to massage your whole body.
It feels good.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you.
I'm going to massage your stomach.
Okay.
Thank you.
I think your blood flow is not good.
I thought so.
I thought so, too.
I couldn't have a baby at all.
If you massage here, it's possible to have a baby.
I see.
I'm going to massage here.
Thank you.
Your blood flow is not good.
I see.
It's getting warmer.
The body temperature is important for pregnancy.
I see.
If your body is cold, you can't have a baby.
Body temperature is important.
I have a cold.
I see.
I'm going to massage your legs.
Are your legs important, too?
Yes.
It's important to warm your lower body.
I see.
I'm going to change your position.
I'm going to put your legs down.
Please face me.
I see.
Like this.
I'm going to put your legs down.
I see.
I'm going to spread your legs.
Spread my legs?
Yes.
Your blood flow is not good.
I see.
You look bold.
How do you feel?
It's different from a normal massage.
Are you ready?
Yes.
What is the effect of this massage?
It improves the flow of lymph.
It makes it easier to get pregnant.
I see.
Is that so?
Yes.
Is this the effect of a cartilage massage?
I see.
I'm going to push your legs.
It's a little ticklish.
Please be patient.
It's difficult.
I see.
I'm going to massage your upper body.
Excuse me.
Do you want me to turn your head?
Yes.
I have to massage your belly.
I see.
If the blood flow here improves, your body will improve.
That's why I have to massage your belly.
I see.
I'm going to massage your belly.
I'll do my best.
I see.
Please do it.
It's a little difficult.
Oh!
If I do more, I'll be sick.
That's all right.
Don't worry about it.
Really?
Yes.
I'm going to massage your belly a little more.
It's a little difficult, isn't it?
Yes.
If you don't do it, it won't be effective.
I see.
A little more.
It's a little embarrassing.
I see.
If you stimulate this area, your female hormones will be secreted.
Do your best.
I see.
I'm going to massage this area a little more.
That area, too?
Yes.
Do I have to massage that area, too?
This area will be more effective.
How much do I have to massage?
That's right.
A little more.
It's a little difficult.
Can't I do more?
No, you can't.
Massage will be ineffective.
I see.
A little more.
A little more?
I'm afraid I can see it.
That area is just right.
I see.
It's getting late.
I didn't know that facial massage was such a thing.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Don't worry.
It's nothing to be embarrassed about.
I see.
I'm going to massage the back of your head.
You can leave it as it is.
Leave it as it is?
Yes.
I see.
Can you raise your hips a little more?
My hips?
Yes.
Raise your hips.
Raise your knees.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Don't worry.
I may be able to see the back of your head.
It's nothing to be embarrassed about.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Don't worry.
Is everyone doing this?
Yes, everyone is doing this.
We're looking for healthy children.
Really?
Let's do our best together.
Raise your hips a little more.
Is it okay?
I can't see it.
It's okay even if you can see it.
Don't worry.
Is it okay?
Yes.
Your muscles are a little hard.
I see.
It may be difficult for you to get pregnant.
Yes.
It's my first time to wear such an embarrassing outfit.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I'm very nervous.
Don't worry.
You don't have to be nervous.
It's okay.
Yes.
I'm going to relax your muscles.
I'm sorry.
You're getting better.
Let's do our best.
I'm sorry.
That's all for today.
Thank you very much.
Is that all?
Yes.
You don't have to worry about it.
As I thought, your muscles around your tits are hard.
I see.
I think you'll get better if you do something about it.
Let's do our best together.
Thank you very much.
What's your schedule for the day after tomorrow?
The day after tomorrow?
I see.
I'll do it at the same time.
It's free for the first time.
It'll be paid from the next time.
Thank you very much.
If you do your best in the studio, you can have a baby.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the meal.
You said it was delicious.
It's delicious.
How was the massage?
It was good.
I'd like to do it again if I can.
It costs money.
I'll pay for it.
You won't complain, will you?
You said it was free for the first time.
I can't help it.
My parents want to see my face.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
Today's massage is short.
Yes, I'm going to use blue today.
So I prepared a more suitable outfit.
That's great.
It's so short.
Is it necessary to make it so short?
I think you can feel a better effect than last time.
I understand.
Thank you very much.
I can't hide my chest.
It's okay.
Even if you can't hide it, the massage will work.
I'm a little embarrassed.
I see.
Don't worry.
I'm going to separate female hormones.
Is that so?
I think it's a little too bold.
Is this right?
That's right.
It's easier to massage.
I changed my clothes.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Can you make it a little bigger?
No, it's just right.
Really?
But I can see it.
That's right.
It's okay.
Wait a minute.
The posture is also important, so please correct it a little more.
I'm sorry.
Please correct it.
Please stretch your chest.
I'm sorry.
If you don't have a good posture, it will be difficult to massage.
I think the blood flow is better than last time.
I think the flow of lymph is also good.
I think it's okay.
Did you have sex with your husband last night?
My husband and I had a little fight.
A fight?
Why?
I'm a little embarrassed.
It's about money.
About money.
We had a little fight.
Do you want to pay for the massage?
It's okay.
It takes a lot of money to get pregnant.
But I think my husband will be satisfied if he gets pregnant.
I see.
Let's do our best.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
This side, too.
Please put your face down.
I see.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
I'm going to use the oil today.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to start the operation.
Okay.
I'm going to apply the oil.
Please have sex with your husband on the day of the massage.
Sex?
My husband doesn't seem to have a sexual desire.
I see.
I know he's busy with work.
But if you massage, your husband will have a sexual desire.
Let's do our best together.
Okay.
I see.
I'm going to start the operation.
Please turn your head.
I see.
It's okay. Please let go of your hand.
My head hurts.
Don't worry.
It's okay.
That's all for today.
Is that all?
Do you want me to extend the operation?
Yes.
I'm nervous.
It's going to cost a lot of money.
I'm okay today.
Thank you very much.
I think the effect of the massage is effective and it's easy to get pregnant.
If you have time tonight, please have sex with me.
Okay.
I understand.
Your body looks good.
Thank you very much.
What's your next schedule?
Next?
I see.
How about the day after tomorrow?
The day after tomorrow?
I see.
I'll be fine the day after tomorrow.
I'll contact you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Are you going to work early tomorrow?
You're early, as usual.
I don't want to have sex.
You're early, so I don't want to have sex.
Can't I have sex?
I don't want to have sex.
I see.
Good night.
What's wrong with you?
I got a facial massage.
You said it was easy.
I see.
I got a facial massage.
I changed my clothes.
Okay.
Thank you for today.
Thank you.
I'll give you a facial massage.
Okay.
I'll do it now.
Come here.
Okay.
I'll use the oil.
Are you okay now?
Yes, I'm fine.
How was last night?
Did you have sex?
I was rejected by my husband.
I see.
If you don't have sex, you'll have a hard time.
No matter how easy it is to get pregnant, you can't get pregnant if you don't have sex.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
It's important to get ready.
I'll give you a facial massage.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'll massage your neck.
I'll massage your femoral hormone.
Okay.
It's good.
It's embarrassing.
It's a sign that your femoral hormone is coming out.
You don't have to be embarrassed.
Okay.
I'll massage your neck.
It's good, isn't it?
Okay.
It's good for your skin.
Thank you.
I'll massage your neck.
Okay.
It's good.
I'll massage your neck.
Okay.
It's good.
I'll massage your femoral hormone.
I'll massage your neck.
It's good.
Please put your body to the side.
Okay.
That's right.
Put your feet to the side.
It's good.
I'll massage this side.
I'll massage your neck.
Directly?
I'll massage your fingers.
Fingers?
It's good.
It's a little hard.
I'll make it soft.
It's good.
How do you feel?
Do you know it's a little hard?
I know.
It's good.
I'll use two fingers.
Two fingers?
I have to loosen this part.
Otherwise, it won't work.
I understand.
It's good.
I'll do it again.
Please relax.
I'll massage this part.
It's good.
It's very good.
If you move your waist naturally like this, it will be easier for you to get pregnant.
It's good.
Please turn around.
I'll massage your back.
It's good.
Next, please open the uterus by yourself.
By myself?
Yes.
Please do it by yourself.
It's easier for you to open the uterus now.
I'll open the uterus.
It's good.
It means that it's going well.
Yes.
It's easier for you to open the uterus now.
I'll open the uterus.
It's going well.
It's good.
It's been a while.
What should I do?
Do you want to extend the period?
Extend the period.
What should I do?
There is a special massage for those who have been extended.
I think it will be easier for you to get pregnant.
Please extend the period.
I understand.
Please do the same as before.
Please turn around.
Please extend the period a little more.
This side.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
It's the best massage to relax the uterus by using the male genitalia.
I'm sorry.
It's going well.
Ouch!
It's a very good thing.
It's a very natural thing.
Please extend the period more and more.
Let's make it easier for you to get pregnant.
Ouch!
It's very loose.
It's very good.
It's the best.
I'm sorry.
Ouch!
It's the best.
I'm sorry.
It's very good.
Please lie down again.
Please lie down like this.
Please feel more and more.
It's the best.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you a massage on this side, too.
It's very dirty.
You're breathing a lot.
It's embarrassing.
It's the best.
Please get up.
Are you all right?
Do you have a runny nose?
It's the best.
Next, I'll have you get up.
You need to be persuasive to get pregnant.
I'll get up.
Please move your hips when you get up.
You're very good.
It's the best.
It's very good.
Please feel more and more.
It's the best.
Next, I'll have you lie down on your back.
Please turn your body the other way around.
Please move your hips.
It's the best.
I'm sorry.
I felt so good that I couldn't help it.
I want you to have sex with your husband.
Your body is easy to get pregnant.
I'm going to do it now.
I got it.
I want you to have sex with your husband.
Do you want me to give you a massage today?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't see my husband's face because I betrayed him.
It's unnatural to rely on massage to get pregnant.
I think it's natural to get pregnant in a more natural way.
Do you want to say something?
No.
Nothing.
Don't you feel cold today?
Really?
It's not the same as usual.
You must be cold.
Did you catch a cold?
I've been busy at work every day.
I think so.
What if I take a day off tomorrow?
I won't go to work tomorrow.
I'll do it next time.
I'm sorry.
I'll go to the bathroom and warm up.
I got it.
How have you been doing?
My husband seems to be busy at work.
I heard you haven't had sex yet.
I haven't had sex yet.
Please have sex properly.
I'm sorry.
Your body is easy to get pregnant.
I got it.
I want to see your body.
Can you stand up straight?
Straight?
I'm a little embarrassed.
You can't stand up straight if you're embarrassed.
That's right.
Do you feel any changes in your body?
No.
Is it the same?
Yes.
Do you sleep well at night?
I think I'm sleeping well.
Your skin is good.
You don't seem to have any problems.
I'll check your body.
Yes.
Can you relax your chest?
My chest?
Yes.
I want to check your uterus.
I'll check your hormone secretion.
Please put your hands on your side.
Be careful.
That's right.
I'll check your uterus.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to be embarrassed.
What should I do?
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
It's okay.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I'll check your uterus.
It's okay.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I'll check your hormone secretion.
Your hormone secretion is normal.
I don't think you have a problem with your autonomic nervous system.
I'm sorry.
Please spread your legs.
My legs?
A little more.
Don't lean in.
I'm sorry.
I'll measure your blood pressure.
Blood pressure?
Yes.
You don't seem to have a problem with your blood pressure.
You have a good blood pressure.
I'll check your blood pressure a little more.
I'm sorry.
I'm in a good condition.
You can go.
I'll measure your blood pressure.
I'll measure your blood pressure a little more.
I'm sorry.
I'm in a good condition.
It's okay.
Hang in there.
I'll go.
It's okay.
I'll take your blood pressure.
I'm sorry.
You don't seem to have a problem with your blood pressure.
Next, I'll check your blood pressure with an oil.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
It's important to warm up your body.
I'll give you a massage.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's hot.
I'll give you a massage.
I think your blood pressure has dropped considerably.
It's hot.
Next, I'll check your pulmonary edema.
Pulmonary edema.
I'll give you an ointment.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I can't measure your blood pressure, so please don't move much.
My body feels so good that I can't help it.
I'll try to measure it.
It's hot.
Please be patient.
I can't do it.
It hurts.
Just a little more.
I can't do it.
It's okay.
It hurts.
Your blood pressure is 105.
It's okay.
It hurts.
If you keep going like this, you'll get well soon.
I hope you'll have sex with your husband.
I understand.
I can't believe it's been so long since I last saw you.
I'm so happy to see you.
Episode 3
Hello, Professor.
Today we're going to do this dissertation as thoroughly as we can.
I'm glad to work with you.
Thank you.
Let's get inside.
Are you Masato-Shirakawa?
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Hey, you should sleep a little.
No, I just wanted to say hello.
I'm sorry.
Actually, I think I caught a cold.
Oh, I see.
It's easy to get sick in this season.
I'm sorry.
It may be rude to ask you this, but...
Yes?
Is the cartilage massage effective?
Yes, of course.
The effect is perfect.
Hey, don't you think it's rude?
I see.
Go away.
I'm sorry.
I see.
Don't worry about it.
Excuse me.
Yes.
How have you been doing since then?
I think it's good.
That's good.
Do you want a boy or a girl?
Well...
I want a girl.
Okay.
My husband said he wanted a boy.
I see.
Well, they're both cute.
Is your husband all right?
Yes, he's fine.
What's the actual effect?
Well, it's said that the effect is about three times after the massage.
The effect of pregnancy.
I see.
Hey, don't you think it's rude?
Go back to your room.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Take care.
Well, as your husband said,
I'll give you a more effective facial massage.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're sweating a lot.
Did you forget about it yesterday?
My husband had a cold, so I couldn't do it.
I see.
Yes.
That's not good.
I'll take care of it.
Yes.
Thank you.
Doctor.
Yes.
It feels so good.
That's a good thing.
Yes.
It's okay.
That's a good feeling.
It's getting better.
Please keep your voice down.
Okay.
Doctor.
What's wrong?
Not only the neck, but also the hip.
Yes, of course.
Let's do it.
Please.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Please touch me directly.
Okay.
It's good.
Doctor, please touch me more.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Doctor, I'm sorry.
Please touch me.
Doctor.
I'm sorry.
Doctor, please touch me more.
Doctor.
I'm sorry.
That's a good feeling.
It's not a finger.
It's here.
It was the best feeling.
That's good.
This is the most effective.
I'm sorry.
It's deep inside.
That's good.
The effect of the massage has increased the volume of the female hormone.
That's a good feeling.
I think I can do it.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Is it here?
Yes.
Don't use this today.
Okay.
There is a doctor next door.
I don't want you to misunderstand.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'll wash your feet.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I think it's wonderful.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I have to wash your feet.
It's hot.
I'll wash your feet.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
If I continue to do this, my feet will be swollen.
I'm going to finish this today.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I think your body is easy to get pregnant.
Please do your best.
Let's finish the surgery today.
Thank you for everything.
How are you doing with the cartilage massage?
It's a little sweet.
Really?
Stop it.
It's a waste of money.
Why?
It's a lie anyway.
If I could have a baby with that, I wouldn't be short of Japanese children.
I don't know if I don't do it.
No matter how much I massage, I can't have a baby unless I have sex.
It's a hard day today.
Don't you want to have sex?
I don't want to have sex, so I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to sleep.
Can I cheat on you?
Do you want to cheat on me?
You can't do it anyway.
I'm going to sleep.
It's too early.
I don't want to cheat on you.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm sorry, Mr. Yamamoto.
I said that before, but I want you to have sex again.
Please.
A few days later.
I'm sorry to bother you all of a sudden.
I'm glad to see you again.
Thank you.
How do you feel?
I'm going to sleep.
Please don't say anything and have sex.
I understand.
Let's have sex today.
Please.
I'm going to sleep.
I wanted to see you.
I wanted to see you, too.
Mr. Yamamoto, please touch me.
I'm going to sleep.
It's hot.
Please drink a lot.
I see.
I'm going to stimulate you.
Please touch me more.
It feels good.
I'm going to use the oil.
Please.
It's hot.
Please touch me more.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Does my body feel good?
It's very attractive.
I'm glad.
It's hot.
I'm going to stimulate you with my tongue.
Please.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Please drink a lot.
It's hot.
Please touch me more.
Is it here?
It's hot.
It feels good.
I feel like I want to go home.
Please go home.
I'm going to go home.
It's hot.
Is it here?
I'm going to loosen my muscles.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's hot.
I'm nervous.
I want to go to the doctor.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Let's lick each other.
It's hot.
You have a lot of female hormones.
It's a very easy-to-pregnant body.
It's hot.
You need to lick a little more.
Come here.
Can you lick me?
Of course.
It's hot.
When the female hormones reach their peak, it will connect.
It hurts.
Doctor, can I stop now?
Let's stop.
You can't do it anymore.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Can I move?
You can move a lot.
It's hot.
It feels good.
She's gone.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Hmmm
What is this scream?
No, no, no!
It hurts!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's very delicious.
It hurts!
Nami-chan!
Nami-chan, it hurts!
It hurts!
Do you want me to do it from behind?
I don't want to do this anymore.
It feels good.
It hurts!
I want you to follow me more.
It feels good.
It hurts!
I'm sorry.
You may be able to do this.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'll make tea right away.
It's okay.
I'll do that from now on.
Sit down.
Thank you.
Do you like facial massage?
Yes.
You are considerate of me and my father.
From now on, I will take good care of my work and my family.
Yes.
Thank you.
A boy or a girl?
I like a boy.
A boy and a girl?
My father is not my husband.
But I'm not bad.
It's all my husband's fault.
Can I call my father?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's been a long time.
How are you?
I have something to tell you.
I have a baby.
Shut up.
Thank you.
I'd like to talk to you.
Can we meet somewhere?