2 MONTHS LATER
It's 2 months from next week.
I guess I can't have dinner with Hinata.
Good luck, dear.
It's good, dad.
2 months from next week, we're going to America.
We're not going there for fun.
I know.
Take care of yourself.
Thank you.
What is it?
Hey, Yuki.
Well...
Nothing.
I've been all alone.
I was lonely.
So...
Don't you want a brother or a sister?
Well...
But...
Because I'm alone, I'm being spoiled.
I don't need that.
Really?
But if you have a brother,
you can meet a new you.
I don't need it.
I could feel my parents' desire for a child.
But because I'm alone,
I didn't want to leave the environment where I can get anything I want.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I see.
You don't need a brother or a sister.
I don't need it.
But if your friends see you,
they'll envy you.
I don't need it.
I see.
You said you don't need a brother or a sister.
Yeah.
But I want a child.
Me, too.
But I don't have the courage.
That's not his opinion.
Yeah.
I want a girl.
Me, too.
I don't need it.
Mom.
You said you don't need a brother or a sister.
I don't need it.
I was shocked.
My mom's body was so beautiful.
I was completely taken away as an alien.
I don't need it.
Mom.
I'm leaving.
Take care of the house.
I miss you.
Be careful.
Yuki, you're a man.
Take care of the house.
Okay.
You're an adult.
Leave it to me.
I'm counting on you.
I'm leaving.
See you.
Take care.
It's been two months.
Let's do our best together.
Okay.
Wash it.
What's wrong?
I saw what you were doing yesterday.
I'm sorry for that.
Don't apologize.
You are beautiful.
And I really like you.
I see.
I like you, too.
No, I don't mean that.
I don't mean that as a family.
I really like you as a woman.
You got excited because you saw a naked woman, didn't you?
If you see an idol, you'll feel that way.
I'm not kidding.
I'm serious.
Thank you.
But that's a one-time thing.
Are you sure?
Did you study properly?
Yes.
You have other things to do, don't you?
You can't do it properly without your father.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Did you like today's hamburger?
Yes, it was delicious.
I'm glad to hear that.
Mom, I'll help you.
Thank you.
Can you wipe my sweat?
You are kind.
Mom, I like you.
I'll just take your feelings.
Mom, I'm serious.
I know.
I like you, too.
I'll help you.
Mom, I'll help you with the laundry.
It's okay.
I'll hold your shoulder.
Thank you.
Thank you, too.
Mom, I'll wipe your sweat.
You are kind.
Mom, I like you.
Mom, you are beautiful.
Mom, you are great.
I'll give you a lot of massage.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I love you a lot.
Mom, I'll help you.
It's okay.
How about studying?
I'm done.
Are you done?
You are kind.
Can I ask you a favor?
Can you wipe my sweat?
Mom, I like you.
I'm serious about you.
I'll just take your feelings.
I'll do the laundry.
When I think about you, I feel hot.
Really?
I'm serious.
Mom, this is very delicious.
I'm glad.
I still have a lot of fruits.
It's delicious.
It's been a month since my dad went to America.
I feel like it's been a long time.
I'm very happy to eat your delicious food.
Thank you.
The taste of miso soup is different from usual.
It's very delicious.
Really?
Thank you.
I changed my way of making soup stock.
It's very delicious.
Really?
Thank you.
All the food you make is delicious.
I'm happy.
I'm glad you eat everything.
This is also delicious.
You have to eat a lot and grow up.
I'm glad you eat a lot and grow up.
It's very delicious.
It's very soft.
I'm glad you eat a lot and grow up.
I love you.
You appealed to me for a month.
It was hard for you, wasn't it?
It was hard for me.
So...
I'll do it for you.
You?
Are you sure?
Mom...
I can't stand it anymore.
I love you so much.
I'm glad you said yes.
I know.
Touch me more.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I'll do it for you.
Mom...
I feel good when you touch me.
Touch me more.
Mom...
Kiss me.
I'm so happy.
Mom...
Touch me more.
I'm so happy.
I didn't know you thought so much about me.
I love you.
I love you so much.
You're so cute.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Here?
You're so cute.
Do you feel good?
I want to lick you.
I want to lick your boobs.
Sit here.
You're so cute.
I want to lick you.
Sit here.
I love your boobs.
They're so good.
Really?
Let me lick you.
I love your boobs.
You're so brave.
Mom, I don't feel good.
What's this?
I may be caught.
Mom, I don't feel good.
You are cute.
I don't feel good, either.
Mom, I don't feel good.
Mom, you are amazing.
I want you to lick me more.
I want you to lick me a lot.
Mom, you are amazing.
Mom, I don't feel good.
I want you to lick me a lot.
This is the last time.
Mom, thank you.
You are a good boy.
Mom, I love you.
Mom, thank you for loving me.
Mom.
Mom, I love you.
I did that to Yuki.
Mom.
Good morning, Yuki.
Mom, what did you do yesterday?
I made breakfast.
What's wrong?
Mom.
Can I do it again?
I want to do it again.
I can't stand it anymore.
Mom, I love you.
I love you so much.
You've been with me for a month.
You loved me, too.
I love you, Yuki.
But...
I'm a parent.
Please.
Mom.
Say yes.
Mom, I love you.
Yuki.
Mom.
You feel good, right?
No, I don't.
I want you to feel good.
I'll make you feel better.
I'm tired.
Mom.
Mom, I love you.
You're a good girl.
I love you.
Yuki.
It's getting harder and harder.
Mom, I love you.
You feel good, right?
I love you.
Do you love me that much?
I love all of you.
I love you.
Mom, I love you.
Mom.
I love you.
Yuki.
I'm embarrassed.
You're beautiful.
So, show me a lot.
I love you.
You're beautiful.
You're amazing.
Yuki.
You're sweating a lot.
You feel good, right?
I'll make you feel better.
You're amazing.
I love you.
You're sweating a lot.
Can I touch you?
Touch me.
You're sweating a lot.
Mom, do you feel good there?
I feel good.
Here?
Mom, do you feel good there?
You're sweating a lot.
You're amazing.
Mom, do you feel good there?
You're sweating a lot.
You're amazing.
Mom, do you feel good there?
You're sweating a lot.
Do you feel good there?
Mom, lick me more.
I like you.
I want to feel a lot of you.
Mom, do you feel good there?
Mom, lick me more.
Do you feel good there?
I love you.
Mom, lick me more.
You're amazing.
Do you feel good there?
Mom, do you feel good there?
You're amazing.
Mom.
Mom, come here.
Yuki.
No.
I can't stand it.
I want to be with you.
I can't be with you.
I can't stand it.
Help me.
Mom.
Yuki.
You're amazing.
Can I be with you?
You love me.
You're amazing.
You feel good there.
Yuki.
Do you feel good there?
You're amazing.
Yuki.
Mom.
You're amazing.
Mom, you're amazing.
Yuki.
Mom.
Do you want to do it?
You're amazing.
You feel good there.
Yuki.
You're amazing.
How about me?
You feel good there.
I'm happy.
Yuki.
You're amazing.
Mom, you're amazing.
Yuki.
You're amazing.
Yuki, you're amazing.
I can't stand it.
I'm going.
Yuki.
You're amazing.
I'm going.
Mom.
It's not enough.
Let's do more.
I can't help it.
You're amazing.
I want to touch you.
I'm going.
You're amazing.
It's not enough.
Let's do more.
You're amazing.
I want to touch you.
It's not enough.
I'm going.
You're amazing.
I want to touch you.
I'm getting a lot of energy.
I'm going.
Yuki, you're amazing.
Asama, you're amazing.
I'm going.
I can't help it.
I'm getting a lot of energy.
I love you.
You're amazing.
I'm getting a lot of energy.
You're beautiful.
You're amazing.
I'm getting a lot of energy.
I love you so much.
I love you.
You're amazing.
I'm getting a lot of energy.
I love you so much.
I love you.
Get me out of here!
I'm holding you.
It feels so good!
Let's go.
It feels so good.
Yuki.
It's amazing that you got out three times.
I got out a lot.
Come here, Yuki.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Mom, I'm great, aren't I?
Yuki, you're great.
I love you.
You're great.
And then,
I kept asking my mom
for help
because my dad wasn't there.
Mom, I'll do the dishes.
Really?
Thank you.
Please sit down.
Yuki,
is there anything you want to eat today?
Anything is fine.
Anything?
Mom, I'm done.
Thank you.
Anything is fine,
isn't it?
Mom,
do you want to eat this?
You look cute today.
Mom,
do you love me?
I'm so glad.
You love me,
don't you?
Mom,
I want to do a lot of naughty things with you.
Okay?
Give me your hand.
Mom,
I love you.
Yuki, you're cute.
Mom,
I love you so much.
I want to do
a lot of naughty things
with you.
Mom,
I love you.
I love you so much.
Mom,
I want to do
a lot of naughty things with you.
Mom,
I love you so much.
I want to do
a lot of naughty things
with you.
Mom,
I love you so much.
I want to do
a lot of naughty things
with you.
Mom,
I love you so much.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
Mom, it's hot here.
Do you feel good?
I feel good, Yuki.
You are good.
Are you excited?
I'm excited.
I'm sorry.
You feel good, don't you?
You are cute.
You are cute, Yuki.
I love you.
I love you, Yuki.
Give me a kiss.
You are amazing.
Stand up.
I'm sorry.
What do you want to do?
It's hot.
It smells good.
It smells like mom.
It's hot.
Do you like the smell of mom?
I love it.
You are cute.
It feels good when I rub you.
Give me a kiss.
I'm embarrassed.
You are swinging.
I'm nervous because I can't see well.
What do you want to do?
I want to see your legs more.
Spread your legs.
You are amazing.
It's hot.
It's messy.
You are sweating.
I'm happy.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
Why are you so good at it?
I want to make you feel good.
I did a lot of research.
You are amazing.
You are sweating.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I love you.
You are cute.
It's hot.
It's snowing.
Mom.
I want you to feel good.
What is that?
Where did you buy it?
Can I put this on you?
It's hot.
Relax.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
You are sweating a lot.
Mom.
I can't help but close my eyes.
Mom, do you feel good?
I feel good.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I love you.
It's hot.
I feel good.
I'm scared.
It's amazing.
It's snowing hard.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I love you.
It feels good.
I'm going to cry looking at your cute face.
I'm going to cry.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I want you to do more.
What do you want to do next?
I want to experience your taste.
I want you to cross your legs.
Like this.
It's embarrassing.
Like this?
It's amazing.
I want you to do more.
Like this.
It's hot.
I want you to do more.
It feels good.
Chanyu.
My hips.
My hips hurt.
I want to see your hips.
It's amazing.
Don't stop, please.
It is gonna be hard for you to eat anymore.
I need to breathe more!
The题er is dried off!!
I need more milk!
Ouch!!
It hurts!
Don't stop!
You can do it harder!
You're doing great!
I'm so happy that you're feeling better.
I can't take it anymore.
Are you okay?
It's a little...
It feels good.
It's hard.
It's really hard.
I love you.
It's hard.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm going.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Your face is all wet.
It's amazing.
I got so wet.
Your face is all wet.
It's embarrassing.
Mom.
I'll wash your face.
I wash her face.
It's different from when we were kids.
I see.
What's wrong, mom?
Don't wash it off.
Here.
You have some there!
Are your hands hot?
Can I try?
Here.
It's nice.
It's not hot but she feels hot.
It is a bloody baby.
Please massage with watching her.
This one is scary, take it easy!
I love you.
Can you sit down there just a little bit?
Okay.
Good girl.
Oh, you have 로ciosed scalp.
It hurts!
Ouch!
Are you OK?
OK.
I feel calm in Japan.
It's been a long two months.
I feel at home.
You did a good job.
Dad, you did a good job.
How are you two?
I was lonely because I couldn't see you.
We were fine.
Right, mom?
Yeah.
I'm glad.
I'm glad, too.
Yeah.
Yuki.
Did you fulfill your role as a man?
I did.
Right, mom?
Yeah.
You did a good job.
I'm glad.
Yuki, how about studying abroad?
Studying abroad?
Yeah.
I haven't thought about it.
Is it possible?
Studying abroad is amazing.
Was it amazing in America?
Yeah.
I want Yuki to work abroad.
It's too early.
I don't want to go abroad.
Don't worry.
I'll study hard.
Yeah.
Study hard.
You must be tired today.
Yeah.
Why don't you take a bath and take a rest?
I see.
I'll do that.
Right, dad.
I took a bath.
What's wrong, Yuki?
You look tired.
You did a good job.
Right, mom?
Yeah.
You must be tired.
I'll go to bed early today.
I'll spoil them.
Yuki has grown up in the last two months.
I think so.
She has changed a lot.
Yuki, you are cute.
I like you.
Good night.
Mom.
What?
Dad is sleeping there.
Mom.
I love you.
It's good, isn't it?
Mom.
I can't stand it anymore.
I love you.
Dad.
You are so cute.
Yuki is so cute that I can't stand it.
I love you.
The clothes you are wearing are cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
You are sleeping.
I love you.
You are so cute that I can't stand it.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it feels so good.
Mom, it's hot.
I'll leave it to you.
It feels good.
Oh, it's hot.
It's hot.
Oh, it smells so good.
I'll spread my legs.
I'm so embarrassed and excited.
You look so cute when you're embarrassed.
Oh, it feels so good.
You love me, don't you?
I love you.
I love you so much.
Oh, it's hot.
It's hot.
You're so brave.
It feels good.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it feels so good.
I'm about to go crazy.
Oh, it's hot.
I'll make you feel better this time.
I'll try it.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, wait.
What are you doing?
Do you like me?
I love you.
What are you doing?
I'm going to fall.
I'm going to help you.
It's okay.
I'm going to take this.
I'm going to help you.
It's cold...
I love you.
I love you!
You are a good foot bath.
I'm so happy.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I'm so happy.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay, mom?
Yes.
I wanted to try this.
Wow.
Wow, mom.
Ouch!
Wow...
My whole body hurts.
Mom...
I want to talk to you.
Is it not enough?
No, it's not.
Wow...
Mom, I want a little sister.
I don't want a little sister.
Let's use it.
I'm happy.
Wow...
You're amazing, Mom.
Mom, you're amazing.
I want a little sister.
I want a lot of it.
Wow...
Ouch!
Mom...
Mom, you're amazing.
You're amazing.
Help me.
I want to play with you.
Let's go.
Mom, let's go.
Can you do it again?
I can still do it.
I'm glad.
Cheer up.
Hang in there.
Mom, I want a lot of it.
I can still do it.
You're amazing.
I want a lot of it.
Let's go.
You're amazing.
Hang in there.
Ouch!
Mom...
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Hang in there.
I love you.
Ouch!
Let me go.
Mom, let me go.
Mom...
Let's go.
Mom, I want a lot of it.
I love you.
I'm glad that you gave me a lot of it.
Mom, I'm glad that you're brave.
Mom...
I love you.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
I'll be free when I finish my work.
Let's go out with three of us.
Okay.
You want to go on a trip, don't you?
You haven't been there recently.
Yes, I do.
You can decide where to go.
Okay, I'll think about it.
See you.
Yuki.
Mom.
Dad.
Because I love you.
Mom, me too.
Yuki.
I missed you.
I love you.
Yuki.
They couldn't stand each other while feeling bad.
And they asked each other many times in secret.
I love you.