What is this score?
Do you think you can be a good adult with this?
But this exam is very difficult.
What is difficult?
You just have to study.
The average score is lower than usual.
You don't have enough effort.
Do you understand?
People who can do vocabulary can save time and study.
You can't do that.
I'm not studying.
That's why you get this score.
Do you understand?
I don't understand.
If you are so strict, you will fail.
Hikaru is studying hard.
Don't be depressed.
Let's eat.
You have already eaten.
I know.
I'm hungry.
I'm sorry for him.
He can only do strict things.
But he is thinking about you.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I got a low score in the exam.
Let's do our best next time.
Let's eat.
We can eat soon.
Wait a minute.
What?
The hamburger steak is good.
Is it good?
There is one more hamburger steak left.
You can eat it after this.
Really?
Why are you grinning?
That's enough.
You are too strict.
I have to be grateful for the meal.
Let's eat.
My father is strict in education.
But my mother was always kind.
When my father was angry,
she always made my favorite hamburger steak and corn soup.
I was always saved by her kindness.
What?
I'll make you another hamburger steak.
Really?
Let's eat.
I'm sorry.
I got a low score again.
Will my mother be angry?
There was a change in my relationship with my mother.
On that day,
I came home secretly to surprise my mother.
I'm home.
Home.
It's coming out.
It's amazing that you can do such a thing by yourself.
I didn't know you were such a great person.
I know.
I know you're smiling over there.
Mom...
Mom, you're crying a lot.
You're amazing, Mom.
Mom...
I'm sorry.
I'll help you.
You're amazing, Mom.
I'm sorry.
It was shocking.
It was the first time to see the chest of a woman.
I feel like I was forgotten already
Mom
What's with all these grades?
You haven't changed at all.
But I tried my best.
Then you don't have enough effort.
What's important is not the family.
The result is everything.
That's the rule of society.
Do you understand?
Yes.
You said the same thing before.
Why do you always say the same thing?
Because I don't have enough effort.
You don't have enough effort.
You talk too much.
I'm saying this for her.
I don't want her to be like you.
What?
Why do you always say the same thing?
Do you want to ruin my family?
What?
Hikaru has a problem.
He's doing his best.
Do you think my education is bad?
What?
I don't think so.
What's your problem?
I don't have a problem.
I'm saying this for Hikaru.
I'm not wrong.
I'm right.
Do you understand?
Wait, dad.
What are you doing?
Mom, are you okay?
Dad.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Mom, are you okay?
I surprised you, didn't I?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry to surprise you.
Mom.
I'm okay.
Are you scared?
Mom.
I love you.
Thank you.
No.
I love you as a woman.
Thank you.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
I can't study.
It's okay.
I'm watching you.
Let's do our best from tomorrow.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
Did it hurt?
It's okay.
Don't worry.
I see.
I won't do that again.
I'm sorry.
I'll help you.
Really? Thank you.
I'll wipe it.
Mom.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Thank you.
I want to help you.
Mom.
I love you.
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear that.
You are kind.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for cleaning up.
No problem.
What's wrong?
You must be tired.
No, I'm not.
I'm fine.
You must be tired.
I'll give you a massage.
Really?
Thank you.
Sit down.
I'll give you a shoulder massage.
It feels good.
Does it?
I'm glad.
I'll give you a massage.
Thank you.
Mom.
I love you.
Thank you.
Thank you for always being with us.
I'm glad.
I'll give you a shoulder massage.
Thank you.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Did you do the laundry?
Yes, I did.
I'll help you.
Really?
Thank you.
My mom did it for me.
Is it good?
Yes.
It's my mom's.
I have to stretch the wrinkles.
Otherwise, you'll get wrinkles.
I see.
Stop it.
I'll give you a shoulder massage.
How about this?
It's okay.
Like this?
Yes.
Thank you, mom.
You're welcome.
You're so kind.
I'm glad you're my mom.
I love you, mom.
Thank you.
I want to be with you forever.
Me, too.
I want to be with you as a woman, not as a family.
Thank you.
I'll help you a lot.
I'm glad.
I love you, mom.
I'll be with you forever.
Thank you.
Mom.
When I think about you, my chest hurts.
I love you, mom.
You're so sweet.
I want to be with you forever.
You're so cute.
I love you, mom.
I want to be with you forever.
Do you like me?
Of course.
I love you.
You're a cute son.
I'm not asking you as a son.
I'm asking you as a man.
I love you as a woman.
I love you, too.
I love you.
I love you, mom.
Thank you for everything.
You're welcome.
We're going to use it together.
We're going to clean it together.
You're so kind.
I'm going to cook for you.
I love you, mom.
Thank you.
I'm doing what I want to do.
You're the best woman I've ever seen.
I'm so happy.
I want to know more about you.
I love you.
I love you, mom.
You're so beautiful.
Thank you.
I love you.
What's wrong with you?
I'm fine.
I'll be away for three days from tomorrow.
Take care of the house.
Three days is a long time.
Buy me a souvenir.
Okay.
Don't go to a strange store.
I'm ready.
We're alone from tomorrow.
What do you want to eat?
Hamburger?
Okay.
I'm looking forward to it.
Hey.
Yes?
Where is my tie?
I'll go get it.
My tie?
I'm home.
Welcome home.
I'm making a hamburger.
Really?
I did it.
I'll help you.
Hikaru really likes hamburgers.
My mom's hamburgers are delicious.
Really?
What should I do?
How big is it?
Okay.
You're good at it.
Really?
You're amazing.
You're lonely without your dad, aren't you?
I'm not lonely at all because I have my mom.
Mom.
I really like you.
Hikaru.
I know it.
I'm serious about you.
I can't help it.
Mom.
My heart.
I love you.
I'm connected to you.
Really?
Yes.
You like me, don't you?
I do.
Mom.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I'm happy to kiss you.
I love you.
Thank you.
I'm happy that you love me so much.
Really?
Yes.
You told me that you love me for a month.
I could feel it.
Mom.
Mom, thank you.
I love you.
Come here.
I'm happy to kiss you.
I want to have sex with you.
I want to be with you.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Mom.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I want to know more about you.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I love you, mom.
Do you want to see my boobs?
Yes, I do.
Can I touch your boobs?
Your boobs are the best in the world.
I've loved your boobs since I was a baby.
Your boobs are so delicious.
Were they?
Yes, they were.
I want to lick them again.
Do you want to lick them again?
Mom...
I'm a little shy.
I love you.
Mom...
I love your boobs.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I love you, mom.
You're like a baby.
It's delicious.
Is it?
Yes.
I want your boobs.
I want your boobs, mom.
I'll lick them.
I love you.
Mom...
You're so cute.
Come here.
You can't breathe?
Are you in pain?
Do you want to talk to me?
You can't breathe?
Are you in pain?
I love you.
Mom...
It's hot here.
Is it hot?
Yes.
It's hot.
Do you smell?
It's not a good smell.
It's mom's smell.
Can I smell you all the time?
I'm getting a nosebleed.
Can you breathe?
Yes.
Can I?
It's hard.
You're beautiful.
Can I look at you all the time?
Open your eyes.
Can you see me well?
Yes.
I'm embarrassed.
You're beautiful.
I love you.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
I'm glad that you feel good.
Mom...
I got a lot of juice from you.
I got a lot of juice.
It's mom's juice.
It's lukewarm.
I'm glad.
You have a lot of juice.
It's dirty.
I'll clean it for you.
It's okay.
You're amazing.
I feel good.
Where did you learn that?
I love you.
I learned it from you.
I'm glad you have a lot of juice.
I feel good.
I'll make you feel better.
I'm glad you have a lot of juice.
I love you.
You're amazing.
I'm glad you have a lot of juice.
I'll make you feel better.
I feel good.
Can you give me your hand?
Thank you.
Do you want me to hold your hand?
Does it feel good?
Thank you.
I'm so proud of you.
I can't help it.
That's great.
Can I look at you?
Thank you.
You've become very strong.
Thank you, mom.
I feel like I've been touched by you.
I'm so happy to be touched by you.
You've become very strong.
Does it feel good?
Look at me.
I'm going to sleep.
Thank you.
Does it feel good?
I'm touched by you.
I feel like I've been touched by you.
Thank you.
Does it feel good?
This is amazing.
Thank you.
Does it feel good?
I want you to give me a kiss.
A kiss?
That's amazing.
How do you feel?
Does it feel good?
I feel like I've been embraced by you.
I'm so happy.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
Your face is so slimy.
That's amazing.
This?
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
I feel like I've been embraced by you.
Do you know what I mean?
I can't stand it.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
I can't stand it.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you a kiss.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I'm hot.
I'm sweating a lot.
Can you drink it?
I'm hot.
I want to be hot.
Do you want to do it again?
Yes.
I love you.
Mom, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Can I hug you?
Yes, you can.
I just got up.
Why am I standing like this?
Because I love you.
I love you.
I feel so good.
I don't know what to do.
I can't speak.
I'm tired.
I want to do it again.
I want to do it with you again.
I can't speak.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I love you so much.
How was it?
It was so good.
I'm so happy that I could eat your food every day.
You're exaggerating.
Hey, Mom.
Thank you for the food.
You're welcome.
What do you want to eat tomorrow?
I want to eat your food tomorrow.
Me?
Yes.
Why?
Because I love your food.
I know.
Can I eat your food?
Now?
Yes.
Okay.
I love you.
I'll think about you all the time after this.
Will you?
Yes.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
Mom's lips are so soft.
Soft?
Mom.
Are you okay?
It's not painful, is it?
I want you to feel good when I lick you.
Is that okay?
I'll lick you a lot.
It's not painful, is it?
Mom's nipples are hard.
My nipples are hard.
It's not painful, is it?
Mom, which nipple do you feel good?
This one?
I'll lick you a lot.
I'm sorry.
It's not painful, is it?
Mom.
I'll lick your nipples.
My nipples?
I love your nipples.
Mom.
I'll lick your nipples.
It smells good.
It doesn't smell good.
Mom.
I'll lick your nipples.
Mom, you are beautiful.
Mom, I love you.
You are cute.
Show me your nipples.
I can't open my nipples.
I'm embarrassed.
Mom, your nipples are beautiful.
I don't like it.
Don't look at my nipples.
It's hot.
You are very wet.
It's very hot.
I feel good.
You are very wet.
It's very hot.
I feel good.
Show me your nipples.
Here?
I'm sorry.
I'll lick your nipples.
I feel good.
It's very hot.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
It's very hot.
Your neck is so stiff.
It's so stiff.
Does it feel good?
Your nipples are getting bigger.
I'm going to stop.
Please stop.
I want you to touch your nipples by yourself.
I want you to stop while watching your mother do it by herself.
Okay.
It's so stiff.
I'm so excited.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's so stiff.
I'm going to stop.
Please stop.
It's so stiff.
Please touch your nipples by yourself.
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I love you.
I love you, too.
It's so stiff.
It feels good.
It feels so good.
You can't stand it.
I can't stand it, so I took it out.
It's okay.
I felt good.
I'm so excited.
I love you, mom.
I love you, too.
It feels good.
It's so cute.
It's so stiff.
I'm going to go
It's been a while since I've had a bath, so I'm a little nervous.
But I'm going to do my best.
I'm going to do my best.
It's been a while since I've had a bath, so I can't wait for him to play, so I put him in a foam roller.
No, he didn't want me to play with him.
All we can are 5 seconds of him sleeping like this, moving his hand in a strange spot formation.
How do you feel?
Good.
I'm touching you.
You're amazing.
How do you feel?
Good.
I'm touching you.
You're touching me?
Good.
I'm touching you.
How do you feel?
Good.
I'm touching you.
How do you feel?
Good.
I'm touching you.
How do you feel?
Good.
I'm touching you.
You're touching me.
How do you feel?
Good.
I'm touching you.
How do you feel?
Good.
Come here.
How do you feel?
Good.
I love you.
I love you, too.
How do you feel?
Good.
Touch my feet.
How do you feel?
Good.
I want to sleep with you.
I love you.
I love you, too.
How do you feel?
Good.
I love you.
You're cute.
How do you feel?
Good.
I have to hold it in.
Hold it in.
I can't.
I have to hold it in.
You can't hold it in.
How do you feel?
Good.
I think I can do it.
I'll do it.
Oh, my God.
That's a lot.
Did you feel good?
Thank you.
I'm glad you're doing well.
This way?
Oh, you're not making any weird faces.
Really?
I'm glad you're not.
No, I'm not.
Yes, yes.
Oh, I see.
Really?
Yes, yes.
Hello?
I'm sorry, I couldn't hear you.
What was it?
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Mom, can I go to the bathroom?
Oh, sorry.
Yes.
Mom, can I go to the bathroom?
Yes, I'm sorry.
Yes.
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm going to hang up now.
Yes, bye.
Oh, no.
Mom.
It would be terrible if you got caught.
I was afraid you would find out.
Mom, you're so wet.
You were about to cry.
You're so wet.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Mom, I love you.
Dad will be back tomorrow.
Yes.
I want to be with you more.
Do you want to be with me?
We're not alone.
Why?
Mom, I love you.
I love you, too.
Mom, what's wrong?
Dad will be back tonight.
So let's do it one last time.
Mom, I want to do it, too.
I'll do my best.
Mom, I'm so happy.
I want to do it a lot.
I love you.
Mom, I'm so happy.
This is amazing.
Mom, I love you.
It's amazing inside.
Can you see it?
Wow, Mom, look at this.
It's amazing.
I bought it for you.
For me?
Yeah.
It looks great on you.
I'm happy.
You're the best person.
You're the best.
Mom, you look great in this outfit.
Mom, you look better than usual.
Can I lick your face?
I want to lick your face.
I want to lick you.
Can I lick you?
Can I lick your face?
It tickles.
Mom, can I lick your face?
Can I lick your face?
It tickles.
It feels good.
I want to go home.
I'll be home soon.
You're standing all the time.
Can I pet you?
Yes.
I love you.
I love you, too.
This is delicious.
Does it feel good?
I'm glad you feel good.
I love you.
I love you, too.
You're beautiful.
You're amazing.
I love you.
It feels good.
You're amazing.
I love you.
It feels good.
I'm going to be teased.
You're amazing.
I can't eat.
Can I pet you?
You're amazing.
It feels good.
Do you feel good?
Feel a lot.
It feels good.
You were about to go.
Don't go yet.
I want to do a lot.
Can I?
Can I pet you?
You went already.
I'm going to be teased.
You're amazing.
It's beautiful.
Can you see where I am drawing?
It seems pretty good.
Really?
Isn't it pretty good?
Please tell me it's pretty good.
It's so nice here.
Ai-chan, let's go.
Wait, I want to go, too.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Ai-chan, let's go.
I'm not full yet.
I'm so full.
I can still do it, can't I?
Yes, you can.
I'm going to cut your chin.
Oh, my God.
Are you all right?
Give it to me.
I'm going to put a lot of it in my pussy.
Give me a little bit.
Give it to me.
Oh, it feels good.
Hikaru, I love you, too.
I love you.
Oh, it feels good.
You're sweating a lot.
I love you.
It hurts.
I feel sick.
What a scary face.
Still a little thicker!
Your face is so thick!
Do you still want to talk?
Then pinch him like this!
Wow, amazing!
Sup tadi!
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Love you.
I feel good.
I feel great.
I'm surprised.
I can't believe it.
I want to go with you.
Your father will be back soon.
If your father gets angry at you again,
I want you to be a pervert, not a hamburger.
I want to be a pervert.
I love you, mom.
I love you, too.
I like sweet meat.
What are you talking about?
I love you, too.
I want you to be a pervert.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Welcome home, dad.
Were you doing well without me?
Yes.
Right, dad?
You guys get along well.
Really?
It's good to get along well.
But I'm tired.
My house is the best.
I'll take a shower when I get home.
Thank you.
I'll take a shower.
It's hot.
Mom.
Dad is back.
I can't stand it.
Can I do it?
Even after dad came back, we couldn't control each other's feelings.
After that, mom and I kept looking for each other.
Thank you for watching.