Yes is
I am pleased.
I came from the babysitter center.
I will call it the city someday.
I am pleased, please please.
The you?
Yes is
Oh thank you.
My husband’s housewife.
Please be welcomed.
I say ski.
Please give me a baby seat.
For the first time, I don’t know.
Tell me a lot.
Please take care.
You cry very much.
Is it okay?
It is OK.
It is really hard,
I cannot fit in hand alone.
No, but I hope you can.
I’m working, and I’m not friends anymore.
After a long treatment, she finally gave birth to a child.
I had to get rid of maternity leave.
I am home, but it is hard to work with my child.
I hired a babysitter.
The baby-sitter is looking forward to being kind.
I thought I could be safe and take care of the child.
Tell me anything, if anything happens.
I understood.
Please come in.
Sorry to sorry.
Oh here and here.
Oh, it is cute.
Baby is really cute, right?
Yes, yes is
Good boy
If you give me lunch, let me give you.
Yes, dinner is at 7 p.m.
Yes is
In case of emergency, the contact details are written on this paper.
If you have any problems, let me know.
I understand.
But I am glad you felt good.
I don’t know who the babysitter is.
I was a little nervous.
Oh you.
I think I should leave my child, so it is okay.
Really good.
You will become a father, so be more confident.
You are doing.
not do it.
You have something to do with me, right?
I will be a dad.
Do not be sorry for me anymore.
Take a good sense of responsibility.
No matter how many men.
Because he is sweet.
No, it is too much for this man.
I am not so sweet.
Because it is also a wick.
Or even Ulm.
I didn’t buy it all there.
They do it when they do.
I did not do.
I cry at night, I’m not waking up.
It is awakening.
Why do you wake up, milk?
Oh the lie?
It is true.
Oh, something, of course.
It is hard, oh yeah.
You are running.
well well.
by
It smells good, good.
Hye to?
Then there is milk.
by
sweetly
Yes is
Sorry to sorry.
and
I didn’t think I had lunch, I made it.
Sorry about it, intentionally.
No, please eat it if you want.
Thank you, sorry, but I have seen the TNT.
No, sorry for making a bad proposition.
Oh, no, I am thankful.
Sorry to apologize.
Please go
Thanks to.
Please eat it.
Then I eat.
Tastefully
Glad to have it in your mouth.
What happened to you?
Oh no, that’s all, Sita, and I think she’s a maternal one.
Sorry, I said something strange.
No, I am glad you say so.
It’s amazing that Ivy is loving her children.
Thank you, I really love my baby.
Lovely, sweet hair, and a little bit of care for you.
Yes is it.
Yes is
Oh, and I’ll get cold, look.
Open your mouth, see.
Oh yeah thanks.
Well, that is okay.
Oh sorry, sorry, sorry to me.
Occupational illness,
It is hard, right?
Really sorry.
Okay, okay, I really don’t care.
Thanks to.
So, I am going to eat it, I am going to eat it.
Please go.
It is delicious.
If you eat this, you will get a throat.
Drink and drink.
I drink.
It is delicious.
Even vegetables cannot balance.
Yes is it.
Sorry if I made it.
I will eat.
Tastefully
So suddenly I ate the coal.
You will fall asleep, right?
When the meal is finished.
You can lie down.
A little rest.
I will cook.
Tastefully
Oh yeah
No to.
Oh, so cute
Sorry, but just put it out.
Okay, okay, you are so cute.
Thank you, I think it will be better for you someday.
What are you saying?
You are very tired.
It is OK.
You should take a little paper.
Working will be efficient.
So much
Can I give it a little bit?
Please let me take care.
Sorry, but I will be working again if I get some paper.
Yes is
Thanks to.
Please rest slowly.
Yes is
I am sorry, yes yes.
Good night to you.
sweetly
Like a baby.
I do not wear pants.
Good morning.
What are you doing?
No, what to say.
Something tired.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh yeah yeah
Sorry, but I like the baby too.
I love these guys too.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
I am poor and want to be sweetened.
Oh, Mr. Dude, this is not possible.
I don’t think it’s good to say.
But you are not your wife, right?
Oh yeah no, yeah yeah
After childbirth, women are busy and don’t feel like that.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
So I will give you a kiss.
No, a little bit of.
Will one day?
I said my body would receive it.
Do not be so.
is OK.
A cute baby.
Oh please please.
Don’t tell your wife, so be calm.
The jigsaw has grown bigger.
Did he not keep silent?
You want to attack elsewhere.
otherwise.
What is different?
Find it.
Okay, let me do it.
If you let my mom do it.
I will feel good when I get an erection.
Fuck me, what about it?
Not to sweat.
No to fuck.
What what?
The voice is not really good.
Playing hard?
Yes
See also
It has grown so much.
meet for a long time.
Let my mom do it.
by
say no
Not to no.
Oh is
Saying no to.
It has become so big.
is cute.
Oh is
hurtly
Really?
No to no.
Tired by Mom.
I have met you in this time.
Oh is
Let us be happy.
Maybe it has been before.
Let me calm you.
No more not.
Put it in my mom’s mouth.
It is bad.
Really leave it.
Heat is
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah
I waited a lot.
You were so dumb, right?
by
cute is
Thanks to Mr. Man, I was saved.
Oh you.
Oh yeah yeah
I will let you go again tomorrow.
Please please.
You too.
So I am this.
Mary is a really good person.
Yes is.
Then eat food.
Yes to.
Oh well was.
It will be a development plan,
Just fill out the last questionnaire.
If you send it again, it will help.
Thank you very much, I apologize.
Oh, is it okay?
The child slept.
Thanks to.
Can I take care of my child again?
Oh, oh, why do you do it?
No, I don’t think that’s good either.
Why is it?
No, that is
Instead of
Why that
I liked your husband.
Oh yeah
Put me inside.
I want to enter.
No is
Oh yeah
No to
You always wanted to touch me, right?
But
I want to marry.
Is it related to getting married?
Even if married.
Your husband’s expertise is interesting.
You usually do your job hard.
Are you being deceived by your wife?
You can give me as much as I can.
You are struggling.
It is blowing.
Oh well
My breasts are blowing too.
by Chick
Do you feel good?
Can you do?
I can do it.
No to
So go go flow.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah
No to
Are you still not drinking the drink yet?
Oh, and h
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
A little...
I didn’t do it, but I got an erection.
Oh thank you.
Raise your feet.
feet are up.
No, no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
Do you feel good?
Do you want to try?
Can’t be illuminated?
I hate it.
Are you having a shot here?
What is trouble?
brother
What is?
What is trouble?
What happened to you?
I will take it off.
No to
If you want to get rid of it.
Please sit up.
That is?
Wait a lot.
Oh yeah
It will be okay.
Sorry to.
Oh yeah
cute chicken
Oh is
Oh yeah
Yes is
Oh, you are cute, no.
Oh yeah
You are in trouble, sir.
You are a baby, you cannot speak a baby language.
What does that mean?
You just don’t say baby, right?
See also Mr.
Yes is
The answer?
Not is it?
with a bigger face.
Oh well Babu.
You are still a little embarrassed.
Is that embarrassing?
Are you ashamed?
Yes is
That is?
Bobo
Feels good?
Oh yeah
Do not wait, speak out.
No to
Not going to go?
Look at the baby.
My mom was born here too.
Is it hurt?
This is small.
Sorry to
That is?
by BUB
Do you want to touch?
Do you know how to touch?
is good.
You can move it.
See also
Mom is great.
You are good.
The mother’s baby.
Sorry to
Sorry to sorry.
Is it okay?
A baby?
Yes
by
Mom, you felt so good.
Mom is there too.
well
Yes
Do you want to see your mom close?
where you were born.
Look closer and look closer.
Oh yeah
OK to OK?
Not by May.
It is Mom.
Are you ashamed?
No longer a bad boy.
Because he is really a good boy.
Be honest.
Liked there.
The child remains.
Do you want to drink?
The breast?
Do you want to drink breast?
Okay is?
Oh yeah
Broke it up.
Oh is
I will give you a Poppy Poppy.
Yes is
No to
The AAA is
Eat it?
Eat it.
No to
by
I was sorry.
No to
See also
by
No to
The mother’s internal organs.
Take your hands in sight.
by
by Boin
Oh, it is over.
No to
by Tj
Oh yeah
If you drink a lot, you will grow bigger.
Drinking is big.
What to drink?
I am a little...
to drink?
I drink it.
Feels good?
Yes is
Not this.
Do you feel good?
Yes is
Daddy, Daddy and Daddy
You went out of the room, you?
Why is my mom, my mom.
You have grown up.
It feels good here.
Mommy, Mommy
It really hurts.
crying alone
The real toy.
sweetly
You can’t stand your toys.
The real toy.
What to do.
What are you doing.
Yes
Don’t worry, I want to move on myself, chocolate.
I will go home.
No, do you not like?
No to
I’m connected to my mom, where can I see it?
Yes
Oh yeah
Oh oh oh, it is hot.
by
Stay with your Christmas.
Administration in the journey.
by 9A
I don’t know how to move.
well is
Oh yeah
I fear
WI is
Oh yeah yeah yeah
You have it.
The meter
Oh well
Oh my hair.
Oh, you are very adult.
In other words, you don’t see it all your life.
Do it inside my mom.
Stay on.
No to
Oh yeah
Oh is
Oh my little milk.
A lot of waiting.
well well well
well
No to
What are you doing?
Did you make a good kid?
You are a good boy.
Did not cry?
Great is.
Takesh
The you?
Oh you?
Sorry what?
What happened?
No otherwise.
I am so glad you could come to me one day.
Oh yeah yes.
What happened? no matter what.
Nothing is okay, okay.
One day, you loved me.
Oh yeah, I loved it.
Yes to.
It was really good to be a good babysitter.
Yes is.
Oh yeah.
Someday, she will be beautiful.
Do not think strange.
Oh yeah, of course.
Yes please please.
Yes to.
Yes, so please please.
If only it was.
That is
Yes is
Please confirm the content.
and then
Oh yeah
The point.
What happened to.
Oh yes yes
The point.
Please set up the email template.
Yes, I have a regular billing function, can I use it?
It is here.
Sorry, but this screen is not good, so I'll turn off the monitor once.
I have to go home, really?
It’s the system, but there’s something you need to be careful about before you use it.
Are you taking a step ahead?
Yes, it is about extension function.
Okay, okay, can you use it?
Yes, but from above...
Why want it?
Oh well, now it is okay.
From the third, yes, press the horse.
Yes, yes is okay.
Data is OK.
Is there any problem with the way data is transmitted?
Please send it here once.
Yes to.
I hear the sound.
The voice is connected.
Can you stand it? – I can’t stand it.
Yes, I have confirmed it. thanks
Next, but back to the tree.
Yes, there is a new control function in the section, so please contact us.
Yes, this is also a template, so you can edit it there.
Mr. Mac, you are really upset.
Yes, I went to the car, yes.
Oh well
Then then
First, we have to change the setup.
Before before
with many others.
I have contacted.
that
I want to open the menu.
Try to
Oh yes yes
Oh well, are you well?
Okay okay, yes
I think that this camera is going to be bad too.
I’ll cut it off, yes.
I continue, but yes.
Is the registration of members okay?
Please set up a chocolate template.
Not to work.
Touch the breast.
It is a reward.
Yes, I am listening to.
Then, please follow the sample and set the template.
If you don’t know, listen to me, I’m always watching.
I see you move your hands.
Yes, it is okay to stay.
Yes, yes, yes, that’s the name of the manager.
Yes, I would like to.
You should not end your work.
Oh sorry to.
Yes, I have returned.
Oh yeah thank you.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Oh yes yes.
So, I will check to interfere.
Yes, please wait once you have.
You are at work, right?
must be done,
I will find out in advance.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Try to.
If you do well, you will get a lot of rewards.
Yes to.
Yes good boy.
If you are already checking, please wait a little longer.
Yes, I am sorry for it.
What are you verifying?
Documents, I am sure to confirm.
If you touch it, you will not have any documents.
Sorry about that.
There is a communication problem with Cognac.
The radio is bad.
I will fix it a little and contact you again.
Sorry, sorry, sorry to me.
That is very bad.
Miley, I have to go back to work.
You say you are in trouble.
I can concentrate so much.
Do it really well.
This is painful.
I’ll let you open a little.
You are at work, right?
Yes but
I have to go quickly.
I will be angry with the pioneer.
Feels good?
First and feel good?
I like the vanguard.
Was it feeling good?
So, let’s just do your job.
Sorry to
I was talking.
Do not worry, please.
So keep doing your job well.
Can you?
Yes is
Oh, if if
Oh yes yes
I am completely
I became captive of her.
There were jewelry too.
Oh yes yes
by Toma
Maybe you have fallen asleep.
I played a lot today.
Maybe the dog was asleep.
that
If you feel calm, I want you to take care of me.
Now I am in front of you.
Yes, it is my own.
No so is, eh.
Do you drink your breasts?
Yes is
I wonder if I want to drink.
I was ready and waiting.
Then lie down and drink.
Yes is
Let’s go up a little bit.
You are well too.
Did you get excited by your breast?
I am bored.
You should cry too.
is delicious?
Tastefully
Grandpa is okay.
I drank so much and I regretted it.
Tastefully
It is delicious.
by my
The mother’s breasts.
I smoked too hard.
A little
Oh my dear, open your mouth.
Who is delicious now?
Tastefully
Oh, you have gone around here.
What happened, little girl?
extend from the outer.
Oh yeah
up up up.
I will raise.
Oh yeah
My mother’s milk is training.
Really really delicious.
You are picky, little girl.
Which of them.
Yes
Tastefully
It is delicious.
I want to kiss.
I want to love.
This too
Yes
Irritated by
Oh yeah
Feel good
Feels good?
Yes
Oh yeah
What happened?
No to
What is
What happened?
Oh yeah
Feel good
Yes
Let’s get a lot of stuff.
It feels good.
Oh yeah
Do you feel so good?
It feels great.
Yes
What is?
What happened?
hurtly
A little more.
Feels good?
Feel good
It feels good.
Do you like your mom?
Liked it
What happened to you?
Do you want more?
Go to go.
Okay, stand up
I waited a lot.
My mom will clean it.
He was a good boy.
If you want to be happy again.
I would always tell my mom.
You seem very tired.
I am busy.
It will be late today.
Maybe not so much today.
Yes, well done
From the company.
Is it okay?
Yes is
You understand?
Is it okay?
I think there was a problem with my company’s system.
Is that okay?
I will be staying at the company today and be sick.
But there are also cuts.
So, take care, I look at you.
Really okay?
Focus on work tomorrow.
thanks to.
by T.
Sorry, Mommy, I can’t go today.
Sorry, I will not go back.
I am okay with my dad and you both.
Mr. Tatsuya, I have been to sleep.
Thanks to.
What happened to you?
You bite me and I bite you.
I miss you, sorry.
Did you miss it?
Yes is
If you are already playing.
Yes to?
What happened?
by OEM
What are you doing?
My wife, I want you to get a lot of stuff.
Do you want to swear?
My wife has grown up.
is right.
Because his wife is staying there.
Are you gonna go?
Because I missed him a little.
I missed you a little.
Raise the face.
What happened?
Feel good
Oh yeah
No to
Oh oh
It feels good.
No to
Oh oh
Yes
Even today
My mom wants to feel better too.
by one shot.
Yes
One shot?
So I think I should give it to my mom.
Pick, can you do it?
Can you?
Have a good luck.
Make your mom feel good.
Instead of my mom.
A beautiful feeling.
Is it getting tough?
Sorry to sorry.
I wear my pants, but I know when I go through the pants.
is soft?
I want to feel more about my mom.
What to do?
Take off my mom’s clothes.
I got it.
This too
What happened to Mom?
I want to take off.
Was it not a baby?
Mom can’t move.
It is awesome.
Oh your reward.
I drank my breasts well.
Oh yeah anyway.
Do you want to have your breasts again?
See also, Dude
Should I eat brownies?
Yes yes yes.
Is this delicious?
See also
The breasts are delicious.
Pooh is delicious?
Very good feeling.
This too
And here too?
I have a hunger.
The examination needs motivation.
With about a month.
I cassette was a meditation.
by Avicin
Oh yeah yeah
Oh yeah
Oh wow wow
I gradually got it.
Your child has been good.
I will post a lot of books later.
well is
Oh yeah
I want a reward.
The reward?
The reward.
What do you want?
Recently I have been rewarded.
here is
You have bitten me.
The reward.
Oh yeah
It feels good.
Yes
Oh is
Pooh is fine?
Feel good
Sleep here.
Sleep to
greatly
Little
My mom can learn.
You are hungry, and you are hungry.
Tastefully
Oh is
Yes
I can no longer endure.
Then
About my mom.
Because you felt good.
My mom will paint it.
really is?
Yes
Oh is
Feels good?
Feel good
Yes is
Oh is
There was
greatly
It is awesome.
Feels good?
It seems like you are hungry.
Mom is pleased.
Pretending to be mom.
Feel good
Oh awesome.
It feels good.
I move a lot.
Oh awesome.
Oh sorry sorry sorry.
I want to move and feel good too.
Will you move?
well
and state.
Now it feels good.
Oh yeah! oh yeah!
I went away.
Oh yeah! It feels good already.
here here?
Yes
Oh yes yes
Something has gone out.
Yes
Oh no
I want to be more careful.
Yes
Oh no
So then that.
And the end?
It is not the end.
Do you want something?
Maybe I want to lick my mom.
Do you want to lick?
Good morning to my mother.
She is taking pictures of her boring breast.
My heart hurts.
Feels good?
My stomach hurts.
You are a good boy.
Inside my mom.
It is warm out.
I brought out a lot.
Have gone out?
You are a child.
really is
You haven’t gone out yet, right?
here
If I come here, I want to eat.
Yes
You are still well.
Oh is
It feels good.
Oh awesome.
Oh is
I try hard.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh awesome.
Oh oh oh oh
Wait a little.
I put water from my cheek.
It feels good here.
It feels good now.
Oh, so great
Oh is
Strengthen more.
to help?
Where are you going today?
Give out spirit.
See also
Let’s beat those we love.
I calmed.
Stop it now.
Yippidy yi yippity yay.
pulled a
Feel good
I want my mom to feel better.
Mom, you are feeling great.
Oh well!
It hurts!
Drop to Drop.
Okay to!
Take a lot of flow from your mother!
was pulled.
was cute.
Give a lot to Mom.
Working hard today.
Mr. M. I would like to help you today.
Yes, lady, please do your best.
Please let me do the house.
Thanks to.
Do your job well, too.
Come to me.
Go to
Come on to me.
I want you to watch a lot today.
No longer a sweet.
I drink my mom’s breast today.
Tired of you.
Yes yes yes
Yes
So I am
I was drowned in the mother’s motherhood.