Thank you very much, I would not have been able to leave until I came to work.
Don’t worry, I was busy.
Help you and your sister.
You can’t always go home when you’re discharged.
Do not tell me that.
Leave me to do the house.
Yes to.
Be careful of.
Yes, I welcome you to the dinner.
Go and go.
Come to me.
What do you want to eat for lunch?
Anything is OK.
A little bit.
Can I go in at midnight?
Yes to yes.
meet for a long time.
Yes yes
Was he well?
Yes
What are you reading?
Comic comic
You are so old, you read it.
Not such an adult.
Is the room too weak?
No, my sister, I will clean it up.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, even if he is a boy.
No, I have to clean the room, I am ready.
A little bit?
Because I am already studying.
and yes.
No go to.
Yes, I will enter.
Yes yes yes
Oh is
Studying is great.
Here is the gift.
You eat it.
The gift?
And then drink.
I am glad you will be able to use your head in your studies because you want to use your head.
Oh is
No to
Oh yeah
My favorite mathematics.
Oh is?
Tell me to.
Oh well?
No to?
Oh is
This this
Oh yeah
here here here here
The hand stopped.
Yes yes yes yes yes
to eat?
See also
I will give you.
OK is.
to drink?
See also
Oh yeah
is delicious?
I photographed it before.
Use this formula.
I want to eat.
No to?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Okay, I’m okay with my driving license.
Why does it not work?
How can we become friends?
Too much home.
Oh is
Forget it.
Oh yeah
No to
meet with naked.
increasingly family.
No to
This is
well with
No to
Where is the bed?
Oh yeah
Why this now.
No, I thought I would wash.
No, a little bit.
No to
What what what?
Is it too early to take a bath?
Usually from now on.
My hair is not wet.
I didn’t sweat today.
Not because I am not sweating.
Do you have a dirty man?
Yes, but I am not hit.
Even if you don’t think you’re sweating, you’re sweating.
I will not do it. okay.
I will cheat you from your sister.
Okay okay okay.
A little, a little, a little, why are you doing it?
Come in and enter.
No to.
Not okay though.
A little, a little, a little, a little, a little.
What is your back now?
No, because
Okay, it will be on your back.
Yes, I can wash it myself.
No, I have not washed it.
I washed it, I washed it already.
Yes
has grown up.
Yes, maybe so is.
Yes
When did you increase in height?
The Middle School.
Are you training muscles?
I did not do so much.
You are muscular.
Take out the arm.
OK is.
Come out here.
Do you wash under the side?
It is a pretty dirty place.
I say okay.
opposed
by
Gabbana
Gathering
It is a bit difficult to wash.
Do not be such a bitch.
No well
No to?
Wait, can you wash it?
No, it is difficult to wash.
Okay, so I wash it myself.
No, I didn’t wash it, so I told her.
No, well well
See also
Oh is?
Leave the hands.
I can actually wash it myself.
Leave it, let it go.
Oh, oh, a little bit a little.
is?
Oh, and a little, it is okay.
First, look at it well.
So, remove the skin.
Drop it properly.
So let her skin.
part of the neck.
There is a little more.
No more is
Wash the V line.
Wash the back of the hole well.
Oh, oh
It is not okay.
Something so important, just put it on.
Great to follow, if you do.
So that will happen.
Sorry to
I did not intend that.
No, yes is it.
It is a boy.
Even if you don’t want to, it will feel better.
Suffering is?
So then oh.
Your sister will take responsibility and let you be happy.
No, but that means it.
to your father and mother.
Let it together.
Certainly moving.
They were almost together.
I did not intend so.
So, do not be angry.
No longer enough.
What do you like?
Oh is?
What do you mean?
by
Oh is?
by Tjap
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah?
Maybe bigger than my boyfriend.
Oh, you have a boyfriend?
Oh yeah yeah yeah
There is
Yes
Is the gold not much more expensive than it was?
Oh yeah, I don’t know.
seemed a bit late a little
It still bubbles.
It was delicious, I slept yesterday.
But today they are exposed.
Yes yes
Are you not too interested in going out?
Oh well...
Oh my dear, my dear, my dear, my dear, my dear, my dear, my dear, my dear, my dear, my dear, my dear, my dear, my dear, my dear, my dear, my dear, my dear, my dear.
What happened? what happened?
No, no, no, no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
So, a little, what happened?
Oh, baby, I am studying
A little, no
Oh yeah, and so
What time will you come home?
Oh, what is
Tell me to go to the library.
Oh no, no, I don’t know.
Can you tell her sister?
Okay, because it is okay.
Oh oh oh
So this is no.
Take it as an etiket.
is?
Okay, no to be sick.
No, no, no
Oh yeah
Oh, oh, I am going to go.
Wait to
Oh yeah yeah
Why are you dressed?
Do you go to the bath again?
Oh is?
is?
But...
Are you ashamed?
Yes, there is also...
I suppose I say.
Little, what are you doing?
See also
I am hiding, I am hiding.
Look at it, naked and bad.
No, it is not naked.
See also.
Oh yeah?
I thought I would say so,
I want to go in a swimsuit today.
I also took a bath in the bathroom.
The bubble?
Yes the bubble.
I can’t see it because it’s bubble.
is?
Okay is it?
If I say so much.
and
Yes
See also, go
It was warm.
This is no problem, right?
Problems to?
No, it is not trouble.
Because it
I said it was like a problem in your eyes.
If so, they will hide in the bubble.
If you don’t wear a swimsuit, you’re not ashamed.
But the bath is nice.
Feel good
It is soft.
Is it soft?
Yes, the bubble
What happened?
Does this bubble have a cleaning effect?
What do you mean?
Oh is?
It is like Lee Soup.
No to?
Little nothing.
Nothing is?
I will paint it on your back.
It is soft, right?
You should have done this from the beginning.
Sorry to
Oh yeah yeah.
Wash it again with this bubble.
It is so soft.
I bought a better one.
Sorry to
No, it is okay.
Well, but
I saw it yesterday, okay.
No, at all
Was you concerned?
What is it? – Mister
No, no, no, no
Sorry, but no more
IO is
She was a ugly sister.
No, not the other.
Oh is?
Oh, what, what is it?
Suddenly, her sister was upset.
It is so beautiful, so beautiful, so good in style.
cute and good character.
My sister suddenly got that.
I am confused and don’t know what to do.
So distance and take.
I was glad I thought you hated me.
Not that I hate.
really is?
Oh well was.
I thought I hated him all the time.
No, it is not so.
I like too much.
Too much strike.
I didn’t know how to do it.
Was it distance?
It was so.
thanks to
I will do everything I like at night.
Why want it?
It is... that...
The breast?
Oh, oh, a little bit of
What a breast.
Oh is?
Why do you want?
So, that’s why your breasts.
I understand
Oh is?
I will wash it.
Okay okay?
Yes
Where do you want to wash?
From here, this
Yes
So stand up.
Stand up up.
Yes
Take the clothes, take them, take them back.
The neck, this is it.
Here and this?
Yes to.
It became softer.
Great, I have it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Yes
So let it out.
Oh is?
Is it the opposite?
I will wash your ass.
Oh is?
See also
No to?
Oh is
This is?
Are you washing?
Wash it... and go.
We don’t stop in the swimsuit.
Take it?
It is easier to wash.
with it.
by
Take it
Wash your arms.
How is it?
such or
This is
A little bit of trouble.
It is like a sponge.
opposed
How is?
A little more.
I have grown up again.
Because it seems to suffer.
There again.
To be relaxed?
You washed your breasts.
is soft?
You are a bully.
Too much already.
Feels good?
A disaster?
It sounds like an epic.
badly is
by Tomorrow
Yes
Because I gave.
by RY.
Yes
Okay, you danced a little.
It is still cold.
Yes
What are you doing?
How is this time?
Oh well?
well well!
They wash.
It smells good.
In your mouth, here
Do you want?
Yes
Is it good? this.
I am going well.
How is it good to be done?
Normal in the mouth.
Ordinary in your mouth?
again
Which of them?
Let us go up.
Go to sleep.
Have you slept.
Yes
You are already very much in.
Now I am dressed in a scarf.
Maybe remove it.
Eating it is okay.
Okay is okay.
Even if you sleep.
You may feel.
Oh, and here, this
Go ahead
Oh, a little
Oh, oh, the board is too low.
They are brothers, so they cannot go in.
Listen to
So listen to.
I wish it was other than that.
Other than that.
That is the tongue.
I hope to rub.
not to enter.
You can do anything other than that.
Maybe not
No to
No to no.
Oh no 😂
A little
Oh oh oh
No to
Great is
If it was tomorrow, you would have gone home.
No to
Then it.
Can I photograph for memories?
Shoot it?
No to no.
My sister is so beautiful.
The Red Sister.
I always wanted to touch you.
Always, don’t know what I feel.
Everyone is already dressed.
I always wanted to drink this breast.
Sorry to
I will take responsibility.
Full of, so
You can touch it.
I understand.
When I was lying, I had a tongue.
You can lick it today.
My sister’s homework.
It became a great voice.
Women feel better when they get stronger.
It is great here, baby.
It has become a great collar.
pleased
This is getting better for me.
Feels good?
Will you expand?
No to
Because I came close.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
What I said now.
When he feels better.
Yes
I said in my finger.
My fingers have become so tick.
Do not show me.
I want to see your ass.
Yes
It is an important round.
You are so hiccups in your ass.
My fingers felt good.
Is it bad?
It hurt again.
I easily got into two books.
I have a lot of important things cleaned up.
No to no.
I will speak to you as if you were in the bathroom.
Not in the mouth.
Do not enter.
Can I even take pictures of it when I lick?
Do you no longer like it?
Oh awesome.
My sister is licking me.
Feel good
No to
Not even your sister.
No, no and no.
No to
Oh yeah yeah
Oh is
Yes
A little
Oh is
Yes
greatly
Try a little bit of sliding or sliding.
Yes to
Yes
A little
Get more stuffed here.
More stuff here.
Maybe it is private.
I can no longer endure.
No, so is
Just to get it.
I can no longer endure.
See also Sleeping.
What do you do?
Okay, do this way.
Do this so.
Even if you are dotted.
It feels like you are inside.
Oh awesome.
Oh is?
This feels good.
Yes
No to?
Oh yeah
Yes
greatly
This is what I did, this has happened.
Oh, and a little there.
Can I do this? a little.
It feels good, I’ll go in.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no no
It is dangerous, a little.
No to no.
No to
I know, you have to do it here.
Yes is.
This is OK.
Yes to.
Wait, let me get a little bit.
No to.
A little.
Just a little.
No to no.
A little bit.
No to
No to no.
A little
No, I will enter.
It is just crawling.
I will enter.
OK is OK.
A little
Wait a little.
It is bad.
Feel well.
Glad to
Sorry to
Fuck, it is out.
OK is.
I did it once.
I will put it in again.
Just slow down a little.
Because he is big, he’s going to be a little crazy.
Slowly and slowly...
Slowly, Slowly
slowly
Yes, wait a little.
You cannot slow.
I know, you can help me too!
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay?
received received received
You are doing slowly.
It is slow.
Slow down this time.
It slowed down.
slowly
This too
If you were focused on filming.
I think it will not be too early.
slowly
Not slow, not slow.
Oh yeah!
there there.
Why don’t I sleep, I’m moving.
What do you mean?
Lie down already.
Oh here.
No to.
there there.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah
Very great very much.
slowly
Oh yeah
Oh, and the equipment, it feels good.
Oh no, wait for me.
I am so sorry, get it!
Oh, oh, no one a little!
Slowly – Slowly!
You say slow.
It has already moved.
be slow.
I turned to here.
What what what?
Go up and turn here.
Oh, the lie
Oh, greatly
Oh is
No to
Oh, and no
Oh yeah yeah?
Funny
cannot move?
This time I move.
So this
Definitely no longer.
Moving slowly all the time.
A bit early.
slowly
Oh well...
No is...
Tuesday...
No to...
Oh well...
I will be...
No a little...
It is...
Lying...
No to...
Oh...
Turn well.
No longer...
extend it a little later.
Oh...
Oh oh...
Oh a little.
Slowly and slowly.
Slowly Slowly
Nessa, slowly and slowly.
Surprising
Slowly
by M.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh oh
stupidly
I said you slowed down.
Sorry to
Tomorrow you will be slow.
by
Have you slept?
I couldn’t sleep well.
Oh yeah, so is it.
Whose fault is it?
Oh is?
Even if you stop a little.
No, it happened a little longer.
Oh is?
Because I came out there, you.
Not so though.
You touched me all the time I was sleeping, right?
Because they dress like this.
No to?
Not, but you can see it.
Oh is
If you dress like that, you are a man.
by
Yes
sweetly
What is?
Oh is
by
See also, wake up.
Yes yes yes
No to?
Go to.
Yes yes
You are already able to.
Is there?
Yes, there is one.
Drinking is fast.
Is it?
by
No to
What is
Why guess from there.
No, I guessed a little.
Not for revenge.
It is different.
No differently
No to
Look like this different.
You are washing this.
No, I did not wash.
well is
What is full of appearance.
No longer
You are Dad.
well is
Go home to.
Oh, just now
Room is so dirty.
Oh yeah
Oh, a little bit
What are you doing?
A little more.
I am inviting you.
Because they are cleaning now.
I did not invite.
A little bit.
Because I am cleaning it.
Are you cleaning?
They are cleaning.
I am cleaning up here.
A little bit.
What is cleaning?
Not so dirty, but in my ass.
cleaning
Not to clean.
I do not want to clean.
Can you clean it.
I can’t, I can’t, I can’t, I can’t, I can’t, I can’t, I can’t, I can’t, I can’t, I can’t.
Oh, what happened to you?
No, you’re going home today.
have a job.
Yes is it.
I have work.
No, otherwise
It is not over today.
will come again.
No to No?
that is
The last
not take a bath.
This time I will throw it out.
Yes, well well
Take a bath.
Let me sleep.
Then I will take it off.
to whom to make.
The breast.
Do not do like a tea.
A lot of shirt.
well is
time here.
Do not look seriously.
No No No No No No
by
When to wear, which one to wear?
I have stripped it up here.
up
I am going to go up from above.
Yes
by
A little
I want to get rid of this because it’s like a man’s dream.
and then
Yes
well is
What was it? was it strange?
I pulled it, that is.
What about shirt?
here here?
Do you often remove it?
and break this.
Okay is.
What is?
Do you get it off quickly, yourself?
So fast.
It is not okay.
I will wash it anyway.
First the arm.
Yes
Are you sweating down there?
Are you oiling now?
Oh, I was fucking
But it has to be cleaned, it can be difficult to sweat.
Is it?
You should clean up here too.
I don’t wash it, I just touch it.
But you touch it and you wash it.
Wash it properly.
No, I am washing it.
I just washed it.
Something has become harder.
Oh no, do not tell me.
It is hard to wash this arm.
Take it behind your head and do so.
I am ashamed.
You can’t wash it, Kyle.
I don’t like to have a wash.
Do this, right away.
and no.
Oh yeah
OK is.
Wash your back too.
I have hand.
Come here a little.
well
Clean your ass, and it’s the big thing.
This is so dirty in the crap, so you have to clean it.
You have a boyfriend, Kyle, he was so dirty.
Why do you say so dirty?
When you washed me, you said that.
Why is the time for the bath so short?
No, it is the same thing.
If it is dirty, it will hate you.
It’s dirty than you think.
I want to wash here too.
Put your feet up, this is easy to wash.
Shamefully
You can wash it like this.
It is so dirty here.
Do you know what I say here?
As much as the name.
What do you say?
by Dud
The official name
correctly
This is, together, made of cotton.
It is so easy to get rid of this dirty skin.
This is the most dirty place.
I have to wash it in the year.
I just washed it a little.
No, I have not washed.
They just wash.
Not washed up.
by Pure Pure.
Sorry to you, sorry to you.
You washed it already, right?
Maybe washed it.
So to flow?
Will it flow?
A little bit, follow me.
Oh is?
Ready well?
Yes
Put it down, put it down once.
What happened?
It’s so much bubbling here.
It just flows.
I washed the left, but I didn’t wash it.
It just flows, why?
I will keep you washing now.
Did you flow?
Has it become clean?
Can you clean up me?
I don’t know what you are saying.
My sister is all.
My sister is really big too.
Yes
It is Bishop.
by
Oh yeah
This is
by
by Tomorrow
by HADR
Hot dress
A little
What is
I felt so bad.
Let’s drop it in the room.
Oh no longer
Oh, and go on.
No longer
Yes
This dress is.
Wait to
not touched it.
If you get chopped and chopped, this is what happens.
I like the chick.
My boyfriend always says this.
Do not say that now.
Oh yeah?
Something, I have done.
Okay my boyfriend.
It is now entirely.
Oh yeah yeah yeah?
Is it just me now?
Oh yeah, that is how.
can flow.
My breasts are out.
If it were a pheromone, the eyes would be big.
Do not eat hungry.
Yes
by Rush
How far away?
here
It is great enough.
It is heavy and long.
This is
Do not put any other girl in the house besides her.
Why why?
Maybe everyone will hurt.
The lie?
My sister came home and it tasted good.
Will you come back soon?
Depends on midnight.
I want to touch my sister too.
Very close up.
Always on top of the Acacia.
really is?
Great, very much a bit.
to take off?
No to?
by
very hardly
No to
Oh, no no no no no.
No, no no no no.
No to
by
Oh, it hurts.
Because it is a hit.
Let us do more.
Oh, oh, oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh oh
Great, I am going soon.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh, oh, oh, oh oh oh oh oh oh
Was he well?
What is behind?
Oh, oh...
Oh well.
Yes...
I already saw.
Then I will enter.
Yes
Oh yeah
Oh well great.
No to
Greatly Sinc
Oh, oh, it hurts
Go to go.
Oh yeah
Oh oh oh
there there
Oh no
No to no.
Oh, that is the one.
Oh yeah
No to
and no more.
Oh oh oh oh
It is so fucking.
I am sensitive now.
It feels good.
and
No to?
and here, here
and no more.
Oh awesome.
Oh oh, it is awesome.
It is famous.
Oh well well.
by Ayyub Ayyub
Oh well...
This is this?
It will break.
But I heard that it felt good.
Feel good
This is like this.
Oh, oh, is awesome
Oh what?
Where are you hit there?
If Katherine moves, she’ll go crazy twice.
It is crazy now.
Wait, something is leaking.
Was something leaked?
I was so sad that the sperm was out.
greatly
No to
Oh is
is in.
Feels good?
No to
Oh is
It is a great gorilla.
I am hungry and gorgeous.
I am getting bigger inside.
Look at it.
Oh awesome.
Oh oh oh oh oh
The floor pulls the prince.
It stimulates
Oh a little.
A little, though.
It will not be crazy.
During the night.
Stop a little.
No, no is no!
Oh is?
Did nothing come out?
No, no...
What is Diagnostic?
No to...
Very pleased.
Oh well! oh well!
Incredibly...
Not my sister!
My sister, I do not know!
Very much noticed.
Oh no! no no!
Oh! there is there!
From it!
Oh oh oh oh!
greatly
A bit really.
A little more.
Oh is
Feels good?
Feel good
Oh well fuck.
Wait a little.
No to no.
If you move, go out.
Okay, my feet hurt.
Yes to!
What to do!? to
I will sleep.
Yes to!
Oh to!
Oh oh oh!
The Senior!
I came to sleep!
Go to now!
Oh, no shit though.
Come to me.
Oh oh oh oh
I am going now.
Okay is ok.
OK is OK.
A little more goodbye.
Are you tired?
You are tired.
It was fun, but it was home.
Do not do that.
It doesn’t mean I’m back.
Drinking a tea?
Yes, drinking to drink.
Then I can enter.
thanks to
I will help too.
is rare.
What was it on top of this?
Oh yeah, you have forgotten.
I am in a hurry because it is on the map.
But now you have a phone.
It was like a guide, like a guide.
You told me about the anticipation.
Oh, well, I am glad you went.
1, 2, 3, 4...
Just that?
Yes to.
Where was the most fun?
There were many hospitals and people.
You are now in trouble, man.
There were not many hospitals.
It’s like a road trip, everyone is going to be there, I guess.
Yes is.
I do not know.
Looking elsewhere, they are full of food.
I want to go too.
Let us do so this time.
The midnight.
What happened?
I think it is not midnight.
I went somewhere.
The toilet.
Is it okay?
It was okay.
Sorry to.
Yes, thank you very much.
I don’t look a little warm.
It is cold, there.
It was hot, thank you.
I broke up.
I recommend you here, here, here.
I have heard here.
I am glad, that is.
From anywhere you can see the eyes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, I am.
The garden was beautiful here.
You say it’s beautiful here, right?
I want to drink tea now.
I drank it.
It was a good place, really good.
The bamboo furniture was beautiful.
Didn’t you come to the unwanted?
Oh, it happened to happen.
I was in?
I ride.
Not knowing.
You want to go to Kyoto.
Oh really?
Let’s go down, everyone.
Let’s go, all of us.
This is the water, this is the water.
You are so shy.
It reflects beautifully.
When you see it, the weather comes.
It was nice every day, so it was good weather.
Wherever you go.
Food is delicious.
This was delicious.
The food or the food was delicious.
by Saxony.
The tofu was delicious.
I want to eat.
I want to go with four.
The late night.
Why not midnight?
No, he is a graduate.
Yes, the exam is over, so I should go.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, no anything
How many years of spring.
When the exam is over, we will all go.
Where are we going, four?
Oh yeah, no, it does not.
Did you buy beans?
Oh, there are some.
I bought a lot.
I will see.
Oh, I want to go too.
I bought a lot of it too.
Probably a gift.
by May
Yes
You can open the gift.
Oh yeah yeah
It is a very famous sweet.
by
Yes
This, this
The most...
What to do for dinner?
Before the out?
Dinner or dinner?
before going out.
How many times?
Oh is?
Sushi and sushi.
The sushi?
Yes, and pizza
The pizza?
The sushi.
Decide either of them.
Yes, let me talk a little.
No a little.
Have you decided which sushi or pizza is best?
Sushi is
Is it sushi?
Shit shit...
Did you eat it too?
It is delicious, right?
No to
Oh yeah
You eat pizza and sushi, right?
Pizza and Sushi.
It is just sushi.
No to no.
Going to bath?
Yes
Go in.
The bath?
Then
It is crazy.
Please let me voice.
Oh, it is there.
Because weak there.
Will feel better.
because it will be.
Mainly
Thank you for cleaning the bathroom.
This is a little trip laundry.
You washed the laundry, right?
The main thing is washing clothes, if you have to.
Yes
The main
Clean the bathroom.
I will do.
OK is OK.
Is it okay?
You are tired too.
Do not worry, it is okay.
Thanks for the late night stay.
Oh yeah
Since I came home.
No to Mr.
Yes
of Tokyo.
When the school tests.
Yes
Then then
It will soon be cheaper.
promise is.
Have a good luck.
Are you in the bathroom?
I want to go home.
Now I can go.
Oh yeah yeah