I'm home.
Welcome home.
Ah, I'm tired.
Good work.
You ate dinner, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
It was a convenience store bento at work.
Ah, I see.
It's for tomorrow.
I was making the documents for tomorrow.
Ah, I see.
I have a business trip tomorrow.
Are you okay? Aren't you tired?
Well, I'm a little tired, but I'm okay.
Really?
As usual.
I'm worried about you before the business trip.
Thank you.
I have a business trip tomorrow.
It's in Hiroshima, but it's a big deal.
It's a big deal.
When it's over,
I think I can take a break for a while.
Really?
Don't overdo it.
Thank you.
I'll buy you a drink.
Really? I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Shinji.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Shinji.
How's dinner?
You haven't eaten yet, have you?
I'll make you something to eat.
Shinji.
I want you to make me something.
Don't be shy.
I'll make you something.
You haven't eaten anything today, have you?
I'll take this.
You're not going to talk to me, are you?
It's okay.
You've been ignoring me for two months.
It'll take a little longer.
I don't think we'll get along.
You don't have to worry.
I talked to you the other day.
Shinji was cheated on by his ex-girlfriend.
He ran away.
He quit his job.
You know, I really like you.
But if that's what you want,
I don't know what to do.
I just think of you as a little strange woman.
I don't know if it was a bad idea
Well, it's almost time.
Hmm.
Shinji is a good guy even if he's scared.
Is that so?
Yeah.
I don't know about that yet.
Well, I haven't talked to him yet.
Yeah.
Also, Shinji-kun...
Yeah, what about him?
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Well, if it's nothing, that's fine.
Well, I'll wait for you patiently.
Yeah.
Well, I'll get ready for tomorrow's business trip.
I see.
Yeah.
Is there anything I can help you with?
No, it's fine.
Really?
I can do it right away.
Oh.
I'm going to my room.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Haah..Haah..
You explained everything by warning about me.
It's a bit hard to see, but there's a lot of dust in the air.
I'm going to clean up the dust.
Sounds are very deep, so listen tightly.
What's coming left is dust.
What's following right is dust.
Wait a minute
What's wrong?
Wait a minute.
You always come to touch my underwear, don't you?
I'll keep it a secret from my father.
It's okay.
I don't care if you tell me.
Say something.
What should I do?
I'm home.
Be careful.
I'll do my best.
I'm going.
Be careful.
I'll call you when I'm calm.
I'm going.
What's wrong?
You're in a hurry.
It's a big luggage.
Where are you going with such a big luggage?
I don't know if you don't tell me.
Are you going somewhere?
Where are you going?
Don't you want to be with me?
Wait a minute.
Are you going out of the house?
Really?
I don't know if you don't tell me.
Let's talk.
Wait a minute.
Why don't you tell me?
Are you really going out?
I haven't told you anything yet.
Wait a minute.
Do you hate me so much?
I don't care.
Wait a minute.
Shut up.
Don't make fun of me.
You're younger than me.
You're up to something.
I'm not.
You're always nervous.
Do you think it's disgusting?
I can't live with you.
I'm fine.
I can't.
Don't hug me.
Don't go.
I don't want to.
I have to talk to you.
Don't go.
Don't touch me.
Don't you care about me?
Don't go.
You've been worried about me, haven't you?
I'm fine.
I can't.
Do you feel good?
Shut up.
You can touch me as much as you want.
What's going on?
Come here.
What do you think?
You can touch me as much as you want.
Don't move.
I'm fine.
You like me, don't you?
What are you doing?
You're worried about me, aren't you?
I'm not worried about you.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
I'm fine.
You're getting bigger.
No.
Leave it to me.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
I'm fine.
Stop it.
You're getting bigger.
No.
Don't touch me.
You're excited, aren't you?
No.
Leave it to me.
Stop it.
You're excited, aren't you?
No.
Stop it.
Leave it to me.
I'm fine.
No.
What are you doing?
I'll comfort you.
Do you feel good?
Stop it.
I'm fine.
It's not good.
Leave it to me.
Stop it.
It's not good.
You can feel better.
What are you doing?
Can I do this to you?
I want to get along with you.
I'm fine.
It's not good.
Stop it.
Do you want to use this?
Yes.
What's this?
You're getting bigger.
Wait a minute.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
No.
You're getting bigger.
Do you feel good?
Don't touch me.
Why?
You're getting bigger because you feel good, right?
No.
Wait a minute.
You're getting bigger.
I want to get along with you.
It's not good.
You don't have to worry about it.
You can feel better.
Don't move.
I can't feel better.
It's not good.
Do you feel good?
No.
Stop it.
I'll massage you.
Don't do that.
It's not good.
Wait a minute.
Why?
What are you doing?
It's not good.
You don't have to worry about it.
Wait a minute.
It's not good.
Stop it.
It's hot.
Are you listening to me?
I told you to stop.
You feel good, right?
No.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
It's not good.
Stop it.
You feel good, right?
Don't move.
It's not good.
It's hot.
Let me go.
It's not good.
Stop it.
It's hot.
You have a lot of blood.
What are you doing?
I'll clean your wound.
Stop it.
Let me go.
It's not good.
It's clean now.
Did you feel good?
It's hot.
You have a lot of blood.
Stop it.
Hide it.
Put on your shoes.
I haven't told you yet.
Let's talk.
Okay?
Please.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
I met your father through an app.
App?
Why?
You're lying, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
I met him through an app.
I don't know yet.
I want you to believe me.
I'm not cheating on you.
Please tell me what I can do for you.
I don't have anything.
I can't live with you anymore.
I'll keep it a secret.
We haven't talked for two months.
It's not enough.
Don't say that.
I want you to spoil me more.
I don't care.
What are you doing?
Don't do that.
Why?
It's strange.
I don't care.
It's not good.
Why do you have to do that?
I don't care.
Wait.
You don't have to take it off.
I don't care.
It's not good.
Come here.
I don't care.
It's hot.
It's okay.
Do you like my boobs?
Yes.
It's hot.
You can do whatever you want.
I can't say that.
Do you like it?
Do you feel good?
Touch me a lot.
I don't want you to say that.
I'm happy when you say that.
Does it feel good?
You can eat it.
I don't want to eat it.
Your face is full of it.
Do you like my boobs?
I don't want you to say that.
I'm happy when you say that.
Does it feel good?
Do you like my boobs?
Next is this side.
You can do whatever you want.
Touch me.
I'm very wet.
Do you want me to touch you a lot?
Does it feel good?
I'm very wet.
Look at me.
It's amazing.
Touch me a lot.
What are you doing?
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
It feels so good.
It's so cold.
I want to drink more.
It feels so good.
I can't do it.
You can do whatever you want.
It feels so good.
I can't do it.
I want to drink more.
It feels so good.
I can't do it.
It's so cold.
It feels so good.
I can't do it.
Ah, it feels so good.
No, no, no.
It feels so good.
Hurry up.
I'm surprised.
Are you okay?
It feels so good.
It feels so good that I'm sweating.
You've grown a lot.
It feels so good.
It's my turn.
I'll make you feel good again.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
You've grown a lot.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
It's hot.
You like it, don't you?
It feels so good.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It's getting harder and harder.
I can't do it.
You can't?
What's wrong?
What is it?
Do you want me to help you?
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
I'm going to lie down.
Is it bad?
You like your boobs, don't you?
No.
It's hot.
It's okay. You'll feel better.
No.
It's okay. Let me help you.
It's hot.
Oh, no.
It's okay. You'll feel better.
Wait a minute.
It's going to come out.
It's hot.
Wait a minute.
It's dangerous.
Are you listening to me?
It's hot.
It's dangerous.
It's amazing.
You slept a lot.
It's okay.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
It's still big.
I can't do it.
It's okay.
What's wrong?
I'll put a blanket on you.
I'll make you feel better.
It's okay.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's intense.
Is it intense?
It's big and it feels good.
It's dangerous.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to go.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You slept a lot.
It's dangerous.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It's intense.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Thank you.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I want you to feel good.
It's hot.
It's intense.
You slept too much.
It's dangerous.
You're sweating a lot.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'm glad.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I can't do it anymore.
You can do it.
I can't do it.
I want to get you out of here.
I'm sweating.
I can't do it.
I want you to get me out of here.
It's hot.
I can't do it.
I'm sleeping.
It's amazing.
I'm glad you feel good.
I'm glad.
I can't do it anymore.
You can do it.
It's still big.
You can move as you like.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I'm glad you feel good.
It feels good.
It's getting bigger.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
I'm sweating a lot.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
I'm glad you feel good.
I can't do it.
I'm sweating a lot.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I'm sweating a lot.
You're sweating a lot.
Come here.
You're tired, aren't you?
Did you feel good?
You can sweat a lot from now on.
I can't do it.
Hello.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Thank you for your hard work.
I had a good consultation, and I'm in a hotel now.
Really?
I'm glad.
I'm glad you're tired.
I talked to Shinji.
Really?
What did you talk about?
It's just a morning greeting.
I talked to him a little.
I see.
I'm glad.
Shinji is a good guy, isn't he?
He's a good guy.
That's right.
He's a funny guy.
Is that so?
I'm glad.
How are you?
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Are you sick?
Don't push yourself too hard. Take some medicine.
I'm fine.
You don't look well.
Is that so?
You've been working hard for Shinji and me for the past two months.
That's right.
You might be tired.
Take some medicine.
Take a break.
That's right.
I'll take a break.
I'll be back by noon tomorrow.
I see.
Take care of Shinji.
I'll be waiting for you.
All right.
See you.
That's great.
Dad was happy, too.
It's hot.
Drink a lot.
That's great.
Shinji.
Is there anything else you want to do?
It's hot.
Do you want to drink more?
You can drink as much as you want.
It's hot.
Is it good?
It feels so good.
It's hot.
Do you want to drink more?
Do you want me to lick your hand?
It feels so good.
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
I'll put this in your mouth.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
That's great.
It's hard again.
It's hot.
That's great.
You can drink as much as you want.
It's hot.
It feels so good.
Un, un, un, un...
Say cheese?
Chomp!
Oh...
Ahhhh!
It hurts.
I can't do it.
I feel sick.
hey, hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey!
You can do it!
Go, go, go!
This feels so good
I'll scratch you next time
Does it feel good?
It feels so good
Amazing
You can do it!
No, no, no
I can't do it anymore
No, go, go, go!
Go, go, go!
This feels so good
Amazing
Go, go, go!
This feels so good
Do you want me to scratch you?
Come here
This feels so good
Do you want me to scratch you?
Go, go, go!
This feels so good
One more time
Go, go, go!
This feels so good
You did your best
What's wrong?
Can I sleep with you tonight?
Okay
Good night
Sorry, I was sleeping
You were sleeping soundly
Dad will come back tomorrow, right?
Yes, he will
I won't do things like today anymore
Can you keep it a secret from dad?
Okay
I won't bother you anymore
I'll look for a job and live alone
What?
I want to live with you, dad and Sunny
No, you can't
It's okay, I'll keep it a secret
Then we can be together
No, you're being too sweet
Really?
No, you can't
I don't think so
I want to be with you
But
It's impossible to live alone right away
I'll treat you as my mom
Can I be your mom?
No, you can't
Really?
I'm sorry for bothering you
What are you talking about?
You can bother me a lot from now on
I can't bother you anymore
No, you can bother me a lot
Look at me
It's okay
I said I can't bother you anymore
Why?
Don't you want to touch mom's boobs?
No, I don't
Really?
Don't you want to touch them?
No, I don't
You're lying
You can touch them a lot
Okay
Can you touch them a lot?
I can't
You can touch them a lot
You can touch them a lot from now on
It's a secret to dad
I said I can't bother you anymore
It's okay
I want you to bother me
No
You're a coward
Coward?
It hurts
Do you want me to be spoiled?
It feels good
Do you like it?
You're a coward
It feels good
You can touch them a lot
You're amazing
I can't see your face
It feels good
It hurts
Can you make me feel better?
It feels good
You've grown up
It feels good?
It feels good
You like it, don't you?
Can you stand up?
You've grown up
Can you show me your face?
It feels good
You're growing up
You can't stand up?
Why?
You said you'd listen to me
It's a waste of time, isn't it?
It feels good
What's wrong?
You wanted to do this
You're rubbing a lot
Oh, no
You're growing up
It feels good
It feels good?
I'm glad you feel good
It feels good
Oh, no
What?
I'll pinch you
It feels good, doesn't it?
You can't move it
You said it felt good
It feels good
You look like you're in a good mood
Oh, no
Oh, no?
Wait a minute
Don't cry
I'm not
I can't do this
It feels good
Come here
You've done your best, so it's always hard
It feels good
I'm sorry
I can't do this
I'll move a lot for you
It feels good
I can't do this
You did a lot
Can you do more?
I want to do more
Really?
It feels good
I can't do this
This is amazing
It feels good
I can't do this
This is amazing
It feels good
Can you do more?
I want to breathe
It feels good
This is amazing
I love this
It feels good
I can't do this
It feels good now
It feels good
You put your head on my chest
You put your head on my chest?
I'm so happy
I'm so sticky
Thank you
Thank you, mom
You called me mom for the first time
I'm so happy
But, it's okay
I have to do the baby shower
You don't have to
I have to do it
I don't want to
I can't bother you anymore
I'm not bothering you
I'm not bothering you anymore
Is it okay?
I can't touch your breast anymore
I can't help it
Why are you coming closer?
I don't want you to leave me
It's okay
Don't say that
Come closer
I'm home
Why are you two together?
Because we're a family
I was waiting for you to come home
I see. Thank you
How was it?
It went well
Really?
I'm glad
Let's eat together
I'll help you with your mom's cooking
Really?
Let's eat together
I'm looking forward to it
You're back to normal
I need to cheer up
Don't you have a souvenir?
I do
I'm looking forward to it
I'll carry your luggage
It's heavy
There are a lot of documents
Let's eat
Wait a minute
I want to eat