I'm not sure if it's a good thing or a bad thing, but I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to
do.
It's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you
want to do, and I think it's a good thing to be able to do what you want to do.
​​​ ​The screen—​ ​​
I guess a man can't have a girlfriend if he doesn't go all out.
Same sex with a girlfriend?
That's nice.
I can do it every day for free.
All right.
Now that I've got a part-time job, let's go to the men's locker room.
Today, I'm going to serve you with all my heart.
Thank you.
What?
Why?
Please don't tell him.
I'm surprised.
I won't tell him.
Why?
Actually...
I see.
I've been thinking about it, and I can't get my parents to pay me back.
I've been thinking about it, but...
I found out on the Internet that one step is a man's death.
I see.
But it's just touching the skin.
It's not cheating, is it?
That's...
That's right.
Then be a man.
Yes.
I'm going to start.
Excuse me.
I'm going to apply the oil.
Yes.
I was surprised.
It's sudden.
I was surprised, too.
Please don't tell him.
I can't tell him.
My heart is still pounding.
I didn't expect my best friend to be here.
That's my line.
Do you often go to places like this?
Sometimes.
Really?
No, I don't.
But you're angry.
Are you tired?
Are you angry?
Yes.
Is your leg okay?
I'm sorry.
That's not good.
Why?
Your lymph is clogged, so I'm just flushing it.
I see.
Yes.
Your lymph is clogged.
I see.
Excuse me.
Your buttocks are swollen.
I see.
I'm going to massage your buttocks.
You're out of breath.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Your buttocks are very hard.
Your lymph is clogged.
I see.
I have to flush it.
Your lymph is flowing and it's getting warmer.
I'm sorry.
It feels good when you massage here.
How do you feel?
I see.
Do you like here?
I feel strange.
Really?
Your lymph is flowing.
I have to flush your lymph.
I see.
Please look up.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Your lymph is flowing.
I'm sorry.
Do you like here?
Yes.
I see.
Do you always get a massage here?
Yes.
Really?
It's amazing.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm going to flush your lymph.
It's amazing.
I was surprised.
It's bigger than I thought.
Really?
It's amazing.
It's three times bigger than me.
Really?
It's amazing.
I've never seen such a big lymph.
Can I flush your lymph?
I can't.
I don't want to be scolded.
I just want to look at your lymph.
I'm your best friend.
It's okay.
I just want to look at your lymph.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
When did you get such a big lymph?
I was surprised.
Don't look at me.
It's amazing when I take off my panties.
Can I hold your lymph?
I can't.
Why?
I'll do it for you.
It's amazing.
I can't hold it with one hand.
I was surprised.
It's amazing.
It must have been hard for you and your girlfriend.
No.
I don't have a girlfriend.
I've never seen such a big lymph.
Wait a minute.
I can't.
It's amazing.
I was surprised.
Wait a minute.
You can still take it out, right?
No.
It's okay.
Don't touch it.
I can't?
It's close.
Why?
It's amazing.
You've just come out, but you're already so energetic.
I can't.
You can still take it out.
It's amazing.
You've just come out, but you're already so energetic.
Did you feel good?
I felt good.
Do you always come out like this?
I don't know.
It's amazing.
How do you feel from behind?
I feel good.
Really?
Have you ever been attacked from behind?
I don't think so.
Really?
Have you ever been attacked from behind?
It hurts.
I'll touch you.
It's easier to feel from behind.
How about this?
I feel good.
Really?
It's amazing.
You've grown up again.
You're so energetic.
It's amazing.
It hurts.
You have a bump on your butt.
I have a bump.
Your body temperature has risen, so your boobs may be hot.
Feel my boobs with your butt.
I can't do that.
I want you to feel my boobs and feel good.
It's harder than before.
I'll touch you again.
Feel my boobs.
I can't do that.
I'll touch you.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
You have a bump on your butt.
You have a bump on your butt three times.
My best friend gave me a ride.
It was a good ride.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
You're charging your phone again.
I'm sorry. I don't have enough money for a part-time job.
What part-time job are you doing now?
It's my day off today.
What?
It's a joke.
Don't surprise me.
If you do a part-time job, you'll smell like alcohol.
I don't know.
Don't do such a job.
I know.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Please share this video.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Please share this video.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Please share this video.
Thank you for watching this video.
I'm so angry at you.
I don't know what will happen if I do a part-time job.
And...
My best friend is coming.
Don't tell anyone.
I won't.
Today...
I'll give you a lot of services.
Okay.
Go to bed.
I'll cover you.
Can I take this off?
I'm fine.
Really?
Don't worry.
I'll take it off.
Thank you.
I'm embarrassed.
Excuse me.
I'll apply oil.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Is this your first time?
This is my first time.
Really?
You're in a good mood.
Thank you.
It's dangerous.
You're going to hit me.
You're very sticky.
I'm nervous.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
You hit my thigh.
Do you like here?
I like here.
What's wrong?
I'm embarrassed.
You're stuck.
I'm stuck.
Is this your first time?
This is my first time.
Do you like here?
I like here.
I want to tease you more.
Get on my back.
What's wrong?
I feel good.
You're very sticky.
How do you feel?
Do you like here?
I feel good.
It's hot.
It's hot?
I want you to feel my hand.
I'm sorry.
Do you always feel like this?
How do you feel?
I feel good.
You're amazing.
I'm weak.
Your buttocks are moving.
Relax.
You're very cute.
Your buttocks are full.
I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
You're very cute.
I'm sorry.
Are you tired?
I'll give you a special service.
It's hot.
It hurts more.
More?
You're greedy.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
I'm glad.
You're amazing.
It's hot.
It's hard.
It's hard again.
I want to do something better.
It's hot.
It hurts.
It's rubbing.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I rubbed it on your neck.
Do you like this?
I like it.
It's getting harder.
My neck is getting harder.
It's tingling.
It's hot.
I'm tired.
It's amazing.
It's tingling.
It's scary.
It hurts.
You're breathing hard.
You can't drink it.
Be patient.
It's amazing.
You've been patient all day.
I've been patient all day.
You have a lot of hair.
It's amazing.
You can't drink it.
I'm sorry.
You're sweating a lot.
Why?
Because I'm a woman.
It's amazing.
I want to drink it.
That's not good.
I haven't been doing it lately.
What are you doing?
I'm playing games.
Is that so?
If I were you, I'd do it every day.
I don't want to.
What?
You're sweating a lot.
Look at me.
It's an accident.
I can't help it.
You're sweating a lot.
It feels good.
I can't help it.
It's amazing.
You're sweating a lot.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's intense.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'm sweating a lot.
You're sweating a lot.
You're crying.
Can I move more?
I love you.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
You're sweating a lot.
Here we go!
You're doing great!
Oh wow
It's moving around in your body
I make things worse
I feel sick
Feels so good
I like this place
I can't do it.
I'll do it.
Bring it to me.
It feels good.
My back is moving more than before.
My ears are weak.
I can't do it.
Do you like it here?
It's going to be wet.
I want you to put it in.
It's coming in.
How is it?
It's amazing.
I can't do it.
It's getting bigger than before.
It's getting more comfortable.
What should I do?
I can't do it.
I don't want to be angry at you.
But it feels good.
I can't do it.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
I can't do it.
Can you see it?
Look at me.
It's amazing.
I can't do it.
Can I do it again?
It's so hard that I can't do it.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
I want to move more.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
I want to move more.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
It's still hard.
I can't do it.
Can I do it again?
It's so hard.
I want to move more.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I want to move more.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I slept a lot.
I'm happy.
I'm glad.
Did you feel good?
Did you get a little tired?
Thank you.
I'll keep it a secret from him.
It's a secret.
This is not a betrayal to a best friend.
It's just an accident.
You're not hiding anything from me, are you?
I knew it.
I've been thinking it was strange for a long time.
You have an account called Tachi and Tsubasa, right?
What?
You also have an avatar.
Avatar?
You still don't know?
If you got a higher score than me, tell me.
I'm sorry.
It's an online game.
I was in a hurry.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
I'm very soft.
You are cute.
It feels good.
Do you like it?
It's scary.
It feels good.
By the way,
You haven't kissed me yet.
That's right.
Hey.
If I kiss you, will you be my sidekick?
Will you be my sidekick?
No, I won't.
You won't be my sidekick?
I'm not your sidekick.
Is that so?
It's very soft.
It's soft.
Can I do it more?
It's very soft.
It's very good.
If I do something like this, I get excited.
Do you get excited?
It's not enough just to hold you.
Let me lick you.
If I do something like this, I get excited.
Do you get excited?
I'm sorry I can't do this all the time.
Let me lick you.
I'm barely standing.
I'm starting to get sleepy.
I feel great.
I've never done this to him.
I love you so much.
Can I lick you?
His chest is so big.
I feel great.
It's hot.
It's delicious.
My voice is getting hoarse.
Let me take off my clothes.
It's hot.
My voice is getting hoarse.
I'm getting excited.
It's hot.
My cheeks are getting hot.
I've never done this to anyone.
It's a secret.
It's hot.
My cheeks are getting hot.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared.
Ouch!
Come here.
Stand here.
Dad, finally you get used to our busy lives visually.
Could you stretch vidéo
I'm going to lose muscles
Ah!
Wow!
Oh, my goodness!
It's so hot.
Help me more
I'm fine
Oh!
Oh, my god!
I'm sweating!
Oh!
Oh, my god!
It's been a long time since I've had a baby, but I'm so happy to have a baby.
You've lost a lot of weight.
I've never seen you like this before.
I'm so happy.
Can I do a surgery I've never done before?
Yes.
Can I remove this?
Can I do a surgery I've never done before?
You're getting bigger.
Lie down.
What is this?
It's embarrassing.
You like this place, don't you?
Is this your first time?
Yes.
I've never done it before.
Can I pour hot water on you?
Yes.
I'll pour a lot on you.
Is it getting better?
Yes.
It's hot.
I'll put your hair back.
It's sticky.
Both of you are wet.
I'll lick you.
It's disgusting.
I'll lick you more.
I washed your butt.
It's disgusting.
I'll lick you.
I'll lick you more.
It's disgusting.
I'm out of breath.
I'll lick you more.
It's disgusting.
I'm out of breath.
Don't go there.
It's disgusting.
I'll touch you.
Don't go there.
It's disgusting.
I'll lick you more.
It's hot.
It's getting hotter.
You can do it.
You're still full.
It's hot.
You can do it.
Show me your butt.
It's hot.
You can do it.
Do it again.
It's hot.
You can't cheat anymore.
You can't do it.
It's hot.
You can't cheat anymore.
Raise your legs.
It's hot.
You can do it.
You're going to stay here tonight, right?
I have a class tomorrow.
Stay here.
It's decided.
Let's drink more.
I'll wait for you.
What are you doing?
I want to drink curry.
I'm hungry.
What?
What did you say?
I'm scared.
I'll be back soon.
Why?
Did you get depressed?
He's weak.
He's a weak drinker.
Are you okay?
You're weak.
You don't have to do this.
Welcome back.
You haven't slept yet.
I just started drinking.
You haven't eaten yet.
You're very active.
Are you?
Are you going to drink that?
You're a strong drinker.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I think I can drink this much.
Are you full?
You're drinking a lot.
You're cool.
It's good.
It's good because I made it.
You're right.
You're a good drinker.
Where's the snack?
Are you okay?
Thank you for watching.