Okay.
My name is Hongzhi
I've been in Tokyo for three years to get into a university in Tokyo.
Although | am always very grateful
The support of my family
| don't know how to say
Always feel like a failure, there are many things
Always a failure
Put the oranges in again
Rarely put the envelope into the ah
For Hongzhi How's it going?
Did you have a good meal?
This year's typhoon is very strong
Just harvesting a small amount of oranges
Need to eat more vitamin supplements Oh
Letter from Dad
Take care of yourself
But even if you eat a lot, you can not change the reality ah
What an asshole.
But there are so many oranges that | can't eat them all by myself.
Try it for your neighbors who have been taking care of me.
(Starring Kyouhana Orange)
Just now | said | was always taken care of
Maybe people don't know what | think. Yes, this ts it.
Let's take a good look
But, Kyo Orange
Why is it always so defenseless?
Hongzhi ah, what happened to you
My family sent me a lot of oranges, so | wanted to give them to you.
-Really, thank you. - No.
If you can, would you like to have a cup of tea?
-This is not necessary. - It's okay, no need to be polite.
-Come on in. - Is it really possible?
-Spoiled. - Okay.
-Please come in. - Excuse me.
-Please drink. - Thank you very much.
| did not know that your hometown is a farming village
Because my hometown is a relatively remote rural area
But | live in Tokyo, and | long for the countryside.
There are no convenience stores, no good food, really nothing.
-Is it? -Yes.
But the countryside is beautiful, right? And can be very romantic
Oh, no. Wait.
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry. - It's okay. I'll get a towel.
What should | do?
No, right?
Orange King, you need to change these Oh
Really? That's great!
-Are you okay? I'm really sorry. - I'm sorry about the mess.
-Are you okay? You didn't get your clothes wet? - I'm fine. I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm not careful.
| have fallen again
I'm such an idiot.
This place also has
I'm really sorry!
It should be fine, right?
What is it? Wait a minute.
-Wait, what? No, it's not. - | can't help it, Kyo.
Pull it out
So comfortable
Amazing!
Seducing me like this
No way!
Why? I don't have one.
No, please.
No way!
I'm going to cum. - It's too intense. - | can't.
You've been seducing me, haven't you?
What is it?
What are you doing? Wait
Do you know what you are doing?
Sorry, | couldn't resist!
| have a husband!
I'm sorry | couldn't help seeing your ass.
I'm really sorry.
Although such a thing can not this time to keep it secret ah
-What are you doing? Wait! - | want to continue.
-No, | already said that. - Great ass.
-Kyo Orange is so sexy. - No way!
| can't, please.
No way!
-Wait, | can't. - Shit, Kyo can't help it.
Amazing!
Already not working
It's really, really over.
-l can't - It's okay, Kyo.
-Great. - Can't go on.
No way!
-That's great. Kyo’'s ass is great. - What's this?
No, wait, it's not working.
Wait, this is no longer possible
I can't do that.
So excited, right?
-l can't look at it. - But it's wet.
No, | can't!
Can not break ah
I'm so shy, | can't.
No, don't!
-| can't. - Superb!
So shy
No way!
No, don't!
So intense!
No way!
It's going to be an orgasm
It's great. Keep showing me.
That's right, lift it up here.
Give me your ass. That's right, that's great.
Superb!
It's very erotic.
No way!
-| can't do it. - It's wet.
No. No.
Fingers in
No, this does not work ah can not move like this
So comfortable
-Go on. - No, it's not working.
No, | can't. I'm going to come.
No, | can't.
| can't.
| can't do it anymore, I'm coming.
Super Porn
No, my fingers are not working.
-What's this? - Can't you?
So cool!
No, it's not working anymore.
This won't work
Great!
No, don't! It's stuck!
I can't! No!
I'm going to come. | can't.
Already not working
I can't.
This won't work
No, | can't. I'm going to come.
High tide
So comfortable, right?
So intense!
I'm going to come. | can't. Wait a minute.
High tide
-| can't. No. - It's comfortable.
-| can't. - It's already wet.
I can't, | can't, it's so comfortable.
| can't.
| can't. My fingers are so comfortable.
I can't.
It's time for another orgasm
High tide
Wet
-l can't - My pussy Is so wet.
-It's not working - It's wet.
-| can't. | can't. I can't. - It's really good.
It's so comfortable! It's great! It's so comfortable!
-Wait ah no no ah - let me also comfortable can it
-Although it's comfortable. - It can be, right? Continue to be comfortable, right?
-But | can't. - Please.
Continue to make me comfortable
Go on, | want to go on, go on.
This ass
Amazing!
-It's great. - It's great.
My pussy feels so good inside!
Super Comfortable
No, I can't.
eo.
Hold the most inside.
So cool!
| can't. I'm going to come.
Great!
Already not working
No, | can't.
Continue ah yes, hands up, yes, so comfortable
Superb!
I can't do it!
So cool!
I can't do it inside
Amazing!
So powerful.
It's awesome!
It's like a poof, poof, poof.
This won't work
This is going to be an orgasm
| can't, I'm coming.
Amazing!
-Right, let's do it again, right? - No, don't.
It's comfortable to be wet, right?
So cool!
Amazing!
| can't do that.
No, | can't.
So comfortable
| can't, It's so good!
Waist can not ah completely can not
I can't do it. It's so comfortable. | can't.
It's going to be an orgasm
High tide
Wait!
I can't! No! I can't!
| can't... | can't... | can't... I'm coming.
This is too intense
It's going to be an orgasm
| can't do it anymore, I'm coming.
That's right, not yet, let's continue ah
So powerful ah completely can not be softened
Come here
Amazing!
So cool!
So comfortable
It's great! It's inside!
Isn't it very comfortable to move?
This means that It is going to be an orgasm
It's awesome!
So cool!
So comfortable
I can't.
Amazing!
Continue
I can't do it inside
-Very comfortable, right? - Very comfortable.
Amazing!
In this case, the pussy is going to come.
It's bad
| can not, so good, so good ah
This won't work
Wait a minute!
Wait, it's going to be an orgasm.
Come here
So cool!
It's the best inside
So comfortable
-It's great. - It's great.
| can't do it with the rod inside
No, it's so strange.
It's time for another orgasm
It's going to be an orgasm
| can't, 'm coming again.
| can't.
No, don't!
ar
oe oe
-| can't do it anymore. - How about moving like this?
No way!
Puzzy Puzzy is great!
i can't... | can't... | can't... 'm so comfortable.
No, don't!
No, | cant.
| can't.
It's inside!
The meat stick plunges in and out
I can't. Wait.
I can't, I'm coming. | can't, I'm coming.
High tide
-Superb. Go on. - Not anymore.
Already not working
-I can't! | can't! - It's so comfortable!
| can't, it's so good, it's great.
| can't, I'm going to come, so good!
This is too intense can not ah
| can't, my pussy's going to come.
| can't. I'm going to come.
Orgasm again
Super Porn
What's up?
Already not working
i can't.
-| can't do it. | can't do it. It's awesome. - It's awesome.
Amazing!
So cool!
Resisted
It's going to be an orgasm
I can't. I can't. 'm coming.
| can't. I'm coming. I'm coming.
| can't. | can't. I'm going to come.
I can't. I'm going to come. | can't.
icant. | can't anymore.
So powerful, so intense.
i can't.
I can't, I can't, please, | can't.
-It's too intense. - I'm going to cum.
| can't. I'm going to come.
lam also about to cum
-I'm gonna come. - |'m gonna cum.
No way!
So many
But, Kyo, you are also very comfortable, you said.
But... this... this kind of thing...
It's really not working inside
Yes, as you can see, this is the relationship
Of course, there is a follow-up
What are you doing here today?
I'm really sorry.
A few days later, | went to Kyo's house to apologize after reflecting.
Not really
That's the thing
-You said that. - I'm not going to college. I'm going back home.
| have to go to work for the sake of my family
This is my own responsibility | will be responsible for
| no longer have the value of living
Hongzhi Head up
You'll graduate next year. It's okay.
And you're still young, you'll definitely meet better ones.
-But... - Your parents will be worried if you do this.
Then
In that case, please help me clean the toilet.
Have you forgiven me?
Thank you very much
lam not good at cleaning toilets
Look here
Is it moldy?
-Yeah, it's easy to get mold in here. - Yeah, it's completely unwashable.
-Yes. - Mold is not good for health.
Yeah, a lot, right?
So, what should | do? | haven't been able to clean it up.
Can you clean this?
Yes, this ah actually ah | have done before
-It's true. - There should be no problem.
Great! Helped me a lot!
-After that, you see, over there. - Yes.
-There's more over there. - Here.
-It's really hard here. - It is, isn't it?
What should | do?
-I'm not tall enough either. - That's right.
-| can't do that. - Yes.
There should be no other
No, wait, what is it?
| couldn't resist
-Wait, | can't. Calm down. - I'm calm.
-Kyo is so charming, | can't help it. - No, wait!
-The smell of this ass is great. - No way.
Wait ah | said no ah
Wait, let me go, please!
I can't.
Wait!
-Kyo Orange is so excited. - Wait!
Can't stop at all
Wait, | can't.
Wait a minute!
Kyo Orange
Let me go!
-No, you can't do that. - But, but it's exciting here.
-Great!
No, wait.
No, | can't.
So comfortable. Wait, | can't.
Wait, | can't.
So good ah wait already can not
No, let me go!
Wait, it's going to be an orgasm.
So comfortable
-Let me open my ass. - Wait, no, no, no.
It's great.
No! No! Wait!
| can't, my fingers can't
- can't. Wait, I'm going in. - Great.
No, | can't.
-That's great. Here it is. - No way.
Two went in
Amazing!
No, I can't.
| can't do it anymore. It's so comfortable.
Amazing!
It's going to be an orgasm
High tide
-| can't. - Get in there!
Why? It's comfortable, right?
-l can't! No! I can't! - Why?
-| have a husband. - I've always wanted this.
‘ll use my mouth. I'll help you with my mouth. - You can use your mouth, can't you? Please.
So comfortable
Can't help it, can you?
| saw you seducing me and | couldn't resist
Use your mouth today, you have to hold back
-You can't put it in. - No.
So cool!
-Oh, no, | can't help it. Give it to me. - No, | have a husband.
No way!
Just rubbing just rubbing can it
Amazing!
So powerful ah so hot ah meat stick friction to
Super Comfortable
Amazing!
Continue
So comfortable
So powerful, so hot, so hard!
Orange Kyung's ass |s great!
So cool!
Here? Hold it here, the meat stick against it.
Amazing!
It's awesome, the meat stick is so thick!
Rub yourself in ah
Because it's so comfortable
It's getting hot
So comfortable
So powerful ah so intense ah
Oh no. So comfortable.
It's bad
I'm going to shoot.
Amazing!
So powerful, all shot out
It's not working!
| also want to absolutely stop
However, although there is such an awareness
| don't know why | couldn't resist and cooked for me personally before.
By the way, isn't mommy a good cook too?
But | was always by myself
Eat outside every time
This is not good for health
That's right, today.
No, right?
This
Men really can not help ah
Today is an exceptional day!
What do you want to do?
Great!
-Is it okay? -Today is the exception.
So comfortable
-Why are you shooting? - This thing.
Because a little bit of excitement, I'm sorry.
-It's so erotic. - It's awesome.
It's amazing. It's shaking all the time.
Super comfortable. - Yes. - Comfortable?
But, the rod keeps shaking.
This side also want to lick a little Oh
| guess so.
Amazing!
-The rod ts so thick. - So shy.
So cool!
Super Comfortable
Do you like me to lick?
Licking so comfortable ah
| said today is an exception.
It's shaking all the time
-That's great. - No way.
Do you want to continue the thing just now ah
Sorry.
You still want to continue, right?
-Can you do it? -There's no way.
Amazing!
-Is that so? - That's right.
So good! It's even harder than just now!
It's so hot and thick
So comfortable
So good, so hard and very tasty
-Super comfortable, yes. - Really?
So cool!
-It's great! It's so comfortable! - Is it comfortable?
Amazing!
So comfortable
It's bad
All included
-I'm going to cum. - It's so good.
This is awesome!
I'm going to cum. Wait.
Oh no, I'm going to cum.
Is it possible?
Shot
Ejaculation
Why?
Although | did not expect
In front of me, Kyo Orange was doing yoga to seduce me
Yes
| don't know how to do it myself.
Can you come and help me confirm?
Good
What's up? You know what?
| want you to confirm from below
-From below. - Yes, from below.
Here is the bar
-Is that right? -Yes.
Thank you ah you watch oh
Wait, what a great gesture!
-What are you talking about? - Nothing.
How is it? Have you been watching it well?
Yes, I'm watching.
Okay, then.
What's this?
Because of Kyo Orange suddenly so
-Then I'm counting on you. - Wait.
It's awesome!
So comfortable
This won't work
Super Comfortable
The ass is so powerful!
| can't. It's holding.
So comfortable
Wait, it's going to be an orgasm.
So powerful, so comfortable
Amazing!
It's going to be an orgasm
Against a good comfortable place
Resisted
| will continue to make you comfortable
Is that so?
Couldn't resist
| couldn't resist either
Wait!
Amazing!
So shy
Great! So excited!
Amazing!
| can't, it's so good!
It's going to be an orgasm
This way, | can't stop!
il can't.
I'm coming. I'm coming.
-I can't. - That's great.
| am also very hot
Such friction oh
So comfortable
Amazing!
It's awesome!
It's hot, it's hard!
So cool!
It's going to be an orgasm
-Is that right? -Not anymore.
Not enough!
Superb!
Want you to touch my pussy
Touch the pussy, right?
So comfortable
Amazing!
It's too intense, so comfortable
-| can't. | can't. It's so good. - Is this it?
| can't. I'm going to come.
Amazing!
So cool!
It's bad
| couldn't resist
I'm going to shoot.
Shot
Together with the orgasm Oh
Sorry
| have to think of a topic for my thesis, so |'m going back.
vo
je: tke
Gone
Okay, no need to be polite, I'll clean itiup for you..
It really does not matter, | will do it myself
But, because the rent is also very expensive, so | may have to move out.
-It's really hard. - Is it?
-But clean it well. - No, | don't use my own room.
It's okay. Leave it to me.
But what to do?
Then
This is a towel bar
-No. - This is too much dust, right?
Sorry
These things should be organized so that it will be better ah
Good
gear ee
There are panties there, too!
-That won't work. - Won't it?
-Very shy. - No.
Il can't.
The skirt is too short
You didn't see it, did you?
-| don't see it at all. - Really?
Wait, what are you doing?
-The taste of Hongji is great. - Wait, don't do that.
Do not like this ah
-Wait, there's something. - I'm really sorry.
Really don't need it
-That's great. - Give it back to me.
-Let me help you clean up. - Sorry.
No laundry ah
No, sometimes it will be several days to wash
Sure enough, it's like this when you live alone.
So, these difficulties are
-Pornographic material. - Sorry, no.
-Let me see. - No, no, no.
I have not seen ah
-No, it's not. - It's like a nipple.
Amazing!
-Masturbate by yourself with this ah - No, no
-| wish you wouldn't do that. - That's great.
So erotic!
No, it really can't.
Amazing!
Such a feeling!
Hongzhi Is this how you masturbate?
This thing
Yes, you are a man ah
Amazing!
Everyone is very sexy ah
| feel so erotic now
What are you talking about?
This way
No
-What's wrong with you? - No, | was just looking.
-That's right. - Yes, I'm sorry.
Then, we must wash the quilt.
Good
-Wait, that tickles. - It's okay.
-Wait, | want you to help me catch it. - Where ts it?
| don't know what happened.
-But... - It's itchy here.
Can you help me to confirm
No, it should be fine.
Then, come closer.
But
- didn't see it. - Really?
-Keep coming closer. - No, wait, what are you doing?
-I'm close. - Am 1?
Confirmation
| haven't tried looking at it like this, but
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
-Too close, too close. - So erotic.
Don't do that!
-You're blowing on me. | hate it. - Sorry.
No, wait, | can't help it.
Let me see, always tempting me
So powerful, so intense.
-I'm so excited too.
Amazing!
So comfortable
-No, wait. - Let me see.
So shy!
-So erotic. - No way.
So cool!
-Wait, your pussy is wet. - No, it’s not. If you lick it like this.
Lick it!
| can't. It's so comfortable.
Amazing!
Wait ah can not ah do not do ah
So intense!
| can't, it's so good!
Wait, it's not working anymore.
Already not working
I'm going to have an orgasm, so good!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't.
| can't. I'm going to come.
It's going to be an orgasm
-| can't! No! - That's great!
| can't. I'm going to come.
Fingers are great!
Amazing!
| can't, it's so wet and comfortable.
Already not working
| can not ah so intense ah
Wait, I'm coming. I'm coming.
Great!
Very comfortable, right?
Keep giving me that ass, by the way.
So shy
-It's so shy to rub it. - It's really exciting!
It's not working.
So shy
-No, I can't. - It's awesome. It's stuck.
It's holding!
-That's good, isn't it? - No, | can't. | can't.
-So shy. - Keep giving me your ass.
This does not look good!
So shy
Amazing!
Great! Fingers in!
| can't do it anymore. Put your finger in.
Puzzy puzzy can't do it No
No, | can't.
So comfortable
It's inside!
Amazing!
No, | can't
It's going to be an orgasm
-Go on. - | can't. I'm going to come.
| can't do it anymore. I'm going to come.
Amazing!
Superb!
| want to report you
So comfortable
So cool!
Super comfortable ah
Already not working
So powerful, so hard
So powerful, so thick!
So comfortable
This is bad
Amazing!
Licking so comfortable ah
So great! | want to continue
-Can | continue? -Yes.
So erotic!
Open your own pussy to see
See it
-It's so erotic. - Watching it with all my heart makes me excited.
-Is this okay? -Yes, it's very comfortable.
Amazing!
The ass is so comfortable
So comfortable
So cool!
So powerful ah, against me
-ls that okay? -That's great. | want the inside.
Amazing!
It's going to be an orgasm
So comfortable
Amazing!
The meat stick into the most inside
-So comfortable. - Super comfortable.
| can't. I'm going to come.
Great! The climax!
Already not working
-It's so good. It's so good. - I'm gonna come.
Amazing!
| can't. I'm going to come.
The head of the turtle went in
Amazing!
Already not working
| can't. I'm going to come.
-| can't. It's good, isn't it? - No, I'm going to come.
Amazing!
Already not working
It's time for another orgasm
To climax again to climax
Amazing!
-Great! - Go on, let's go on!
-It's hot. - Is it hot?
Superb
Come here
So happy
Super Porn
So cool!
Amazing!
Super slippery so cool!
So comfortable
Amazing!
It's inside the pussy
So comfortable
Amazing!
-It's great. - It's great.
-Puzzy puzzy. - That's great.
I'm very happy. Look at me with affection.
It's so wet. It's so exciting.
I can't. I'm going to come.
So comfortable
So powerful.
Amazing!
So comfortable
Already not working
It's going to be an orgasm
Continue
Amazing!
So cool!
So powerful, so comfortable
-| can't. | came. - It was so good.
We are comfortable together | can not
So comfortable
Amazing!
| can't. 'm going to come.
It's going to be an orgasm
: Pe
-That's great. - That's great.
So powerful No, no, no.
So comfortable
It's going to be an orgasm
Wait, it's time for another climax.
Amazing!
See
So cool!
So thick
Already not working
Super Comfortable
-Keep moving like that. - Keep moving.
Amazing!
This its so cool!
Resisted
I’m coming. | can't. I'm coming.
Wait, it’s going to be an orgasm.
Amazing!
I can't. It's so comfortable.
It's awesome! | can't do it! My pussy feels so good inside!
Orgasm again
-1 can't. - So comfortable.
Amazing!
-| can't do it anymore. I'm going to come. - | can't help it.
-I’m cumming. I'm cumming. - I'm coming.
Great! All shot out!
Amazing!
It's bad
All shot out
Afterwards
With my ass
Let's get you excited!
www.x18r.com