Top with sliced justice pickles
and season with a pinch of pepper.
What are you making?
I'm going to make a salad with cabbage.
This is cream stew.
You like it, don't you?
Do you want to try it?
I'm going to use a spoon.
It's hot.
I was surprised.
How does it taste?
Is it good?
It's hot.
I'll give you the toy.
I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough.
It's been a while since I've been here, so I'm going to take a look around.
It's amazing.
It's more beautiful than I thought.
Is this a pond?
It's a pond.
It's amazing.
It's a dead tree.
It's beautiful.
It's like a painting.
It's reflecting because it's yellow.
It's like Mt.Fuji.
That's right.
What are you doing?
It's like a painting.
It's beautiful.
There is no one here.
I was surprised.
Something is flying.
What is it?
Is it a fish?
What?
It's flying.
I'm scared.
Don't push me.
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
I'm scared.
Stop it.
I was surprised.
Let's go.
I was scared.
I was surprised.
It's a joke.
The road is narrow, but it's okay.
Did you see something?
I bought a fish.
Can I touch it?
Yes.
It's amazing.
How is it?
It's delicious.
It takes time to chew it.
I'll taste it.
Fried chicken is delicious, isn't it?
Wait a minute.
I was about to turn it over.
What will you do in the future?
What do you mean by the future?
I'll get a normal job.
What do you mean?
I'll talk to you when I get a normal job.
Will you talk to me when you get a normal job?
What?
What do you mean?
I'll talk to you when I get a normal job.
Is that so?
I want to talk to you.
Do you want to talk to me?
Maybe...
Will you marry me?
No.
I'll prepare a ring this time.
A ring?
Yes.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
I'm happy.
Yes. It's a ring.
I'll wear a ring this time.
What are you filming?
I wanted to film you washing the dishes.
What are you going to be?
I want to record a lot of things.
What do you want to eat today?
I don't know.
Let's go to the sukiyaki restaurant.
I received the meat from my relative's house.
Let's use it.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Let's use this.
This is Matsusaka beef.
Is that true?
Yes.
Can you stop filming?
I'm going to make sukiyaki.
What's wrong with you?
I'm nervous.
I want to record everything about you.
I want to record everything about me.
I feel loved.
I understand.
Take it off.
Take it off by yourself.
I'm concentrating on filming.
I understand.
Don't show it to anyone.
Take off all the buttons.
Why did you decide to film this?
I want to record everything about me.
I understand.
I feel loved.
Stand up.
Hurry up.
Let's stop.
Why?
I understand.
Take off all the buttons.
Take off the bottom, too.
Take off the bottom, too?
I'm going to record everything about me.
You look so cool.
Don't you want to eat something?
I want to eat something.
You are very wet.
I'm excited.
Why?
Because you are being filmed?
Yes.
You said you didn't want to be filmed.
That's right.
I'm excited.
Why are you so wet?
I feel good.
I'm excited.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
I'm excited.
What are you always thinking about?
I want to fall in love again.
I don't think about anything else.
You don't think about anything else?
Today, you made me a side dish.
I'm thinking about that a lot.
I didn't know you were such an erotic owner.
I don't think about anything else.
Why did you blow salt on the owner?
I feel like I'm going to fight.
Did you feel good?
I feel like I'm going to kiss.
Aren't you excited?
I'm excited.
Why are you so enthusiastic?
Why?
I'm sorry.
You're wet.
Does it feel good?
Which side do you look at?
Down.
Look this way.
I'm sorry.
Why did you blow salt on the owner?
What are you going to do?
I'm sorry.
Look at the camera.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
Which side do you look at?
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
Which side do you look at?
It's beautiful.
You're always looking at it.
Do you like it?
I'm sorry.
Which side do you look at?
Do you like it?
I like it.
I'm sorry.
Do you like it?
I like it.
Look at the camera.
What's that face?
Do you like it?
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
Look at me.
Are you going home?
Aren't you embarrassed?
I'm embarrassed.
I'm so excited.
It's only for today.
Look at me.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
I like it.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
I can't pet you.
I want it.
I can't let you go to the vet.
Does it feel good?
I like it.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
I like it.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to carry you?
Let's start from here.
Go this way.
Open your mouth.
Slowly.
It's painful.
My back is hurting.
Are you alright?
Yeah, I'm okay.
You've already started coming to your senses.
I'm fine.
Let's get started.
【Please do not cry.】
Hmm?
It's hot.
I'm going crazy.
What kind of face are you making?
It's hot.
I'm going crazy.
Can I eat this?
It's hot.
How was it?
Can I kiss you?
Do it.
Don't show it to anyone else.
It's hot.
Hiro-kun.
He's not here.
So, I'm going to be the main character.
I'm lonely.
I fell in love with it the other day.
So, I'm going to try it myself.
Is it like this?
Can you see me?
Yes.
Like this?
I'm going to use this.
I'm going to think about it.
It's hot.
Let's do it together.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Hiro-kun.
It's hot.
I'm going to eat it.
I'm going to use this.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can do it forever.
Come back.
Chimpanzee.
I'm melting.
It's hot.
It was dangerous.
Come back.
Can you see me?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm waiting for you.
I fell asleep.
It's too dangerous.
I was wet before I came here.
Come back soon.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Come back.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Was it fun?
Hey.
Why are you dressed like this?
I took a picture of you the other day.
Did you take a picture of me?
Did you take a picture of me by yourself?
Yes.
Look at this.
Why?
Are you excited?
I'm excited.
This is a record of us.
What did you take a picture of?
Your name.
What?
Did you take a picture of me by yourself?
Yes.
I got wet before I came here.
I took a picture of you by myself.
I'm sorry.
You're wet.
I was lonely.
Why did you take a picture of me by yourself?
I wanted to see you.
I didn't wait for you.
I wanted you to take a picture of me.
You can't.
I'm sorry.
Can you take a picture of me?
You took a picture of me by yourself.
No.
I want you to take a picture of me.
You feel better, don't you?
No.
I want you to take a picture of me.
Please.
No.
I want you to take a picture of me.
What?
I don't want you to take a picture of me by yourself.
I wanted to see you.
What is this?
What are you hiding here?
I like toys.
What?
Don't you like toys?
No, I don't.
What?
Don't you like toys?
No, I like you.
I like toys, too.
I didn't know you were here.
What?
I'm recording you.
Are you recording me?
Yes.
Are you all right?
Are you sick?
No.
Why?
I thought I could make you feel better.
How do you feel now?
I feel better.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
I'll bring you some water.
Do you feel better now?
Yes, I do.
I'll bring you some water.
Can I see how much you feel better?
What are you doing?
I'll give you some cream.
No.
I told you I'd bring you some cream.
I'll give you some cream.
It's wet.
Wow.
Does it smell?
No?
I'm happy.
Thank you for giving me a lot of cream.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Why?
It's weird.
It's so hot.
You like it more, don't you?
No, I don't.
What?
I like it more.
Do you like it more?
Yes.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Don't look at me.
Look at me.
Tell me what I'm doing.
It's so weird.
I'm called.
It's weird.
Tell me what you're doing.
It feels good.
Tell me what I'm doing.
It's so weird.
I like it.
Do you like it?
I can't do it.
Do it yourself.
You want me to do it?
I can't do it.
Do you want me to do it?
I'll do it.
I won't let you go.
Do you want me to do it?
I can't do it.
Look at the camera.
What are you doing?
I'm doing a live broadcast.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I'll hold your head.
What are you doing?
I can't do it.
What do you want me to do?
I can't hear you.
I can't do it.
Don't cry.
I'm sorry.
I don't need your attention.
I can't do it.
I don't want to do it.
I'll do it later.
I can't do it.
What are you doing?
Can I put this in your stomach?
I'll put this in your stomach.
Give me a lot.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Why is your butt so beautiful?
Do you really like it?
What do you like?
I don't have much confidence.
I'm serious.
Why?
I'm fat.
I'm not fat.
Let's go to a hot spring next time.
I want to go.
I've been to a hot spring in Kusatsu.
There was a better hot spring in Kyushu.
Kyushu?
I think Dogo hot spring is good.
Where in Dogo?
I think it was in Shikoku.
I think it's good.
That's right.
It was a good place.
You look like you're really hot.
Let's go in.
let's go in.
Oh my god, this is crazy.
Let's wash it with shampoo.
It's good.
We'll wash it properly later.
This is a good temperature to take a bath.
It feels good.
It's good.
When you take a bath, it's good.
We look like a perfect couple.
We look like a happy couple.
Yes, we do.
That's how we feel when we take a bath.
Let's take a bath together.
Let's take a bath.
My hair is wet.
My phone is wet.
It's not wet.
It's okay because it's waterproof.
It's waterproof.
You're cute.
You're so cute.
It's good.
What?
My phone battery is low.
Is it low?
I don't know if it's because of the VR.
Is it because of the VR?
I want you to do it again.
It's good.
This happens just by kissing.
It's amazing.
It's amazing. Look.
Can you see it?
To whom?
I don't know.
What should I do with this salad?
Family.
Have you ever been in a family?
No.
I've never been in a family.
But I've never been in a relationship.
I've never been in a relationship.
I don't know because I haven't seen it.
I'm a little bit sexy.
Do you like it?
I like it.
I have breasts.
Do you have breasts?
It's done.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Do you like breasts?
Yes.
I like breasts.
What do you like?
Here.
Here?
I like it.
It's hard.
Do you like it?
It's big.
It feels good.
Do you like it?
I like it.
I can do it with both hands.
It feels good.
Look at me.
Do you like it?
It feels good.
I'll leave it outside.
Sit here.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good?
It feels good.
Do you want to try it?
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I think it's a good idea to give him a bath every once in a while.
I think it's a good idea to give him a bath every once in a while.
The cuteness of these사
The cuteness of theseä
The cuteness of thesас
Hmm?
Ah...
Wait
Oh, no
Do it where the carbonic acid is
Ah?
Do it with your hand where it gets caught
Oh, sorry
I'm sorry
Ah...
It's okay
It's okay?
Wait, wait
It's okay
Steam bounces in Mikan's arms.
If they do not use their arms, the structure will collapse.
The amount has increased a lot.
The flour."
Mikan is younger than me today.
He is family with Lea who is alone.
Lea's older brother was completed.
And then?
Ouch.
Ah, you okay?
It's been a long time since I've seen him like this, so I'm a little worried about him.
He's got a lot of hair on his face.
Poop.
I'm going to clean his jumper.
It feels like everybody is working so hard over there.
I like this kind of play.
You like it, don't you?
Yes, I do.
What's wrong?
It's spicy.
It's hot.
Use your skin.
What?
Do you want me to use your skin?
Yes.
Look at the camera.
Do you like fighting?
Yes, I do.
It's hot.
Use your skin.
Skin?
Do you like fighting?
Yes, I do.
Look at me.
Do you like it?
Yes.
I kissed you.
I can't move.
I'm sorry.
Do you like it?
It's hot.
Yes, I do.
Do you like it?
What?
It's hot.
I can't move.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
That's so mean.
It's hot, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Thank you.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
My legs are cold.
What?
I can't do this.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry.
Look at the camera.
I can't do this.
I'm sorry I made you wet.
You're wet.
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
What do you feel?
I'm sorry.
Did you want to be wet?
Yes, I did.
It's hot.
What time is it?
Aqueous varnish
How about that?
Looks pretty thick
I'm sorry.
Open your mouth wide.
You're getting tired, aren't you?
Yeah.
I used it too much.
You're sleepy, aren't you?
Yeah.
Like this?
Like this.
I love you.
What do you love?
Do you love me?
I love you.
What's that?
Did you kiss me?
It looks delicious.
It's delicious.
Look at this.
Kimchi
Kimchi on my lips
I love you.
It's hot.
I started to speak.
I'm sorry.
Why?
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
What?
I don't know.
I love you.
What should I do?
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Is it hot?
It's hot.
Use it.
Use it a lot.
It's hot.
Use this.
Use this, please.
It's hot.
Use this.
Grandpa?
Thank you so much.
Well, that's all I can say...
I'm so hungry.
I'm so tired.
Why are you moving by yourself?
No.
I'm so tired.
I'm too tired.
No.
I can't do it anymore.
I love you.
Good girl.
Come here.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm sorry.
It's so sticky.
It's all sticky.
Give me a kiss.
I'm sorry.
It's so sticky.
Give me a kiss.
Get up.
Put your hands together.
Give me a kiss.
I told you to put your hands together.
Please put your hands together.
Give me a kiss.
Do you feel good?
It's so sticky.
Let me get up.
Open your legs.
Do you feel good?
It's so sticky.
I'm sorry.
Give me a kiss.
It's so sticky.
I love you.
I love you all.
It's so sticky.
Give me a kiss.
Let me get up.
Do you feel good?
It's so sticky.
I did it a lot.
Let me get up.
You can do it!
How was it?
It was delicious!
You took a lot of pictures!
You took a lot of pictures of my scalp.
Thank you for watching until the end.
Please subscribe to my channel and follow me on Twitter.