Yes, yes.
This is important
Next time we meet, let's discuss specifically
Then | will call you again.
Okay, I'm sorry.
President, the car is here.
Thank you. Then I'll go.
Good
What about the schedule?
Today at nine o'clock Ota from the sales office will come
Yes?
Eleven o'clock to start to go to dinner
Too good to understand, right?
That's not true.
Tell the newcomer to you a piece of advice
The relationship between the president and secretary Mino
You are too loud
No one in the company doesn't know that
Although the president said he was going to a meeting
Actually, it's to a hotel.
President Secretary
Is it his mistress?
l envy you!
But the president is very good to our staff
He has a big heart, so the staff likes him a lot.
So what kind of mistress affair
-We all agreed not to mention it. - Let's go.
Good
| do understand golf
It looks like we need a hobby sheet for the staff.
We are not familiar with the game of otaku, right?
No, | don't think so.
Does anyone understand?
The
Please enter
Lost my temper
| am the second village of the editorial department
You are the second village ah
Sorry about the work time to find you Sit down
Spoilers
-I'm out of order. - Sit down.
Not work-related matters
Don't be nervous, just relax.
Good
I'll get right to the point
My only child has a son
It's the young people of today!
Favorite game
What game its he playing?
What is the game called
This
This is a katakana | can not remember
This is a recently opened game, right?
-You know what? - Yes.
It's also very popular online, and I'm playing it too.
Adults play also very happy
That's right, | don't understand it.
I'm looking for
Is there anyone in the company who understands
Lost my temper
Please drink tea
lam not a guest
You are accompanying me on a personal matter
Drinking a tea is not much, right?
Thank you
Then
If | can play games with my grandson
Maybe my daughter will also come to my house to play
This is what | thought of
By the way, have you registered for an account yet?
Account number Not registered
Want to register?
You've entered the game
First open the game what name you want to take
Name words
Can not take the real name?
If you have a real name, the rest of the world will know your name.
| can't do that.
Marry a nickname or nickname ah
This ts better
-Let's call him Old Man. - Old Man.
-Then I'll write it. - Please.
By the way, my boss suddenly called me over
Guess what my boss asked me to do
The result was to ask me to discuss the games his grandson was playing
Amazing!
Thanks to this, | also started playing games with my boss.
It's nice to be able to play games at work.
Miki
What did you say?
Nothing
Not good
Not at all well done
What should | do?
How about this?
| can't do that.
Futamura, let's go together today (in a few days)
Wait, I'm going to the boss's office.
Go again!
You are totally the boss's game friend
What was Mino doing at that time?
What to do
Do your own work ah
Occasionally come to watch us play games
And then
They are really having an affair, right?
It doesn't feel that way.
Anyway, I'll go first.
Lost my temper
Futamura Sorry for looking for you during lunch break.
If you can, let's go to dinner together.
You haven't had your lunch yet, have you?
Futamura, you can have soba noodles across the street, right?
-Okay. - Let's go.
Take care!
Please drink tea
Sorry, I've been troubling you.
Sorry for making tea for me as an employee
No, this is the boss's orders, do not care
He said it seems that the traffic jam will be late
Have you had your lunch yet?
No, but it's perfectly fine.
I'll sit on your side. Sorry.
The
Actually
| have a personal request for Futamura
Please ask?
What is it?
| have a nephew
It's his birthday coming up.
Then | wanted to give him a game as a birthday present
If possible
When you have time next time, can you go with me to buy games?
Okay, | got it.
Of course | can accompany you now
Great!
Okay, | got it.
| have been relying on you since | came back to my senses
| didn't think my interest could help you either
It would be nice if your nephew could have fun
The boss is also as happy as the child to fool around.
Pe Th . .
Ermura, have you been married for a long time?
It's been about three years.
What does your wife do?
My wife is a comic book artist
Comic artist?
Yes, | met him at my previous company because of my work.
This way
| have no encounter at all
You don't have a boyfriend?
Do you care?
| like the kind of childish people who love games
Come
Futamura | can't help it anymore
So powerful, the body is so hot
Finally, I've touched it!
My ears are so sensitive!
Is it comfortable here?
Yes
Good for you. You have a great body.
Thank you
Have you done this at home lately?
No, | didn't do anything.
Not doing much?
It's been a long time since | did it!
Bigger
What a great taste!
You can feel it through your underwear?
Slowly getting bigger
So comfortable
Great! What a big stick!
Amazing!
So comfortable
That side is so comfortable
So comfortable So comfortable
So comfortable
i came. | came.
High tide
horny
This is awesome!
So comfortable
No, no, no.
| came. | came.
High tide
So comfortable
That way
Not that way.
Delicious
This
| have no problem today
Amazing!
So comfortable
I'm going to cum.
Good
Stop! Stop!
Amazing!
I'm sorry about that.
It's okay. I'm fine today.
But it's still hard
Keep doing it
It's been so hard
So powerful, so comfortable
Amazing!
That way
So comfortable
No. No.
I came. I came.
High tide
Come in from the back
So comfortable
No. No.
I came. | came.
= /
High tide
Let's make it more intense
That side is so comfortable
I came. I came.
Come and kiss me
So comfortable
No, no, no.
More intense
I'm going to cum.
| ejaculated
Great! So hot!
Pussy is so hot
You're awake
| can't sleep
Tomorrow its the deadline
This way
Thank you for your hard work
Youichi ts
You stayed up late with the client.
| can't do it at all
You go for it too!
What happened suddenly?
Good Night
Yes (in a few days)
| got it.
Futamura, the boss is looking for you.
Good
What? Even at work, you can play games!
Lost my temper
Where's the boss?
The boss is now out
But
I'm the one looking for you.
Because
We don't have much time to spend alone together
But
And you've been avoiding me ever since that day, right?
That's not true.
The
No, that.
This will not work
It's okay
Are you really not hiding from me?
So hard
The boss will be back
It's okay
No, no, no.
It's okay. It's okay.
-Great. - Come here.
Is it possible?
It's okay
You can sit down.
The smell of sweat is very smelly
Are you excited?
Yes
So comfortable
Hard nipples
I'm sorry about that.
Just a little bit. It's okay.
Amazing!
In the boss's office
Doing what you can't do
But I couldn't resist
This one? No.
Comfortable?
Get comfortable!
So powerful and hard today
No, that.
Doing what can't be done
I'm so excited!
Delicious
It's dirty.
You have beautiful fingers.
You're working hard.
That side is very sensitive
Over there, that...
| can t.
This will not work
Still saying that?
Not really
| couldn't resist
No need to be so patient
But
You can't do that in the boss's office.
But you're excited, right?
Can't lick here
It's gotten so big!
Wait, really, no.
I'm going to cum.
You don't have to put up with it
Tits are also comfortable
Not that way.
No, I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum.
Ejaculation
| would like to insert into the can be inserted into the
No way!
You can still do it, right?
Hello
Okay, | got it.
The boss ts coming back soon
What a pity
We need to be free tomorrow night!
Good
-I'm back. - I'm sorry.
Please come in
Watch your step
Sit down.
So happy
Do you want to drink water?
No need
Give me the jacket
Sorry
By the way
Mino
Futamura Want to drink beer?
Okay, anything.
So rich!
I've been waiting for a long time.
Sorry
It's okay
Please have a beer.
Thank you
So, let's drink again.
Cheers
Futamura, what happened to you?
| te
re) a
Your house
Right?
Are you living alone?
Do you care?
Yes
You know about Futamura, right?
My relationship with my boss
I'd better go home, right?
It's okay
He will definitely go back to his house only on Friday
But
So you want to go home?
| like both of you
| want to lick it too
So comfortable
Futamura
Stay today
Want to drink?
Will be late for work
Will be late
This is how it starts in the morning
No way!
| will want to make love
You have become so big
Just a little bit to do oh
Can't do it?
No way!
Will be late
Your face is so cute
Don't look at me like that
| can't. I'm going to cum.
| ejaculated
I've ejaculated a lot since the morning
That's all for today.
We'll be late. Let's go.
Let's get ready
What's up?
Yuichi recently seems to have a different temperament
Yes?
Are you cheating on me?
No, how is it possible?
I'm kidding
It's okay, | know Yuichi is not so bold
i
— an 6M i
Will the boss find out?
It's okay.
| still want more.
This... this...
Boss
What's wrong with you?
Actually
| have a girlfriend
It's a girl about the same age as my daughter
Wife
It has also been found
But it did not say anything
This...
Her.
| suspect that she may have another man recently
| care so much
Could the boss have made a mistake?
Don't look at me like this | have a strong sixth sense
That
Did you find out who the other party is?
Then | don't know.
This is also not something | can manage
But | care so much!
| never thought | would reach this age
Still have this feeling
What's up?
Nothing
Futamura, you actually understand it very well.
The
Me and my boss
Which one do you like?
What are you talking about?
Answer me seriously
As | said before
| can't decide which one to choose
Because you are both very cute ah
And
Even if a certain one is chosen
You both have wives ah
Wait, it's too intense.
What's up?
Can | be more intense?
Take a good look.
Even here to lick?
So horny!
I cant.
No, I'm going to come.
It's going to be an orgasm
| came. | came.
So intense
Plug in
Great, great, great!
Intense point
| came. | came.
High tide
Shot
| also want to
| came. | came.
Again, I'm going to have another orgasm.
I came. I came.
= |
High tide
Great, great, great!
Amazing!
No, no, no.
No. No.
High tide
| came. | came.
So comfortable
I'm going to cum.
-l'm cumming. - I'm coming.
Break up with you
Advantage One
| love you
What about you?
What happened suddenly?
| love you too!
Sometimes you have to say this kind of thing to be able to
I'm going to cheer up
Sorry, seems to be a traffic jam.
That, Mino
That we
It is better not to have a relationship
I like you
Where is Futamura?
I like you too
3d 0
oP
Lal Oy (Lad
Leon
Vp
Shove
SET cy ore
Vee me
“«4
a
ne Pay
eee
p08 over cee et
Cod voorop Ree eee
io ope, POOR ee om BE
vd fsooofoenee peal at a
eStore pedal
Pera eetes “ee
ees ®*ew .
(Menaqui)
x18r.com