(2 consecutive pairs 25%)
Okay, okay, about this ah
Okay, hold on a second
Okay, got it. Okay.
Okay, | see.
| know that too. - Okay.
Okay, | understand. Then, Kimura, arrange to make copies.
Mizukawa
Can you help me make copies?
Good
Thank you. I'm counting on you.
Jun Mizukawa
| don't know her very well
Never said a word since I joined the company
And there is no special intersection of work
Very serious type of work
Seems like the type that is not good at talking to people
-Thank you. - Okay.
| guess it's okay.
No problem
-Thank you. - Yes, thank you.
This way
By the way, we're having a farewell party after work today.
-Let's all join. - Yes, I'll join.
-Kimura joined us. - Yes.
Where is Mizukawa?
I'm sure you'll be very happy if you participate.
Today | want to drink as much as | can
Minister, this can not be ah, we rarely drink
Not now
AE
-Yeah. - Yeah.
Mizukawa, it's a rare occasion.
Like to drink
Right?
So have fun today!
Sorry!
But Mizukawa drank a lot of ah
| am very surprised
It's a little dangerous.
But not really can not ah drink too much ah
Really, that guy really
| drank too much, but | can't, can | Mizukawa?
Mizukawa
Mizukawa, are you okay?
Wait a minute, Mizukawa, cheer up!
What's up? Can we go?
Sleep, right? What should we do? Let's go back first.
Oh no, what to do?
What should | do when | arrive at the hotel?
Mizukawa Mizukawa
Will not get up ah
Mizukawa
Mizukawa Mizukawa
You won't get up, will you?
It's okay, just a little bit.
Mizukawa is unexpectedly wearing a sexy lingerie.
&% —~-KeE .
What's this? It's amazing!
x.
iE
Mizukawa
Wearing such underwear
Drunk should not get up
- -~ AE
It's amazing!
Oh no, it's so erotic.
Break it open and see
So that's how it is!
So sexy!
it's hot! It's hot!
It's amazing!
_ ~ AE
a
- ~4E
It's amazing!
Already wet
\
-Wait, what are you doing? - Mizukawa, this is not... This is...
What are you doing?
-Wait. - I'm sorry.
| can't do this.
Mizukawa
rc
-No, it's not. - Wait.
This
| can't do that.
No way!
Mizukawa here, here for me
How its it?
It's already wet, right? Just a little bit.
Amazing!
Lick me as much as possible
Mizukawa I want to continue
What? - No. - Continue.
That's this?
No, I'm comfortable too.
No way!
Very comfortable, right?
So powerful, so tight!
-Can you do it? No, | can't
Wait, | can't.
Touching like this
Keep going, right?
Mizukawa
Here. Here too.
No way!
That's great. What's up?
No, this will not work, senpai, can not do so ah
Wait ah so comfortable
Amazing!
So powerful and so intense
No way!
Comfortable So comfortable
Mizukawa, look!
Amazing!
I'm so excited!
No, | can't help it.
It's awesome inside
No, don't!
Mizukawa, Mizukawa is already so wet here.
(filo
7 aod
Wait!
Amazing!
The rod is inside me
Go =
; i Bue
Not so intense
-Don't stop. - It's good. It's good.
So comfortable
Mizukawa
Pornography is too erotic
-It's holding. - It's holding.
Mizukawa
So powerful ah into the inside
-Great! - Mizukawa!
So comfortable
So cool!
Mizukawa
This won't work
So intense!
No, | can't.
Mizukawa No, no, no.
I'm gotng to cum.
Amazing!
Wait, where's Mizukawa? Not here.
Oh no, it's late at this time.
| == Pt
I'm sorry I'm late. I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
Everyone is waiting for you!
Sorry, I'm late. Sorry.
Before already said ah today to the meeting why not come earlier
Good
What should | do?
Can you come over a little?
Good
Damn, it's definitely yesterday.
This is where my life ends
This is what happened yesterday, right?
I'm sorry
I'm really sorry for being angry, right?
Wait, what are you doing, Mizukawa?
Wait, what are you doing?
Mizukawa Here is the company ah
Wait ah no ah
I'm really sorry, | can't do this.
Don't you want that?
I'm sorry
Wait ah no ah
Mizukawa, | can't.
Wait, what are you doing?
Mizukawa
Wait, | can't.
This does not work ah someone came how to do
What's this?
It's delicious!
No, | really can't.
No way!
— iJ =
Licking like this. ~
Wait ah lick where ah
It's delicious!
The meat stick is delicious
It's delicious. People will really come.
It doesn't matter. It's comfortable, right?
Wait!
It's great! It's an erection!
Wait, | can't.
Mw PL
Here?
Very cute!
Wait, | can't.
-What's this? - No!
The meat stick is hard
No, | can't.
es ,
Friction is very comfortable, right?
So comfortable to ejaculate
-So comfortable. - The rod is so hard.
Wait!
AE
What's this?
Wait, | can't.
Don't you want to see it?
Really, really not
Here
What a great stick!
Meat stick
This is bad
ya
-Comfortable, right? - Yes, comfortable.
Be comfortable
Amazing!
This look
What's up?
Wait!
Wait ah Mizukawa really can not ah
I'm cumming I'm cumming
Amazing!
| ejaculated in the company, it's really disgusting!
I'm so excited!
I'm sorry
-Kimura. - I'm coming.
What are you doing?
Not yet. - Yes.
Hurry up and bring the information here!
Okay, I'll be right there now.
So tired
Work overtime every day
Mizukawa, what are you doing here? You're off duty now.
Before the things | will not talk to anyone, I'm really sorry.
Don't you want to do something?
Now here it is!
We all go back, no one will come
AE
Right?
No, if they are found
Everybody's back. It's okay.
It's okay.
-Mizukawa - What about it?
Yesterday's incident was because’of drinking
The feeling of long-lost is very exciting, right?
Really, really will be expelled
But | really like the stick!
No way!
Is it really possible?
Wait!
Don't do that!
| said this does not work ah
Because you're against me.
Wait!
Amazing!
-So powerful, so hard. - Wait.
No, this one.
Friction to
Wait!
It's a great feeling!
So hard
--E
It's amazing!
Let me see if | can?
The meat stick is awesome! Wait, let me see the hard meat stick!
-| can't do this. - It's really great!
| haven't tried this before.
-It's so good. - It's good, right?
So comfortable
| want to touch it.
Want to touch ah can oh
No way!
Amazing!
How its it? Feel it?
I 27 - os
This friction can not be
How is it?
-It's comfortable. - It's comfortable.
Mizukawa
It's amazing!
_ ~ AE
Amazing!
-Isn't it comfortable? - It's comfortable.
So powerful, the meat stick is so hard
| want to continue to be more intense
By the way
-It's awesome, hard. - Wait a minute.
-I’m cumming! - I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
It's shaking all the time
-No. - Is this it?
mie
-No, don't. - No?
No way!
- —~AE
It's amazing!
Inside the company
So excited, right?
Here
I like it, right?
Want to
The meat stick is so hard
e ol
So comfartable
This is not possible, so fast
No, it's too fast.
No, don't!
-It's awesome. - It's so comfortable.
so hard. - It's so comfortable. Licking my breasts as much as possi
Lick me as much as possible
Amazing!
I'm so excited!
Help me suck in
This way
By the way
Great! So great!
So comfortable
So cool!
slippery
-Great. The juice is coming out. - The juice ts coming out.
Amazing!
So comfortable
-Give me the back. - The back.
Continue to give me
Amazing!
I'm so excited!
Sucked so powerful
So cool!
Mizukawa really can't help it, can you?
Plug it in for me
By the way
Insert as much as possible
Amazing!
So comfortable
Give me as much penetration as possible
no oom omy.
Continue to give me
-It's comfortable, isn't it? - It's comfortable.
-Mizukawa, come here. - Here!
So cool!
So comfortable
io
So cool!
Keep moving
ful, soc
I i) ia)
omfortable
Mizukawa is no longer available
Go on, keep plugging away.
Continue to rub so comfortable
Come here
Wait!
Come to the front
That's right, it's working.
Amazing!
Poochie poochie.against the inside
So comfortable
By the way
Very comfortable, right?
,E =
That's it.
Damn! So comfortable!
No, don't!
I .d CGI EG ee. — rae | ais
I like this
Sorry
By the way
This won't work
No way!
Give it to me. Keep giving it to me.
Continue to give me
| love this!
| can't. Keep giving it to me.
-Mizukawa - Keep giving it to me
| guess so.
No way! Shot ah
Amazing!
Next time, come to your home
Mizukawa, where are your glasses?
Very beautiful
Thank you
Very pure feeling very good
It's beautiful.
i)
nel nes o, r ,0"e
Great underwear
Usually this is also the same ah
-Occasionally. - Occasionally.
Let me see
Amazing!
Keep playing with me
How does it look? It's wet.
Amazing!
It's so hard!
Mizukawa, you're touching yourself.
-It's great. - Isn't it comfortable?
il can't.
Hurry up!
The pussy ts. clamped
So comfortable
Continue Continue
Gontinue to give me
Amazing!
Great! Great! It's stuck inside!
Wait!
-That's great. - Wait..Keep giving it to me.
Continue
So comfortable
No, I'm sorry.
Continue to be comfortable
Do your best to do oh
nf]
Give me
So comfortable, right?
-Wait, | can't. - No.
-Mizukawa is great. - Isn't it comfortable?
-Comfortable, comfortable. - Comfortable.
-It's comfortable, isn't it? - It's comfortable.
So comfortable
e ‘e
a .
25°.
Qe
a
-Here, too. - Yes.
-That's not good enough. - That's not good enough.
So intense
Shaking all the time
You see, the ejaculation ah
You see
You brought this to the office?
-Wait. - So sensitive, right?
Help me to resist
-Great! - Hold me as long as you can!
Amazing!
Very comfortable, right?
Continue Suck me in
-That’s great. - Hold it against me.
Very comfortable, right?
So comfortable, yes
“a mom. Lo.
-Keep giving me that. That's right. - Here.
oS) gle)! ie
So comfartable
That's great!
Already not working
| can't, I'm coming.
Go on, it's wet in here.
That's it.
-This is so comfortable. - This is so comfortable.
The nipples are erect, so exciting, right?
This way
Here ah nipples are so hard
-The vagina is awesome. - | love it!
nom wh.
Continue to give me
This does not work ah stop to
-That's it. - That's it.
Wait ah no ah
Stop
| want to continue this
Continue to hold against me
Next, hold it against me here
Go on, that's right, keep giving it to me.
A.
It's starting!
It's bad
Wait!
Amazing!
It's holding!
So comfortable
Thatisiit!
Keep going. - Keep going.
That's right, go ahead.
This won't work
US UR eeu tt penlge BS cress Rg
L Licey aw OME eu 2, Ue SAT SS gS,
| can not ah so comfortable continue ah
That's right, keep going.
noo AE
Continue
Mizukawa wants to go in
Plug in, plug in!
Plug in
-You have to. - I'm in.
t's so comfortable. - It's so comfortable. - It's so slippery in there.
A= =F ==
Slippery now
-A little more intense. - Go in.
So tight!
-So comfortable. - So comfortable.
cE
That's it. That's right.
Continue to give me
It's great! It's great!
I can't. it's bad.
| wei ML
This won't work
No, I can't.
This is awesome!
-Great. - Great.
Wait!
Plug it in
So comfortable
Amazing!
This won't work
So powerful ah continue to insert ah
= f=)
Orgasm. Orgasm.
So comfortable
-Hold it against the inside. - Great! Great!
Amazing!
This won't work
Plug in, plug in!
No, don't!
Amazing!
It’s great. - It’s smooth. - It's smooth and comfortable.
Come here
-So comfortable. - Keep going.
Amazing!
ojJf BY
So comfortable
Sag
x J
-It's awesome. - No way!
| love it!
Resisted
-I'm going to cum. - No, keep going in.
-I'm cumming. - | can't.
-It's so comfortable. Here. - Come here a little.
Here
That's it.
Get moving
Poof, poof, poof.
-Great! - Here!'So comfortable!
Wait!
It's awesome! Wait a minute!
~* Amazing!
JA0
Great!
Wait!
Amazing!
Look at me here
Resisted
Es
What is it?
You've had many orgasms.
“ho ome. nom. mE, an ee
-Go on, keep giving it to me. - Go on.
Understood
Into the ah
Amazing!
Very comfortable, right?
-| like it, don't I? - | like it.
Keep it that way
Wait!
Come by yourself
Amazing!
-Mizukawa, I'm going to cum. - Cum for me.
Shoot on my face Shoot me a lot
-curth, me. - Cum.
Mizukawa
-| have a favor to ask you. - Okay.
I'm counting on you.