6 WEEKS LATER
Come sit over there.
Yes.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Yuuki Yuzuru.
I see.
Yuuki, do you play in a band?
Yes, I do.
I mainly play in a live house.
I see.
What instruments do you play?
I play the bass.
That's cool.
Are you busy with your activities?
I have a few gigs next month, so I'm busy.
But I'm free this month, so I can play 5 or 6 gigs a week.
I see.
I hope you'll do your best at home.
If you're busy, I'll let you take a day off.
Thank you.
Yuuki, have you ever worked at a convenience store?
No, it's my first time.
I see.
Have you ever served a customer?
Yes, I have.
I'd like to check your order form.
Sorry, can you do it later?
I'm sorry. I was in the middle of an interview.
Nice to meet you. I'm Yuuki.
Excuse me.
If you don't mind, I'll let you work at my store.
Really?
Thank you for your help.
Thank you.
She's my wife.
Oh, she's your wife.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Can I have a cigarette?
Sure.
Can I have a bag?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Please press this button.
That's all.
Thank you.
The total is 1,720 yen.
Well...
Yes.
I'd like to replenish your order.
The new one is in the back.
In the back.
When the peak time is over,
I'd like to check the inventory and the quantity.
And...
I'd like to check the temperature of the refrigerator.
Okay.
Thank you.
By the way, you're a band man, right?
Yes, I am.
I'm not famous at all.
But it's amazing that you're a band man.
You look cool.
Do I?
Yes.
I like nails, too.
I'd like to study, but I'm busy at the convenience store.
But you look good as a nail artist.
You're beautiful.
Your Kansai dialect intonation is cute, too.
It's fun to talk to you.
What?
You're very happy to hear that.
You speak Kansai dialect very well.
I'll be back soon.
Okay.
What's this?
This is...
It can be used by babies, too.
This is a weak type.
How many do you have?
I don't know.
I'd like to have 20.
Okay.
Honoka, come here.
Yes.
What's up?
Can you check if there is the same product in the warehouse?
If it's not here, it's not in the warehouse.
Just look for it.
Hurry up.
Okay.
What do you think your job is?
I'm doing my best.
It's not up to you to decide whether you're doing your best or not.
You don't have to say that.
If you put on such a thick makeup, you can check the stock at that time.
That's...
Don't you work too much?
Let's forget about work and go on a trip.
Don't be irresponsible.
And don't talk about your family at work.
Okay.
What?
Are you taking a break?
Yes.
I'll have a 30-minute break.
Okay.
Honoka, are you having a hard time with your husband?
Well...
I'm not fighting with him.
But he's only thinking about work.
I see.
I think so, too.
But I think he's a little strong.
Well...
I wasn't a strong person in the past.
I don't sleep because I don't have enough people.
I see.
By the way, are you sleeping well?
Your face is tired.
I've been writing songs late at night.
I can't sleep.
What kind of songs do you write?
I wrote a song about people who shouldn't fall in love.
What?
Is that based on real experience?
Well...
I want to hear that song.
I'm a little embarrassed now.
Why?
Let me hear it.
Don't you have anything in common with him?
No.
I want a child.
But he's busy at the convenience store.
I'm busy at home and at the convenience store, too.
It's beautiful, but it's a waste.
Don't say that.
I'm just a housewife working at a convenience store.
I'm writing a song about you.
I'm sorry.
What?
Don't make fun of me.
I'm sorry.
I don't write a song about lies.
If I write a song about lies, the audience will find out.
I'm looking forward to your new song.
I'll go to your concert.
Honoka-san.
My song will be completed when I'm with you.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
This is my husband's store.
But you really want to kiss me, don't you?
Don't say that.
Don't do that.
Because you look like a Kansai person.
No.
Don't do that.
Calm down.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
He'll find out.
It's okay.
Don't do that.
Calm down.
I'm so excited.
Wait.
Honoka-san.
Don't do that.
What's wrong?
There is...
There?
No.
He'll find out.
It's okay.
I'm scared.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't look at me.
Your hands are beautiful.
Don't do that.
He'll find out.
It's okay.
Don't do that.
He'll find out.
Hey.
It's okay.
What's wrong?
Why?
Do you feel good?
Do you feel good that you can't speak?
Don't do that.
Let's end this.
No one is here.
It's okay.
I can't see anything.
It's not okay.
He'll find out.
It's okay.
Don't do that.
He'll find out.
It's okay.
Don't do that.
Please look at me.
He'll find out.
It's okay.
Be patient.
Don't do that.
It's okay.
Please be patient.
Does it feel so good?
No.
I'll do it more.
Does it feel good?
No.
You're sleeping.
Please open your mouth.
Wait a minute.
Stop it.
Does it feel good?
No.
I'll do it more.
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
I'll do it more.
Your voice is hoarse.
Are you okay?
Don't do that.
He'll find out.
Does it feel good?
Please fix it.
What?
Don't do that.
Do you want me to fix it?
Please fix it.
I can't do it anymore.
Does it feel good?
I'm married.
He's right there.
I can't do it anymore.
Which do you think is better?
Don't talk nonsense.
When was the last time you saw him?
Tell me.
I haven't seen him for more than a year.
Is that so?
Stop it.
I can't fix it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for him.
I can't do it here.
Do you really hate it?
Do you feel so good?
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
I have to fix it.
I can't work.
I'm sorry.
Please fix it.
I can't do it anymore.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
Do you really hate it?
Excuse me.
Yes.
What's wrong?
Did you run out of coffee?
I ran out of coffee.
Is that so?
Do you have any benefits?
This is...
I think it's a campaign after a week.
This is from now on.
I see.
I think this is a different campaign.
That campaign was popular.
I'm sorry.
This is the only one now.
That's right.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Did you run out of coffee?
Let's stop.
I can't do it anymore.
What's wrong?
I'm afraid you'll find out.
I'm afraid you'll hear my voice.
I'm afraid.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Let's stop.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I'm hungry.
I'm so wet.
When did you get so wet?
Don't ask me.
I'm hungry.
What?
Don't ask me.
I'm hungry.
Can I help you?
We started this street as a gate on the front gate of a house that has been established at a distance of 1km from the main gate.
Moreover, no one are speaking.
Thank you
Yay?
Oya, I think we should quit
Why?
Your voice sounded like you were ushering in a pacifier
It was explanation
The voice sounded like you were ushering in a pacifier
I know
Feels good.
You can't really see this, can you?
It's not exposed, is it?
I'm scared.
It's okay.
Let's really stop.
I'm scared.
You just have to move.
Are you okay?
You can bear this, can't you?
Or do you still want me to move?
No.
Please.
It's moving.
It feels good.
I'm scared.
I can't do this anymore.
Can I give up?
It's coming again.
It's moving again.
I'm scared.
It feels good when it moves.
It's moving.
I'm scared.
Yuki, let's stop.
It's not good for the customers.
I'm scared.
Can you hear me?
It's okay.
It's not good.
Are you okay?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Let's stop.
I can't do this anymore.
It's moving again.
I'm sure you can hear me.
Don't be mean to me.
I'm scared.
Should I stop?
Let me stop.
Do you want me to stop?
I'm scared.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
Why are you lying?
I'm scared.
Are you still going to do it?
You want to do it, don't you?
Please forgive me.
I'm scared.
He's going to come to the backyard soon.
I don't want to be seen like this.
I'm scared.
I'm not resisting at all.
Are you still going to do it?
I'm scared.
I can't do this.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm scared.
Do you feel good here?
I have to go.
I'm scared.
Let's go.
It's 1,919 yen.
Here you are.
I'll pay by barcode.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Stop it.
Honoka, I like you.
I'm going to clean the bathroom.
Yuki, you shouldn't do it here.
But, I can't help it when I see you.
What are you talking about?
Stop it, Yuki.
But, I can't help it.
Stop it.
You shouldn't do it here.
Why?
Customers will come.
No, I'm fine.
Honoka.
Then, can you go back to work here?
Can I?
Yes.
Really?
Take it off.
Yes.
Yuki, you're really a pervert.
But, Honoka...
You shouldn't get so big here.
No.
I can't help it when I see you.
Can you go back to work here?
Yes, of course.
Promise me.
Yes.
I want you to touch my head.
Do you like it here?
Yes.
Just today.
Like this.
It feels good.
Yuki, you're really a pervert.
I don't know what to do.
I want you to lick me.
Please.
You're faster than me.
Then, do your best at work.
Yes.
Yuki, you're really a pervert.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I can't take it.
It tickles.
what will she do if she finds out that you can't text back me?
never!
they will be able to text you back
they will be able to respond to texts
they would text you back
but for English, not in English
Jen has spoken to some bustards
without page numbers
I am asking the camera m cracking
Jen I am asking the camera me
Jen and
Jen
I'm sorry.
I want you to eat an egg.
I don't know what to do with myself.
It's good.
I think I'm going to puke.
Ouch!
It's good.
Please stand up.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
This is the bathroom.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Please cover your face.
Okay.
It's heavy.
I can't do this.
Please cover your face.
It's heavy.
Thank you for your hard work.
Huh?
Yuuki, didn't you go up two hours ago?
I was waiting to see you.
Don't do that.
You'll be found out someday.
It's okay.
You have a night shift today.
By the way, won't you come to my room today?
I can't go.
I'm a housewife.
I have to cook dinner for my husband before he goes to work.
I can't do this.
Hey.
What are you doing?
I'm done with my work.
It's smelly.
Stop it.
I want to smell the smell of your hard work.
I can't do this.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm waiting for dinner.
Are you listening to me?
It's smelly. Stop it.
It smells good.
No way.
I can't do this.
Did you sweat a lot?
Yes, I did.
I can't do this.
I'm going home to cook dinner.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm sweating a lot.
That's good.
I'm embarrassed.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm embarrassed.
If I do this again, someone will come.
You can hold your voice again, can't you?
Do you want me to hold my voice again?
I'm sleepy.
I didn't have time to eat dinner.
You're sniffing too much.
You're sweating a lot.
Who do you blame?
Wait a minute.
I can't do this.
I'm embarrassed.
Miyuki, you don't have to cook dinner.
That's not true.
I'm embarrassed.
You're sweating a lot.
Don't say that.
I'm embarrassed.
Does it feel good here?
Yes.
It feels so good.
I didn't know it was this big.
Let's hold our voices together.
I'm embarrassed.
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
Why?
You can hold your voice, can't you?
I understand.
Miyuki.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
You're so cute.
Just by kneading a little, it was done
Do your best
I did my best
Lucia
I'm sorry.
Honoka-san, you'll cry too, won't you?
I understand.
I'm sorry.
Honoka-san.
This is bad.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
Honoka-san.
We don't have time.
Let's go over there.
Honoka-san.
I'm going to throw up.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
I'm scared.
Don't worry.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
Honoka-san.
I don't know what to do with myself.
I'm sorry.
I can hear your voice.
It's no one's fault.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, Makoto!
I'm sorry…
I can do it!
It's fine. It feels good.
Let's kiss.
I see. It's a shame.
You've gotten used to work.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to live in the room that the office is renting.
It's far away, so I can't go.
A band?
My wife listens to it a lot at home.
I also downloaded it and listened to it.
If Yuuki sells it to me,
Can I be proud of working at home?
Please, please.
It was a short time, but thank you.
My wife is lonely.
Thank you.
I'm rooting for you.
I'll do my best.
Mr. Honoka.
It's an hour after shift.
I got a message yesterday.
I was worried, but I wanted to say goodbye.
Mr. Honoka.
Would you like to go somewhere with me now?
I'm going to work from now on.
I forgot about my husband once.
Would you like to be with me?
What are you talking about?
I'm not going to break up with him.
I will definitely be famous in music.
Would you like to be excited next to me?
Yuuki.
Don't say that.
Mr. Honoka.
You're already here.
Yes.
I wanted to see you.
Actually, I'm going to quit today.
Is that so?
I didn't know that.
I've been working with you a lot.
You can give me a day off.
Please do your best.
I'll do my best.
I can't break up with him.
I'm not good at living, but I'm a good person.
I can't be rewarded just for being a good person.
I...
Is this really the last time?
How is it?
Don't sleep.
You're sweating a lot.
How is it?
How do you feel, Yuuki?
Drink a lot more.
How do you feel?
Don't do that, Yuuki.
Make yourself feel better.
You're sweating a lot.
How do you feel?
Touch yourself.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm so wet.
You're not that wet, are you?
I was with him for a long time.
I didn't wet you that much.
Make yourself feel better.
How do you feel?
Don't do that, Yuuki.
You're sweating a lot.
How do you feel?
Make yourself feel better.
Don't do that.
You're sweating a lot.
Make yourself feel better.
Don't do that.
How do you feel?
Make yourself feel better.
You're sweating a lot.
I've never done this with him.
Do you want to go with me?
No.
I don't know him.
How do you feel?
Make yourself feel better.
Next.
Please move.
Like this?
Yes.
How do you feel?
Slowly.
You're sweating a lot.
How do you feel?
How do you...
It feels so good.
Let's do it one more time.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm fine.
This is gross.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
, ah , ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, Ah
〜 Ah 〜 Ah 〜 Ah
Ah and
Ah start
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh, oh,
ah, ah,
ah,
This is...
Um...
Really...
Does this really...
be the end?
I'm going back to my normal life.
Thank you for all the wonderful memories.