Haneda, what do you mean?
You said you'd make sure I signed the contract, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
You seemed busy, too.
I don't want to hear any excuses.
There was a complaint from the front line.
There were two complaints this month.
Cut it out.
I'm sorry. I'll never make the same mistake again.
Never again? I'm tired of hearing that.
Are you really reflecting on yourself?
Yes, I am.
Go back to your seat.
Excuse me.
I'll go get some food.
It's already noon.
I don't have any work to do.
Chief, could you check my application?
Okay.
Mino is the chief of this department.
She's a tough boss to her subordinates.
But she's a very serious person.
She's not sexy at all.
Okay.
Haneda.
Yes?
Did you finish the list I asked you to do?
I'm sorry. I forgot.
You forgot?
You have to submit it by Monday morning.
I'll finish it by the end of the day.
Of course.
Finish it even if you have to work overtime.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I haven't finished my work yet.
I'm working overtime.
Are you going back to my house?
Okay.
I'll finish my work and go home early.
I know.
You're going to see Yuka's parents next week, right?
Of course.
Of course I'm nervous.
I'm sorry.
I still have work to do.
I'll hang up.
See you later.
Haneda.
Yes?
How far have you progressed?
I've finished the application for a month.
A month?
Yes.
You haven't progressed at all.
You're working too late.
I'm sorry.
I can't help you and finish it at this pace.
Okay.
Haneda.
Yes?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
You can't go home.
God is noisy.
It's okay.
Submit it with this.
Yes.
It's finally over.
Thank you very much.
Haneda.
Yes?
Can't you work hard?
I'm doing most of it.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for your hard work.
Haneda.
Yes?
It ended earlier than I thought.
Let's go for a drink from now on.
From now on?
From now on.
I have a plan after this.
If I wasn't there, Haneda.
I haven't finished my work.
Go out with me once in a while.
I don't drink a little.
Yes.
I understand.
Get ready to go out.
Yes.
What is a little?
After all, I have to go out for more than 2 hours.
Haneda.
Yes?
Let's go again.
I'm going home.
Let's go for another one.
What's wrong?
The last train is gone.
Is the house far away?
Yes.
Then you can stay at my house.
Is it your house?
Because the last train is gone.
But...
You can stay at my house.
Then I'll listen to you.
Let's go.
Yes.
Come in.
What's wrong?
Your room is like a girl's room.
What are you talking about?
I'm a girl.
Sit down.
Let's drink again, Haneda.
Yes.
I'll make tea for you.
I'm excited to visit a girl's house.
I don't feel that way when I'm with my seniors.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Let's drink.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Yes.
How long have you been dating?
About 6 years.
6 years?
I've been dating since college.
That's a long time.
I haven't told anyone yet.
I'm going to get married next year.
Get married?
Haneda?
How about you?
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
I haven't had a boyfriend for years.
I knew it.
You knew it?
You're a hard worker.
You're cute.
You can have a boyfriend.
I don't need a boyfriend.
I know I'm not attractive as a woman.
That's not true.
Will you go out with me?
I have a girlfriend.
If you don't have a girlfriend, will you go out with me?
If I don't have a girlfriend...
I'm kidding.
You don't have to answer seriously.
I'm going to change my clothes.
Okay.
What kind of joke is this?
I don't understand.
I don't go out with my seniors.
Yuka is sleeping.
That's bad.
Yuka is angry.
I'm angry.
Haneda.
Haneda, sleep on the sofa.
Use this.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Thank you.
I'm tired today.
Haneda made me work overtime.
My body is stiff.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know my seniors were such a big deal.
That's a big deal.
My back is stiff.
I think my back is stiff.
Haneda.
Can you help me?
How can I help you?
Can you lie on me?
Can you pull my shoulders?
I want to stretch my back.
Okay.
Can I lie on you?
Yes.
Can you hold me from behind?
Can I hold you?
Yes.
Can you pull me up?
That's right.
My back is stretched.
That's great.
Are you okay?
I feel good.
Can I pull you a little more?
Yes.
Can you hold me a little more?
I feel good.
I can see your back.
My back is stretched.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes.
My back is stretched.
Next.
I want to stretch my back.
Can you push my legs?
Can you hold my shoulders?
Yes.
Like this?
My back is stretched.
Can you do the other side?
Yes.
Can you hold my shoulders?
Like this?
Yes.
I can't stretch this much alone, so it's helpful.
That's right.
Next.
I want to stretch my legs.
Can you push my legs forward?
Yes.
Like this?
My legs and back are stretched.
I see.
This is a good exercise.
Yes.
I can sleep well with this.
Thank you.
Can I push your legs?
Yes.
It's okay.
Can you push my legs a little more?
Yes.
My back is stretched.
Hey.
Haneda.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Haneda.
Hey.
Stop it.
What's wrong?
I can't stand it when I see your body.
I saw your breast milk.
Are you kidding me?
You are luring me.
I don't mean it.
You were shown my breast milk.
Haneda, calm down.
Wait a minute.
Your breast milk was very big.
I didn't know that.
What are you talking about?
Hey.
You were shown my breast milk.
I didn't mean it.
Wait a minute.
Hey.
Calm down.
Wait a minute.
I can't calm down.
I didn't mean it.
Don't show me your breast milk.
It's beautiful.
Hey.
What are you doing?
It's beautiful.
Don't show me your breast milk.
Haneda.
It's beautiful.
You have big breasts.
It's easy to feel your nipples.
Wait a minute.
Don't do that.
It's beautiful.
It's a waste to hide it.
Don't do that.
No.
Wait a minute.
Haneda.
Hey.
Don't do that.
Haneda.
Don't touch me like that.
Do you like touching?
No.
Don't do that.
Wait a minute.
Hey.
It's a waste to hide it.
Don't do that.
Is it here?
No.
Don't do that.
I'm so embarrassed.
Your face is getting red.
No.
Open your eyes.
I'm sorry.
I'm so embarrassed.
Wait.
Don't look at me.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
Don't look at me.
What's that?
Oh, my God.
No, you can't.
You can't do that to her.
This is a pimple.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Momo
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
This is bad
I'm scared.
What's going on?
What?
Please.
What do you mean?
Wait a minute.
Please.
Oh, my God.
I stopped.
What?
Please.
What? What should I do?
Do you want me to lick you?
No.
I can't do this.
It's okay.
Please.
I'm in this state because of you.
How do you feel?
Do you want me to lick you?
Please.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Please.
You're very good.
It feels good.
No, it doesn't.
It's hot.
It's very hot.
It feels good.
Really?
It's hot.
It's very hot.
I'll put the fire on you.
What?
No, I can't.
I'll put the fire on you.
Why?
You're acting as if you don't need it.
It's very hot.
What should I do?
Wait, wait.
It's been a while since I've done this.
So, will you be nice to me?
Yes, I will.
It's hard, isn't it?
Take your time.
I will.
Ouch!
It feels good.
I can't.
Ouch!
It feels good.
It hurts.
Take your time.
It's amazing.
Your nose is big.
Does it hurt?
Are you okay?
It feels good.
Ouch!
There.
It feels good.
I can't.
It hurts.
Ouch!
It feels good.
I can't.
Ouch!
It feels good.
It's been a while.
Your nose is big.
It's because of your nose.
Is it because of me?
More, more.
It's amazing.
I want to feel it.
It feels good.
I'll put it in.
Ouch!
It feels good.
I can't.
Ouch!
It feels good.
Can I move more?
Yes.
Ouch!
It's amazing.
I've never been so painful.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Ouch!
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
You had sex with your co-worker.
You were attractive.
I'm sorry.
It's a feather.
You had sex with your co-worker.
I'm going to take a shower.
Okay.
You don't have glasses.
You look better without glasses.
Why didn't I notice it until now?
Your face and body look great.
I'm going to take a shower.
Don't come in suddenly.
I'm going to take a shower, too.
I'm going to wash your body.
I'm going out.
Don't worry.
What's wrong?
It's okay.
It's hard to wash your back.
It's okay. I can do it myself.
Thank you.
I'm going to take a shower.
I'm a little embarrassed.
It's okay.
Don't you wash your butt?
I don't do that.
Really?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to wash your butt.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to wash your butt?
It's okay.
I'll wash it myself.
Do you want me to wash your butt?
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Can you wash my body next?
What?
I've never done that before.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
I want you to wash my body with my boobs.
Boobs?
I don't need it.
Wait a minute.
Do you want me to wash your boobs?
I've never done that before.
You can do it.
I'm going to wash your boobs.
I'm sorry.
I've never done that before.
I think you're doing a good job.
Do you think I'm doing a good job?
Yes.
I think you're doing a good job.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Can you wash my boobs?
Is this okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Can you wash my arms?
Arms?
How do you wash your arms?
Like this?
Yes.
How do you wash your bottom?
Your bottom?
What should I do?
Like this?
It's hard again.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
My boobs...
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
Wait a minute.
I'll clean your bottom.
It's hot.
It's a bath.
I'll clean your bottom.
It's intense.
I'm sorry.
I'll clean your bottom.
You may be more wet.
I'll make you feel better.
I've never done this before.
I feel good.
Look at me and do it.
I'll do it for you.
I feel good.
Can you do it?
My boobs...
Like this...
Move your boobs like this.
Please try it.
Please.
That's right.
You can do it slowly.
You're doing great.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
Can I have a drool?
A drool?
It'll feel better.
You're doing great.
Move your legs like this.
Ah...
Maybe, you're trying to get a shot on your nipple.
What?
That's right.
Hold it like this.
Try to get a shot on your nipple.
Wait a minute.
You were trying to get a shot on your nipple.
What?
Try to get a shot on your nipple like this.
It feels good.
If you get a shot on your nipple, you'll feel better.
Ah...
please tell me anything
what did you want to say?
oh yes
did you want it?
yeah, I'd love to hear
it's stiff
Keep breathing in and out.
It's hard. It's hot.
Wait a minute.
I can't do it anymore.
Is it okay? Please warm up.
It feels good.
Did you go with your boobs?
After all, this is cheating.
I suddenly felt guilty about her.
Hello, Yuka.
I have to finish my work at the company.
I'm really sorry.
I'll be back in the morning.
What do you want to do?
I'm sorry.
I'm still working.
I'll call you later.
Were you on the phone with your girlfriend?
Please forget about today.
Of course.
I can't tell anyone about this.
I'm sorry.
You're not wearing makeup.
You're cute without makeup.
I can't do it.
I want to do it again.
Why are you staring at me?
Nothing.
I forgot to check my work email.
Senpai, you're not wearing makeup.
You're wearing makeup again.
Are you staring at me again?
No, I'm not.
Really?
Senpai.
It's hard.
It's been a while since I had sex.
It felt good.
But we said we'd forget about it.
Senpai.
Do you want to have sex?
No.
It's hard.
This is the best.
It's good.
You have a sensitive neck.
Is that so?
You're standing up.
Did you say that?
It's hard.
It feels good.
I can tell you're moving from your pants.
It's hard.
My pants are going to rip.
Senpai.
It's wet.
It feels good.
It's hard.
I want to lick you.
Come here.
It's hard.
It feels good.
You're making a lot of noise.
It's hard.
Senpai.
It feels good.
It's hard.
I want you to feel better.
It feels good.
It's hard.
I'm going to throw up tomorrow.
It feels good.
No.
It's hard.
It feels good.
No.
I'm going to throw up.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's hard.
Hurry!
It hurts...
It hurts so much...
It's so...
It's so disgusting...
No, no, no...
I'll go, I'll go, I'll go...
I'll go, I'll go, I'll go, I'll go...
No, no, no...
It's so disgusting...
I'll go, I'll go, I'll go...
I'll go...
Haneda...
I want Haneda's chip...
Can I just put it in like this?
I don't have any rubber...
It's okay. Just put it in like this.
How long are you going to put it in?
I want to put Haneda's chip in.
I've never done this before.
I'll put it in.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Push it up from below.
It feels really good.
I want to do more.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's too hot.
It's hot.
Ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah...ah
ah
Thank you
Yeah
Oh
Of course.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
!
Ah ah
ah
There's so many of them
I'm so scared
I'm going, I'm going
It hurts, it hurts
It feels so good
I'm so scared
I'm going, I'm going
It feels so good
It hurts, it hurts
I'm so scared
It feels so good
It hurts
It hurts, it hurts
I want to do it more
More?
It's coming out
I understand
Put it in, put it all in
From the back
Suck it in
Put it in
There
It feels so good
More, more
I'm going, I'm going
It hurts, it hurts
It feels so good
More
It hurts, it hurts
I'm going, I'm going
I'm going
It hurts, it hurts
Hey
Can you still stand?
I can't, I really can't
You can still stand, right?
I can't, I'm at my limit
Please forgive me
It's the first time I've had such a good sex
I want to go home because she's waiting
Senpai won't let me go
It's all because of me
Senpai, what are you doing?
Good morning
I have to go home
You can't yet
I can't yet
I'm not satisfied yet
But she's waiting
It looks like you've been dissatisfied for a long time
I can't go home
You're standing a lot
It's because it's stimulating
Do you feel it from the morning?
No, it's because I was doing that when I was sleeping
It's amazing
It's delicious
Your body is trembling
No, I can't
I can't go home
You can't go home?
It's too early
No, I can't
I can't
Senpai, I have to go home
She's waiting at home
I won't let you go yet
I'm not satisfied yet
It's delicious
Let's do something sexy in the morning
Senpai, I can't
I can't
Your body is trembling
No, it's because...
Your nipples are standing
No
Your nipples are weak
I can't
Your nipples and nipples are weak
You don't say you want to go home
But she...
I can't
How is it?
It's hot
Your nipples are trembling
It's cute
Your nipples feel good
Yes, but...
What should I do?
It's hot
How is it?
Does it feel good?
It might feel good
It's hot
No
I can't sit down
You can't
Your body is honest
It's hot
Your nipples are trembling
No
You just licked your nipples
No, I just did it
It's hot
Your nipples are sexy
It's sour
It's hot
Haneda, bow to me
Bow to me
It's hot
How is it?
Your nipples are cute
It's embarrassing
Your body reacts when you lie down
It's hot
Don't touch
It feels good, doesn't it?
I've never been licked
What?
You've never been licked by your girlfriend?
No
Really?
It's embarrassing
I'll lick your nipples
It's hot
Are you okay?
It's good
It's hot
I'll lick your nipples from behind
It's round
Your nipples are full
It's hot
I'm sorry
Your nipples are getting bigger
It's embarrassing
It's hot
How is it?
It feels weird
Haneda, look up
Up?
I want you to feel good about me
About you?
Yes
Let's feel good together
Will you lick my nipples?
Yes
It's hot
Move your tongue
It feels good
It's hot
My hips are moving
There
It feels good
Do it harder
Let me feel good
It feels good
Kiss me
It hurts
Don't stop
Lick me more
Your nipples are full
It hurts
Your nipples are the best
Lick me more
Harder
It's hot
Lick me more
It feels good
It's hot
You can feel it
Do you still want to go home?
Yes
It hurts
I want to feel good
What?
Haneda, can I lick your nipples?
Now?
You don't refuse me
No
I want to feel good
It hurts
You don't refuse me
It feels good
It hurts
Your nipples are full
It's hot
It feels good
Lick me more
It hurts
It's hot
It feels good
It hurts
Feel my nipples more
It's getting harder
It feels good
It hurts
Your girlfriend is calling
Can I ignore her?
Hello?
I'm sorry
I was working
I fell asleep
I'll be home soon
I can't help it
What?
It's just my imagination
It's just a greeting
It's okay
I'll be home soon
What are you doing?
Are you still happy?
Are you excited?
No, I'm not
I don't want her to find out
You're thrilled
It hurts
I'm not satisfied yet
Let's do more
More?
It hurts
I can do it
It feels good
It hurts
Feel my nipples more
It feels good
It hurts
Feel my nipples more
It feels good
More
I can't
It hurts
It feels good
Can I do more?
More
Your nipples are the best
It hurts
It feels good
I can't take it anymore
What? Why?
I can't
I can't take it anymore
I'm not satisfied yet
Can I do more?
She's waiting for me
It feels good
More
I want your nipples
I can't take it anymore
She'll find out
It's still hard
I can't take it anymore
Can I do more?
I can't
If you feel better, I'll give it back
More
I want you to be satisfied
I can't
It feels good
Feel my nipples more
I can't
It's hot
Can I do more?
Yes
More
It feels good
Feel my nipples more
I can't
Can I do more?
More
It feels good
I can't
More
It feels good
Feel my nipples more
I can't
It feels good
Feel my nipples more
I can't
It feels good
You're satisfied, right?
Not yet
Not yet?
How many times did I tell you?
Not yet
Haneda, you've been standing for a long time, haven't you?
I can still do it, can't I?
I'll do my best.
Do you want to put more?
I want to put more.
My body is getting hot.
I'm not satisfied at all.
I can't do it.
Do you want to put more?
I feel good.
I can't do it.
I can do it.
I feel good.
I can't do it.
It's hot.
I can do it.
I can't do it.
Do you want to put more?
I can do it.
I can't do it.
Are you satisfied?
I'm not satisfied at all.
Not at all?
I can't do it.
Senpai, your girlfriend is waiting for you.
You have to go.
This is the last time.
Please.
Let me go.
It's a promise.
It's hot.
Haneda's Jinpo is the best.
I'm going to get married soon.
I have a relationship with my senpai.
Thank you for watching.