I'm tired today.
I'm tired, too.
I know.
I had a lot of work.
You were busy.
I was.
I know.
The boss is angry.
It's okay.
There are days like this.
I'll make up for it.
Are you okay?
What?
We're going home together.
No way.
You're fine.
You're too strict.
Really?
What if someone sees us?
Then you should say something.
What should I say?
You're holding hands.
You should say,
It's a fantasy.
I'm happy.
What?
I'm happy to be with you.
I've never been told that.
Why?
I'm happy.
You're popular, aren't you?
I've always wanted to be popular.
Why are you saying that all of a sudden?
I'm serious.
I'm happy, too.
Why?
You're cute.
You're handsome, too.
What are you talking about?
I'm happy.
I'm really happy.
When we go downstairs,
we should say hello.
Yes.
That's right.
Why are you saying that all of a sudden?
It's the same as usual, isn't it?
What's wrong with you?
It's not like that.
You don't want to go home, do you?
I don't want to go home, but...
I don't want to say it here, but...
We've been together for a long time.
I haven't been to your house yet.
My house?
Is it my house?
That's right.
I want to go there next time.
Do you want to go to my house?
Why did you say that in a loud voice?
I said it in a low voice because I was embarrassed.
Do you want to go to my house?
I said it twice.
I don't mind, but...
Let's go.
Can I come to your house on my day off next week?
Can I?
Yes, you can.
Yes, I'll go.
I want to go.
I'll clean your room.
No problem.
I'll do it.
Really?
I'll cook something for you at home.
I'm glad.
What do you want to eat?
I like curry.
I like spicy food.
Is that so?
I want to drink alcohol today.
All right.
I'll prepare it for you.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to it.
Me, too.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to it.
Me, too.
Then, let's meet here.
I'm looking forward to going on a date at my house.
I understand.
Thank you.
Take care.
See you tomorrow.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm looking forward to going on a date at my house.
Good morning.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
It's okay.
Did I make a mistake?
No, you didn't.
It's okay.
I made a mistake.
We're the same age.
It's fashionable.
Really?
I bought this yesterday.
Did you?
Yes.
For today?
What?
I bought it.
You're cute.
Really?
Thank you.
I only say it once.
I only say it once a day.
I'm looking forward to it.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you for taking the day off.
You're welcome.
Thank you for meeting me.
It's okay.
Shall we go?
Yes.
Did you have breakfast?
No, I didn't.
Shall we go to a cafe?
Yes, let's go.
Let's go.
I'm nervous.
Really?
You're cute.
Why?
You're different from your usual job.
You're right.
I'm nervous.
Really?
You're cute.
My heart is beating fast.
I see.
Do you come here often?
No, I don't come here often.
I see.
I'm sorry to have you come to my house.
Not at all.
I can enjoy the atmosphere where you are.
I need a lot of air.
You're a pervert.
This way.
Let's go.
It's a heart.
You're cute.
Did you order it?
No, I didn't.
It's on the house.
It's amazing.
Let's drink.
Is it hot?
It's hot.
It's good.
Is it good?
I thought I should put it here.
Did you put it here by yourself?
I put it here.
Why?
I thought I should put it here.
It's more fun.
You're right.
I came here to enjoy it.
I see.
It's a lot of fun.
Do you usually eat cake?
Yes, I do.
You're slim.
Really?
Yes.
You're amazing.
You have a good style.
Don't you think so?
I don't like puffiness.
You don't like puffiness?
What's wrong with you?
I want to do my best.
You're beautiful.
Thank you.
It's okay.
If you say it's okay, I'll accept it.
I think you're beautiful, too.
Thank you.
What kind of cake is this?
Why are you blushing?
What kind of cake did you order?
This is chocolate.
Do you want to eat it?
I'll have a bite.
Then, please give me a food report.
Okay.
I'll do my best to give you a food report.
I'll do my best.
Thank you for the food.
It smells.
You don't have to do that.
You're funny.
How is it?
Is it good?
It tastes like white chocolate.
Is it white chocolate and normal chocolate?
Yes.
I didn't know that.
Can I eat it?
Yes.
I want to eat it.
Can I eat it?
Yes.
It's on the cake.
What?
It's on the cake again.
Wait a minute.
I'll eat it.
It's a pain.
You've decided to do it, haven't you?
What?
I don't know.
How long haven't you had a boyfriend?
I haven't had a boyfriend for 4 years.
Really?
Really.
Why?
I don't have a boyfriend at work.
That's true.
I'm busy.
Yes.
But...
Why do you like me?
What?
I'm going to ask you that.
I'm embarrassed.
I see.
I want to protect you.
You have a great sense of humor.
And you're cute.
When I came to Kuroi, everyone said that I was handsome.
Really?
Really.
I've never heard that.
I don't say that directly.
Really?
I don't say that.
I'm glad to hear that.
Who told you that?
It's a secret.
What?
I don't want you to know that.
Please tell me who told you that.
No.
You don't want to tell me?
I don't want to tell you.
I wanted to tell you.
But I didn't tell you.
You're a good girl.
I'm a good girl.
That's right.
It's refreshing to be with you on your day off.
We don't have many days off.
That's right.
Were you younger than me?
What?
Younger than you?
Yes.
Are you going to ask me that?
I'm younger than you and older than you.
Are you younger than me?
No.
I see.
I'm younger than you for the first time.
You look younger than me.
Really?
I'm glad to hear that.
You look like a senior to me.
I want you to tell me that.
I'm tolerant.
Can I tell you that?
Yes.
You're a senior to me.
Can I tell you that?
No.
I'm tolerant.
I do everything for you.
You do everything for me?
Yes.
You're kind.
I'm kind, aren't I?
I think girls are kind.
It's my first time to be polite to her.
That's right.
You're polite to me.
You can't go home now, can you?
But...
I don't want to.
What?
I don't want to stay here.
I don't want to talk to you.
Do you want to talk to me?
Yes.
You're my girlfriend.
I'm your girlfriend.
I want to have a lot of fun with you.
If I talk to you politely, I feel like I'm a junior to you.
That's right.
Can I talk to you politely?
Yes.
Can I?
Really?
Yes.
Are you angry?
No.
Are you really angry?
I might be angry if I talk too much.
What if I talk to you politely at work?
I'll tell my boss.
Okay.
Do your best.
I said, okay.
Really?
You said it, too.
Okay.
Let's break up.
Let's make a promise.
Okay.
What if we break up?
If we break up, I'll punish you.
What?
Make a decision then.
I'll make a decision.
Okay.
I'll make a decision of love.
I'm looking forward to it.
Me, too.
Let's go somewhere.
Let's go.
It's safe whether we go to Mashoka.
Yes, it's safe.
Let's go somewhere.
Let's go.
Let's eat something.
It's safe.
The next day
It smells nice.
Does it smell nice?
Yeah, you're really good at cutting.
I'm not making fun of you.
Really?
Yeah.
You don't make that much.
Oh, really?
You're going to make it for me.
I thought I'd do my best.
Thank you.
We're finally alone.
What?
It's been a while since I've been in a man's room, so I'm nervous.
I see.
What?
I'm nervous.
What should I do?
What's wrong?
Your fingers are beautiful.
Thank you.
I'm getting nervous.
Really?
What should I do?
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
I'm nervous.
Really?
Touch me.
All right.
Can I touch you?
What should I do?
How about curry?
Curry?
Later.
Later?
Okay.
It's hot.
What?
Do you want to eat curry later?
What's wrong?
Look at me.
Let's do something pleasant.
Something pleasant?
It's been a while.
It's been a while?
I'm nervous.
Really?
You're cute.
Give me your hand.
Touch me.
Can I touch you?
You have big boobs.
Really?
Your boobs were this big.
Did you find them today?
It feels good.
It's hot.
What are you doing now?
I'm petting you.
Does it feel good?
Does it feel good now?
You look like you're in a good mood.
You're staring at me.
Look at this.
Do you want to see it?
Do you want to see it directly?
You have a beautiful voice.
Can I touch you?
It feels good.
I want to see it directly.
Do you want to take it off?
Can I take it off?
Do your best.
Can I touch you?
Why are you hiding it?
Your boobs were this big.
It's really big.
It's really soft.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's really soft.
It's fluffy.
Why is it so fluffy?
I wonder why.
Can I touch you?
It feels good.
Do you like being touched?
Can I touch you?
It's okay.
It's really beautiful.
How do you like it?
Slowly.
Slowly?
What's wrong?
It feels good.
You like it.
It's so cute.
I'm sorry...
I don't want to...
Do you want to sleep?
Yes, I want to sleep.
Let's get warm.
Here?
It's hard to get up.
Can you show me?
Yes, I can.
You are too impatient.
It's so cool.
Really?
Let me touch you a lot.
Yes.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I do.
It's so cool.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I do.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
Do you feel good?
Yes, I do.
Senpai.
What?
You are so smooth.
Yes, I am.
Why?
Because I like you.
Do you feel good?
Let me touch you a little more.
You are so smooth.
Can I touch you a little more?
Yes, I can.
You are so smooth.
Do you feel good?
Don't do that.
I'll do it.
Senpai.
What's wrong with you?
Wait a minute.
Senpai.
Do you feel good?
Wait a minute.
You are so big!
You are big!
I'm shy.
I'm hooked
It's hot.
It's very hot.
I'll turn on the air conditioner.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It's too hot.
It's hot.
It's in.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's in.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's in.
It feels good.
I'm going to go crazy.
It's hot.
It's in.
It feels good.
I'm in, too.
What are you going to do with your feet?
My feet are stuck.
Your feet are stuck?
Yes, they are.
Like this?
It's hot.
It's in.
It feels good.
It feels good?
It tickles.
It feels good.
Wait.
It tickles.
It feels good.
Wait.
It tickles.
I can't do it anymore.
You can't do it anymore?
I told you to do it.
It feels good.
It's cute.
It tickles.
It feels good.
It feels good?
It tickles.
I can't do it anymore.
It felt good, didn't it?
It felt so good that I left right away.
I'm glad.
Are you going to take a shower?
I'm going to take a shower.
I'm sweating a lot.
You are sweating a lot.
It's hot, isn't it?
What about curry?
I forgot.
Let's eat it after taking a shower.
I'm going to wash your body.
Please.
It's hot, isn't it?
Is it hot?
No, it's not hot at all.
You are so fluffy.
What about the soup?
It's hot.
Please look this way.
You are sweating a lot.
I'm sweating.
I'm sweating with you.
What are you doing?
I'm just washing you.
Do you wash yourself like this?
Do I?
I'm going to wash you well today.
You are so fluffy.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You are so fluffy.
Next time,
I'm going to wash your body.
Can I do that?
I think you should do that.
I'm going to put a bandage on your neck.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
Do you always wash your hair like this?
Yes, I do.
Then, I'll wash your hair too.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
Do you have a pimple?
No, I don't.
I don't have a pimple.
You don't have a pimple, do you?
No, I don't.
You look like you have a pimple.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Does it feel good?
I'll make you feel better.
Can I bring a towel?
Yes, you can.
It feels good, doesn't it?
What happened to you?
What about here?
It feels good, doesn't it?
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
Is it hot?
No, it's okay.
Thank you.
It's warm.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's okay.
Isn't it cold?
It's a little cold.
It's cold, isn't it?
It's okay.
Thank you.
It's a little cold, isn't it?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Thank you.
It's warm.
It's warm, isn't it?
Thank you.
You are so cute.
What's wrong?
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
You feel like you're going to throw up.
Kuroi-kun.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
Senpai.
Senpai, you feel like you're going to throw up, don't you?
Drink it again.
You have a beautiful face.
Do you want to taste the sake?
No, thank you.
It's warm.
It's warm, isn't it?
You have a beautiful face.
Do you want me to do it with your boobs?
Boobs?
Kuroi-kun, you like boobs, don't you?
It's okay.
What should I do?
It's warm, isn't it?
Does it feel good?
Do you want me to do it with your boobs?
It's warm, isn't it?
Does it feel good?
I'll make you feel better.
What?
I've finished myown part and filled it in and Dodie's going to do the rest.
You can do it all I'll finish the yolk first too.
It might be too much when you're a bit excited but I hope you really like this stuff.
And Dracula, it's good to live.
I wonder if it will be OK.
Emi-chan...
I'm so hungry...
Kuro-kun, you've got a lot on your face
Yes, I've got a lot on my face
Wow, you've got a lot on your face
Ah, it's hot
Ah, does it feel good?
How is it?
It feels good
You've got a lot on your mind
Did my boobs feel good?
How is it?
It looks good
Thank you
It's good
Shall we eat?
Yes
Let's eat
Do you drink a lot?
Yes
What?
Yes, I like it
How about alcohol?
Kuro-kun is weak, but he likes it
Then I'll drink a lot
You can drink a lot
But I feel like I'm getting better
That's true
I drank a lot
You drank a lot
How about this T-shirt?
What?
Does it look good on me?
It smells like you, Kuro-kun
Does it smell the same?
Yes, it smells the same
It smells like you
How is it?
I feel like I'm getting better
What do you mean?
I don't know
I feel like I'm getting better
Why?
Did you pretend to be drunk?
No
Do you want to kiss me?
You're mean
Does it taste like alcohol?
Both of you
You're touching me
I'm touching you
Do you feel it?
Yes
Does it feel good?
I'll give you a lot
Touch me directly
Are you sure?
Does it feel good?
Do you feel it?
No
Does it feel good?
Can I look at you?
I want to look at you
This way
You're amazing
You're big
Does it feel good?
You're cute
You're standing up
Does it feel good?
Yes
Touch me with your hand
Does it feel good?
You're cute
Do you feel it?
Touch me
Touch me more
Does it feel good?
Let's go to bed
Come here
I want you to touch me with your boob
Okay
Does it feel good?
You're fluffy
Really?
I'm happy
You're pulling a string
Does it feel good?
You're so soft
It feels good for me
Does it feel good?
How about here?
I'm pulling a string
Does it feel good?
You look so happy
I'm hungry
Does it feel good?
Do you want to do it slowly?
I'm going to do it hard
Does it feel good?
Do you want to sleep together?
No
Let's sleep together
Does it feel good?
You're reacting too much
How about here?
Do you want to sleep together?
Does it feel good?
No
I'm going to pull a string
Does it feel good?
It feels so good
Ahh!
It feels so good!
Ah, it's so hot.
It's so hot.
It's okay.
Ah, it's so hot.
It's so hot.
I love you too.
Ah, it's so hot.
It's so hot.
Take your time.
I love you.
I love you too.
It's so hot.
Ah, it's so hot.
I love you.
It's so hot.
Take your time.
Ah, it's so hot.
It feels good.
It's so hot.
It's okay.
Ah, it's so hot.
It's so hot.
It feels good.
How do you feel?
It's so hot.
Ah, it's so hot.
Take your time.
It's so hot.
Ah, it's so hot.
I want to put it in.
I want to put it in my bag.
Your bag?
It's so hot.
It feels good.
Ah, it's so hot.
It's so hot.
It feels good.
I can sleep well.
It's so hot.
You do great things from the morning.
Sometimes I want to have a sex in the morning.
I don't want to have a sex with you.
I want to have a sex with you.
I'm lonely.
Your body is dry.
I like this kind of thing.
I'm lonely.
Do you feel better?
I'm fine.
You love me, don't you?
I feel so good.
I'm happy.
I want to have a sex with you.
Really?
I know you're here.
Do you remember me?
I remember you.
I'm here.
What are you going to do?
You want to sleep, don't you?
Look at your face.
You're too sexy.
What are you going to do?
Hurry up.
I feel so good.
What's wrong?
Do you feel good?
I feel so good.
Don't do that.
Put it in.
I'm going to do it.
I feel so good.
Good girl.
No!
She's going!
She's so cute.
She's so close.
Let's do something fun.
What is this?
Senpai.
It feels so good.
Don't do that.
What are you doing?
I'm going to get on the bike.
Are you going to get on?
It feels so good.
I'm going!
Wait for me.
Why are you doing this to me?
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I can't.
It feels good.
Do you want to drink?
It's hot.
Are you ready?
Yes.
It was fun.
I'll take you to the station.
Kiss me.
Kiss you?
Let's go.
When are you coming next?
Next?
Can I come right away?
Sure.
Let's hang out soon.
Thank you.
Let's go.