A Year Left to Resume
After big sister married and left our house...
for about a month.
My father and I were the only ones in the family.
It was very lonely.
When I looked at my sister's room,
I was struck by fear.
I lost my mother when I was young.
Since when did my sister become my mother?
That's why this house, where my sister died,
was shrouded in loneliness.
At that time,
my sister died.
Sister?
I'm sorry.
Where's your father?
My father?
He's out right now.
What's wrong?
Well...
It was hot.
Isn't it hot today?
Yeah.
The train was so crowded.
I'm tired.
It's been a while.
Did you cut your hair?
My sister came back.
It's been a while.
It looks delicious.
It's been a while since the three of us ate together.
You're right.
Take your time.
It's your house.
Thank you, Dad.
I'm sorry.
But...
Don't you have to talk to each other about fighting?
Time will solve it.
I'm going to bed.
Good night.
Go out with me.
What?
It's my favorite.
It's delicious.
Don't drink too much.
You can't drink much.
But...
You should drink, too.
What's the cause of the couple fight?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Is it hard to say?
It's hard to say.
I think it's a matter of the night.
A matter of the night?
Is it a matter of marital life?
Maybe.
What do you mean by impossible?
I'm sorry.
It's hard every time.
Is it hard?
You mean you don't want to have sex with me?
I don't want to have sex with you.
What?
I don't understand.
You have to tell me clearly.
I don't know.
I want to leave you alone for a while.
It's okay.
It's not impossible.
Mion.
Why did you leave the house?
You don't understand.
It's hard.
You're doing something strange.
Is that so?
Do you have any idea?
What?
Why don't you try it?
What's so hard about my sex life?
What do you mean?
What?
What did you do to my underwear?
I didn't do anything.
Please.
I'll do what I always do with my husband.
What are you talking about?
Wait a minute.
What's so strange about my sex life?
What?
Mion.
What are you doing?
Do you want to have sex with me?
No, I don't want to.
You're having sex with your girlfriend, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
You're very sensitive.
You have to see what's wrong with my sex life.
You'll look at me, right?
Is that so?
Don't you want to have sex with me?
I'm a little embarrassed.
It's not that I don't want to.
What do you think?
It feels good.
You've grown up.
Does your neck feel good?
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Does your neck feel good?
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Do I look like this?
I'm a little embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
You used to be like this.
It's getting hot.
It's hot.
That's amazing.
I'll lick you.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Does your girlfriend lick you like this?
She usually licks me.
It feels good.
It's hot.
What do you think?
What do you think of my sex life?
It feels good.
Is there anything wrong?
There's nothing wrong.
Really?
Come here.
Here?
Sit here.
I'll give you a massage.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Turn around.
Over there.
I'm sorry.
What do you think?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
What do you think?
Is there anything wrong?
There's nothing wrong.
It feels good.
Really?
Yes.
Do you want to do it next time?
I'll do my best.
You have a lot of breasts.
Can I lick your breasts?
Yes.
You have a lot of breasts.
It's beautiful.
Yes.
Do you like breasts?
How about here?
Yes.
It's beautiful.
Don't look at me like that.
It's the first time I've seen you like this.
It's embarrassing.
I'll lick your breasts.
What do you want to do?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
You're good.
Really?
It feels good.
Yes.
I'll lick your bottom.
My bottom?
Where?
Come here.
I'll lick your bottom a little more.
It feels good there.
Here?
It feels good.
Does it feel good here?
The other side.
It feels good.
I'll lick your bottom a little more.
I like it.
Here?
I'll lick your bottom a little more.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
I'll lick your bottom a little more.
Lie down.
Lie down a little more.
It feels good.
The other side.
It hurts.
I'll lick your bottom a little more.
I can't stand it.
It feels good.
It hurts.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
It hurts.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
It hurts.
I'll lick your bottom a little more.
It feels good.
It hurts.
What do you want to do next?
It feels good.
Can I move?
No.
I'll lick your bottom a little more.
Lie down.
Can I move?
I'll lick your bottom a little more.
It feels good.
Can I move?
Yes.
It feels good.
One more time.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I'll lick your bottom a little more.
Can I lick your bottom a little more?
It feels good.
I'll lick your bottom a little more.
Can I move?
Yes.
It feels good.
I'll lick your bottom a little more.
Are you doing something strange?
No.
It feels good.
I'll lick your bottom a little more.
It's warm.
Did you feel good?
Yes.
How was my sex?
It felt really good.
It was the best I've ever had.
I didn't mean that.
Maybe.
What?
Be honest with me.
The hole in your bottom?
I can feel it.
Maybe I like you.
I don't like you.
Really?
I didn't mean that.
My Anaru was licking me.
Maybe I made him do it.
You made him do it?
I don't hate you.
You're the worst.
Don't worry.
I'll lick your Anaru.
And that's how our secret relationship came to be.
And that's how
our secret relationship came to be.
After that, my sister didn't end her quarrel with her husband, and decided to stay at home for a while.
but since the story started, I think it would be really great if you enjoyed it!
It's a good place to take a break from the busy life of the city.
Hey, I'm seducing you, aren't I?
What?
You're showing me this.
Which one?
What?
Do you want to lick me?
Don't you want to lick me?
Ouch!
Lick me properly.
You don't have to lick me.
That's it.
It feels good.
Do it again.
One more time.
Ouch!
It feels good.
Why are you staring at me?
What?
Are you tired?
No, I'm not.
I'll show you.
Okay.
Your nose is amazing.
Can you see me well?
Ouch!
It feels good.
I can't stand it anymore.
I can't help it.
Stand there.
I'll show you.
Look at me.
Okay.
Ouch!
It feels good.
You made me so big.
I can't stand it anymore.
It feels good.
Stand there.
I can't do it yet.
I want to do it more.
Can you do it?
It feels good.
Ouch!
Look at me.
It feels good.
Look around.
Let's go together.
Let me pet you.
Ouch!
You have a lot of them.
Can you see them?
I ate them.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I was licked by Furu.
You want to be licked?
I can't help it.
Can I lick you a lot?
Can I lick your butt a lot?
You're not wearing anything.
You're not wearing anything, are you?
Maybe I'm not wearing anything.
You're so wet.
You're sweating.
Just here?
You're sweating all over.
You're sweating over there, too.
You're all wet.
You're so delicious.
Is it good?
I can lick you a lot.
I'm getting warm.
I'm going.
You're going to lick me again, aren't you?
I want to lick you a lot more.
I want to lick you a lot.
Is it salty?
I'm sorry.
I'll do my best.
Are you all right?
You're still wet.
Can I lick you more?
It feels good.
I'm sweating a lot.
I want to lick you a lot.
Can I help you?
I'll help you.
I'm sweating a lot.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Sit here.
It's still hot, isn't it?
Can I lick you?
It feels good.
It hurts.
No, no, no.
I'm going.
It's hot, isn't it?
Can I lick you?
I'm sweating a lot.
I don't know how to do this.
I'll give you a pair of scissors.
Scissors?
Yes.
Can I?
Wait a minute.
Before that, lick me.
Yes.
Lick me properly.
If you don't lick me properly, I won't play with you.
Yes.
Does it feel good?
You want me to play with you, right?
Yes.
Lick me a lot.
Who do you play with?
Well, I've seen her before.
Really?
Yes.
I don't know.
I don't know her well.
Really?
Yes.
I see.
Then, I'm going to pull your tooth as hard as I can
so this feels good
How do you feel?
Does it feel good?
Is it slimy?
How do you feel?
Does it feel good?
Don't do that.
You only licked a little.
How do you feel?
Good evening.
Can I do it?
It's not right.
You have to do it properly.
Do it properly.
How do you feel?
You're moving a lot.
Relax.
It feels good.
Can I do it?
You're moving a lot.
Can I do it more?
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Do you lick me?
Lick me again.
It feels good.
How do you feel?
Lick me again.
Can I do it?
It feels good.
Can I do it more?
How do you feel?
Can you see me?
It feels good.
How do you feel?
Can I do it?
It feels good.
Can I do it more?
My hips are warm.
It's like here.
It feels good.
I slept a lot.
My hands are wet.
Even the best days were about to come to an end.
I'm sorry.
From now on, I'll lick you.
If you don't like it, you don't have to lick me.
There are people who want to lick.
I don't hate it.
I want to lick your ass hole.
Wait a minute.
I got it.
Don't say it out loud.
Really?
Thank you.
Let's go home.
Okay.
I got it.
I have luggage.
I'll go home tomorrow morning.
Go home alone today.
Okay.
Are you going home?
I don't like it.
I'm the one who can lick you the most comfortably.
I won't lose to you.
Here?
You like it here.
I like it here.
I got it.
I'm sorry.
You're so stupid.
I'm not good at licking, am I?
You're doing a great job.
I think you're getting better.
Are you getting better at licking?
You're doing a great job.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who can lick you the most comfortably.
Okay.
But today is the last day.
Today is the last day.
Okay.
I'll lick you a lot.
I won't let you down.
You like it, don't you?
I'll lick you a lot.
I want you to lick me.
I'm sorry.
I left you alone.
I feel so good.
I'll do the same for you.
I feel good when you lick me.
I feel good.
Is it good?
You smell so good.
I feel so good.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
I'm sweating a lot.
I want you to lick me.
I feel good.
Ah.
Ahh...
Ah...
Ah!
Oh...
Ah...
Eh?
misunderstanding
Ah...
ah...
Oh, you're so good...
Ah
Neku
You're getting better at petting me.
You pet me so many times.
Look at me.
Pet me.
I want you to pet me.
It feels good.
Open your eyes wide.
Can you see me?
Your nose is running.
Look at me.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Open your eyes.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Let me pet you.
It feels good.
Let's go.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I'm petting you.
You're petting me a lot.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's okay.
What should I do?
It feels good.
Let's go.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Is it really over?
You said it was over.
Forget it.
See you.
I can't forget you.
Let's go.
Come here.
It hurts.