I'm going to draw a line on the back of the head.
I don't like my eyebrows because they're too awaits.
I draw a line on the back of the head to make his eyes look bigger.
I hate you...
I'm going to make a hole in the back of the head.
I've got a hole in my back.
I think it's too late to start dissection.
I'm going to make a hole in the back of the head.
I'm going to put it here.
Excuse me.
Please contact us through the app.
Please bring a glass.
Are you ready to drink?
Let's start drinking.
Cheers!
Thank you.
Can I start by introducing myself?
I'm Yuton.
I'm 28 years old.
This is my friend Takeshi.
We're the same age.
We work in the media industry.
Media industry.
That's cool.
That's amazing.
How about you?
I'm Miwa.
I'm Haruka.
Nice to meet you.
Really?
What did you come here for?
To kill time?
Or to have fun?
Actually, she broke up with her boyfriend.
Really?
We were drinking together until a while ago.
But we were talking a lot.
So, we came here to look for a new relationship.
We came here to look for a new relationship.
Let's make a toast.
Again?
Let's make a toast for a new relationship.
Let's do it.
Excuse me.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Where should we go?
I know.
I like this place.
Let's go.
We're going to go fishing.
I heard a good place to fish.
So, I'll go fishing.
What?
I'll go fishing.
See you later.
Good luck.
Excuse me.
Is it okay to have a boyfriend?
I broke up with my boyfriend and he cheated on me.
I broke up with him.
Hey.
I ran out of battery.
Don't you want to go out?
It's okay, isn't it?
Let's go out.
No?
Do you have plans for tomorrow?
Let's go out.
Come here.
Touch me.
I haven't seen you for more than a month.
So, can I touch you after a long time?
Let me take off your skirt.
Touch me.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
Do you like my butt?
Look at me.
I didn't do it at all.
So, I stopped.
Touch me.
How do you feel?
How about my boobs?
Do you like big boobs?
I want you to look at them.
Touch me.
How do you feel?
You don't hate big boobs, do you?
Let me take off your skirt.
How do you feel?
Touch me.
You don't hate them, do you?
Can I take off your clothes?
Do you like my neck?
Can I lick it?
I like to lick.
How do you feel?
You like it.
Can I take off this part, too?
I learned a lot from him.
Can I do it?
You are bigger than your boyfriend.
Can I take it off?
I'm glad you are this big.
Look at me.
How do you feel?
Are you okay?
Come here.
Touch me.
How do you feel?
Touch me, too.
I slept a lot because I didn't do it for a month.
Come here.
It's amazing.
Let me take off your panties.
Look at me.
Touch me.
It tickles.
Put your fingers in from behind.
My boyfriend didn't do it for me.
It tickles.
Let's sleep together.
Come here.
I want you to drink a lot.
It tickles.
I can't stand it.
How do you feel?
Can I kiss you?
You are very sensitive.
I'm happy.
It's going to be intense today.
It tickles.
I like this place.
I didn't like the bath at all.
I'm glad you feel that way.
It tickles.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's so hard.
Can I put it in?
It's been a while since I put it in.
Be nice to me.
It's amazing.
It tickles.
My boyfriend is big.
Come closer.
It tickles.
I've never done this before.
I can't stand it anymore.
It tickles.
I couldn't stand it at all when I was with my boyfriend.
Come closer.
It tickles.
What is this?
I can't stand it anymore.
It tickles.
Can I put a lot on you?
Let's hold hands.
It tickles.
I've done it twice.
How do you feel?
You look charismatic.
It tickles.
Let me put more on you.
How do you feel?
It tickles.
You're amazing.
You're good at putting on a boyfriend.
I've never done this before.
It tickles.
You're amazing.
I'll do it again.
Shirai.
Yes.
I made a mistake here.
I'm sorry.
I'll fix it.
Okay.
Thank you.
Hey.
Come here.
What's going on?
Look at this.
Can you see it?
This.
What's going on?
I made a mistake.
I can't use it.
What if the customers see this?
They'll think it's a joke.
You're always like this.
What are you doing?
You don't use it at all.
Please.
Fix it.
Are you listening?
Here.
Fix it.
Can you fix it?
What?
Are you okay?
I'm worried about you.
Go to sleep.
I bought a lot because I was worried about you.
I'm sorry.
Are you eating?
Did you take a nutritional supplement?
I bought a nutritional supplement.
I also bought a nutritional drink.
I thought you weren't eating.
I also bought a banana.
Did you drink water?
Do you want to sleep?
Wait a minute.
Do you want to drink water?
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
I spilled it.
You'll get a fever.
Are you okay?
If you don't take off your clothes, you'll catch a cold.
If you get a fever, you'll catch a cold.
It's not cold.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
You've grown up so much.
You...
You're not good at your job.
But you're doing great here.
You're amazing.
What's wrong with you?
I made you naked.
Did you get a cold?
Well...
If you touch this part,
You'll get a fever.
I'll cool you down.
Try it on.
You're amazing.
You've grown up so much.
If you lick this part, you'll get a fever.
You're amazing.
You're getting better again.
I'll cool you down.
The fever may go down.
It's getting hotter here.
Let me see.
It's okay.
You want to cool down, don't you?
You're amazing.
The fever may have gone down.
I'll cool you down.
You're always angry.
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
But today,
I'll be nice to you.
It's hot.
How do you feel?
You're getting better.
Can I take it off, too?
Take the back jacket off.
Thank you.
I'll take it off.
How do you feel?
Touch it.
How is it?
Is it soft?
Look at my feet.
Touch my feet.
Let me take off my panties.
I took off my panties.
Thank you for everything.
It's hot.
It's very warm.
Keep it a secret to everyone.
It's a secret between the two of us.
It's hot and hard, so it feels good.
You're amazing.
It's hot.
You're very sexy.
It feels good.
It's wet.
Let's do it at the company.
I'll serve you a lot today.
You're amazing.
It's so hard that my boobs feel bad.
I'm glad.
Why is it so hot?
I'm going crazy.
It feels good.
It's very hot.
I'll serve you a lot.
I'm glad.
I feel better.
Look.
You're amazing.
I served you a lot.
It's delicious.
I'll do my best tomorrow.
Good luck.
I'm going to pick up a girl.
Do you remember what I taught you so far?
If you're in trouble, just call me.
Do you understand?
What should I do?
Let's go.
What is it?
Are you going to pick up a girl?
Okay.
Let's go.
But...
I prefer your house...
than my hotel.
Do you sleep in this room?
object!!
I'm studying psychology at university.
Next,
I wanted to write a paper on men's sexual assault.
I'm glad you're here.
Could you help me?
It's okay.
I don't think research is good.
Please cooperate with me.
You're the one who picked me up, aren't you?
Do you like kisses?
Is this okay?
I'll take it off.
Don't be nervous.
It's research.
Don't be so embarrassed.
Can I lick you?
Did you feel it now?
I'm glad.
Is this okay?
Do you like to be licked like this?
How about being teased with your fingers?
I'm glad you feel that way.
It's getting bigger.
Do you like to be touched from above?
I'm going to write a good paper today.
Can I take this off?
I'll take it off.
Don't be so embarrassed.
It's amazing.
It's getting bigger.
I'll write it down.
It's amazing.
It's getting so big.
It's fun.
Where do you feel good?
How about here?
You're very sensitive.
I'll take it off.
It's amazing.
How do you feel?
You're honest.
Where do you like best?
Here?
Is it here?
Can I lick you?
How do you feel?
Does it feel good?
How about here?
You feel great.
Is it okay to lick like this?
How about this?
How do you feel?
I've done a lot of research.
You seem to like it.
Do you like to be licked?
Like this?
It's amazing.
You're right.
Are you okay?
I've done a lot of research.
Do you like butt?
It's hot.
Please touch your chest.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
I have something I want to try.
Have you ever done this?
Are you waiting?
Are you okay?
It's very warm.
Please look closely.
It's very hard.
I'm glad I studied.
I'll take off my glasses.
How do you feel?
It's my first time to wear this.
I'm a little embarrassed.
It's strange, isn't it?
Please look closely.
It's very hot.
Can I lick you once?
Did you like it?
It's very hot.
I can feel the heat in my chest.
How do you feel?
I've done a lot of research.
I'm not sure.
Can I touch you?
Can you look at me?
I'm a little embarrassed.
Have you ever seen this?
It's very embarrassing.
Please look closely.
How do you feel?
Please touch me.
I feel great.
I'm so excited.
I feel very comfortable today.
I feel great.
Can I write this on a piece of paper?
I'm sweating a lot.
It's a little embarrassing.
I'll write this down, too.
Can I talk to you again?
How do you feel?
You seem to like my nipples.
I'll lick you a lot.
Do you like my nipples?
Can you take off the ribbon here?
I'll take it off.
I took it off.
It's very embarrassing.
This is also for research.
Can I touch you?
How do you feel?
I feel great.
How about this?
I'll rub you a lot.
I feel great, too.
How do you feel?
It's very hot.
I'm singing.
I want you to lick my nipples.
I feel great.
Please touch me more.
You're very good.
Can I touch you?
Can I take it off?
It's coming in.
I feel great.
How do you feel?
It's very hot.
I'll move a little.
It's coming in.
I feel great.
How do you feel when I touch you like this?
Your nipples are very sensitive.
I feel great.
Do you like it here?
Please touch my nipples.
How do you feel?
Do you feel like this?
Please look at me more.
How do you feel?
I feel great.
Please look at me more.
This is popular.
I wanted to try it.
I didn't think I'd feel this way.
I feel great.
I've never done this before.
I've done this before.
How do you feel?
Do you feel great?
I watched a lot of videos and studied.
I wanted to try this.
I feel great.
I wanted to do it faster.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Taka-kun
Ah, ah, ah, ah ...
It seems that you regularly come out
I'm happy
Please write this part in your book
Thank you very much
How about bicycle department oflease?
It's so good.
Here you are.
Thank you.
It's 1,680 yen.
Here you are.
Thank you.
It's 1,680 yen.
You always look at me, don't you?
Do you hear me?
Look at me.
Come here.
What are you doing?
It's okay.
Come here.
You always look at me, don't you?
You don't come to me, do you?
If you look at me like that, you can't do that, can you?
You look stiff, don't you?
You can't work like this, can you?
Do you want me to do it for you?
It's okay.
Sit down.
Can I lick you?
It's okay.
You don't come to me.
It's easy for you to bite me, isn't it?
You're cute.
I'll take this off, too.
Take it off.
I'm nervous.
Can I take this off, too?
I'll take it off.
It's embarrassing to be seen.
How do you feel?
I'm nervous.
I want to see you.
I'm so nervous.
You're having fun, aren't you?
I know you're having fun.
I'm nervous, too.
It's okay.
You don't come to me.
It's good to be like this sometimes.
Touch me.
How do you feel?
Do you like my breast?
You're not used to it.
You're cute.
Touch my neck.
How do you feel?
You're cute.
I'm embarrassed.
I touched you.
It's hot, isn't it?
I'm glad.
I can see you all the time.
I'll put this in, too.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry for doing this.
But you're having fun, aren't you?
I'm glad.
You're cute.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
Can I lick this?
I'll take off my panties.
I'll eat it.
I'm glad.
It's been a long time, hasn't it?
Me, too.
It's amazing.
It's getting really hard.
I'm glad.
Have you ever done this?
Come here.
It's amazing.
It's hot, isn't it?
I'll be right back.
It's hot.
I can't do it yet.
Do you like sticky things?
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm glad.
I want you to put a lot on me.
It's amazing.
It's really hard.
I'm sweating so much.
I'm glad.
I'm still sensitive.
Next time, I'll put on a shift.
Let's do it again.
I'll do it again.
Excuse me.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Honoka.
Where are you going today?
I'll take a look at you.
This area is quite swollen.
I'll focus on this area today.
Thank you.
I'll use this oil today.
Excuse me.
I'm tired because my legs are so swollen.
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you.
I've just started, so if it hurts or feels weak, please let me know.
I'll change the weight.
I'll massage this side, too.
I'm tired here, too.
Please let me know if it hurts.
Does this area hurt?
Are you okay?
Is it better not to massage this area?
There's a lot of lymph here, so it'll feel better if I do it.
Please open your legs a little.
Please put your legs on the floor.
Please relax.
How is it?
I love being pressed here.
Did I overdo it?
Actually,
I...
I'd like you to touch me before I clean up.
It's pretty hard, isn't it?
Actually, I shouldn't do this.
You're very nice.
I've been doing this all the time.
Can I take this button off?
It's a secret.
If I find out, I'll be fired.
I'm embarrassed.
How is it?
Please touch me.
I get excited every month before I clean up.
Can I take this off?
I'm going to sleep.
Do you really like this place the most?
I'll add more oil.
I'll take off my pants.
It's amazing.
I think my blood flow has improved.
I'll add oil here, too.
It's very hot.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm getting very excited.
Can I take off my socks?
Thank you very much.
Can I stick to you?
It's so hot.
Please touch me.
Both of you are slimy.
It feels good.
It's so hot.
Don't go yet.
It's not over yet.
Don't do that.
You like this, don't you?
It's hot and hard.
I can feel it a lot.
I may feel better.
Please lie down.
Do you like this?
It's hot.
I'm glad you can feel it a lot.
How about this?
It's amazing.
It's warm.
Your blood circulation is getting better.
Are you tired?
I'm glad.
It's so hot.
It's so delicious.
Can I be selfish?
Can you look at me?
I'm being massaged.
Can I be selfish again?
Can you touch here?
It feels good.
Can I take off my panties?
It's hot.
Please touch me.
I'm getting wet.
It feels good.
It's amazing that I'm so wet.
Am I getting hungry?
I want you to feel better in a different way.
It's hot.
How do you like this massage?
I'm glad that we can feel better together.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Let's feel better together.
Can I?
It's a secret.
Don't tell the shop.
I'll put it in your ears.
It feels good.
It's hot inside.
How do you like this massage?
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's hot, but my voice is coming out.
It's dangerous.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Can you follow me from behind?
Look up.
It's hot.
It feels good.
My voice is coming out.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Please do more.
It's hot.
It's dangerous.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm running out of time.
Please follow me.
It feels good.
My voice is coming out.
It's hot.
There are a lot of customers.
Thank you.
It's hot.