I'm not sure if it's a good thing or a bad thing, but I think it's a good thing.
It's not a bad thing, but I think it's a bad thing.
Yes.
Welcome back.
Oh, I'm here to pick you up.
Are you here to pick me up?
Yes. This is a large stone, so it will be 19870 yen.
Is it a large stone? I don't remember asking for a little.
Don't you have any other family members?
I have a husband, but I don't think he ordered anything.
This is your house, isn't it?
Yes, it is, but...
For now, how about you pay first and then return it?
Well, but...
That would be better.
What's wrong?
Next door...
I'm sorry, but I just received a package that I don't remember ordering.
You really didn't order it?
Yes.
Then you don't have to pay.
Please take it home as it is.
But that's...
It's been decided that you don't have to accept unordered products, so please take it as it is this time.
If you're still going to leave it, you don't have to pay for it, so I'll get rid of it right away.
Oh, I see.
Thank you very much.
I'm not good at refusing.
If you couldn't help me, I'd have paid for it.
No, it's not a big deal.
Thank you very much.
How are you feeling today?
It's going to be a little late today.
I see.
Then I'll go.
See you later.
Hello.
Are you jogging?
Yes, I have to move my body on my day off.
You're off today, aren't you?
Yes.
I see.
I'd like to thank you for helping me yesterday.
Would you like to go to my house for dinner?
No, I have a husband, so I don't refuse.
Come on.
It's okay to eat.
I'll be waiting for you at home at 1 p.m.
Wait a minute.
You're a lawyer.
No, it's my first year.
But you're a great lawyer.
Please sit down.
Thank you.
I just made it.
I'm glad you like it.
This is omelet rice.
Thank you.
I love omelet rice.
Really?
It's cute.
Thank you for the meal.
Please eat.
Isn't it hard to be a lawyer?
No, I can only study.
I got used to studying.
That's amazing.
But I can only study.
Don't you have a girlfriend?
I had a girlfriend a week ago, but she dumped me the day before yesterday.
I see.
It's a waste.
I'd never let you go.
Are you okay?
Don't tease me.
I'm not teasing you.
You're funny.
Do you know Shibuya next door?
He's a high school student.
He's a lawyer.
That's great.
If you're in trouble, you can talk to him.
That's right.
How long are you going to look at your phone?
I'll be done when I get back from work.
You have to go to work tomorrow.
I'm sleepy.
I'm sorry.
Please sit down.
I have something to discuss with you.
What is it?
I'll make tea first.
Don't worry about me.
I'm worried about you.
It's the first time a woman has been in my room.
It's been a long time since I've been told I'm a woman.
I'm glad.
Here's your tea.
Thank you.
What do you want to talk about?
I think my husband is cheating on me.
I'm a lawyer, so I can't cheat on you.
If my husband is cheating on me, I'll do the same thing.
Do the same thing?
I'm not good at studying.
Come here.
You're a virgin, right?
If a man who has never had sex with a woman is a virgin, he may be a virgin.
You don't have to think about such a difficult thing now.
You just have to leave it to me.
I don't think it's a good idea.
I knew it.
It's so big.
I don't know if this is soft.
You don't know?
You're so responsive.
Be more honest.
Let's take this off.
What are you looking at?
Well...
What?
I mean...
Maybe...
You want to touch here.
But...
I don't know.
I mean...
It's comfortable.
Do you want to see the other side?
Yes.
Then I'll show you.
Wow.
You've never seen it, have you?
No, I haven't.
You can do whatever you like.
Yes.
It feels good.
Wow.
You're very good at touching.
Is this okay?
Yes, it feels good.
That's good.
Wow.
You touch me in a very erotic way.
Like this?
Yes.
Wow.
How is it?
It's very soft and big.
Don't think about anything.
Just think about erotic things.
Only erotic things?
Yes.
How about here?
It feels good.
I feel very erotic.
I want to see more.
Wow.
It's amazing.
Touch me.
Yes.
Wow.
It's amazing.
You touch me in a very erotic way.
Yes.
It's very good.
I want to see more of this part.
This part?
Yes.
Wow.
It's getting harder and harder.
Chibuya-kun.
Yes.
Is it okay to see only this part?
What?
Don't you understand?
What do you mean?
What?
I don't understand.
I don't have experience.
I can see it.
I'm showing you.
Wow.
Come closer.
Yes.
It's embarrassing, but I'm very happy.
I'm very happy to see you so much.
It's amazing.
Wow.
It smells good.
Yes.
It smells good, doesn't it?
This is more fun than studying, isn't it?
This is also interesting.
I'm glad.
I'm very happy that you're getting more and more sexy.
Yes.
It's amazing.
You're getting more and more sexy.
Wow.
Hey.
Touch me.
Yes.
It feels different when I touch you from above.
I think so, too.
Yes.
Wow.
It's transparent.
It's transparent, isn't it?
Yes.
Look.
It's amazing.
Look at me.
Wow.
Yes.
I feel very good just by touching your butt.
I feel very good.
Yes.
Shibuya-kun.
It's very intense.
It's too intense.
Yes.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Shibuya-kun.
It's amazing other than studying.
Thank you very much.
It's amazing.
Yes.
I can't.
I feel like I'm going to puke.
Ouch.
Wow.
It's amazing.
That's right.
Go to sleep.
Yes.
I'm going to do something very sexy for you.
What is it?
What do you think it is?
I don't know.
This.
I can see everything.
Does it hurt?
Here?
Yes.
I'm going to show you a lot of things.
It's amazing.
How is it?
It's your first time, isn't it?
Yes.
What do you want to do here?
What do you think?
What do you want to do?
I'm going to do it.
Shibuya-kun.
You're very good.
It's amazing.
Shibuya-kun.
Do you know what I'm doing now?
Yes.
It feels good.
I can't.
I'm going.
Shibuya-kun.
I fell asleep.
You're very good.
Is that so?
You really like me, don't you?
What do you mean?
Because...
Because you're so big.
You're so big.
You're so big that I can't believe it.
Can I lick you?
Yes.
It's amazing.
I can't believe it.
How is it?
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You've never experienced anything like this, have you?
No, it's my first time.
You're reacting so well.
Let's do a lot.
Oh, my God.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
How about this?
Oh, my God.
How is it?
It's like being in heaven, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Do you like me?
Yes, I do.
Oh, my God.
You're reacting so well.
You really like me, don't you?
Do you like me more?
Yes, I do.
Oh, my God.
Hey.
Yes?
Do you want to put this in?
What?
Is it okay?
Maybe it's something you've always wanted to do.
Okay.
Let's use this.
I put it on you.
Let's put it in.
Okay.
I'll put it in.
Is it okay?
Oh, my God.
It's in.
Do you understand?
Oh, my God.
It's connected.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's better than studying, isn't it?
Oh, my God.
It's in deep.
It's melting.
It feels good.
Can I do it faster?
Yes.
Let's do it together.
It feels good.
Oh, my God.
Are you really a virgin?
Yes.
You're so hard.
You're so thick.
Oh, my God.
All the girls will be happy.
Is that so?
Because it feels so good.
Oh, my God.
Did you feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
I want to do more.
I'll do more for you.
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
It's in deep.
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
It's getting better and better.
Oh, my God.
How is it?
I feel like I'm going to die.
Are you going to die?
I'll do it faster.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to die.
It's okay.
Oh, my God.
Can I do it again?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
In this position,
Can I do it again?
Oh, my God.
Oh, it feels good.
It feels good.
I remember my personality.
Oh, my God.
Shibuya is the best.
You're crying.
It feels good.
Oh, my God.
How do you feel?
You can see my butt a lot, right?
Oh, my God.
Oh, it feels good.
I'll give you a lot of crying.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're crying again.
Are you still standing like this?
Why?
Does that mean we can do it one more time?
Probably.
Then let's do it one more time.
It feels good.
Let's do it one more time.
I want to feel good with you, Shibuya.
Can I make you feel good?
My stomach feels tight.
I've never done this before.
My stomach hurts.
But I want to feel good again.
Can I do it more?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I have to do it one more time.
Look at me.
It's amazing.
It was amazing.
Shibuya.
It was my third time.
It was amazing.
Did you feel good?
You slept a lot.
Shibuya.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Good morning.
Are you going to work now?
Yes.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Shibuya.
It's very intense.
I can't help but move.
It's delicious.
Shibuya.
I'm glad I met you.
I'm glad.
He's not coming back today.
Thank you.
I was going to give Shibuya rice.
It was really delicious.
You are good at cooking.
Really?
Thank you.
Is your husband on a business trip?
He's not coming back today.
If he doesn't come back soon, it's a waste of rice.
Can I ask you something?
Yes.
You said you broke up with your girlfriend.
I was dumped.
I see.
You were a virgin until you had a girlfriend.
I'm still a virgin.
Is it because you're studying?
Maybe.
I don't have a chance.
I'm interested in you.
I see.
Are you interested in me?
I'm interested in you.
But you're a married man.
It's against the law.
I don't know the law.
This is my first time.
Do you want more?
How do you like this?
My head is fluffy.
Do you want more?
Put your tongue out.
Your tongue is soft.
Is that so?
I want to touch your tongue.
Do you want to do it again?
I don't mind.
Come here.
Have you ever seen this?
No.
I'll show you.
It's amazing.
What do you think?
It's very beautiful.
I think so, too.
I'll show you.
It's amazing.
What do you think?
I think it's beautiful.
Thank you.
Touch it.
It's amazing.
It's very soft.
It's been a long time since I touched it.
How do you like my boobs?
I think it's very beautiful.
Really?
You didn't touch me at all.
So I'm very happy.
Touch my hand, too.
It's amazing.
You're good at it.
It's very soft.
Do you want to touch my hand, too?
It's amazing.
Touch my hand.
How do I touch your hand?
I'll do it gently.
I'll do it like this.
It's amazing.
It's amazing just by tracing it.
I'll do it slowly.
It's amazing.
It's been a long time since I touched it.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's amazing.
Here.
Look at me closely.
It's embarrassing.
What do you want to do here?
What do you want to do?
Do what you want to do.
Here.
It feels good.
You're very good at it.
It's amazing.
It feels better than before.
That's right.
That feels really good.
That's amazing.
It's getting wet.
Do you understand?
Yes.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Look.
It's like this.
It's good.
It's amazing.
My fingers are going deep.
It feels so good.
It's amazing.
Do it a little faster.
It feels good.
That's right.
I think I can't do it.
It hurts.
Shibuya went away.
I can't stand it anymore.
Come here.
Shibuya.
I want to go to Shibuya.
It's okay.
Are you embarrassed?
Are you okay?
Shibuya.
It's really big.
I've never seen anything this big.
It's amazing.
It's not hard yet.
Shibuya is really amazing.
That's right.
It's amazing.
Why did you become a priest?
It's a good opportunity.
It's amazing.
That's right.
How do you feel?
Are you being treated like a human being?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Can I lick you?
It's really big.
It's amazing.
It's hot and big.
Shibuya is too big to fit in my mouth.
It's amazing.
It's really painful.
Are you okay?
It's amazing.
I've never had such a hard bath.
I want to go to Shibuya.
Can I sleep here?
It's amazing.
Have you ever had a bath like this?
It's a little hard.
How do you feel?
It's too hard.
It's done.
It's okay to put it in your mouth, right?
Don't you like it?
I don't like it.
Do you feel uncomfortable?
No.
It's your first time, isn't it?
Yes.
I'll put it in your mouth.
Okay.
Shibuya.
It's amazing.
This house is amazing.
Is that so?
It's amazing.
Can I move it a little more?
Yes.
It's amazing.
I can't believe you were a virgin.
Look.
It's amazing.
There's a lot in there.
It's been a long time.
It feels good.
Can I do it faster?
Yes.
How do you feel?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll do it faster.
It's amazing.
Touch me.
I'll do it faster.
How do you feel?
There's a lot in there.
It feels like I'm going to do it.
I'll do it.
Are you going to do it?
Okay.
Ouch.
Ah...
I'm out.
Look, I'm out this much.
How about this?
That's a lot.
You fell asleep.
Ah...
It's still this big.
Amazing.
I can't believe it's this big.
Ah...
Do you want to do it again?
I want you to do it from behind.
Ah...
From behind?
No, not this way.
This way?
Ah...
I'll move it for you.
I think this is difficult.
Ah...
I think it's starting to feel good.
It seems to go well.
I think you can do it.
I don't want to sleep anymore...
Can I go to sleep?
My love...
It's the first time in a long time...
Can you remember me?
It feels good!
I can't...
I want more...
It hurts...
Oookay
續薬さっきのすごかった
からあげしてあげる
あぃ気持ちい
Oh, it feels so good.
I'm getting bigger and bigger.
It feels so good.
I can't, I can't. I'm going to cry.
Ai-kun!
I want to do a lot of things with Shibuya-kun. I want to do everything.
Pull me.
Oh, wow.
It feels so good.
Ai-chan! Ai-chan!
Oh, wow.
You can be more intense.
It feels so good.
What is this?
You're so good.
Shibuya-kun, you're so good.
Oh, wow.
Oh, wow. I'm going to cry.
I want to sleep a lot.
Oh, wow.
Shibuya-kun, you're amazing.
I'm sorry. I didn't know what was going on.
But it was amazing.
Hey, can I invite you to dinner tonight?
Sure. Why?
Actually, you helped me with the mysterious mail. I wanted to thank you.
Oh, I see.
Sounds good.
Really?
Yeah.
Then, let's open a bottle of wine.
That's my goal.
No, it's not.
It is.
I have to go to work.
See you later.
See you.
It's amazing that I passed the exam.
You just studied normally.
But not everyone can do that.
It's amazing.
Shibuya-kun.
Yes?
Can you help me?
Sure.
Do you want me to help you?
No, I'm fine.
Really?
Can you wipe this?
Sure.
Here you are.
A lawyer?
It's amazing.
I should have told you earlier.
Should I go now?
Yuko, you shouldn't stay here.
I'm fine.
The law will be enforced.
I told you I don't understand such a complicated story.
I want to go home.
But...
It's amazing.
Don't worry. I'm drunk now.
I'm fine.
Hey.
I drank too much.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You're going to collapse soon.
Look at him.
I can't stop drinking.
I'll drink more.
Hey.
I'll make you feel better.
What are you going to do?
It's amazing.
I'll put on some ointment.
It's getting harder.
It's amazing.
It's hard.
I can breathe.
It's amazing.
I'm out of breath.
I want more.
Come here.
What?
Yoko.
It's not good here.
Don't worry.
He won't wake up.
But...
And...
What?
777.
I don't know.
He's cheating on you.
What?
So...
I don't care.
Are you sure?
No.
You're cheating on me.
It's unfair.
I'm sorry.
I'm out of breath.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It's amazing.
I can't stand it anymore.
What?
Can I sleep?
I want to sleep, too.
I'll start with you.
Okay.
It's amazing.
You're doing a great job.
It really feels good.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
You're doing a great job.
It's amazing.
It's unfair.
You're licking me.
It's amazing.
Around here.
It's sensitive.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's unfair.
Shibuya-kun.
Yes?
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
Yes.
It's wet here.
Don't say that.
It's amazing.
It's not like Shibuya-kun at the beginning.
It feels good.
Look where you're being touched.
Look behind you.
It's embarrassing.
It feels good.
Does it feel good because it's wet?
It's a tall building.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's embarrassing.
It's wet.
It feels good.
It's embarrassing.
No, no, no.
I'm going.
It's embarrassing.
It feels good.
You're really good.
It's embarrassing.
It's wet.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's wet.
My tongue and Shibuya-kun's are wet.
It's amazing.
Can you hear me?
It's really wet.
It's wet.
It's amazing.
It's really wet.
It feels really good.
It's amazing.
Shibuya-kun, what should we do?
I can't stand it anymore.
You can't stand it?
I can't stand it.
What do you want to do?
I want to go.
I'll give you water.
Shibuya-kun, you've become really good at this.
It's wet.
It's really wet.
Shibuya-kun makes me feel good.
It's amazing.
It's wet.
It's thick and hard.
It's amazing.
I'm shaking inside.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
It's wet.
I'm shaking inside.
I'm sorry.
It's wet.
I'm shaking inside.
It's amazing.
It's wet.
You're amazing.
I'm going to go crazy.
It's wet.
I'm shaking inside.
It feels good.
I'm going to keep doing this.
I'm going to go again.
It feels good.
I'm going to keep doing this.
I'm going to...
I'm going to go crazy.
It's okay.
You did a lot today.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
I want to do more.
This?
I'm going to sleep more, right?
It feels good.
I'm going to...
It still feels good.
It's getting harder.
You're doing great.
It feels good.
Are you going to sleep again?
I'm going to sleep.
You're doing great.
It's warm.
Are you going to sleep again?
You're right.
You're going to sleep again.
I'm going to sleep.
Hey.
Can you do it from behind?
I'm going to sleep.
I'm sorry.
You've become so good at this.
Yes, it's all thanks to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to go.
Okay.
I'm going.
Good morning.
I'm sorry.
Shibuya-kun, aren't you going to sleep?
I forgot something, so please go ahead.
Okay.
I'm sorry.