It's been a long time since I've been to the beach, so I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to the beach.
I'm going to
Stop that!
I'm sorry.
It's early in the morning.
What? You got a problem?
No, no, no.
Shut up and drive.
Yes, I will.
Hey, bring everything in.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
You're so annoying.
Hurry up.
There's still some left.
What are you doing?
You're going to turn over.
Hurry up.
You're so slow.
What are you doing?
There you go.
Hey, you.
What?
Do you have any supplies?
Yes, but what are you going to use them for?
I'm going to use them to stretch my legs.
I'll do it at home.
Really?
Yes, I'll do it.
I'll leave it at the counter for a minute.
Cut it in half.
Hurry up.
There's still some left.
I'll do it.
Leave it to me.
I'll leave it to you.
I'll do my best.
What are you doing?
Don't you eat?
I don't have money this month.
What are you doing?
There's no convenience store around here.
If you had told me in the morning, I would have bought it.
I can't help it.
Here you go.
Hold it.
You can't do it as much as you want, can you?
No, I'm sorry.
I'm telling you to eat.
Here you go.
You can't even hold chopsticks?
Do it properly.
You're easy to hold chopsticks.
Are you done?
Here you go.
Eat it.
It's delicious.
It's delicious, isn't it?
You have to eat it properly.
Are you done?
No, I'm fine.
Thank you.
You can eat it.
I'm sorry.
I'm tired.
I'm sweating.
Would you like to go to the hot spring?
What kind of hot spring is there?
It's just down the mountain.
It's like Kyoto Hyakujo.
Really?
Let's go.
You can go straight down that road.
No, you have to go straight.
To the left.
You can go down the road.
I'm tired.
Thank you for waiting.
I don't mind.
Really?
Are you relieved?
What's wrong?
Oh, I know. You must be hungry.
Hey.
Yes?
There's a store inside, so I'll buy you something.
What do you want? Anything.
No, I'm good. I can do it myself.
No, I'm good. Sit down.
Wait for me.
I'm sorry.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I told you.
It's the best.
I'm sorry. I'm the only one who drank.
Why don't we go out for a drink next time?
I can't drink.
What? You can't drink? You're so boring.
You're a man who can't drink.
By the way, do you have a girlfriend?
No, I've never had a girlfriend.
You don't?
Then, you don't have any experience, do you?
No, I don't want to talk about that.
By the way, what's your relationship like with your parents?
I'm just doing my job.
Then, you're just like them.
Don't compare me to them.
The next day
The weather in the Kanto region is getting worse.
It will start to rain in the afternoon.
There will be heavy rain like a waterfall in the Sankan area.
We need to be careful of car accidents and flooding.
The weather is still good.
It's not going to rain.
They say that the weather in the mountains can change.
It's going to be late in the afternoon.
It's not good if it starts to rain.
Will it rain?
Of course, because we're at the scene.
Is it really going to rain?
The next day
Hurry up!
The weather in the Kanto region is getting worse.
I'm going to pull up the tent.
Shinji, hurry up!
Hurry up!
It's raining heavily.
It's dangerous for the driver.
Please stop the car.
I'll stop the car.
The rain is getting heavier.
Toilet?
I don't know.
It's raining heavily.
The next day
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What's wrong?
Is it stuck?
It seems to be stuck.
I'll take a look.
Be careful.
It's stuck.
Where is it?
The next day
Please help me.
I'll help you.
It's stuck.
What's wrong?
I'll help you.
The next day
Please help me.
I'll help you.
It's stuck.
The next day
I can't move.
We have to wait until the rain stops.
We can't help you in the morning.
You're right.
The next day
It's stuck.
We can't help you in the morning.
Really?
What should we do?
We have to stay here.
We can't help you in the morning.
You're right.
What's this?
I'll help you.
It's stuck.
I can't move.
The next day
I'll help you in your wet clothes.
Thank you.
It's better if you wipe it off.
I'll help you in your wet clothes.
You're always helping me.
Are you okay?
This is bad.
This is really bad.
Come on, get up.
Can I take this off?
Yes, you can.
Take it off.
It's really cold.
Oh no, it's really wet.
Oh no.
I'll go this way.
I can't get up.
Thank you very much.
Come on.
Oh no.
It's so cold.
This is bad.
What?
I can't help it. It's raining.
Come on.
Let's go this way.
Oh no.
It's okay.
Come on.
It's so wet.
Seriously.
Come on.
This is bad.
I'm sorry.
It's not raining.
I can't do this in the morning.
Come on.
It's really bad.
Oh no.
What if the car gets washed away?
I don't know.
We're in the middle of the mountain.
I hope the car doesn't break down.
Don't say such a scary thing.
But it's possible because we're in the middle of the mountain.
Why are you so calm?
I'm not calm.
I'm scared, of course.
I'll wipe it off.
You're strong.
Come on.
It's so cold.
I'm scared of this kind of thing.
You're a man.
Be strong.
I'm sorry.
It's really bad.
What if it doesn't stop until tomorrow?
It might stop in the morning.
I don't know about this rain.
I can't see anything outside.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Can I wear this?
Please hide it.
We can wear it together.
It's cold.
Did you wipe it off?
Yes, I did.
I see.
I know you did.
Yes.
It's cold.
I hope the car doesn't break down in the rain.
I don't know about that.
I hope the tire doesn't break.
I think so, too.
I'm scared.
It's cold.
It's getting warmer.
I'm fine.
What was that?
A thunder?
Yes.
Are you afraid of thunder and lightning?
Shut up.
I'm not afraid.
You're cute.
Are you making fun of me?
No, I'm just praising you.
What are you praising me for?
I think you're cute, too.
I'm not afraid of thunder and lightning.
You said you were afraid of thunder and lightning.
But you were brave.
I wouldn't have been afraid of thunder and lightning.
So you're not afraid of thunder and lightning.
Shut up.
It's warm to be with you.
You're right.
Are you still cold?
I'm warm.
I want to sleep.
It's cold.
It's cold, isn't it?
Yeah, it's cold.
Why do you say that?
Why?
Because it's cold.
I don't know.
Cold.
Me neither.
It's cold.
I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to die if I don't do something about it.
. . .
You look nice!
I felt like you were following me.
I wanted to be like that.
There is a video where the entire process of making this often shows.
The past videos found on YouTube looked prettier, however,
So, they are mostly unreleased videos.
I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to die if I don't eat it.
It's hot, isn't it?
I'm rules.
Let's go.
I'll do more.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20
Ahh...
Ah, this is bad.
I can't do this.
This is bad.
Ahh...
It feels good there.
There...
Ah, this is bad.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it's bad.
Be more intense.
More.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it's bad.
It's hot...
My hands are freezing.
Feels good now.
It's hot.
I feel great.
I feel good.
It's hot.
Can I put it in?
Can I?
If you don't mind.
Yes.
Can I?
It's hot.
I feel good.
It's great.
It's hot.
Ah, I feel sick.
Alice.
Should I try it from behind?
Ah, I feel sick.
Ah, I'm going crazy.
My stomach is growling.
Oh, no.
Come on, lift me up more.
More.
Help me.
Oh, no.
Mike.
I feel sick.
Oh, no.
Mike.
I feel sick.
Oh, no.
Crap.
I feel sick.
Oh well.
This is all a sweet dream.
You're not here ..
Because you were kidnapped.
Teddy is your only family.
Tehre your wife pets you ..
Help me first ..
Help me ...
Let me iPhone ...
It hurts!
It feels so good.
I love you.
I want to love you too.
Oh, my God.
Aah
Well, well, well
I can't
Although it is surprised
Ah
Nooo
Oh, go
Oh, no
Aa, I have to use my hand
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Well, I'm going
My stomach hurts.
You have a stomachache?
No.
I feel sick.
Do you have a stomachache?
No.
What is this?
I'm going to eat it later.
Is that so?
Let's eat together.
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
Yes.
It's delicious.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the hospital.
Is that so?
It's good to go to the hospital in the morning.
I can't go to the hospital.
What should I do if I can't go to the hospital?
That's terrible.
I may be swept away.
It's a bit windy.
I'm not sure if it's just us in this world.
I think so.
It's not good to be alone in the rain.
I thought I was alone.
It's better not to be alone.
I'm not alone.
I'm going to put it on the back of my head.
Ouch!
I can do it!
Mike! Mike!
Wait!
I can do it!
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
It's okay.
I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
Let's go home.
Hey.
Let's take a bath.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Is this a men's bath?
No one comes in the morning on a day like this.
It's not a men's bath.
Do you have any complaints?
What's wrong?
It's not a men's bath.
Let's go again.
Oh, my.
Can I sit here?
I can rent a seat if you want to rinse lava, too.
Can I rent a seat if you want to rinse lava, too?
May I sit here?
It's nice and clear!
I'm so tired.
It was tough, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was.
But I'm glad we made it.
I'm sure we did.
Did you take your time taking a bath?
Yeah, I did.
Are there any people coming?
It's fine. It's the first thing in the morning.
I'm out of money.
Come here.
No one's coming?
It's fine. I'm on my back.
Like this?
Why? Are you embarrassed?
No, I'm just embarrassed.
We spent time in the car together.
I can't look at you.
Look at me.
You're cute.
What?
You're still dirty.
That's right.
Are you taking it off here?
You're good at this.
You taught me.
You learn fast.
What?
I'm still embarrassed.
It's going to be on camera.
Did you wash up?
I'm going to wash up.
I'm sleepy.
Are you weak?
It feels good.
I'm sleepy.
You're beautiful.
Why?
You smell good.
I washed up.
Are you feeling better?
I'm not feeling well.
I see.
That's right.
You're dirty.
I'm going to take it off.
You're good at this.
You should have brought it yesterday.
You look like you're in pain.
I'm sleepy.
Why?
I want to see you more.
You can sleep.
Don't look at me.
It's embarrassing.
I'm sleepy.
It feels good.
It's sweet.
Do you want me to go further?
I'm not feeling well.
I'm sleepy.
You can't hurry up.
I haven't done anything yet.
I don't want to sleep.
Don't do that.
Do you want me to lick you?
Yes.
Was it good?
It feels good.
Ouch!
I'm so happy.
I'm going to pee.
Please stop peeing.
I don't know.
You don't know?
I'm going to pee.
I don't know.
I wanted you to feel good.
You're so weak.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
I want to touch you.
I just peed.
I can't.
I'm so weak.
You can't move now.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I feel sick.
I want to do it more.
Oh oh oh no no no no no no.
That hurts!
Keep going
phew
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
Kiss me.
I want you to say a lot of things to me.
It feels good.
I can see your face.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Wait.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Wait.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Wait.
You're sorry.
It feels good.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
, as if it's piled up ...
Ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, wa.
Ah ah, ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
oh my god
fuuu!
You got dirtied again
I'm sorry.
Let's do it again.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I'm so embarrassed.
You're embarrassing.
Can you put that there?
Are you angry again?
Can you use it?
I can use it.
Thank you for watching.