Yuichi Oeno was in the middle of a college entrance exam.
It had been a week since he had left our home.
Yes?
May I come in?
Come in.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Would you like to take a break?
Thank you.
Here you are.
Would you like to change the sheets on the bed?
Thank you.
You're doing your best.
Yes.
Thank you.
By the way, I just got a call from Yuichi's mother.
She was worried about Yuichi.
I'll call you later.
Okay.
What are you studying?
Mathematics.
I see.
You're solving a very difficult problem.
I used to be good at math, too.
But I don't understand it at all.
I'm sorry.
I don't understand it at all.
Hey, Yuichi.
Yes?
You've been staying in your room all the time.
Why don't you go out sometimes?
What are you talking about?
The exam is coming soon.
I can't relax.
I see.
I'm sorry for saying unnecessary things.
I'm sorry.
I'm not angry.
It's okay.
But don't get stressed.
If you can do something,
please ask me anytime.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Is Yuichi doing well?
Yes.
Honey, the bath is ready.
I'm going in.
I have to study.
Yuichi is studying hard.
Yes.
But I'm nervous.
It can't be helped.
It's the exam period.
Yes.
What is it?
We haven't done it for a long time, have we?
Yuichi is here now.
You said you were tired before he came.
You haven't had sex at all.
Am I not attractive?
No, you're not.
You're really tired.
You can do it when he comes out.
Okay.
Let's go to bed.
Good night.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
I can't concentrate on studying.
I'll do my best to go to college and make a girlfriend.
I'll graduate from the university, right?
I'll do my best.
It's my aunt's body.
Good morning, Yuichi.
Good morning.
It's past noon.
You were studying until late last night, weren't you?
Yes.
I made breakfast. Do you want some?
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Let me know if it's not enough.
I think you're a little tired. Are you okay?
No, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I was worried about you.
I'm really fine.
I see.
What's wrong?
Oh, no.
I want to clean my ears.
Do you want me to use an earpick or a cotton swab?
No, I'll do it later.
Thank you.
Hey.
Yes?
Do you want me to clean your ears?
What?
I'm pretty good at it.
Put your head on my lap.
Okay.
Like this?
You can't do it like this.
What?
Turn around.
Okay.
Like this?
Yes.
Tell me if it hurts.
Okay.
I'm sleepy.
I'm sleepy, too.
I have a lot of earwax.
Really?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
It's hard for me to sleep.
Does it hurt?
I'm sorry.
I ate a big one.
What?
I'm sorry.
The other side, too.
The other side?
Turn around.
Are you okay?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Doesn't it hurt?
Yes.
What's wrong?
I can't stand it anymore.
When I'm with you, I can't concentrate on my study.
What do you mean?
I can't concentrate on my study.
What's wrong?
Wait.
Wait, Ichikun.
Why do you always wear clothes to show Tanima?
I'm not showing him.
You're right.
Hey, grandma.
You told me to talk to you if I was stressed.
Yes.
You'll talk to me, right?
Then, I'll have sex with you.
What?
Then, I'll get rid of my stress.
No, I can't do that.
Why not?
Wait.
I can't have sex with you.
Why not?
I'm sorry.
Then, I'll concentrate on my study.
Don't say that.
You said you'd be by my side.
Look at this.
It became like this.
Ichikun.
Do you know what this is?
It became like this.
Look at this.
Do you know what this is?
Yes, I do.
Look at this.
Do you know what this is?
No.
Let me have sex with you.
Okay.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I can't have sex with you.
Why not?
Then, I'll make you feel better with my hands.
Bear with it.
Let me have sex with you.
I'll make you feel better with my hands.
Okay?
Okay.
Will you make me feel better with your hands?
Ichikun.
It's red.
Wow.
It's shaved.
Then,
will you make me feel better with your hands?
It feels good.
Wow.
It feels good to be touched by someone else.
Keep going.
Ichikun.
Is this your first time?
What?
Yes, it is.
It feels good.
Keep going.
Hey.
What?
Ichikun.
It feels good.
Move your body.
It's heavy, isn't it?
It feels good.
What's this?
Can you touch me while I'm breathing like I did before?
What are you doing?
It feels good.
Can you touch me while I'm breathing like I did before?
No, no.
Don't touch me.
It hurts.
Don't look at me.
Keep breathing.
What are you doing?
Don't look at me.
Don't lick me.
Why?
It hurts.
Can you touch me while I'm breathing like I did before?
What are you doing?
Keep licking me.
I can't do it.
You can't do it?
If I lick you?
It hurts.
I'll do it with my hands.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Keep doing it.
Don't touch me.
It feels good.
It hurts.
You can't do it.
Keep doing it.
You're making a lot of noise.
You can't do it.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's going to come out.
Keep doing it.
Thank you.
It came out.
Can you concentrate on studying with this?
Yes.
Thank you.
I don't want to.
I still feel like I was stimulated by Yuichi.
I'm not satisfied.
I'm going to go.
See you.
Good morning.
Hey, mom.
I haven't been able to concentrate since this morning.
Hey.
I want to concentrate on my studies.
Can you help me?
Okay.
Good morning.
Oh.
Hey.
Is this okay?
Yeah.
When I was asked to do it,
I couldn't refuse.
I started to do it myself.
Yes.
Dinner is ready.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Okay.
What's wrong?
I can't concentrate on my studies.
Can you do it again?
But...
I haven't been able to concentrate on my studies at all.
Can you do it again?
I'll finish it soon.
Just a little more.
Just a little more?
Look at this.
Look.
It's like this.
I'll be back.
It's okay.
I'll finish it before that.
Wait a minute.
It's like this.
I have to get a doctor.
Please.
Let me take it off.
Me?
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I have to hurry.
I know.
It feels good.
I think I can do it.
Keep going.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Keep going.
I can't do it anymore.
Don't do that.
It's okay.
It's very soft.
It's okay, right?
What are you doing?
It's hot.
I have to hurry.
I think I can do it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's better to sit down.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
I can't do it.
Why can't you do it?
Don't run away.
Don't touch me.
It's hot.
It's very hot.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Stand up.
Sit down.
It's hot.
What are you doing?
I have to hurry.
It's hot.
I can't do it.
I have to hurry.
It's hot.
It's very hot.
I can't do it.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
Don't touch me.
Sit down.
Don't do that.
Don't look at me.
It's a little numb.
No, it's not.
What's wrong?
It's cold here.
No, it's not.
I'll make you feel better.
I didn't feel so good.
No, it's not.
I'll make you feel better.
Don't look at me.
That's amazing.
Something came out.
Don't touch me.
That's amazing.
Something came out.
Don't look at me.
That's amazing.
I have to hurry up.
Don't touch me.
I told you to look at me.
That's amazing.
No, it's not.
Let me go.
That's amazing.
Don't look at me.
I'll touch you.
That's amazing.
Do you like this?
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Where is Monami?
She went out for a while.
I see.
When is the exam?
In three days.
Good luck.
Thank you.
I wonder if I can take a bath.
I'm back.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Come here.
I'm back.
Does it hurt?
Do it with your mouth.
That's faster.
I'm going to take a bath.
That's amazing.
I'm going out.
Me...
Grab this for me, please.
I got to know you for the first time
I felt great
You're so good
Yuichi-kun, it's morning. Wake up.
Good morning.
Good morning. Today is an important day, isn't it?
Hey, Yuichi-kun.
Yes?
Do you feel refreshed?
Is that okay?
Please.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I couldn't hold back my excitement.
I asked for it.
Ah.
Are you taking the entrance exam today?
Yes, I am.
How confident are you?
It's my real name, but it's a little hard for me.
You can't be weak from now on.
Do your best.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Then I'll go.
See you.
When I'm alone, I remember Yuichi-kun.
Ah.
It feels so good.
It was pretty fast.
Yes.
Did the exam go well?
Yes, thanks to you.
That's good.
I heard your voice in the hallway.
Yes.
Do you want to do it?
What are you talking about?
Stop it.
I'll do it for you.
No.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
Don't lick me.
You have a sore throat.
Do you feel sick?
It's blood.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
Don't look at me.
You have a sore throat.
What's wrong?
Don't touch me.
No.
Don't lick me.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it for you.
Stop it.
Don't touch me.
Why?
Stop it.
You have a beautiful voice.
I'm a little ticklish.
It's hot.
Let me go.
I'm sorry.
No.
Come here.
Did you go to the hospital?
You said you were going to the hospital.
Did you feel good?
Don't lick me.
I'm sorry.
Did you feel good?
You're wet.
I'll drop it.
Don't do that.
It's loud.
I'm sorry.
I'll drop it.
Don't do that.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
Can you laugh more?
I can't do it.
Don't do that.
I want you to feel better.
Aunt.
I want you to lick me.
Do you feel good?
Do it like before.
Can I take it out?
Do you feel good?
Keep going.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
That's bad.
Wait a minute.
Do you feel good?
It feels so good.
It's so good.
Do you feel good?
I'm going to fall asleep.
You're so stiff.
Do you want to do it?
I'm fine.
You're so stiff.
You want to do it, don't you?
I don't want to do it.
I can't.
You want to do it, don't you?
What's wrong with you?
Can I sleep?
I can't.
I'm begging you.
I'll do something for you.
I'm sorry.
It feels so good.
Let's take it off.
Wow, that's a lot of pain.
Oh no, she's feeling sick.
Don't move her like that.
No, no, no.
Ouch!
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Oh no, oh no.
That feels good.
Oh, that's a lot of pain.
Wow, that's a lot of pain.
I can't do this.
Why not?
Ouch!
That feels good.
Don't move her like that.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
That feels good.
Ouch!
Masaya, you wanted to go, didn't you?
That feels good.
Oh no, oh no.
You can't do that, Michiko.
I can't.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
You can't do that.
That feels good.
It's getting harder than before.
I'm going to call the doctor.
That feels good.
Oh no.
You can do it.
That feels good.
Did you put it inside?
It's too intense.
It's really over now.
But you felt it, right?
Get out of here.
If you continue to be with me, you won't be able to go back.
That's what I felt.
My exams were all over.
The day to go back to my parents' house was approaching.
I was going to go back to my parents' house.
When will the results come out?
The results will come out next month.
I see.
If you pass, you'll be able to go back to your parents' house.
Yes.
How's the rent around here?
I think it's a little expensive around here.
I see.
I thought it would be convenient for transportation and easy to live.
Well, if you live a little further away, it's much cheaper.
I see.
I've been keeping my distance from my parents since that day.
Monami.
What?
You're going home tomorrow, right?
Why don't we all go out now?
I have something to do.
You two go ahead.
I see.
Let's go, Yuichi.
Yes.
Even though I cut off my own relationship with my parents,
my body was aching as if I was looking for my parents.
What?
Monami.
What's wrong?
Oh.
I...
I just couldn't forget about you.
Oh.
It seems like I can't stand it either.
But I won't have sex with you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh.
Oh, I'm standing.
I'm standing here.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
It feels good to be able to go to the bathroom.
It feels good?
Yes.
Oh.
You've grown so big.
It feels good.
Oh.
Your belly is really big.
What?
Let me see.
Oh.
Ah...
I'm surprised.
Oh.
Wahoo!
He's not bad at all.
It was obvious.
The equivalent of an old lady.
Oops...
I feel great!
How do you feel?
Oh, it feels good.
You've grown so much.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it feels good.
I want you to play with me again.
Okay.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it feels good.
You're mumbling.
Try moving a lot.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's hot.
Your boobs are so big.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's hot.
I can't see you anymore.
Oh, it feels good.
It feels good when I rub your neck.
Wait a minute.
Check it out.
You're still wet.
Oh, it's hot.
Next time, I'll make you feel better.
Oh, it feels good.
Try moving a lot.
I can't see you anymore.
Oh, it feels good.
You're still wet, so let's go over there.
Ouch!
You made me feel good.
There.
Please.
No, no.
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
You're getting better at it.
You're amazing.
You're so beautiful.
Please move a lot.
It feels good.
There.
You're hitting me.
It feels good.
You're so good at it.
If you move that much, I'll go.
I'll go.
I'll go, I'll go, I'll go, I'll go.
Wow, it's so tight inside.
It feels good.
You're getting better at it.
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Move from the back, too.
Okay.
Wow.
You're amazing.
Yeah.
It feels good.
Is this okay?
Yeah.
There.
A lot more.
Stick out your fingers.
There.
There, there.
It feels good.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Wow.
My hips are shaking.
Do you feel it?
It feels good.
Where are you licking?
Here.
It's so clean here, too.
Ouch!
I'm the only one.
You were the first one.
Let's cuddle.
What should I do?
Lie down.
Ouch!
Ouch, it hurts.
Does it?
Ouch.
It feels good.
Yeah.
Let's cuddle a lot.
Are you running away?
No.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
No, no.
Ouch, it hurts.
You're so good at it.
You can do it right away.
Really?
It's your favorite time.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Can I pet you?
It's good, isn't it?
Does it hurt?
Sit down.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
It's good, isn't it?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yeah, it does.
Wait a minute.
You said you wouldn't do it at the end.
I said that, but...
I really want you to pet me.
It's good, isn't it?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll pet you.
It's good, isn't it?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It hurts.
You're hitting me a lot.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It hurts.
I'll move.
Move.
I'm sorry.
It hurts a lot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're pushing me a lot.
I'll massage your back.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm touching your skin.
I'm losing my muscles.
I'm already losing my muscles.
Oh...
Ah
Oh
It stings
No
It's so hard
Yeah
Mmm
The ez is making a sound
Give me a kiss.
So good...
If you break the glass at a distance of about six feet, you will break the plane almost every 30 seconds!
Can you do it?
How do you feel?
I feel bad.
It feels so good.
It's so good.
It's amazing.
It feels so good.
It's so good.
Let's go together.
It feels so good.
Let me out.
Uncle, aunt.
Thank you for taking care of me for a long time.
Call me when you get the result.
Okay.
I'll go get the car.
Thank you.
Yuichi.
Be sure to come again.
I'll be sure to come again.
I promise.
Okay.