Good morning, only fire service.
Please wait a little.
Good morning.
Only fire service.
Please be kind today.
Are you sure of the cleaning course today?
I am sure.
I understood.
I am now a college student, but I am currently writing reports about women working on the subject, can you also write down pictures?
Can you be me?
It is OK, thank you.
If you want to eat 500 yen, yes.
Okay is it?
Yes to.
Thanks, I’ll take a camera.
Do you have anything to offer in college?
Yes is it.
You have a huge challenge.
If you wish me.
Are you married?
It’s 5 years now, I’m married.
Now a child, a child.
I have a girl, I am 2 years old, but she is still very young.
Or is it okay to avoid this usually?
Yes please please.
It’s pretty nice, I can’t clean up here very often.
Yes, you have been getting a lot of stuffing and stuffing lately.
Really sorry for you.
Or even this shadow.
Easily climbing in.
I want to clean it regularly.
Are you talking about cleaning?
Well, when you know how to clean up.
The shoes are so dirty, so it can be dirty.
I wash my shoes sometimes, and the door is dirty.
Yes, I want to do a little at the time.
Or the name below.
What is being said?
I say goodbye.
I say, I am telling you that Tango is a Tango.
I wanted to know a little about the name.
A bit embarrassed.
No, it is okay.
It is getting clean here.
Yes is.
It is easy to paint this piece of paint.
Maybe it is beautiful here.
You have noticed.
It became so clean.
meet for a long time.
Yes, the door is the entrance.
It feels good when you are beautiful.
Oh is
Is the worker long enough?
Yes, I am
About three years, just.
I like cleaning, so it is fun.
You are doing what you like to do.
Yes is
I went to the 5th floor and said something.
by Tejas
I really didn’t care about cleaning or cleaning.
Even angry with their parents.
Then I became aware and loved cleaning.
I still have family now.
It is very helpful.
Or even physical production.
Good thing to do.
Is there anything else to worry about?
Where you care.
The scenery has already become cleaner.
Can you do a little bit of kitchen?
Yes of course.
So here is the kitchen.
So I’ll go around water.
I will go around water.
Yes, I am sorry.
I am here, here, please please.
So let me start.
Please please.
So, get a lot of stuffed.
Did you make something yesterday?
Yesterday, I saw curry in real water.
But it is not great to water.
You were a student yesterday.
You felt a little water.
How many times a week, you can do something.
I wanted to make it a little.
I wanted to create.
Until it is made.
Until it is cleaned.
A little bit, it is difficult.
Yes is though.
A small wall.
Oh yes surely.
This plate.
If I had a knife.
I know
They will be colored and water will be drawn.
The water is bad, but the kitchen is bad.
Left too much.
Or a little bit of a regular food, or something you usually care about.
Is there such a thing as well?
That they are married.
5 year marriage.
I have heard it many times.
Use this too?
What kind of people are doing this job.
Did you also report that in the report?
If you can answer it completely, it is okay.
Sorry for listening deeply.
No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No
Now have a child?
I have a girl now 2 years old.
A girl?
Is it not the most beautiful of two?
Yes, she is cute, but I think she’s a bit disgusting.
Eating food or something, or even eating.
So cleaning is very difficult.
Is the dish okay with this?
Yes is.
Yes
Yes, I can do a little bit of it, but I can even clean the floor.
Yes, it’s dirty, and the floor.
Okay, some of the here.
Yesterday was okay.
Eat cookies or potatoes.
It is dirty.
Oh really is.
Right in the corner, it’s stuck.
Are you stacked?
Yes
This too, let me leave it.
There are insects, so be careful.
Yes, I know
and recently
Insects are increasing.
I need to ask for fire.
That means his hand won’t catch.
Yes, in a report.
to be chased.
Yes, I have not much time.
It was just good.
and report.
Great around.
The rubbish is filled.
Your towel is dirty now.
Very black.
It is dirty, so you have a cleaning machine.
You love to clean.
It feels good, but if you look at it, it will be pretty.
Yes, I know
Maybe this invisible place.
Because there is a huge trickle.
Looking at it, it is very, very crowded.
Not in here, not in here, not in here.
You did not do at all.
Okay, you have become beautiful.
Really thank you.
Next, do you do the bathroom?
Good for the bathroom.
Can I ask for a bathroom?
Which is?
The bathroom is here.
Please let me.
This is the bathroom.
Yes is
Watercrumbs here too.
Yes is.
Go to bed and make it clean.
Please go to bed.
Can I leave it here?
I have not left this at all.
It is very humid.
Yes, I do
Ventilation needs to be around here.
Even the crabs will come in.
The bathroom is
Do you have ventilation?
I do it.
Maybe when I forget.
Yes is it.
I forgot, I am glad.
Yes is what.
well
I will clean the bathroom.
Good morning.
Yes is
First, take a little warm water.
It is nice to have a family, such.
cleaning the bathroom.
Yes is.
Once in a while, you can get it all in hot water.
A little bit of dirt.
After that, it will be easier for the cattle to live.
Oh, you didn’t know that.
Do you want to take a bath with your husband?
No, no longer at all.
Tango, how do you get used to it?
Are you interested?
Do you want to report this?
I know my husband and I know he’s always in a restaurant.
I will clean the bathroom.
This is, I thought.
My daughter is younger.
Not so active, not so active.
In either case, it felt like me.
I am scared, right?
Such a beautiful grass.
There is plenty of water here.
Well, it’s more of a corner, water.
Do you have a bath sauce, or a soap, or a cleaning?
I often do what I do.
Each time, put water or water in the bath.
There are such a bathroom chairs.
Or even a very easy crap.
Put the heavy there.
They can bite and bite together or do something very short.
It is helpful.
Are you dressed?
They are sold cheaply at the pharmacy.
Very easy to get in.
You should try it once.
I will try to buy it today.
I highly recommend.
This pink nigerian.
It will fall when it falls.
Yes is it.
I often find out that it is broken.
Your hair is getting a little bigger.
Clean it twice a week, then clean it thoroughly.
Or I think it will keep it beautiful.
It is beautiful, if you want to clean it a little.
It looks like a bath.
Is it okay? it’s pretty clean.
Good was
Put a little bubble around.
Once this is over.
Okay is ok.
Next, do you clean the living room?
The living room is fine.
The room is probably the dirtyest.
So move quickly.
So please please.
This is a cleaning game.
It is different.
No, not at all.
It is awesome, Hockey.
Really a hiccups.
Are you always eating here?
I am ashamed to eat here.
Eating or not eating.
pleased
Arrived out.
No to
Oh yeah
by
No to
Sorry, but I can’t stand it.
Oh is?
Really sorry now.
No, I really regret this.
Can you not let me do it until the end?
Oh is?
Until the end.
Yes, yes, no, no is not.
What, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what,
So, for a moment, go home.
Oh, really, really, really, I’m sorry, I can’t.
No to no.
A little, that
I am going home with this today.
Oh, oh, please wait a little.
No, not until the end.
Come here a little bit, please.
Really sorry.
No no no
A little bit.
Wait, please wait
still a little.
No no no
Why not be pursued here.
If you come here a little.
Really please.
Do not do so, do well.
Wait a little.
A little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little, a little.
I want to ask him for a drummer again.
I would like to ask for the same as the previous time, Shiro.
Yes Yes Yes
Please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please.
Yes, thank you very much.
Oh yeah
Sorry to sorry.
I actually sorry.
This is what surprised me.
I thought you could come.
I think you should keep it secret before.
I understand.
This time from the snow.
is fast?
I couldn’t do it before.
Can I prepare a little?
Not to replace?
A little bit of my heart is shaking,
About that time.
When that happened, I couldn’t even hold myself back.
The truth is the secretary.
I will not make this a secret, just for this.
Can I go through this window?
Please see this window.
The ass is beautiful.
Thanks to.
Are you filming again?
Sorry, but the research is.
I wanted to photograph a little.
I really apologized for yesterday.
It was a beautiful ass.
not be patient.
If you feel it, it will be okay.
Sorry to
The taste and water were a bit worried.
Some books are getting better.
Is your mother dirty?
Yes
Good night to you.
Are you reporting? are you progressing?
A little by little.
Good was
Thanks to your mother.
No, I am so.
Okay, this is okay, it’s crazy.
What happened?
No, I am not waiting for you.
You wait until you have finished cleaning the toilet.
The toilet cleaning is not finished.
So, can we wait?
So please please.
I’ll wait for the toilet here.
Toilet will also be cleaned.
It is the most used.
It is so dirty in the seat.
Yes, it is the dirtyest.
How long do you clean the shell?
The toilet goes at least once a day.
You should be worried about it, so you should be aware of this.
Yes, it will be hard afterwards.
What are you doing a little?
No to no.
Do not change this.
It is really dirty.
and ina
that
I can’t really do it anymore, so I can’t even get a lot of people.
What are you saying?
No, not here.
Just a little more.
If I show you that.
But it is dirty.
Please do something there.
Then
It is really secret.
It sounds like a pretty ass.
A bit embarrassed.
See also
Oh is?
The ass.
A little bit of it?
A beautiful ass sound.
So close to.
Can I take my bag down?
Very beautiful 7 stars.
Are you moving a little?
No, please do not say that.
It moved great, very much.
So familiar with.
A little, a little
No such thing.
Go around, it’s dirty.
I did well.
It is he.
He is going out.
Do not smell that beautiful ass.
by voice, by voice.
It is really dirty, just a little.
Oh, it has become this way.
So much so
Can you tell me to lick?
It is
Please please.
No, of course
Just a little.
I want you to clean up here too.
This is really a secret too.
Yes is
It smelled very good.
It became this way.
Except for Magma.
Oh awesome.
Feeled...
Oh yeah
Shrill
Yes
Oh yeah
No to
Yes is
I look at it.
Oh yeah
No to
Birthdays
I feel it.
Very cleaned up.
Where will I clean up next?
Do you clean the bedroom?
Can you please?
Yes is
Start the cleaning again.
Thanks to.
It is my own room.
This shirt will be clean.
Thanks to.
It is a pretty large bed.
Yes, it is a pretty good bed.
Is it a little dirty?
Oh yeah
A little more, yes
My hair is tired.
Are you washing it? - Shane
A little more cool.
But good, cooking the food.
Washing or washing.
It is hard to study and study.
Yes, I am not happy to cook.
I have a great respect for those who have a family.
No no no
It feels like I have to do it anymore.
You get used to it while you are doing it, it’s okay.
Oh yeah
Oh is?
Wait a little.
And again?
Can you better?
Oh is
Not that, not that.
What is?
No so is.
Oh well delicious.
It is delicious.
Do not bother yet.
Very delicious.
Oh yeah...
Oh that...
If you approach, I suggest.
It smells very good.
So that
No taste of anything.
No missing place.
River criterion
In this really.
Slept in it.
A little eyes.
I can no longer endure.
Sit down anyway.
I cannot endure.
Is it yet?
I did it again, is it okay?
Or another time?
I suddenly licked him, so I was surprised.
Sorry to
Do not really say.
I will keep it secret anymore.
Do not really tell me.
No to
Oh is
Can I lick my ass again?
And again?
Can I show you a little better?
Shame on this.
So used to.
greatly
A little bit.
No eye to touch.
Yes is
Take some sand.
Oh is
There is
Do not tell me that you did.
Oh, it is delicious.
Can I put it on my face?
I want to lick more.
Can I ride that way?
I want to ride.
Yes
Oh so so so.
Oh, is this this?
Can I spread my ass?
Oh oh oh
Taste is
Oh yeah
Oh oh oh
It is.
Oh oh oh oh!
Wait and wait!
Oh oh oh!
by Hoi
No to that.
Oh to!
Oh oh oh!
Oh so did.
Do not stand up!
Oh well...
... is it okay?
Oh to!
Yes to!
Yes to!by
No to
Yes to!
Oh oh oh oh!
Yes is
Yes
and is
by
Yes
Ha ha
That
Oh to!
Feel it...
Rotten has come.
Great, I haven’t seen it yet.
It is trembling.
Very differently.
It is moving.
Do not say that.
Oh well!
Can I get you to the wall?
Share your life
It is hard, right?
Oh yeah
Alphabet is
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah
Give me a little hand.
Yes
greatly
Is there?
Can I put my feet up, Weight?
I can no longer do law.
Asty
Oh is
Oh awesome.
Oh yeah
by
Oh is
on
Firstly
is beautiful.
Give me your ass here.
No to
by
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh is
by Pri
Oh yeah yeah
Oh yeah
Can I get you out behind?
by
Get closer to your nose.
Keep your ass lying.
Okay is?
You feel a little worse.
not feel bad.
I have a sense of security.
by Stephenson
Oh is
This news key?
Great news key.
Oh is
More of
More full of.
Give it a lick.
Oh is
Oh fuck you.
No to No.
Oh oh
Oh is
I no longer
I was unable to endure.
Do you have anything to wash in the kitchen?
There is
Is there a place to hold?
There are plenty in the kitchen.
Let us go quickly.
Please wait a little.
Why? why?
and suddenly.
Because it is also packed.
I will wash.
I know. thanks
You’re always looking at my ass, right?
No, that is
Okay, but closer to it.
You wanted to put my bubble, right?
I wanted so much.
What happened?
Come closer to me.
Oh yeah
Too much my.
by Jade
Great is
You were scared.
still now
still a little.
I cannot endure.
Sorry to
Oh yeah
Oh, I got into the smell of myself.
It smells so much echo.
Oh yeah
Very hardy
It is good.
Very beautiful.
is intercepted.
Oh oh oh
The same thing happens to the dead here.
Press more.
Really the same.
Opening the stomach.
One step ahead.
in the ass.
Give it up.
Press it.
in the ass.
This this
by Fell
You are
Want to see closer?
I want to see you closer.
You can see it well below.
As if it would not stop all the time.
I look at it until it’s cold and I cross it.
Please soon.
OSSE is
Great is
Do you know?
What Cambodia
Try to push something.
Try to change this?
Exceptionally well
What is smell?
I smell one.
Oh yeah
Try to push this foot.
Or seriously?
I am going in.
greatly
I feel going in.
Will I try this drink?
Okay of course.
No to
I have a.
Oh is
I am
Stop now
Standing up and forgiving.
No to.
I also wore it there.
The same anal.
Touch it directly.
I also wore it there.
Ately
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh, his
Oh yeah can
Oh, and staff
well is
It feels great.
It is awesome.
That is awesome.
Oh is
Oh yeah
If you are scared, see more.
Arp
hurtly
It hurt.
It does not hurt.
Arp
Sold out
OK to
Be friends.
friendship well
I am not afraid of the smell of my nose.
I have to say it smells so good.
Feeled up.
Yes is.
Ha...
Oh yours
No longer a little crazy.
pull the wind.
Ha...
Oh well
Hahahahahah
Great is
It is not going to stop low.
by
and is
there
by
No to
It tastes.
Go to sleep again.
again
Let’s slow down a little there.
Take a break.
I slept so much again.
I am full of hunger.
Full of stomach.
greatly
I want to smell the smell here.
What is?
What do you smell?
What is smell?
Rice is
to spend.
Disease of Wind
A full hole.
Oh yeah
It is awesome.
It is beautiful.
A lot was seen.
Feel better.
I will surprise.
Lick it.
Can I lick it?
Ram is so delicious.
Do not move repeatedly.
You know it is moving?
It moved great.
by themselves
Smell of smell.
Oh yeah yeah
Oh yeah yeah yeah
No to
Oh yeah
Oh yeah yeah
I want to have more white beets.
Thanks, I want to lick you a little.
Oh... oh...
Lick the eyes.
Oh...
Oh yeah
mood is
and Ada
Oh, I feel it.
time
Wait a little.
Come to Conchita.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
by
I felt very bad and came close.
It is bin.
Sleep here.
Do you feel your breasts?
Yes
Very hot
It is warm.
Can I drink it?
I open my hole and stand up so much.
Some were inside.
and then
So, be like a baby.
How about?
is delicious?
I became such a baby.
I want to feel better again.
Oh yeah
Oh really.
I drink a lot and feel good.
Is it true?
Oh yeah
I also drank a lot of girls.
No to
Twenty
Okay Okay Okay
No to
2nd
Oh, so much pain.
Feel good
Lick my anal.
Oh, I was so excited.
Annie is excited.
No to
BGM is
If you do, it will go through your nose.
Oh yeah yeah
water
Yes
Picious
Very hardly.
Tastefully
Yes
If you are hungry, I would like to react to my anala too.
Gasherry
Oh awesome.
Go in this.
Oh oh oh
well well
Oh awesome.
I also like the smell of ananas.
I love the smell, Ann.
I will make your breasts feel good.
Feels good?
It feels good.
Oh is
Oh oh oh
increasingly easy.
Oh is
Oh that, that
No, not yet
Feel good
Oh yeah
Oh is
by Es.
No to no.
No, not yet
Oh is
I want to feel better.
Yes
Sleep here.
But you cannot endure.
I can no longer endure.
I’m also always hiccups there.
Yes
Feels good.
Oh is
Yes
You are very wet, you know?
It is awesome.
I think it moves like that.
Feel good
Oh yeah yeah yeah
No to
2nd
Yes
Oh well