You don’t argue much, right?
I also call you Mr.
The fourth year, right?
I want to get married, a little.
10 of the chopsticks.
I hit my husband’s chop.
Do you mean you don’t see your face?
Use a drink.
Take the sperm.
The taste of sperm.
to judge.
If it is right.
3 million yen.
What is this.
Oh you knew?
I will strive.
Okay, it is start.
Please come here, please come here.
Sit on that chair.
Hi to
Can you say something strange?
Mrs is beautiful.
And suddenly?
Suddenly suddenly
A couple so far.
I am letting you make a voice.
The most beautiful.
Why Why?
I am surprised, there are many people.
So, I’m going to get a prize and get you to play the game.
First, I want to talk a lot.
Did you tell me your name, age and job?
From Mrs.
Yes, I am Sasaki, 28 years old and now a housekeeper.
So who is it?
Are you at the time?
I am 35 years old and work in a restaurant.
The business is a bakery, but it is a business manager or manager.
Is it your own shop?
Yes yes yes yes.
Is it Nora?
Noah is yes.
Are you the owner of a bakery?
Oh I am the owner.
Are you still running your own shop?
Yes to.
You are so busy, right?
Be busy that.
I also ate, but I am lying.
Is it a lie?
Do you feel like protecting your home?
Yes to.
How long is the wedding?
Three years?
The third year, right?
What about children?
There is no.
Not yet is.
It is hard to say, but
Why such a beautiful child?
At 35 years old, there are seven different things.
Yes yes yes.
Where did you cheat and cheat me?
At first, I was a guest at my shop.
Go through, you mean.
I am close to the company.
It is a delicious bakery.
It seems to be common.
I went through too much.
Go to camp.
with her husband and guests.
Their common type was camp.
Are you close to the store?
Yes is yes.
and guests?
But we are each other, you, you, you are a friend.
How do they call their names together?
Respond honestly to your opinion.
I call you Mr.
See also, M.
Shame on me to say that.
When we are both, Mr.
See also M.
Is this big question? Shamefully
Can I call you a little?
Why is it?
See also M.
and sir.
What is this?
Did you have a proposal or proposal to get married?
Oh, of course it was.
What about the STI?
It is night in the camp.
It was so beautiful, I told him when the stars were so beautiful.
It is romantic.
At the stage we met.
My husband had gone.
What did you like?
As we become friends.
The store is very careful.
Take care of your guests too.
Great people, very good people.
You are hard at work.
I am older, so I can rely on you, yes.
Can say now.
Why? I don’t say much.
Instead, I say a wife.
Saying her wife.
I am adopted, but of course.
I can even cook,
What is it, again, so much for me?
Not touching money.
It was exactly his stomach.
Yes is.
I want to ask more questions, though.
hit it.
How long is the night now?
It can be a little night, it can be difficult.
How many people do you have sex with?
Do you get such a question?
This is the answer, everyone’s answer.
Please answer, you know this reaction.
But I have to answer.
It is necessary.
Oh yeah.
Can I answer?
I am ashamed.
Shame to?
It seems everyone is answering.
The pain is not much now.
Not so close.
My own job...
Two shops, and I am very busy.
Did you start dating or get married?
How long did you start dating?
Okay, why do you say that to yourself?
Start with answering...
How long did you start dating?
How much is?
As much as people.
Like a person?
How many times a week, how many times a week?
Three times, I don’t know.
2 days a week.
5 weeks, 5 weeks.
Now hardly need.
No is
Oh yeah yeah.
I’m late home and don’t have time.
Japanese is now 20 years old.
Yes is
The average number of times a week.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Yes, I’m going to the country.If you’re busy with work, take a vacation.
You will calm down sometime.
What advice are you giving?
I want to go to the game quickly, but...
This is the product I have purchased before, but
Maybe a little bit. here. yes, please.
Oh wait to.
Oh is?
Selling something...
More than a month?
Oh, can I take it?
Oh is?
Have you ever had silver?
No, I never had it.
Three million?
Yes, it is over.
Oh, it is over.
Soon, sooner to go.
Do you need to get 3 million?
If I get 3 million.
How to use?
Oh, I want to go a little trip.
to work.
But you have no time, right?
I want to rest, but only then.
You can travel well in 3 seconds.
Yes is.
For that trip.
The game content, though.
Here is the flip.
Oh yes yes
See also camera.
Put the neck car here.
Yes please please.
A little Mrs.
Can I get you to read it?
Oh is?
General monitoring of men and women.
V is?
Special project
This this
Take a life in one.
3 million yen.
Consulted
The good husband.
Oh is?
What is?
I have to say right.
Even in the bullet.
In the bullet?
Or do you not get a prize?
Is that also?
Is it so?
ChenPoo
What are Rules?
The time limit is 30 minutes.
Take 10 steps in 10 steps.
Use your mouth to take the push and judge by the thickness of the push.
If you get the right, you will receive a prize of $10 million.
If you make a mistake three times, you will be missing.
A penalty game when you make a mistake.
Yes, it is in content.
The penalty game will go away when it becomes the penalty game, so it’s not now.
Read it now and you may not know anything.
I just got a lot of stuff in it, and I can say that there are nine chips, and there are seven chips in it, and there are ten chips in it.
Hide your body and only get out the chip, so put your husband’s chip in that chip.
Why do you know the taste of your sperm?
You haven’t tasted it lately.
I don’t know the taste anymore.
So, let your husband get the sperm out of his own room.
I want to try the sperm for my husband.
I will try to remember the game and challenge you to the taste of the game.
I live in my own room, it’s great.
Not too soon, not too soon.
Good luck, no wait.
Full of stomach.
A little, fast
Please get out a lot.
Do you understand the game’s description?
I somehow understood.
Was it such a game?
Such a game.
A moment without her husband.
I want to hear you guys.
In fact, the husband
You are busy in work.
Yes is
You are 28 now.
Yes it is 28.
Are you not hungry?
Farewell to...
Mean it is not there?
I want to stay...
There must be...
There is no?
Or a rumor?
I do not rumor.
Maybe it’s not a year-on-year?
Not is it.
I do not abandon my husband.
Do you ever miss you?
What are you actually doing at that time?
Very much I will listen.
It is increasingly cold.
I thought I would listen.
But I missed.
I miss things.
Unlikely to this.
It seems you are not alone.
It becomes feeling.
Yes Yes Yes Yes
not is
one one
by alone?
What are you doing alone?
Is it messy?
What are you doing?
Oh Oh Oh
Polite
somehow
It is red.
How many times a week do you do it?
A week?
Weekly
Tell me with your finger.
Not enough?
Because it
Only seven or seven, the highest.
No, I will give it back.
to return?
Oh yeah
Oh is
Oh, it is 7.
What do you mean?
I do not do that every day.
But almost every.
by hand
What is?
Do it with hands.
With the hand?
by hand.
Or as a tool.
And the tools?
Do you know that husband?
When there is no husband.
I am ashamed, because I am not at home all day.
Do you not invite?
I said it before, but I’m tired of coming home late, so I can’t ask you.
I really want to do it, no problem.
Have you been busy at the camp recently?
You have not gone, right?
It is fun to camp, right?
Fun is.
Great, if you see an experiment.
My wife is busy,
Yes is
No no no no no no?
Do I not have to say?
The cigarette I just smoked.
of her husband,
Something is awesome.
There are spouses.
Why can’t you do so much with Doro?
No, a little bit
It is awesome,
Instead, we have to move forward.
Okay you are.
Well, because it is 3 million.
Yes but.
You can’t get 3 million so easily.
If you hesitate, you might be ashamed.
Yes but.
So, try a little bit of dough and lick it.
Do you feel like you are licking this with your hands?
How do you like it?
I don’t know, how do I lick it?
No, I didn’t do it, I did it, I’m lying.
How long do you have to play Dancing?
I am not licking at all.
So please, what is the taste?
How difficult is comparison?
Is it salt?
A little deep, a little deep.
With a loud mouth?
With a strong mouth.
Why a bakery.
I remembered it, what else?
Is it okay?
Now, my husband, I have a plan in front of you.
There were rules just before.
If you fail three times, you are unqualified.
Failing means giving out players.
If you want to taste your husband’s game, try it.
Meaning of demand?
If you think this is not the taste, do not challenge, go to the next chicken, chicken.
If you have failed, failure is 1.
It is unqualified three times.
If you are trying to get out of the road, this shit is different, in your mouth.
If you think this is not so much, go next.
Maybe you can get it back underground.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Do not use hands.
Oh, oh, and only hands.
It is a mouth feeling.
Go to the camera at last.
with enthusiasm.
Oh, I didn’t do it recently.
Good luck, I want to be with my husband.
I will strive.
So yes, that is.
What is going on behind now?
See also...
Yes I see.
within this
I have numbers from number one to 10.
Only one in this.
I have a husband.
Touch it...
Some people are touching them.
of a man.
If I show
I want to show you where you stand.
So much
Everyone is doing a little.
Great on this side.
Team on the right.
1 to 5 is great.
So from now on.
Just a mouth here.
Take sperm and taste it.
My husband guess.
Limit time is 30 minutes.
Are you ready here?
Yes is
Lastly to my husband.
One is going.
Oh, oh, I don’t know.
Please give me a clear signal.
No, it is not.
Go on, go on, go on with one shot.
matched by one shot.
Will it feel strange?
The time limit is 30 minutes.
Okay, to start!
No time? no time.
Let me see you, please show me.
I am touching something all the time.
Wait, stay a little tight.
You are always touching.
You don’t want to be wrong, right?
Yes, I do know.
How bad it is.
You don’t want to lick any other chips.
If I could.
There were so many incredible forms.
So, how many have you seen so far?
Oh yeah!? to
Before we meet...
Before we meet?
Not about 5, 5 or 5.
Yes Mr Secretary.
Okay, I don’t listen, I don’t listen.
I don’t know who? where? but I don’t know.
It is so big, I am scared.
Mr. President, I’ve been watching for a while.
Yes is what.
I have no time,
Wait a moment, what to do, what to do, what to do.
Oh, greatly
Because he was out a long time ago.
This man
Awesome before
Meaning is
Or her husband.
It comes out in front.
Not a hand.
It is moving great.
something
It seems to be me.
Is it different?
Wait a little.
appear to be
So much hair.
Not too strong either.
But it is so small, I just feel good.
This man is hot.
Please turn over.
Wait a little, wait a little.
Oh this
Oh is?
No matter what, I believe it.
It is moving.
Do not move a little.
Congratulations to you.
Probably
Probably more and more.
Do not move.
I do not know.
What is.
such such
Sorry to sorry.
Put it like this, no.
I want to see a lot, I feel different.
But in the end it became the Bible.
But I remember well.
Oh, a little
Third number
I feel like I’m trying something.
Looks like husband.
But I don’t feel so opposed.
Why are you opposed here?
I don’t see because I don’t know.
You just opposed it.
No, it’s pretty serious, it’s serious, but I don’t think it’s.
It is the most important thing that the hair has the most hair.
No, this way
A little
is large
Eat so much is okay.
It has become bigger.
Is this this?
I am hungry fast.
No to?
I feel like something like this.
Is it fine, is it taste?
Can I taste it?
I can taste it.
It looks a bit like Sarah.
Yes, he might have come.
Do you demand?
Yes, I will demand.
Yes
Is the 10th man your husband?
You are husband.
No to NO!
Sorry to.
here here.
Hi to.
No to!
Oh the lie!
It was sad.
Why Why?
So here, here is
So is the clip.
Next please do.
It will appear underwear.
I think it will appear underwear.
Is it here?
Yes, it is already 10 minutes.
Is this taking time now? Time does not stop.
The lie? Wait a little.
Because it is fast.
But it was scary.
I was wearing glasses.
Oh, a little
Mr. Todd, your wife is now dressed.
Oh, what are you doing.
No, because I thought.
I think this man is there.
Wait a little, time, time, or about 20 minutes?
Can I get another 20 minutes?
No to no.
Yes is
Good luck to you!
No, no, wait a little.
It is in top.
Topping is in.
Yes is
Wait a little.
Can you stop me now?
Time does not stop.
Why Why?
No, what do I mean?
So, you are going through it, you are going through it, you are not going through it, you are not going through it.
More and more, if this is the case, would you be working?
Do you not do it?
I do not know.
I am gone, I don’t like myself anymore.
You have been sent down.
What to do.
You are so beautiful, below.
What to do, what to do, wait.
I am always worried about it, here.
Like myself here, I know.
But I’ll get out of the first one.
It is very difficult to get out of this.
Oh yeah yeah yeah?
Oh, oh, it seems to be dirty.
What did you say?
Oh well!
I cannot say it will be shaken.
What about taste?
The whole mouth.
greatly
Very long
Oh awesome.
This is this.
The big cow.
This or
I see this, but I know.
Are you coming? Yes, I am coming.
Please please.
Something will run away.
Wait a little, wait a little.
No to no.
Yippidy yi yippity yay.
Oh, the cowboy
Oh, it is awesome!
How about taste?
A bit thin.
No to no.
It wasn’t hard.
No to
Let’s say tough.
Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next Next
The Peach,
What is different?
Feeling of mouth.
Two years ago it was probably like this.
Two years is short.
something
My chest is empty.
I fear
by Nur
by Taa
The baby trap.
1 is
before
Clean them
by
well well
It is awesome to float.
Well, but it is time.
I feel no.
No yet
greatly
Probably the closest ever.
Fitt is great.
This is
I ask you to ask your husband if the eighth person is your husband.
It was like a selling bandman.
You have no husband, this is your husband.
Is there? There is.
are somewhere.
Are you somewhere? Are you somewhere?
So, let’s see tomorrow.
You have only one more time.
The second time.
What is written, it will be confusing.
Yes is
Not a king.
Where are you.
Sooner guess it.
is completely naked.
Black and time.
10 minutes remaining.
Wait for lies.
How many cups is your mother?
The G cup.
I have never heard.
No No No No No No
It is a Duna Cup.
I am scared.
Donna is not really there, it is no longer that way.
of Danny.
She didn’t say that she was WWE.
not do it.
I say nothing but Danny.
time is
A little
You cannot see it.
No, but you don’t see it.
I am so happy, I am just going to be happy.
Oh yes yes
But I’m going to care here.
There is something instinctive.
I am always interested in the sixth.
I care about.
I am going out so much more than others.
6 is
I’m going to go out, but I’m a little bit on my feet.
This is probably my first impression, my husband.
You are going from the root.
Let me try.
It smells good or good.
Yes, you do, you do sometimes.
My husband is very clean and smells like soap.
Come out something.
Now... no?
I’ve been saying this all the time, but I really feel like this.
So you should leave the players.
Yes
Yes yes yes
hard to work.
I like and strong.
I often feel like a moment of mourning.
It is a bit... colour.
The color is different.
It is not Sarah.
It is more and more Sarah.
It was a little Sara.
The eyes of Sarah.
Sara is not white.
Thin eyes
Sarah has a deep eye.
The taste is a bit deep.
Yes is
It looks like a ram.
No to
No to no?
I don’t think it’s the most important impression.
I do not know.
What to do.
I have lost understanding.
Do not tell me.
The Minister’s Prize, number six.
Which is below?
form from below.
This may be this.
The feeling is
Feeling in the mouth.
Maybe the same.
Oh, the fucking bread!
Does your daughter have her breasts?
The breast, right?
I think you interrupt.
Keep your breasts in, no interruption.
Oh well, Pooja...
Oh yeah, yeah yeah!
Dad, are you hungry?
No to
Oh yeah
This is this.
lightly
I think light.
Because it is light.
No longer the rest.
Wait to
There is no time, this is it.
The last?
It may be the last time, try it.
But the taste is strong.
More tough.
Is this this?
Is the second man your husband?
Please please.
I am pleased.
No to
I am glad.
The best is.
This is the best.
Meaning is
The third time failed.
This is last.
Lying
Deca by
by Send
Decathlon is a service.
The final penalty game.
Oh, what what what what.
And then, that
What is open?
Don’t you see Gina?
Wait and wait.
Is it explained?
Gina, you might hear it.
The correct answer is number 7.
by Gana
was near
A little near the 7th.
Do you not see it?
Okay, enough is enough.
Wait well.
A little more.
Feel badly
What is bad?
Waiting for the neck.
Tell me when you look at the camera.
Is it okay?
Not a lot of prizes.
Yes is
Not three million.
What is?
by million.
I tried hard.
From now on, a lot of rewards.
by OEM
Thanks to.
Please come here.
Please go, hello
Hi to you.
Hi to
Please please.
by your husband.
You are young.
Young and young.
Are you growing?
It is doing.
Can I tell you your name, age and job?
From Mrs.
It is far.
At age 27 years old,
I work in the district office.
The District Office?
The District, yes
It is chick.
I am 27 years old and work for a travel agency.
Same with?
Same as you.
Same with.
It is a nice cup.
Thanks to.
Good to be.
Man’s wife is caught, so.
It is pretty big.
You are purposely dressed like this.
intentionally
How is it?
Look at the men.
If you actually see it, it is big.
I understand that.
It would be like walking naked.
It is a little.
This feeling is
How about Dangerous?
If you look a little bit more, don’t you think it’s beautiful?
Do not be excited about this.
Don’t be excited, it’s not.
Style is good.
Are you doing any exercise?
I go to exercise and pilates.
The Pilates?
Like a teaching version.
Tyranny
Pilates is
How old are you married?
The fourth year.
27 years old.
How long have you been dating?
Have you been dating since you were 20 years old?
Yes is
Or a classmate?
Yes, from the university.
The same university.
Yes is
Are you doing a circus?
A tennis club?
Yes, it’s tennis together.
The Tennis? The Tennis? The Tennis?
Did you come from either? Where is? Where is?
It was like a flower in a tennis circus.
It feels very clean, right?
You look like a lady, yes.
What do you think is confessing?
He is so kind and can treat everyone the same way.
I thought awesome.
Anyone will look good.
Or even then.
Not the type of person you like.
It is so cute.
It is true.
Did you mean a proposal?
There was a proposal.
tomorrow is
I think young people are not very young recently.
It seems to be.
When you sleep, you get married.
I married to sleep.
to sleep.
What did you say?
Please marry me.
by Simple
Yes, it felt like it was.
What kind of scheme did you say?
I was traveling to Yogyakarta.
In the midst.
I have offered.
Are you happy?
Yes, I am happy.
is happy.
And now, your child is?
Yes, not the
Planning to build now?
From now on, you will be able to adapt to the situation.
But we are friends with each other...
Yes, it is so, is it?
But I know that I will make kids.
You can’t keep silent, baby.
To some extent, that is.
You have to have sex.
Yes is.
Have you ever seen such a small thing before?
Yes, but it has happened a few times.
I have had sex several times.
Well, I have a way to say.
You can’t have sex with a child, right?
What to do at that time?
How can I have a child? – How can I have a child?
So I left the station...
The station?
not otherwise.
The station of Zee?
The station...
Where is?
Inside is...
Inversely to?
I hate it.
Would you hate?
I am...
In the words of the story, the two of us are now at night.
How many tracks do you do?
Well, if it is 1 week.
Yes yes
How many tracks are you doing?
No, a little bit of.
I thought I said enough now.
Why can I say so much?
Because he was very loud.
About 1 week.
Yes is it.
You are busy.
Sure of it.
But there was only a book.
Good for your mother.
A very early wife.
The beginning or
Not is.
It is bad.
I will ask your husband later.
Oh is?
No is not.
Today is today, but
What are you talking about coming here?
something in the game.
as if participating.
Yes is.
Couples and play games together.
Provide me to challenge.
I mean, but it is a reward.
I take out the woman’s hand.
Oh be it.
Is it Bamil?
Not so though.
Very heavy.
Will you return?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
3 million yen.
I was surprised.
Both of them are currently saving money.
Oh yes yes.
You are normal.
We are a couple, guys.
Yes to.
How much is it? at the beginning.
About 100 now.
About 100.
This is since the time of college.
We cut a little and then we cut out, and then we get together.
Both of them used.
Oh yeah yes.
It is real.
Yes to.
Now is 1 million.
If you play today, you will have 3 million.
Oh, it is too much.
A total of 4 million.
I want to make 300 games, but I want to make a game.
What kind of game.
I’m preparing for an explanation here in Flip.
Show me a puppy.
So, let me take that flip.
Let’s read with Bern.
Put it in your mouth.
from here?
The first time.
1st General Dancing Monitoring av Special Projects
Take a $3 million prize for this photo.
What do you say, Chipo?
This is SIP.
Why here?
You know why it feels like that.
If you don’t get a chance, you won’t get 3 million.
This little
Without it, three million won’t start.
is true?
Then listen to.
Listen to
Listen to, listen to.
Let us read the rules.
Time limit is 30 minutes.
10 is in line.
Use the fruit of the mouth to take a static, dry with a static taste.
If you get the right, the prize is 3 million yen.
If you make a mistake three times, you will be disqualified and punished without making a mistake once.
As if yes.
The penalty game will be later, and will be played in the game.
Oh yes, is it here?
Someone who doesn’t know something now.
Does it mean you don’t see your face?
Yes is
I know the taste of death.
But if you do not know more than the day, do you know that you drink daily?
No, not, but when did you drink it?
Not much lately.
I have recently given you a tick.
Yes yes yes
Where have you been going most recently?
Or is it normally in the shell?
This minute is.
Yes is
So you don’t taste it too much.
If you tell me you know surprisingly.
Yes is it.
Maybe you don’t know.
Do you know the shape?
Yes, yes, you will understand it.
Is the twin of Gumi stupid?
beautifully
is beautiful?
I want to get you boobed, so you should start by getting yourself out of the spirit first.
Bring a sausage, try it here and remember the taste once.
Can you do it?
Yes, I can do it.
Then there are nine chickens, and there is a darshan.
This is a game of 10 chicks in a Darson chicken.
You are giving up sperm.
I’ll give you a snap and show you Darth Vader.
Please here please.
No stars to Appreciate Asako
Great bread, I have this.
Not really do.
I think sex.
Once a week, I say “Tapping” – the number of times AJ.
n  T
The forest is Tadeo.
This week, or twice more.
You should listen to it for a day.
Yes is.
That means a very little day.
But very little.
What is the missing part?
and self.
How do you do it?
How is it?
I think it feels common.
Have you ever seen a selfie?
Maybe the selfie you’re doing is an unusual selfie?
Oh, it feels like that.
As far as the video is concerned, it may seem like a common thing.
How much is it generally a week?
About three. about three.
Stay for a day?
Yes to.
You like it.
Is that so?
Do you like it?
I like it.
Because men will do it too.
Yes, yes is it.
It is inside it.
100% of freshness
Not very spectacular?
Now for a moment, the freshness.
Have you tasted it fresh, and you can taste it?
Do you need to remember?
How do you taste it?
How do you feel? – Normally.
How do you taste normal?
How is it normal?
Take it in hand.
How do you feel about touching?
I am doing Sarah.
Soon a lot.
Go in.
entered in
I don’t know, I’m not sure, I can’t be sure, but yes.
It is not like this, water.
I am a little worried, I will say something more.
Yes yes yes yes yes
Is it okay?
Yes
is OK
Probably
Yes is
From now on.
Not to be any.
Yes is
Standby is ready.
First then
Yes is
So I’ll go to this stand.
How much did you taste it?
by
Not a month.
About a month.
2 or 3 times in the mouth.
I had no mouth.
There was no mouth.
After I got out.
After I got out?
Suitable to
No to
Get out of the coat, get out of it, and something.
Are you following?
You followed me afterwards.
Especially when it comes to cleaning ferrari.
Would it be?
I will give you 3 million yen and you will be able to do it.
Please be excited about the camera.
There is a lot I want to do with him from now on.
I have 3 million yen and I can do it.
So, I arrived at the venue.
I am very Nirvana.
Oh yeah, I did not.
Did you see behind?
I saw it.
How many minutes do you have?
10 minutes
The time limit is 30 minutes.
Do not use hands.
Only the mouth.
Let me get the sperm.
Try it after you have tasted.
Whether your husband.
by Jade
If you think you are husband.
Please call it demand.
The Request.
Yes, I will leave.
Yes to.
If you are out, it is a punitive game.
The penalty game is unknown.
I know when the penalty game.
During the penalty game.
Oh yes yes.
So are you ready for this?
Yes to.
And then last.
Send a message to the ascendant.
Please be understandable.
So I want to go fast.
30 minutes from now.
Okay, to start!
What do I do? what do I do?
Looking like, how long can I go?
But, it seems, there is something different.
Which is?
The second number.
Number two? what is it?
No hair.
Is that person?
Yes, it is not, there is a shadow.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Yes is
But do you taste it?
But you don’t have to do it.
I can say that I am shooting in number.
If you want to play with other teams, then you want to play with other teams.
No, I don’t know, but I don’t know surprisingly.
It is 2 minutes.
Wait, wait, it is a shit.
What to do.
Oh yeah?
The number one?
Not going from number one.
Oh yeah yeah yeah?
Going from number one, it looks like it is right.
You are very sicky.
It is awesome.
Instead, I can’t get the first.
Will I try?
Yes yes yes
Oh is?
Please go
Please please.
Looks to be happy.
No, it’s a strange space, it’s a bit funny.
The number five?
5th, 5th, 5th, 5th, 5th, 5th, 5th, 5th, 5th, 5th, 5th, 5th, 5th, 5th, 5th, 5th, 5th, 5th, 5th
Do you think it is the language?
I think it is the true language.
Yes please please.
What should I do? – Normally.
Do you cry like this all the time?
It is normal. - You can't use it.
Is it 5th?
Please go.
No to? Oh well
Too much out.
Is it many?
It felt like there were so many.
No I know.
I do not know at all.
2nd
Come now.
No word in it, painful.
I feel different from two times.
Is it over once? You can start again.
But not, it might be you, Shiro.
Oh, maybe it is.
But I think it probably isn’t a game.
5 minutes passed.
Oh what to do.
I don’t know the game.
You don’t see it, you know.
I do not know.
What to do.
The number one?
The first one.
Otherwise I don’t know.
Okay to?
Okay is it?
Someone who is a bit well.
What did you say?
I don’t know, something
I am well.
No to
I thought he would go out.
A little
Hold your hand again.
No to
Gray
It is.
That is awesome hello.
Shortly -
Badly in Vienna.
by TJ
It flies great.
I can feel the taste close.
You think it was possible to get out of it.
Yes to.
I thought it would look a little like that.
and once.
Yes, I am a Barbie.
and then is
Oh yeah
I will try once.
The Request?
So, look at one.
The best then.
The progress of your husband?
and then is
was different.
Sharon please.
Yes, this is a game, please take a look.
The first part game.
A lot of things.
appear underwear.
Meaning to take off?
Is it there?
No, no, but not so.
is difficult.
But I don’t see them from everyone.
You do not see it, right?
Yes, of course is.
I don’t see the men either.
You know, you don’t see it.
Yes is
not see it.
The punitive game.
No, because the request failed.
Yes is
By the way, time is moving forward.
Oh yeah yeah
I take off.
Thirteen minutes
Oh yeah
It is a shame, 30 minutes.
Yes is
Oh, and fuck it.
Tagged as: fucking, fucking
by SWEET
The underwear.
What about shoes?
Shoes up and up.
Oh the shoes.
Not a stitch?
Stitching is good.
I am a little embarrassed about this dress.
Tagged as: time, time, time
Would you help?
Okay maybe.
It is hot.
time and sick.
I will help you.
Oh awesome.
My husband has a big breast.
I sweat a little in my chest.
A little hot.
It is hot.
How many times have you seen your father?
How many?
As to talk...
I think I won’t go.
Is it?
How many books do you do?
But I know that I’d rather be dating them.
Yes is
Yes, it is connected.
What to do, what to do.
Oh well...
Did you go again?
No, not
It’s not the first one, it’s a failure, right?
What at noon?
Which?
Oh this is this?
I feel a little bit.
The Lucky Seven.
Lucky Swan, a little bit.
I feel like it is noon.
The original time.
Surely it is.
Sorry, but it feels unusual.
But I feel slight.
I feel something.
Is it seeming?
I feel like.
The angle of well.
I probably felt so.
You know you brought it out.
Yes, of course
Have you gone out?
out out
I went out, I went out.
How about?
Awesome doll
Something yes
But this
It feels the same as before, I think it’s Shogun.
Are you doing an interview?
The one I just tasted.
I think it is a shootout.
Oh yeah?
Oh, this is what I want to demand.
Demand, Demand, Demand and Demand
And then the 7th.
Oh my husband, oh Shaugo, Shaugo
Please call me.
Showa
Please wait.
It was a great whisky, whisky.
Why is different?
It was almost noon.
It was 11:59 minutes.
That is what? that is what?
The punitive game.
I took it, I took it.
It will be completely naked.
Not even underwear, not even clothes.
It is not the right to wear clothes for someone who has made the wrong twice.
In a tough world.
I have not seen Danner’s chip.
No, but it is very close.
Maybe the genes are the same.
So a little.
Oh, but it is near.
10 minutes and I’m back in 10 minutes.
It is more than 30 minutes, but out.
Yes, there are no 3 million.
Oh, I do not like it.
I just wore the other stuff besides my husband.
I do not like it.
And Sanchez right.
Husband, do you hear it?
Now she is Mrs. Zena.
Do you have no hair?
There is a little.
Yes to.
Your husband will do it well.
I told him that he was easy to understand.
What is it.
Oh is?
Please let them all go once.
once
Please do the app at the same time.
A little apple.
I want to let the flyer.
No to
Great, the fifth is the first.
In this area, in this area.
That is different.
Everyone has an app, I don’t know.
No time to hang, no time to hang.
No, no, what do we do?
Can’t you touch this with your hands?
No to No.
What if I do it elsewhere?
What do you mean?
Is there anything intertwined here?
Do you usually do that?
I like it, really, the language.
Do you know if you are in touch with it?
I’ve been in a mess, so you know.
Okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
Is it OK?
Please bring out the players.
Yes
No player has the right to answer.
Yes, it is yes.
Well, that means to use.
What to do.
I don’t even know about the apple.
Instead of 8.
Did you wrong?
It is full.
This once.
After being urgent.
Sorry to
You are wrong twice.
I do not know.
Next time you can’t make a mistake.
It is ended, right?
I fear
OK to OK?
Maybe not know.
I do not know.
If it doesn’t start, can you say differently?
Oh, and so
Yes is.
Certainly
And here too.
I am going to breast.
I hope you are well already.
I don’t know your breasts.
But it looks like a pleasant.
I do not know.
Do not know?
Heavy
Very scared.
No, this is different.
This is different.
Taste is different.
No to
I do not demand.
Tagged,  Tagged  Tagged
No, not not not
What to do.
I have no time.
I have gone missing.
Anyway, it is different, but definitely not.
I feel absolutely different.
already already?
I feel different.
I no longer know.
No longer time.
I am no longer sure.
You can only go from the end.
not sure
Sorry to sorry.
I do not know.
Meaning not know?
I don’t know anywhere or not.
I no longer know.
Wine is all public.
But I have no time.
by
W is
by Griffin
properly
Give it.
Oh, and Akan
Oh go go
Put it on.
back to
1 is
Oh yeah, no more
set up
What now
I did not.
The day before too.
You were right, but I have another question.
So, try to taste it, what about it?
I no longer know.
Do you demand?
No longer time, right?
One question remains.
I don’t know. ask for it.
I do it.
No more can.
Try a show from the Chimpei.
Number 10 is just.
something,
Not is it!
Then it burned.
What did you think was different?
Oh yeah
1 is
High is
Is it height?
I thought it was different.
Wait a little.
I saw a little.
Deca is HEM.
Wait to wait.
No, go in there.
Oh, it is shit.
Wait a little.
Is this a punitive game?
A little bit, eh?
No, it is not proof.
Not evidence, not evidence, not evidence.
Wait, it is not a proof.
It’s really different, not really evidence.
No is different.
Do you have a shovel on the other side of the wall?
Shogun, I don’t know what you are doing.
In front of my eyes.
No, no, no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
Wait, I’m in front of the shark.
In front of your eyes?
Or somewhere.
The correct answer is number three.
Number three?
No No No No No No
No shark to see.
in front of eyes.
Is it TB?
I only do what is.
cannot at all.
Nothing is
increased again.
disrupted
and months
No to
Wash it inside.
and more
No to
Oh is
Really hot
by
No to
Oh yeah
Can I compare?
really
Oh, this will be.
Oh, I have come
Wait and wait.
It hurts.
Do not put too much.
Give them $3 million and go ahead.
Something, what to do.
I will talk to you when I get home. - Okay.
Thanks to.
Hi to.
Welcome to Mr. Jian.
Can you tell me your name, age, and job before you tell me?
Yes to.
I am 31 years old and I am working on personal jam receipt.
I am 34 years old and work in a home electricity store.
Are you both, you couple?
Yes to.
Are we good together?
Oh well is.
You don’t argue much, right?
What are you fighting about?
At that time, we worked for each other.
I always said I would help, but I didn’t do much.
At that time, you are fighting.
How long have you been married now?
Now is the sixth year.
So, I mean, half the head.
Yes, because we’ve been married for two years.
Now the child?
There is no.
Planning to build?
Even at age, I have a little talk.
Well, there is also work.
You are already a friend, it’s hard.
The timing.
Do you want to meet, do you want to meet?
Presentation by a friend.
So, is it like you two are called and you two are dating?
No, I said it at first, but I don’t feel that much.
It is time, I hope we see you.
First, we gathered together a few times and we both met.
I think it’s a good idea to start thinking about getting to know the next lady.
You may be the most compassionate or too active.
I mean, I mean, I said it from either.
How is Cox’s approach?
At first, I contact and invite many people.
How did you feel?
No, you were happy.
Great to come.
I was a little concerned too.
I guess you didn’t feel that at first.
Did you kiss before or after dating?
and afterwards.
After you kissed?
What hand?
Hands before dating.
And from your wife?
Do you remember?
I remember it.
We have been together for eight years and have been together.
It was hard, it was fun, or it was a memory.
It was really the first time.
I have no money, both of you.
In the early 20s.
I cannot pay for electricity.
It has stopped.
You have stopped.
What about electricity?
I always bought goldfish.
That’s why the pump stopped.
Woke up in the morning and noticed.
In the morning, there is no electricity.
It is not charged.
That is?
Didn’t you stop at the water?
The gas stopped a little.
I want to take a bath.
Not because it is hot water.
I cooked the keto several times and brought it.
Eat it.
Do you remember the offer you made when you got married?
Do you remember?
What are you told?
Really simple.
I want to marry.
Do you remember?
A good restaurant.
Have a reservation.
Good restaurant in Yokohama.
Can I eat after I’m finished?
Should I eat before eating?
Eat on the way.
I was preparing too.
Why do you know that?
Because I usually didn’t go that way.
What is there, what did you play today?
Go and me too.
When did you play first?
recently
The latter time?
Not recently, for months.
A few months time.
Yes, two months
Yes, until then.
Do you feel open every time?
Yes is.
A bit embarrassed.
A little too.
It became more difficult to invite.
I usually have no time to do it.
When the breast is
Where do we go?
Mostly from me.
It was though.
So I got busy with work.
That time, then again.
You missed the timing.
I will try to win the game this time, but
The prize here.
Is it enough?
Okay is it?
Oh awesome.
Good, have you never had that?
So I’ll give you $3 million to challenge the game.
3 million yen, what would it mean?
I wanted to go abroad, but I was a little home.
A little, I want to go.
$3 million is a good trip.
I can go a lot.
I want to go.
This is a game that will challenge you on your second wedding trip.
See here, see here.
It is.
Show me the camera.
See to?
Can you read it from above?
1st General Men and Women Monitoring av Special Projects
Take a shot, get a 3 million dollar prize.
Oh yeah
Listen to husband.
I understood that bullet.
Champion
How will it come true, right?
Listen to Mr. Chen
Time limit is 30 minutes.
10 is in line.
I put my husband’s chest in the chest.
Use only your mouth.
Take the sperm.
It is determined by the taste of sperm.
If you are right in the 12th.
3 million yen.
If you make a mistake three times, you will be missing.
Every time you make a mistake, you play a penalty game.
As for the game’s content, I’m not going to show you here yet.
There are nine other shops in the room.
Put your husband’s hand in it.
A total of 10 chips from the taste of her husband's sperm
Please give your husband’s chest.
I do not remember.
You do not remember, right?
Yes
Players don’t eat that much, right?
not do not
So from now.
to her husband.
I have a little room.
So, you really get the sperm out.
The husband’s sperm.
Tasting here.
I can remember the taste of sperm.
Let me join you in the game.
The taste of sperm.
Yes is
I understand
not sure
No, this game is.
Not is.
You can never see his face.
The face is hidden, of course.
I only see the chip.
Of course, I think there are many shots.
How many have you seen so far?
Except for 7.
10 is not.
Did you notice the 7th?
I think it will look like a clue, of course.
I hope you can finally taste the sperm.
So, my husband will now be guiding you.
Go to another room and get your sperm.
I want to talk a lot about her until her husband comes home.
What is the good thing about your husband?
Yes, basically, I’m kind, but I’m working with friends, actively sharing about the house, but I do a lot of things, or I’m going to throw away rubbish in the morning.
You are collaborative, right?
Yes to.
I think you talked a little bit, I feel.
I feel very calm and not angry.
Have you been with a man for more than a month?
It is about a month and a half, a month.
You are still young enough to get used to it, are you still young enough?
I would like to meet two or three times a month and I think we work together.
Can you endure that monotony?
It is my personal time.
What to?
Alone and style.
Oh, what are you doing?
to woman.
meet you?
When you are at work or when you are late home.
How often is that?
There are about twice a week.
Is she still a woman, is she also a man?
Yes is.
Do men do it alone?
I think you’ve probably seen that in a box like this.
You are writing seal, right? I started so far.
Yes, it seems he has come back.
Yes the spirit? The Psychiatrist
Well, I don’t know what this kind of infertility treatment is, I don’t know how much I am feeling like this.
Do you follow two?
Followed by 2.
So, let’s taste it for a moment.
Remember the taste.
I brought out.
Stay here
How do I.
If you do this in your hands.
Is it straight?
and straight.
Then straight.
by smell.
It looks like sommelier.
How is the smell?
Not too much.
Something was hit in front of me.
Did you understand?
I remember this.
I remembered
yet another time.
Do you remember?
is okay.
I remembered.
She is Sarah.
It feels a little relaxed.
So, you will be able to move to the stadium immediately and challenge the game.
So, my husband is ready, so I’ll see him a little bit ahead.
Yes Yes Yes Yes
I will now be able to get a chick with your husband.
You should not use the rules of the game.
Just keep your mouth standing.
While somehow licking.
If I think it might be different, I will try to move it into a different shell.
How many times do you have it?
So, try the game and try it and try it.
If you think that the player is your husband, please ask him.
Yes is
If you think it’s different, I’ll go to the next chip.
If you do not try any of these, try any of the chips.
Yes is what.
If you fail, you will be punished by a game.
If it happens three times, it will be disqualified.
Yes is
I understand.
Then the last.
Go to camera.
Go to this camera.
Please be excited.
Impressed
Yes is
I want to go on a wedding trip abroad.
I think there is more and more love.
I will strive.
So yes is.
Mr to Mr.
Yes is
Look at the back.
What is it.
Really Jumping.
You can see her husband now.
No, I do not know.
I just saw you, I don’t know.
Finally, a word to your husband.
not see.
You will not answer me?
Can you answer, husband?
Yes is
Good luck to be.
Yes
Which one did it from?
You cut off somewhere.
So if you start now, the time limit is 30 minutes.
Yes is
First, wherever you go.
Can you be in your heart?
Yes is
Maybe from the previous one.
Oh yeah, so then
Draw, Duna, Chips, Gamble, Game
Yes is
Okay, it is start.
What do you do?
How about it? it is quite rotating.
some form.
Can I say next?
On this side?
on this side.
How about?
appearance is
Hair and eyes, too.
How about?
Yes, yet another time.
This is L.
Yes, I put it in here.
Oh yeah.
First and again.
This chip is,
Would you like to ask for Narnia’s chop?
What to do.
I feel like, but I feel like.
Yes to.
Requested
Have you asked three times?
Three times.
Requested
Request is good.
Then, please take the second face out of the door.
No to
Meaning is
I failed once.
It will be a punitive game.
It’s a penalty game, but you get it.
I don’t want to play the game, so this is a penalty.
Please, let’s go first.
Should you wear all of the clothes up or down?
Yes is
You are a good lady, you are a bit shocked.
If it fails, it is a shock.
Maybe someone who is crying is his husband.
My husband is now in his underwear.
Yes is
What do you say?
must say
I have not re-measured the size.
A little
What is this staking?
This is limited time.
Oh, it’s inside here too.
You can sit alone.
Madam, do you have style?
Thanks to you.
A little shoes.
Is it OK?
If that
I just started, but I just wore it.
If it is the best, is it?
Is it yes?
I understand.
You can’t use your hands, right?
cannot use hands.
So I thought.
It is similar.
Different from ours.
It smells different from body soap.
And that too?
No to you, President.
Third pass once.
By the way, 10 minutes have passed.
It was a little too early, surprisingly.
It looks like it is similar in weight.
Only two more chances.
Yes, because it is only twice.
Will you try to test it all?
Okay okay?
Pushed
I said goodbye to dinner.
They look similar.
How about?
taste just.
It won’t change so quickly, right?
Not much taste.
have a life habit.
by smell
What do you do?
not do.
Not to regret?
What do not do.
The next one.
6 minutes
See also!
Oh, andilly
Hank is!
Hanoi is awesome.
Oh yeah
anyway
Very scary.
What happened.
Oh is
Luke is
I think I will.
But
I feel like I am similar.
The smell of nose.
The smell is similar to the previous.
It is similar to her husband’s nature.
Yes
Yes the request.
Show me 60,000 faces.
Sorry, I have closed my eyes.
No, it is great.
There are 10 minutes left.
So I failed, here.
Please come second.
Yes, how about you?
What is?
Yes is it, right?
Do you know what time it is?
After the shirt.
Yes is
Lana, it is not going to happen at all.
Sorry, I will see.
Please go
I say please.
You can’t see them all, so you may not be ashamed.
Is it?
Yes yes yes
Because I see it.
Sorry to
I know you know, but you don’t have hair.
Oh, you are out.
I am out, sorry.
Yes to.
Next, how many are you going?
Because I have already come.
How many?
Yes to.
Is it OK?
Oh, it is different.
Oh yeah.
Do you have time?
Yes to.
Do you have no time?
Oh well well.
by Tanya
All went out.
greatly
I fear
some form.
Oh, no, no, I feel different.
No, I do not demand.
Oh is?
I cut off five minutes.
And five minutes?
Yes to.
not demanded.
The ninth is yes.
Yes, not to do.
There is no time, so do you not regret it?
Yes to.
Okay, then the next time.
I wear it here too.
Next is number 10.
The 10th person.
The length of the legs is different.
Of course, a man is big.
Yes, I feel a little different in height.
I remember that.
No time.
Sorry to
not otherwise.
Are you in the past?
How about?
Yes is.
Okay, but if you go back.
Third number
Yes please please.
I went out.
Yes is
Now, there is no longer time.
I have to say fu.
How about?
Requested
The third number.
The husband
Request number three.
Let me show you face.
Is the third husband?
was husband.
Oh yeah?
It was sad.
I thought this was a little.
Were you confident?
I was the third most confident.
So the last.
If you fail three times, you are disqualified, but the penalty game.
Is it OK?
What are you writing?
Decairs...
Decathlon is judged.
Decathlon is right?
A little, who?
Who are you?
differently otherwise.
Wait and wait, wait and wait.
This is a punitive game.
Wait a little.
Can you not find it?
But there is.
I am somewhere.
Not behind me.
is here
It is okay, there is nothing.
Yes is
Who is it?
A little snow.
Someone is watching.
I saw his face.
Who was it?
No to
So that no one can hear.
Tell me what you are doing now.
Unknown people at the station.
They are crack.
I was behind recently.
I heard from behind.
I feel bad.
Feels bad?
Feel badly
Have you not seen?
I have not seen.
Really mana
Minority
Cosine
Oh yeah
Maybe this side too.
I do, it hurts.
difficult to handle.
Is it true?
I will send you drinks.
I was surprised.
The prize is no longer available.
Yes is
Who is this person?
A professional AV.
I regret it.
Thanks to.
Please come here.
Please please.
Hi to
Today, I am applying for your couple.
Yes is
You are a couple, right?
Yes is yes.
Are you not parents?
Not the parents.
It is often said.
Can I listen to your sleep?
Oh, I am 33 years old.
and 53 myself.
Isn’t it a high school girl?
Isn’t it high school school at the time?
If it is right.
Even if stupid.
No, I am wrong.
She was an ex-girl.
Yes yes yes.
I worked in a advertising agency.
I want to ask you a little more,
First your name and again your name.
Do your work.
I say a boy.
Is the name okay?
What is the name below?
I am a kid, 33 years old.
Now a little work.
I have returned,
Again a advertising agency.
I am working.
I am 53 years old and work in a advertising agency.
Please be kind.
Please please.
It will nerves you.
I am nervous, really.
Is it okay?
Are we the same company, or are we the same company?
I can now do small business at home as well as teleworking.
Different from the company?
Yes, the industry is the same.
As a child, I am the boss of the same company.
Yes is
20 years away, that is.
At first, he came in and then he cut back to the boss.
On the marriage.
Yes is
What do you do now feel like?
When I became a boss.
He had great reliance.
If you get married, a little.
I am in the company, I have link.
Do you mean you regret it a little?
Today I clean up that gap.
A little child, a little year.
Do you have plans or hope?
I think it is, but with all the age.
I wonder if you are still 20 years old.
Did you have a confession?
Oh yeah yeah
But say not.
Oh yeah yeah.
The boss?
I had confessed to my boss.
I have even approached it a little.
How do you feel?
and sound.
When we were together.
A little bit.
Talk about work and more.
It is a night audition.
I thought a lot.
within the company.
Arriving at work.
It is not.
Are you concerned about the future?
But actually
I like it above.
Is it a lot of computer?
I mean to reassure you a little.
Someone who feels like a generic gap.
Oh yeah
I myself
History and old things.
Sorry if I said it is old.
Isn’t he so old?
Sorry sorry sorry
The last time.
What are you calling together?
No to No.
Now Mrs Hina
Is it nervous?
They are called puppies or puppies.
When you say you have to do something bad.
But there are times when I think it is.
So what do you call me?
I call her a thief.
by Kitty.
You seem very friendly.
Must be bad together.
Are you not afraid of anything?
No, I am not afraid.
I am nervous.
I just heard about making kids.
What is the night really?
How is it?
I talked about my age, but I am not satisfied with myself at all.
Do you not have to get an enema lately?
I don’t remember. I don’t remember.
So much so?
Yes, I am working.
I also went back to work.
33 years old.
Yes yes yes
Still really
What do you say, I am also an actor.
You are female.
Yes, I am pleased
What kind of story can you tell here today?
Something, that is it.
When playing a game.
I will show you the prize first.
It is awesome!
You are well prepared.
I am scared.
Be careful, the electricity is running.
Fall to!
It is awesome!
It is awesome.
Playing games 300 times.
You are scared, it is awesome.
Playing the game, staff participates.
I am going to help.
You have to clean it, right?
I will get it now.
can be done.
I will disappoint.
Meaning is
What kind of game to play.
I want to explain it a little from now on.
I already have a flip.
A little here.
As if you could see the camera.
More and more.
Yes, you have checked it.
Then Mrs.
Can you read the first general male and female monitoring?
Special AMV projects
Take a win, win 3 million yen.
Listen to... what... what... what... what...
No, I... No...
Can you read her, lady?
Come to be there.
Oh... oh... oh... oh...
What is confirmation?
I have a special reading.
Time limit is 30 minutes.
I am surprised, wait a little.
10 minutes, just a little bit of stomach.
What kind of shit.
Use your mouth to pick up players.
I judge by the taste of the players.
What is it? difficult.
Did you know?
If you get the right, you will receive a prize of $12 million.
If you are wrong three times, you fail.
A penalty for every mistake.
The content of the punitive game itself is when it is done, and if it fails, it will fall into the punitive game itself.
It is best to prevent now.
So you understand the rules?
I understand, but I do not know.
What do you not know?
What does it mean to do such a thing?
Yes it is.
Think well.
3 million yen.
If you earn $200,000 a month, how many months will it take?
It was old.
10 calls to.
It takes about a year and a half today.
Oh well okay?
I read it a little but it may be difficult to understand.
In the immediate location, we already have nine chips.
In addition to her husband’s chips, there are 10 chips in it.
You can see the body, you can see the face, you can see the body.
This is a game that only the man can play.
It is bad.
I guess, but it’s a taste for your husband.
When did you last taste the spirit of the wicked?
I said it before, but do you remember it?
Yes is it.
It is shameful, this.
You are bad, right?
A little no.
It’s hard, so from now on, I’ll have my husband go to another room and get his sperm out.
So, try the sperm here once, and you will remember the taste, Mr. Sperm.
and yeah.
Then, you will actually be able to stay in the place.
Once you get to see that staff.
Is it okay?
Do not go too far.
There are AV and Erofertil.
Wait a little.
I am surprised.
I want 3 million.
I want it.
If you say that, what are you thinking?
How can I use it?
Travel, travel abroad or travel abroad.
There are many, you guys.
I told her I didn’t remember the last sex.
Yes is
There is no husband now.
Yes
I listen to hiding.
It means he is 33 years old.
It is not to die without dying, right?
Oh well, yes
There are times when you want to?
Yes is
What do you think at that time?
No, what is one?
I became alone.
What to do? 😂
How do you feel, how do you feel?
No, but it is normal.
Ordinary is?
Normally I bother.
Where are you fighting?
How much? I can’t say.
I know, where do you bother?
Oh is?
Where do you do it if you are a woman?
The same lower half.
The knee
No, not not
What is bamboo?
The axis.
The stake?
Where are the feet?
This around?
What to take?
by Cret.
Is it many?
Yes is
How much do you do that weekly?
every day.
Every day?
every day
Once a day?
1 or 2 times?
Sometimes one or two times.
Yes is
Sorry I am sorry.
It was quite time.
Not very handy.
Are you not very handsome?
Even when the hand.
Really?
Have you just put out your hand?
The hand I put out.
Actually, I taste it from now on.
The taste?
Yes is
I forgot to taste it.
Have you ever eaten yourself?
I have eaten it myself.
It is awesome.
How is the smell?
Oh the spirit.
A little perle.
with finger.
So many people go straight.
really is?
You don’t like to finger.
But gradually.
something a little.
Is it fine? is it fine?
No to no.
Do you give it out twice?
Now after this.
Give it in the game again.
Dangerously
I have eaten.
How about food, rep?
A bit painful?
Full of?
If you are in the next league, it will be bad.
Good was
Not just sweet.
I am worried about health tests.
full of
Suffering very much.
It is hard.
Is it over? is it okay?
OK is
So, I’ll show you the game now, but down has a little bit of preparation, so let’s show you first.
Stay in this state.
Yes, you worry a little, right?
Is it not a very bad situation?
Yes to.
Is it okay?
It is a rule, but you should not use your hands.
Yes to.
Just the mouth.
Oh yeah.
Please go out.
If you want to know your husband, try to know if he is a player.
The Request.
If you are correct, you will be rewarded, if you are wrong, you will be punished.
Oh yeah.
So, I took this sperm and tasted it, but if you don’t think it’s your husband’s, I don’t say challenge, I think you can go to the next fall day.
So, finally, let’s stand up for the camera and look at the moment.
This is my camera.
Yes to.
I was very pleased to hear the plan, I thought it was difficult for our couple, but I will work hard for the trip.
So, I arrived at the venue.
I saw it, now.
No, I am sorry.
You saw a shot, right?
There are signs from both sides.
What is Sign?
Sign of people.
Signs of people.
This sign is.
So please look at it.
It feels like this.
No, it is too much.
Oh yeah.
In my life so far,
How many chicks have you ever been transported at the same time?
It is gradually getting here.
Can I tell you?
How many?
About two books.
Have you heard it now?
by Mr.
Have you heard?
I did not know.
Poorly
from now
Limit time is 30 minutes.
Dance in 30 minutes.
Do not use hands.
Please tell me a last emotion.
I was nervous, it was a strange situation.
A word for Danny.
Make it easy for me.
All the girls, make good.
I will strive.
It seems to be hard.
So let’s go?
So, well, it is a start.
Not at all, sorry really.
How old do you look, how old do you look?
Not a year, probably.
Do you look?
Yes to.
Are you dressed?
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
What should I do?
You should look at it next time.
Oh is?
How many times have you seen the third?
I understand.
Oh is?
Oh this
Very nice cliché.
Wait a little.
I don’t think you look so close.
It has become this.
Probably pretty big.
It was 😂😂
I think it was a bamboo, but I think it was a bamboo.
Something is beautiful.
It must be bright, right?
You are a tequila.
Soon, I have to do it.
It is 30 minutes, right?
You may not see this, this.
Maybe she is the sister of the saint.
What should I do?
You just have to let it out.
This guy is also very good.
It looks like something.
It might look like Danone.
Not to say Tate.
Tate, you can drink it.
I do not know.
It is difficult to speak with your mouth.
I think it is a bangkok.
So much so.
And when did I find Ferrari?
I am scared, there is.
It is awesome, I have grown.
You understand.
He was a big man, right?
and unexpectedly.
I was surprised.
Yes, you do not know.
Yes...
Oh well...
No to...
Oh yeah...
Was it?
was
How was it?
No, I do not know.
No to...
It may taste a bit strong.
A hard?
You just tasted it.
Yes, I think it was a bit more flavorful.
Do not do?
not to
Can I tell someone else?
Okay is.
Thanks to.
still people
What to do.
What was it?
Yes is it.
by 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂
But I feel different.
What to do.
What should I do?
What is the smell.
I do not know.
Sorry about the sixth.
You all get tough.
Great here.
It is quite a hunting character.
I am sure it wasn’t like that.
Over the past year, the hunting has grown.
It is awesome.
appear to move.
Oh well, it is awesome.
You did it.
Did you do it?
It is a good pace.
It is awesome.
The demand.
Oh yeah.
What to do?
Can I try it here once?
If you hit here.
Yes is it.
OK, on the request.
Try using a car chip.
Please write your name.
The Take?
It is a whore.
The Dude?
The beginning.
The beginning is.
It was a crap.
Very difficult, very difficult.
So yes, please go.
The punitive game.
Yes the first time.
Oh oh oh oh!
Yes, what is it?
appearing underwear.
I need questions too.
Well, but I don’t have time.
Certainly not a problem.
Mrs. Tuchel, you will be in your underwear.
Sorry to you, Tate.
Good luck Hino.
I really don’t know if you will try hard.
If you wear it here, it will be okay.
Take it off, it is okay.
Sorry, really
Do you not see it?
I have no time, there.
Oh is?
Are you filming?
I do not see.
Oh yeah yeah?
Is it true?
I will not be fooled, it is.
well is
Forget about it.
Yes, the underwear friends.
It is awesome.
Oh, you are fat.
Okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
It is 11 minutes.
Shit, shit, what do we do?
greatly
He is applying something.
He is applying me.
Maybe the waterfall.
Do not give any hint.
I said it was easy to understand.
Surely is.
Maybe the waterfall.
How about.
Oh is?
I do not know.
Teeth are difficult.
No to
Yes
Oh oh oh oh oh oh.
Oh well! it is great!
Fuck you fuck!
It was amazing, surprised.
It may be different, but it is okay.
I am not surprised! – I am surprised!
Sorry, I think I’m starting to make a picture.
I felt something different.
Only one person does not ask.
You are not, this man.
Oh, but I do not know.
Is it not a moving movement?
Yes is it.
We are not moving either.
I go, now I go.
Yes
If you say you can go to your place.
I say she is 19 years old.
No, no longer, almost no longer.
Sometimes it
No to
Yes
Oh no more.
It looks different, it seems like it, I think.
by
Because cake and cake.
Not a pipe.
The pipeline?
Do you not do something like that?
It is not such an image.
I feel like I was born.
Oh yeah
I have a little more concern for you.
Can I write on the way?
Is it true, Nora, I’m sorry.
I thought different.
What to do.
Something is just moving.
and here?
Where is Mr. Hutchinson?
Mr. Nancy just said.
Mr Nannie, you are
A little bit of Hutchinson.
It is characteristic.
It is Nanoman.
difficulty
No to
Then we will think about what will happen to the Zionist.
This time I can't get the link to the Stronghouse frame, so please look at it.
I found the spaniel.
Can I demand?
So, go to the Zhang’s face and call him his name.
Takedown
I am tired.
He was young.
Maybe it is a cocoa.
Sorry, I am sorry.
Sorry, what can I do?
Wait to.
No, there is a penalty game.
The Rapid Cousin.
and Zena?
No time.
I have no time.
I will finish this lesson, the ninth.
The former boss.
If you did so far.
Oh, and it wasn’t great.
You are dead.
Illuminated
sweetly
The makeup bag is small.
Not once carried.
was early.
Outer is
Oh yeah yeah
and more
It is.
Oh is
by Ba
Oh, so good, I have a rabbit.
It may be different, up.
I just said I was going to go 11 times.
I haven’t done 1, 3, 5 or 5 this month.
You did not have one, you did not have one.
Maybe not one, three or five.
It is until 5.
Wait a little.
Please wait a little.
No, it is already.
No to?
Oh yeah
It may be a little different.
Sorry to
3 minutes can?
Oh yeah
How to do.
This is 3 minutes.
Lying
Oh yeah
How about?
Can I drink the strawberries?
Drink it.
If you get one or three.
difficulty
It is awesome, awesome.
Just another minute.
Oh, it is difficult
Really?
You should have newcomers.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
by
Sorry to
I got broken.
I was surprised.
I can only demand this now.
Just time in time.
This is your last chance.
So this is demand.
Yes is
What is it talking about.
More confidently.
No, I am not honest.
No to?
Please go.
And then, last chance is last chance.
Yes to.
If not this person, this person has to choose the one, the last time.
People who are confident, don’t worry.
Someone with confidence?
Then the 10th.
Number 10 was just removed.
Something, was it so?
Yes, I am out of 10.
Not the number 10.
9 is the first?
Maybe the first.
No. 2 is in Morocco.
I really did not shoot it, I did not shoot it.
I just said I care about it.
But wait.
It is awesome, something is coming out.
Can you taste it? can you taste it?
Is it OK?
Maybe it’s a bit close to taste.
You are the most confident person.
I think it was probably the most understandable.
Try to call me, Tate.
The Take?
It is Hilo.
I am Mr. Hilary, I am sorry.
You are very strongly pressed.
Sorry, sorry for a little.
When it is sensitive.
Why did you shoot?
No, it is a punitive game.
Welcome to Why?
Why Why?
The final penalty game.
Oh, I am worried.
What is it.
Deckard
Or not so?
So much for what?
Wait a little!
I was surprised!
Oh wait to!
Why Why?
I do not know.
I don’t see the Tate, but the Tate is the second.
Tate, I don’t see much.
Sorry about it, Tate.
It is awesome.
Sorry, what do I do about this?
Time for this.
I don’t know, but though.
But but though.
much too much.
Oh oh oh!
Oh yeah
Why, this way.
You are okay.
Why is
Oh yeah