After all, there were no newcomers this year.
In the end, everyone got full tickets.
Well, I did my best to join in.
I'm just watching anime and singing.
Oh, but I'm going to get in trouble if I circle this time.
I wish there were at least one more person.
I wonder if a cute girl will come.
It's called Princess Otasawa.
It's impossible.
More than that, the top of the university.
Superior goods.
I'm in trouble.
It's hard.
Then I'll call the newcomer with full tickets again.
How many people will you bring?
Excuse me.
It's a circle tour.
Is it okay?
Of course.
Sit here.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kagumiya from the International Information Department.
I'm in the aquarium music circle now.
For the time being, I got permission to run the circle.
My favorite works are the door of the second floor and the thousandth burst.
I don't know much about anything else.
The stars and the thousandth.
Both of them have high quality paintings.
It's okay. Our circle welcomes beginners.
Is that so?
I have a question.
I heard that there is an illustrator named Shion in this circle.
It's Takasugi.
I think he'll be here soon.
I'm glad.
I was wondering what to do if I was wrong.
I see.
It's a typical gardener in Kamishima.
I'll forgive you because you're cute.
How was it?
I got 10,000 tickets.
That's right.
Who is she?
She is...
Nice to meet you.
I'm...
You're a newcomer.
Yes.
But I'm here for a tour today.
Nice to meet you.
I was waiting for him, and he came.
He was a very handsome man.
I was surprised because I thought he was a woman.
And he asked me to go to the Dojinshi event.
I'm going to Tsukuba this Saturday.
I can't wait to go with him.
I'm nervous.
What should I wear?
Should I buy a new one?
But I'm always in a pinch.
What should I do?
I'm sorry for talking about myself.
We promised to go to the movies together this Saturday.
I have to apologize.
I'm happy if you're happy.
But I'm worried.
We used to meet every day, but now we can only meet on weekends.
I'll pass the entrance exam next year and go to college with you.
I'm rooting for you.
Let's do our best together.
Are you jealous of me?
I'm your boyfriend.
If you're my boyfriend, I want you to be more confident.
But you're handsome.
I'm afraid you'll fall asleep.
I'm kidding.
I'm sorry.
Don't be angry.
I'm kidding.
I'm not angry.
I didn't mean it.
I don't care.
I'm sorry.
Are you comfortable?
Does it feel good?
Yeah.
Did you have a hard time?
I've been hitting you.
What?
Did I hit you?
Yeah.
Wow.
Does it feel good?
Yeah.
It's sour, isn't it?
It's sour.
Okay.
But let's do it properly.
Let me know if it hurts.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll give you a massage today.
Let me know if it hurts.
Okay.
I'll do my best today.
Look at me.
Wow.
You laughed.
Okay.
Look at me.
I'll do my best today.
It feels good.
Isn't it heavy?
No.
Really?
Does it feel good?
Yeah.
Look at me.
No.
Why are you laughing?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Do you like it?
Yeah.
You like it, don't you?
Are you purring?
Yeah.
Look at me.
It feels good.
No.
You're purring inside.
It feels good.
Can you bear it?
I'll do my best.
Okay.
I'm sweating.
I'm sleepy.
You said you'd do your best today, didn't you?
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're getting better.
I'm sorry.
You said you'd do your best today, didn't you?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
You're purring.
I'm sweating.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
But...
I want you to react a little more when I'm mean to you.
If I'm the only one who gets angry, I'll look like a pervert.
I'll look like a mean girl, won't I?
Yes.
Do you understand?
I'll do my best.
It's hot.
Like me.
Like this?
It's hot.
Yes.
It tickles.
Give me a hug.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I love you.
Do you love me?
Yes.
You're cute.
Over there.
Look at that.
It tickles.
I'm doing my best.
I love you.
It tickles.
I'm glad.
You said you wouldn't do it.
I understand.
I'll do it right away.
I'm sorry.
No.
I'll tickle you.
It tickles.
I'll do it quickly.
Hang in there.
I'll do my best.
No.
Don't do it yet.
I'll do my best.
Hang in there.
It's not enough yet.
Okay.
You'll do your best, right?
I'll do my best.
We'll do our best together.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
It tickles.
You said you wouldn't do it.
Does it tickle?
It tickles.
Senpai.
I'll pass the entrance exam.
Then...
It hurts.
It's okay.
It hurts a lot.
It felt good.
Senpai.
When I go to university,
I want to have a session with you again.
You have a good heart.
But our university is expensive.
Be prepared.
I'll do my best.
I'm looking forward to it.
Good morning.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's amazing.
What is it?
It's a medium-sized event.
Next time,
there will be a bigger event.
I see.
Anyway,
let's have dinner together tonight.
Let's have dinner together tonight.
Okay.
By the way,
do you have a boyfriend?
Yes.
He was a junior at the Aquatic Department.
But now he's in the same university as me.
He's younger than you.
Can I meet him?
Ah...
Ah.
There was something strange about the atmosphere last time.
Yes.
Ah.
I treat him as my little brother.
I wanna reach the tension
between our seniors and juniors.
Well, I think it can't be helped that I'm getting older, but sometimes I want to be spoiled by someone.
Hmm.
But it's a shame.
If Fugumiya-san didn't have a boyfriend, I would have sent it by now.
Let's go to another one.
Yes.
Well, let's have another toast to today's event.
Cheers.
Fugumiya-san.
You brought it home.
Great success.
It's nothing, it's nothing.
I'm talking to you.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Fugumiya-san.
What's wrong? Have you had enough experience?
No.
I'm nervous when I meet you.
You're doing something like cleaning.
Fugumiya-san.
I thought you were a virgin.
No.
What is it?
I'm sure they're disappointed.
Come on.
It's cramped, so let's sleep.
Let's sleep together.
It's huge.
It's big.
Don't do that.
It's hot, isn't it?
You didn't have to do this.
Why do you say such a thing?
You wanted to be spoiled, didn't you?
That's right, but...
I'm sorry.
You wanted to be spoiled, didn't you?
I love you.
What's going on here?
I don't know.
Let me see.
Is it wet?
Did you want me to do this?
No.
It's hot.
I can't do this.
I can't.
I'll make you feel better.
I can't do this.
It's hot.
Have you ever been touched other than your boyfriend?
It's like a new one.
A new one?
What's a new one?
It's nothing.
It's my foot.
I can't do this.
If you can't do it, it's okay.
What's wrong?
I can't do this.
You guys are amazing.
Try it again.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's because it's a new shoe.
I can't do this.
I can feel the right side of your face.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
It's very sensitive.
Come here.
Touch mine.
How is it?
It's hard.
You've never seen anything other than your feet, have you?
That's amazing.
Look at me.
It's amazing.
I can't do that.
There you go.
I'm sorry.
You can lick it as much as you like.
He always licks it like that.
Try licking it like you always do.
Do I?
That's amazing.
That's how you lick it.
Don't do that.
Does it feel good?
That's right.
I'm going to use your big boobs.
I'm going to put them in your mouth.
Do you want me to do that?
That's right.
That's good.
Are you doing this, too?
Are you nervous?
I didn't know you were doing this.
Your boyfriend is a happy man.
How is it?
It's very hard.
It feels good from the bottom to the top.
That's amazing.
Now that you've done this much, you can do it, right?
That's...
Wait a minute.
Please don't deny it.
You don't trust me that much.
It's not that.
I'm worried if I can do a lot now.
So you haven't experienced it yet.
That's...
That's good.
You're just the one who's going to be in the future.
That's how hard it is.
That's good.
Put some rubber on it.
I put it on.
Can I do it?
It's a mess.
I'll do it.
That's amazing.
It feels good.
How is it?
Did you like it?
It hurts.
That's good.
I can easily understand your weakness.
You're twitching.
That's good.
That's amazing.
The wall on your right side feels good.
I'm scared.
That's amazing.
That's good.
I'm scared.
I'll do it.
That's good.
It's my first time doing this.
Look this way.
Did you feel good?
Yes.
Are you filming?
I'm filming.
It's okay.
Really?
Yes.
It's a promise.
Of course.
It's okay.
Do a double kiss.
Did you just take a picture?
You're cute.
I don't want to.
I'm jealous of your boyfriend.
He's so cute.
Is he?
Yes.
I'm jealous of your boyfriend.
It feels good.
Do a peace sign.
Do a peace sign?
Do a peace sign with one hand.
One hand?
Do a face-hiding peace sign.
Like this?
Yes.
Show me something.
Like this?
Yes.
It's too close.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm sorry.
You've been waiting for a long time, haven't you?
No, I haven't.
It's rare for you to be late.
I can't tell you that I've been waiting for a long time.
I'm wearing the same clothes as yesterday, but it doesn't look good on me.
What?
Your neck is red.
No.
Are you worried about me?
I was stung by a bug yesterday.
You have to hurry up or you'll be late.
Okay.
Let's go.
The movie was interesting.
I couldn't remember the content of the movie at all.
But it was amazing.
With Mr. Takasugi yesterday.
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
The movie was interesting.
I couldn't remember the content of the movie at all.
But it was amazing.
The movie was interesting.
Hello.
Mr. Takasugi isn't here yet, is he?
Takasugi and Kaijima have a meeting today.
I see.
Can I read a book while you're waiting?
Sure.
There are a lot of books there.
Thank you.
What should I choose?
Wow.
There are a lot of books I don't know.
What should I choose?
You can take it home.
Can I?
Thank you very much.
The senior I met the other day was strange.
I'll call her.
Hello.
I'm sorry to bother you at this time.
There's something I don't understand.
Can you tell me?
If you can't, it's okay.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Thank you very much.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Your face is red, but are you okay?
I've been working out.
I've been getting fat lately.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I see.
Then this is the problem.
I'm sorry for the sudden call.
Thank you very much.
It's okay.
See you later.
Yes.
I didn't notice you.
This is my shirt.
I heard you're in the hospital.
You look good.
Wait a minute.
I don't think you're fat.
Let's continue what we were doing.
I'm bored while I'm waiting.
But today...
What?
I was thinking about my boyfriend.
Why are you having sex with me?
Stand up.
You can't be satisfied with your boyfriend's sex.
I'm sorry.
What's going on here?
I was just talking to my boyfriend.
You were thinking about me, weren't you?
You have to concentrate on your boyfriend.
Don't say that.
Why are you so wet?
I'm sorry.
What's this?
Let's continue.
Stick out your butt.
You wanted this, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Be honest with me.
Did you get it?
I'm going to put a bandage on you.
I feel sick.
I'm sorry.
Did you do it because you thought Hayashi would find out?
It's here, isn't it?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's easy to understand.
I'll stop it for you.
Gugumiya.
Which one of us is having sex?
You.
Then...
Who's better at kissing?
You.
Does it feel good?
Then...
Who do you like better, me or your boyfriend?
You.
I'm sorry.
I wonder if you'll let me in next time.
Thank you very much.
I'm shaking hands with you.
It's amazing.
I thought about it for a moment.
That's right.
I've been like this lately.
I'm going to be late.
What should I do?
I agree.
It's a waste to go home.
That's right.
Here?
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Are you out of newspapers?
Look.
You have to respond to the customer.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Senpai?
I thought I'd surprise you.
I didn't say anything.
Was it a nuisance?
It's not a nuisance.
It's okay.
You came to see me.
It was just right.
I have a favor to ask you.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to touch me so much.
Why?
I leave the rest to him.
I found it.
What is it?
Sit down.
Are you happy to be here?
But...
You've noticed a few people, haven't you?
Is that so?
I was watching you.
It's strange.
Didn't you notice?
It's not that.
What is it?
You've been out of breath for a while.
You've become sensitive.
That's...
Are you okay?
You're in a mess.
Why?
If you make a loud voice,
People outside will find out.
Hang in there.
If you make a loud voice...
I'm sorry.
You're in a mess.
Hang in there.
I'm sorry.
You...
It's hard to stand up, isn't it?
You're in a mess.
Don't look at me like that.
It's hard to stand up.
It's okay.
I'll make you a reference for my manga.
Are you happy?
You're so kind.
Where do you feel good?
You're twitching, aren't you?
I just put in one.
I can't get it out.
Here?
Here.
What happens if I put in two?
Take a break.
Hang in there.
I'm sorry.
It's a little late, but...
It's okay, isn't it?
I've done it before.
I can't get up anymore.
Thank you very much.
Yes.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
By the way, how about after this?
Let's have tea together.
No.
I have to go home and go to school.
I see.
It's hard.
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
I was surprised that you came so suddenly.
You look like you're serious.
You gave me a piggyback ride.
I feel sorry for my boyfriend.
By the way, Kugumiya.
When are you going to break up with him?
That's...
You should lick it.
As for me, I don't mind if you don't touch me.
Then, can you be serious?
It's hard.
Can I go home?
I don't care about the method.
Hurry up and decide.
I haven't heard from you since that day.
I want to know how you feel.
Hello?
I'm glad you're here.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry I made you worry.
I thought you wouldn't answer the phone.
I'm sorry.
I was busy with the circle activity.
Oh, that's right.
Do you know?
We've decided on the second star jump.
That's great, isn't it?
You've been looking forward to the second one, haven't you?
Hello?
Are you listening?
Huh?
Your voice...
Don't worry about it.
How much better have you gotten in this month?
Your boyfriend wants to see you.
Because...
His...
...feet are not comfortable...
He doesn't peel his skin...
So it's not comfortable...
...isn't it?
Mr. Tsukazugi's...
...shiny part...
...is...
...crumpled...
...and it feels good...
Hey...
Can I go inside today?
Ouch!
So...
We found a way...
...to break up without hurting each other...
Yeah...
If we can't make it clear...
Our relationship ends here...
You're so mean...
I...
For Mr. Tsukazugi's sake...
...could do everything...
...including...
...the hair...
...and the eyes...
...and the face...
...but...
I've been studying...
...so please...
...don't say such mean things...
You're so mean...
I'm surprised...
Ouch!
You're so mean...
I'm so...
...sad...
...and...
...angry...
I just gave you a kiss...
...and you're...
...angry...
I want a kiss...
...because I love...
...this curry...
You're such a pervert...
I don't want it...
Mr. Tsukazugi...
...won't buy it...
I love this curry...
Rin-pon...
...please don't take it away from me...
I want this curry...
...Mr. Tsukazugi...
Okay, Kugamiya-san...
...drink up...
Ah...
Hey...
Do you want more?
Yes, I do...
Ah...
Okay, then...
Yes...
Here...
...please...
Yes...
Mr. Tsukazugi...
Rin-pon...
Mayuri...
...please come here...
Ah...
I love this curry...
I love Mr. Tsukazugi...
Rin-pon...
Ah...
I love it...
Here...
Ah...
Mr. Tsukazugi...
...
I love you.
If you love me so much,
tell me what you love.
Tell me while you are alive.
I love you.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Ah, Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah,
N
I want it.
Where do you want it?
I want it here.
Thank you.
This is...
This is so good.
Thank you.
Thank you
Let me hug you.
Oh no...
Oh no, oh no...
Oh no!
Umehake is on the phone.
Don't make fun of me.
Go away.
Just go away.
I'm sorry.
You're the only one who feels better.
Come here.
I love you.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to cry.
I'm going to do my best for you.
I love you.
Come here.
I'm sorry.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to cry.
I love you.
What should I do with you?
What should I do?
I cant breath
Is it painful?
Do it a little bit more
Confirmation. Confirmation.
Please confirm.
Confirmation of the spear.
I'm sorry.
I was too careful.
I think you're already dead.
I'm sorry.
Good boy.
Do you like it?
Yes, I like it.
I like it.
I'm sorry.
You were crying too much.
I like it.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
Good boy.
I'm so happy.
I'm sorry.
Help me.
Thank you.
Mayuri.
You said you'd listen to me.
Let's take a picture.
What's wrong with you?
Stop it.
It's funny.
Look at me.
Don't hide your boobs.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'll water you.
You're cute.
Show me your boobs.
You like me, don't you?
Do it.
That's good.
I don't like it.
Open your boobs.
I can't see it well.
Peace.
Look at me.
Yes.
What should I do?
How was it?
It felt good.
What do you want me to do after this?
I want you to be a good girl.
You said you'd do anything because you like me, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Pose while peeing.
Pose while peeing?
You can do it, right?
Can I do it here?
I'll do it.
I don't want to do it anymore.
Don't do it on the bed.
My boobs are wet.
It's close.
It's embarrassing.