It's been six months since I joined this underwear manufacturer, and I'm finally getting used to my job.
And today, I'm going on a business trip with my boss in Okinawa.
It's my first business trip, and I'm going to work with my boss, Mr. Narasu, who I admire.
I'll do my best not to mess up.
It's unexpected, but I wonder if I can eat a little Okinawan food.
There's nothing coming.
Thank you for your time today.
As expected, the manufacturers of Tokyo-do are different.
You're doing a good job.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm very happy to be able to go to Okinawa for the first time.
I heard you're going home today.
That's right.
You should take your time.
I'll come back to play again in private.
You're busy.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.
It means thank you in Okinawan.
That's right.
I was surprised.
It's hot.
It's still hot.
It's a record-breaking day.
Is that so?
I'm glad I did a good job on my business trip.
It's great to drink beer like this.
Hashimoto, you always make mistakes.
You forget the documents.
You made a mistake in the flight time and couldn't get on the plane.
You should do it properly.
I'm sorry.
But thanks to you, I managed to do it.
It's not that you managed to do it.
You're really good at it.
Yes.
Is the flight time all right?
Yes, it's all right.
As you said, I put it in the app.
So, the flight time is all right.
Are you making a mistake again?
I think so.
It's all right.
Let me see.
Yes.
It's all right because of the malfunction of the electrical circuit.
Does that mean the plane won't fly?
I think so.
I'll contact the manager.
Yes.
Hello.
Did you hear the news?
I think so.
Yes.
I'm looking for a hotel here.
I'll stay overnight and go home.
Yes.
I'll come back early tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I'm looking for a hotel here.
I'm looking for a hotel to stay tonight.
Are you going to stay overnight?
I'm glad.
Why are you happy?
I have to think about what to wear.
I have to contact my boyfriend.
Yes.
I'll leave it to you.
Leave it to me.
Look for it.
Yes.
Hello, Takuya.
Hello.
What's wrong?
The plane broke down.
I can't fly anymore.
I'm stuck here.
Are you all right?
Yes.
It's a record malfunction.
I've been waiting for you.
Is your boyfriend with you?
Yes.
I can't rely on him, but I'm doing my best.
I see.
Be careful not to get a heat stroke.
Thank you.
Let me know if you find a hotel.
Okay.
See you.
I'm looking forward to the souvenir.
Okay.
Buy a good one and go home.
Thank you.
See you.
Be careful.
Okay.
I found a hotel.
Really?
Thank you.
I couldn't find it.
I managed to get one.
But...
But what?
The air conditioner is broken.
What?
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
It's broken.
Let's have a drink.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Two beers.
And a goya-champuru.
Okay.
It's good.
Beer is good because it's hot.
Thank you.
Hashimoto-kun.
What do you mean by one room?
I'm sorry.
I thought it was a double room.
What?
You didn't know that?
I'm sorry.
I'll look for it now.
The person in front of me said that.
It's not open unless you make a reservation this season.
Yes.
I don't want to stay in this room.
But it's hot.
Yes.
It's hot because the air conditioner is broken.
It's hot.
I want to change my clothes.
Hashimoto-kun.
Bring me a bathrobe.
Okay.
It's hot.
Thank you.
I'll change my clothes.
Okay.
It's hot.
I sweat a lot.
It's hot today.
It's hot because the air conditioner is broken.
Yes.
It's hot.
I'm ready.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
You sweat a lot.
Did you change your clothes?
I'm fine.
Really?
Yes.
It's hot.
What are you doing?
Sit down.
Okay.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No, I don't.
What?
Do you have a girlfriend now?
Or have you had a girlfriend for a long time?
I haven't had a girlfriend for a long time.
What?
Is it your first time to have a girlfriend?
Yes.
What?
What's that?
Well...
Do you care about her?
No, I don't.
You've been looking at her for a long time.
No, I haven't.
Are you a virgin?
No, I'm not.
You're cute.
What?
Look at me.
Please don't.
I want you to look at me now.
No, I'm fine.
You're cute.
Look at me.
No, I'm not.
Don't look at me.
Senpai.
Please don't get dry.
What's wrong with you?
I'm getting dry.
Calm down.
Ajimoto.
Don't do that.
I'm getting dry.
I'm sorry.
I teased you too much.
Ajimoto.
I'm kidding.
I have a boyfriend.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
I teased you too much.
I was just kidding.
I'm sorry.
I teased you too much.
Hey.
Yes?
I have a boyfriend.
I can't tell you everything.
Can I tell you a little bit?
A little bit?
Senpai.
Just a little bit.
Just a little bit?
You've never done it, have you?
No.
You've grown up so much.
It's a little embarrassing.
It's because I teased you, isn't it?
No, but...
I'll take it first.
I'll give it to you.
I can't do that.
I'll give it to you as an apology for teasing you.
Senpai.
Have you ever kissed me?
No, I haven't.
Then I'll tell you.
Let me see.
I'm sorry.
You've grown up.
Just a little bit.
Open your mouth.
Okay.
Let me see your tongue.
Let me see.
I'm sorry.
You're sweating a lot.
I can't stand it.
You don't like it?
No, but...
It's embarrassing.
Let me see.
You can touch here, too.
Senpai.
What?
You have to tell me.
You have to tell me...
how to make Hashimoto...
explain his underwear...
at the next store.
Okay.
You have to tell me...
how to make him embarrassed.
Okay.
You're amazing.
You're so soft.
It's your first time. You're cute.
It feels good.
I'm not good at it.
Touch me gently.
Okay.
Don't be rough.
I'm sorry.
Is it okay?
Here?
Yes, like this.
Touch me gently.
Okay.
You're amazing.
I didn't know you were so good at it.
Is it enough?
Yes.
But...
Is it okay?
What do you want to do?
What?
I want to see it.
Okay.
Take off the hook.
Can you do it?
Well...
It's hard.
You're a underwear maker.
You have to take it off.
I always take it off.
But...
I'm nervous.
Do your best.
Did you take it off?
Yes.
You can do it.
It's beautiful.
Is it?
Yes.
Don't just look at me.
Touch me like this.
Okay.
It's warm.
Like this?
Yes.
Touch me gently.
Okay.
You're amazing.
Make me feel sexy.
I've never done it before.
I don't know how to do it.
What's this?
Like this?
Yes.
Does it hurt?
It feels good.
Really?
It's warm.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
What?
Do you want to make me naked?
No.
I've never seen you naked.
If I don't take it off now, I'll be a virgin forever.
It's okay.
You're a man.
You're getting bigger.
Yes.
I'm embarrassed.
Why are you embarrassed?
I've never been naked.
I don't want to be a virgin.
You might be a virgin today.
I'm embarrassed.
Do I have to take it off?
You have to take it off.
Okay.
I made you so big.
I have to take responsibility for you.
Wait a minute.
I'm embarrassed.
Why are you embarrassed?
Wait a minute.
I'm embarrassed.
Does it feel good?
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
Does it hurt?
It's too hot.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
Yes.
It feels good.
You're sweating a lot, aren't you?
I was sweating a lot.
Are you serious?
Yes.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
Is it warm?
Yes, it's warm.
You're sweating a lot.
It feels good.
Yes.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's hot.
Where does it feel good?
There.
It feels good.
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
It feels good.
No.
No?
It's hot.
It's sensitive.
It's sensitive?
You're sweating a lot.
Yes.
It feels good.
You're sweating a lot.
What?
It's hot.
It feels good.
You're sweating a lot.
Yes.
It's hot.
What?
It's too hot.
It's hot.
Your legs are moving.
My legs are moving.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You're sweating.
It's hot.
I'm sweating, too.
I'm sweating.
It's hot.
Did you sweat?
Yes.
I couldn't help it.
Did you feel refreshed?
Yes.
It's hot.
You're sweating.
I'll get a tissue.
It's hot.
Did you sweat a lot?
Yes.
I'm sweating.
I'll take a shower.
Senpai.
What?
What's wrong?
I can't do it yet.
You can't do it.
Please.
I can't do it.
You're not wearing a rubber band.
You just took it off.
I can't do this.
I don't want to stop you.
Senpai.
I have a boyfriend.
You can't do it.
Hey, Nama.
I don't want you to take the band-aid off.
Please.
It's hot.
Calm down.
You can't do it.
No, don't do that.
Hinochi...
Wait a minute.
No, don't do that.
Calm down.
Wait a minute.
Really...
Look at me.
What?
Are you a man?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't help it.
Did you make up with her?
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Don't make up with her.
I have a boyfriend.
It's a safe day.
Really.
One more time.
No, don't do that.
Calm down.
Listen to me.
I'll tell you.
Calm down.
Don't be so rough.
It's not good.
I'm sorry.
I'll put it in.
Okay.
If a girl doesn't wet her pants, it's not good.
Touch here.
Okay.
Your feet are wet.
What is this?
This is the clitoris.
This is the pancreas.
Okay.
Do you understand?
What should I do?
This is the clitoris.
Like this.
Touch it gently.
It feels good.
My feet are wet.
Half of your feet are wet.
Okay.
Here?
It feels good.
Okay.
If you touch here, your feet will get wet.
I see.
And...
Touch here.
Here?
It's hot.
Is it warm?
It's warm.
It's amazing.
Touch here.
Does it hurt?
It feels good.
Okay.
How do you feel?
You're very good.
I'm sleepy.
Because you were crying.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Your feet are wet.
It's wet.
Do you want me to massage your feet again?
Yes.
Do you want to?
Yes, I do.
Okay.
I'll teach you how to massage.
This is your pelvis.
Massage it slowly.
Okay.
Here?
Slowly.
Okay.
A little lower.
Here?
Yes.
Massage it slowly.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's wet.
I'll do it here.
You're very good.
Does it feel good?
Here?
Yes, massage it slowly.
Massage it deeper.
Deeper?
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
It feels good.
It's warm.
Is it warm?
Yes, it's warm.
It's hot, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
It's okay.
It's difficult.
Is it here?
Yes, it is.
Do your best.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
Yes, yes.
Try to move as you like.
Okay.
It's slimy.
Yes, it is.
Next, I'll massage here.
Here?
Yes, it feels good.
My neck is getting longer.
It's getting longer.
Oh, no.
My neck is getting longer.
Here?
Yes, it is.
It feels good.
It's getting better.
It's difficult.
Is it?
It feels good.
Yes, it is.
Try to move faster.
Here?
Do your best.
Yes, it is.
It's slimy.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
It doesn't feel good at all.
Oh, no.
Hold my legs.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Give me a kiss.
Okay.
Can you move as I kiss you?
Yes, I can.
It's slimy.
Give me a kiss.
Oh, no.
Move your legs as I do.
It feels good.
Stretch your arms.
Does it feel good?
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Does it?
Yes.
Oh, no.
Do you feel ticklish?
Yes, I do.
No, I don't.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
It feels good.
Oh, no.
You have a hard neck.
It feels good.
Does it?
Yes.
You're a virgin.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Do you feel ticklish?
Yes.
Move your legs.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's too ticklish.
Oh, no.
Do you feel ticklish?
It feels good.
Yes, I do.
Move your legs.
Do you feel ticklish?
It feels good.
It's good if you feel ticklish a lot.
Oh, no.
Do you feel ticklish?
Yes, it feels good.
Oh, no.
It's getting bigger.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Stay like this from behind.
From behind?
Oh, yes.
You can do it.
I'll do my best.
I can see your buttocks.
Put your hands in here.
Can you see it?
Here?
Yes.
A little more.
It's in.
Like this.
It feels good.
Your buttocks are hard and it feels good.
Shimota, move.
Hold your hips like this.
Oh, no.
Move more like this.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
You're doing great.
There.
Oh, no.
Move more.
More?
More.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
Oh, no.
It feels good there.
There?
There.
Shimota, does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
Oh, no.
More.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
What's wrong again?
Oh, no.
You want to go outside this time, don't you?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
Oh, no.
Did you go out a lot?
Yes.
You must be tired.
Do you want to take a shower?
Yes.
Let's take a shower.
Oh, no.
Get ready to take a bath.
What do you want?
You want to take a bath?
Yes.
I'm not good at it, but I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
My husband is unusually quiet today.
Very good.
Is it good?
Yes
It's good
What's that?
It feels good
Is it good?
Yes
Wow
It's amazing
It feels good
Hashimoto-kun is amazing
Yes
My boyfriend
It's over in one go
Is that so?
It's over
Wow
It feels good
Does it feel good?
Yes
It feels good
I am going to stand up
To stand up
Is it over in one go?
Yes
What is that?
What?
It's good
Ah, somewhere
Sensei
Mm
Incredible
Hmm
Where are you licking?
Ah...
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it feels good.
Ah...
Mmm...
It feels good.
Ah...
Mmm...
It feels good.
Ah...
Mmm...
I'm going to lick you a lot again.
Okay.
It's hot.
There, too.
There, too?
Yes, there, too.
It's weak there.
I'm going to lick you a lot again.
Okay.
It's 1.
Yes.
I'm going to lick you a lot again.
Okay.
It's hot.
I'm going to lick you a lot again.
Please.
You're amazing.
It's hot.
Thank you.
Do you want to lick me again?
Yes.
Put your hand in here.
It's hard.
It's hot.
It feels so good.
I put out a lot, but it's still hard.
It's hot.
Do you want to lick me again?
You can put out as much as you want.
Can I?
Yes, you can.
It's hot.
It's hard.
I put out a lot.
You're amazing.
It's hot.
Yes, it's hot.
You're sweating, so I changed my clothes.
What?
Do you want to see?
Yes.
Ta-da.
You're amazing.
Does it look good on me?
Yes, it looks good on you.
I tried on the underwear.
You're amazing.
Do you want to see?
It looks good on you.
Yes.
I got a call from my boyfriend.
Hello.
Hello, what's up?
Did you get to the hotel?
Yes, I did.
I just got there.
I was worried because you didn't call me.
I'm sorry.
I was in a hurry.
I heard it on the news that it was very hot.
I took a bath several times, but I was sweating.
That's terrible.
Did you check the air conditioner in the hotel?
The air conditioner was broken.
Was it broken?
Yes, it was broken.
The air conditioner was broken?
Yes.
That's terrible.
It was very hot.
Is the room of your subordinate broken, too?
My subordinate's room is broken, too.
Is the room of your subordinate's room broken, too?
Yes, it was broken because it was hot.
What's wrong?
It was hot.
Did you say something erotic?
No, I didn't.
Really?
Yes.
I'm tired.
Are you hiding something?
Yes.
I'm not hiding anything.
I heard a loud noise. Are you all right?
I'm fine.
A cleaner came to my room.
Did he come to your room?
Yes.
He came to my room.
Isn't it strange?
Did he knock on your door?
He knocked on my door a while ago and came to my room.
He's cleaning around here.
I see.
Did he come to your room?
Yes, he came to my room.
I see.
Yes.
Did he clean around here?
Did he make a mess?
No, he didn't.
He said he couldn't clean because he took my room suddenly.
What does that mean?
I've never heard of it on TV.
It's a strange hotel, isn't it?
I see.
Is your room spacious?
My room is normal. It's not that spacious.
I see.
Did your subordinate go home after eating?
Yes. My subordinate seems to be sleeping because he's tired.
I see.
I was worried that your subordinate would make a mess.
That's not true. He's unreliable.
He's unreliable?
Yes.
Does he make a lot of mistakes?
Yes, he makes a lot of mistakes.
He doesn't teach me at all.
I don't remember much.
I see.
He's good at teaching you, isn't he?
He doesn't seem to be good at it.
But I think he's getting better recently.
I see.
He's a nice guy, so he must be fascinated by you.
No, he's not.
You seem to be in a hurry.
Am I?
Yes.
I'm not in a hurry.
Really?
It's amazing.
There's a sound.
Really?
Is that so?
Maybe it's because the air conditioner is broken.
Really?
I see.
What?
Did you say something?
No, I didn't say anything.
Really?
I thought you were hiding something.
I wouldn't do that on the phone.
Really?
It's true.
If I did that, he would find out.
He would find out?
Yes.
If I did that on the phone, he would find out.
I can see that from you.
Really?
Do I look like that?
No, I don't think so.
Do you drink alcohol?
Yes, I do.
If you drink alcohol, you become sexy, don't you?
No, I don't.
I'm alone in my room.
You have a cleaner, don't you?
Yes.
Tell him you love him so that he can hear you.
So that he can hear me?
Tell him you love him.
I love him.
He can't hear you.
He can hear me.
Tell him you love him.
I love him.
Can you hear me?
I think he's looking at me.
Really?
I think so.
Did you get a plane ticket this morning?
Yes, I did.
I see.
I'll give you a souvenir.
I'll give you a venison tart.
Is a venison tart enough?
No, it's not.
What about Yukishio Chinsuko?
I don't need it.
You can eat it with shikuwasa.
Shikuwasa is a kind of ginger.
I'll give you a venison tart.
Is it chili pepper?
Yes, it's a kind of chili pepper.
I don't know it.
It's like chili oil.
I'll buy it.
It's a kind of chili pepper.
Is that a voice?
It's a voice of a man.
A voice of a man?
Is there a ghost here?
I don't know.
Is that a ghost?
I don't want to say anything.
I'm scared.
Don't say scary things.
I'll go to bed.
Don't go to bed.
I'm scared.
Who do you like?
Tell me who you like.
I love you.
Are you going to have a good dream?
I'll go to see you in my dream.
I'm glad.
What's wrong?
Do you have a cough?
I didn't do anything.
Really?
Be careful.
I'll be careful.
It may be a haunted house.
Do you hear something like a cough?
I didn't do anything.
People around here left.
Really?
Be careful.
I'll be careful.
Good night.
See you.
Why did you do that?
I wanted to do something like this.
You were about to be found out.
I was excited.
I love you.
Do you like it?
Good.
It's so hot these days.
Yes, it is.
I'm about to throw up.
Do you want to throw up?
Yes.
It's hot.
It's a talent to be able to spit out so much.
It felt good just now.
It's hot.
Do you want me to stop?
Yes.
Don't you feel good?
I feel good.
It's hot.
Do you like it?
Yes.
It's hot.
I can't.
No?
No.
Then, do you want to end it?
No, I don't want to.
Then, what do you want to do?
Well...
I want to go to bed.
You want to go to bed?
Yes.
Then, I'll go to bed.
You don't have to go to bed.
You haven't gone to bed yet.
It feels good.
Yes.
Do you want to end it?
It feels good. Do you want to end it?
Yes.
I want to go to bed.
Do you want to go to bed?
Yes.
Where do you want to go to bed?
I want to go to bed.
Then, I'll go to bed.
Yes.
It feels good.
You have a lot of hair, but it's still dry.
Does it feel good?
Kotaro, does it feel good?
Yes.
Can I make a lot of dumplings today?
This?
Yes.
Is it good?
It's hot.
Yes.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Yes.
How about here?
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
You shouldn't hold it in.
What is it?
You have a lot of hair.
Can you see it?
It feels good.
Look at my belly.
You have a lot of hair.
I can see it.
It feels good.
It tickles.
Touch my belly.
It feels good.
It tickles.
What is it?
Don't go yet.
It feels good.
It tickles.
It's wet.
I'll dry it.
It feels good.
It tickles.
I'll dry it again.
A little more.
It's not working.
Put your hand in here.
There.
Ah!
It's so slimy that it's in there.
It's so slimy.
Ah! It's in there!
Ah! It feels so good in there!
It feels so good.
Ah! It's in there!
It's in there!
Ah! It feels so good!
Ah! It feels so good in there!
Ah! It's in there!
A bit more.
Ah! It feels so good in there!
I can't take it anymore.
I can't do it anymore.
I want to go there, too.
It hurts.
Ouchhh!!!
I can't breathe...
You're right.
You're sweating a lot.
It feels so good.
You're right.
Why are you sweating so much?
Really?
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's hot, isn't it?
I can still do it.
You can do it?
You can only do it once.
It's the best.
Let's do it again.
Do you want to do it again?
Let me do it.
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Do you want to do it again?
Does it feel good?
I can't stop sweating.
Do you want to do it again?
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
Do you want to do it again?
Hang in there.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
Hang in there.
Do you want to do it again?
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Do you want to do it again?
Hang in there.
It's hot.
It's none of your business.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
I'm full.
Oh, my God.
It's amazing, isn't it?
What's amazing?
It's still itchy.
You're sweating a lot.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Your face is salty.
It tickles a little.
Does it tickle?
You said it felt good.
Something's coming out.
You're sweating a lot.
Does it tickle?
It tickles.
Really?
Do you want me to give you a lot more?
I'd love to.
Really?
Yes.
Can I lie down?
It's amazing.
You're sweating a lot.
It tickles.
Does it tickle?
Do you want me to give you a lot more?
Yes.
It tickles.
Does it tickle?
Did it tickle?
It tickles.
Does it tickle?
You're sweating a lot.
It tickles.
Does it tickle?
You're sweating a lot.
It tickles.
Does it tickle?
Do you want me to give you a lot more?
It tickles.
Does it tickle?
I told you to eat a lot.
I can't.
You can eat a lot.
It's the best to eat with hands.
Do you want me to give you a lot more?
It tickles.
It's good, isn't it?
Can I have some more?
Yes, please.
I'm hungry.
What should I do?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
It's time for the check-out.
One more time.
One more time before I leave.
It's time.
One more time.
If you can't do it, I'll do it.
Please.
I can't do it.
It's the worst.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
You're getting bigger.
I'm getting bigger.
Does it feel good?
If you do this, I can't do it.
I'll do it.
I love you.
Hurry up.
What's wrong?
It feels good.
A little more.
It's hot.
That's it.
Good.
I want to sleep with you.
Me, too.
It feels good.
I want to sleep with you.
What's wrong?
Good night.
Here you go.
I'm going to pour some tea.
Here it is.
Take a deep breath.
Oh...
It's hot.
Are you soaked?
It's delicious.
My back is burning.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
It feels good.
Open your mouth.
You're sweating a lot.
It's hot.
Awesome.
I love you.
You love me?
Nami?
Did I do a good job?
I'm okay, mom.
I'm okay!
Mom, help me...
I can try!
Mom...
I'm okay!
I'm going to cry.
I feel good.
I told you not to go yet.
I'm not ready yet.
Let's do it again.
I don't have much time.
I want to do it again.
I feel good.
I'm going to cry.
Wake up!
It hurts!
We have to get out of here!
Go! Go!
Don't sleep!
I can't do it anymore.
I feel sick.
It's cold.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sick.
I'm sorry.
It hurts again.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Let's do it again.
Why are you doing that?
I can't do this anymore.
Ah, it feels so good.
I'm so sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
Ah, it feels so good.
It feels so good.
That's too much.
But it feels good.
You have a big belly like this.
Did you make a belly ruff?
Do you feel better?
It's hot.
Why are you so hot?
I'll do it again.
I'm a senpai.
It's hot.
I'm going home.
Can I do it one more time?
But I'm a woman.
You're a woman.
I can't do it.
It was the best.
I want to do it again.
I'm sorry.
I'm going home.
No.
I'll be late for school.
Let's take a shower.
It's hot.
No.
I'm going home.
It's hot.
This is the end of the best trip.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel.