Good luck and tired.
Are you used to being a professional player and the team?
Yes, I’m used to being kind to the team.
I am the coach of my company’s ballet team.
This year, the team was a new member of our team, a new person.
Coach, I want to work hard, so please give me a more stringent instruction.
Yes, but I still have a lot of time as a coach.
Their work is hard for both, but keep it hard.
Yes, I will try hard.
The weather agency said that the influence of heavy rains has caused Tokyo to experience very intense concentration rains, which currently record 200 millimeters of observation constant outbursts per hour.
The Dohor is calling for alert to earthquake disasters, floods, river water and floods.
Traffic is also being disrupted, and railways have announced the suspension of some routes.
The heavy rain will continue until tomorrow morning.
It is raining very much, I am sorry.
Sorry I'm going home, but good luck.
Be careful with the rain.
I tired of saying goodbye.
Sorry I was late to help.
No problem, I am a new man.
And the Lord has a job of knowing.
I’m not used to Jim’s work, but I’m a new coach.
Sorry to
I’ll try to do it both, sorry.
The railway lines, including the central railway, are operating on the front lines.
Metro all lines are also announcing vacation in the whole city, and the bus companies in the city are also driving.
Traffic is paralyzed throughout the city.
It’s really down, really down.
I don’t bring you the wind today, I too.
I will look a little.
Okay, let’s try hard.
It is a great rain.
Oh, if if
It’s raining, so come home soon.
Yes, I know
But today, my work is not over.
If you go home sooner, the train will stop.
Yes, you know
Maybe I won’t go home today.
Where do you stay? there is no money.
I know, I won’t stay at a hotel.
Maybe I will stay at the company.
Yes, I still have work to do, so I cut it off.
Yes, then then
Oh yeah, it is finally over.
Oh yeah
It was a huge rain outside.
Coach, it is over.
Really did it.
It seemed like the train stopped in the rain.
Do you? – Yes
I don’t have money at the end of the month, so I can’t stay at a hotel.
And you won’t be lying here.
What to do.
Would you stay at home? it is nearby.
Oh is?
It will be wet, but if it were us, it would run.
But sorry.
Don’t worry, it’s because of me that I’m so late.
It is a great rain.
It was a great rain.
I have glasses and a bitch.
Oh, it has become cold.
Is it cold?
It is a little cold.
I will take the towel.
I am a bit troubled.
You have a wife.
What if I had no wife?
Okay is.
I had sex with my wife all the time.
I thought she was so cute since the time she came in.
I understand.
Let me care about it.
I will make her face fermented.
Isn’t she a wife at all?
No, not all the time.
Do not tell this to everyone.
I know.
Keep your hands clean, so be patient.
Feel more well.
be hard.
Is this?
is good.
and kiss.
hardly
Drop your head.
Be careful of the big ones first.
Feels good?
It feels good.
No to No.
I will clear it once.
Then more.
Take it out.
Use both hands.
It feels good.
Feels good?
Can I do this? here.
You are very good.
You can get out.
Amelia, can you put it on your mouth?
What is your mouth?
Please please
He is a job, please.
If it is said.
Okay then?
So call them not Amelia, but Hibiki.
Yes is
Sounds like you’ll speak in your mouth?
Sounds like, you are very good.
It is difficult, so don’t say that.
Continue to.
Can I sleep?
It feels good.
Yes to?
Soooo...
Oh...
Sky is...
Oh well...
Just now...
Oh, I go...
Oh yeah...
Oh well...
Yes...
Have you cleared up?
Now you can sleep.
Open it!
Did you get out?
Very beautiful.
very beautifully
beautiful breast
is best.
Not there.
Very very wet.
I was angry a lot.
OK is OK.
Turn backwards.
Shamefully
Your ass is beautiful.
Show me well.
Very very clean.
I am ashamed.
Finger is good?
Feel good
not live.
Maybe I can beat.
Okay this?
Can I enter?
Feel good
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I was no longer shy, I was not.
Same as me.
It feels good.
This time I followed him from behind.
Can you do this?
It is okay, I must be born.
No, it feels bad.
It hurts and hurts.
Then the pulse.
Feel badly.
The phone is ringing.
Isn’t it from your wife?
No, it is okay.
It still rings.
Okay, let me relax.
Should I not call?
My friends, BE
Dirty is
I said
I am I, I am I, I am I.
I was barking.
It felt good.
So I’ll go shower.
Sorry to
Not all you have done now.
No, it is getting better.
Oh, oh oh oh...
It is growing.
What about gum?
OK is.
Oh yeah
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh!
Oh, but not become.
Oh, oh oh oh...
Put it out here.
No to
Oh yeah yeah
by
Oh is
by Fee
How was Black?
It felt good.
Very very sexy.
So, look at it, don’t look too much.
You are cute.
Shamefully
The skin is beautiful too.
Do you already feel it?
Just got a bath.
It is already hard.
It sounds like a big taboo.
It is already wet.
Just got a bath.
Cut off the knife.
difficult to
Because very cute.
Really
by Home
I also hit.
Very good feeling.
Feel good
Feels good here?
I want to tie it in the breasts.
here here
Are you playing with my breasts?
Because it feels good.
If you like it so much, I’ll give it more.
Be on the floor.
Very good feeling.
Feel good
My breasts are packed.
Do you feel good?
It feels good.
Relaxed
Feel good
It has become hard.
Very well?
well is
It feels good.
Oh go go go.
This was good.
here here
Sorry, it is dirty.
I slept a lot.
Because I did not do it at all.
Still hard
You don’t have to wear rubber.
I already used a condom.
Out the back.
Try to spread it with both hands.
Shamefully
Very beautiful.
Feel good
is beautiful?
Is it better to live?
Yes, it feels very good.
Soon and fast.
Show me open.
Oh well, it feels good.
It feels good.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
Feels good.
Feel good
Without knowing
Feel badly
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
I am not tired, I feel good.
Feel good
Something, something
I did.
It hurt.
Not good?
It feels.
Is your hair good?
Grandpa, I am not visible.
is true.
A healthy breast.
Very very large.
Can I become this?
Feel badly.
by
Oh, he’ll be gone.
No to no.
No, all the way.
No to
Have you gone all the way?
I went away.
I said you shouldn’t go inside.
Sorry to sorry.
Today is a safe day, so it’s okay.
I was in a hurry.
It felt great inside.
It felt good.
really is?
We might be comparable.
Because he sounds athletic.
You have very physical strength.
My wife is soon tired.
So the shrimp.
So good to.
Are you joking?
No, it is not so.
It is true.
I will make something.
Yes
If if
It’s also raining, right?
It’s raining, the train stopped and I can’t go home.
Yes yes yes
No money to stay at the hotel at the end of the month.
Is the rain okay?
Yes is.
Yes
No, yes
Be careful.
Oh is?
Yes
No, it is nothing.
No is
Is it rain?
It sounds like a great rain.
Yes
Oh no longer
Something is very tired.
Yes
Then wear it.
Good night.
by Kira
I will suspect.
Oh, she is standing up again.
Stand up.
Can I enter?
by Kira
The food is cold.
Let me let you eat.
is delicious?
Tastefully
The cooking of the caterpillar is very delicious.
Being a boyfriend is great.
There is no such person.
But your wife is good at cooking, right?
No, it is entirely.
The cooking of the caterpillar is more delicious.
is noisy
here here
Are you going to sleep?
I will exercise tomorrow morning.
Let us sleep.
by
A little
I could drink something and I liked it.
I think it’s fun to get up several times.
Lick me too.
Lick it.
Do you think it is getting tough?
I like this.
It feels good.
This is a good thing, your wife will be gone.
Not forever slow.
Have you not just cracked? Sorry to.
Because he is standing.
Is he up in the morning?
Why are you angry?
This is the day class.
I get sick every morning before training.
Yes, so I will help you.
Here and chut.
I can sleep again, so I can sleep again.
Feel good
Very good feeling.
Feels good?
Feel good
Do you want to have your breasts again?
Very good feeling.
How about this?
Even if you sleep.
Feel good
The cold fire.
Let wait.
Yes
Can I ride up?
OK is.
Oh is
Feel good
Sirily is
It feels good.
hurt is hurt.
Feel good
Come here.
hurtly
Put it inside.
Get out.
Put something out.
You did it again.
This is OK.
I will also go to the practice of biscuit today.
I am a crapper, be kind today.
I know, so I go out first.
So I will be late.
Six months later, I divorced my wife.
I have to retire from Valerie.
I got a baby.