The next day
No, Master.
You can't do that.
Master, you can't do that.
Master.
I'm so surprised.
You can't do that.
I'm scared.
Are you feeling better?
I'm just worried about you.
You have to be careful.
I'm nervous.
You can't do that.
I'll help you.
I can't do that.
Oh, my God.
You can't do that.
Are you okay?
I feel good.
I can't do that.
The next day
I'll take care of you from today.
My name is Rio Murukawa, and I'm a maid.
I'll do my best to take care of you.
Thank you.
If you don't mind,
I'll do everything.
Take your time.
Okay.
You look like you're getting older.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you.
I'll clean your shoes.
I'm sorry for being dirty.
No, it's okay.
You look like a dog.
What do you mean?
Your feet are dirty.
I see.
I read this book, too.
Did you?
Yes.
It's interesting, isn't it?
It's our hobby.
Your hobby?
Yes.
Master.
What?
There is a string here.
Thank you.
I'll put it on your shoes.
It's important that you breath calmly because the breath you are taking is hard.
Master.
What's wrong? Do you want me to wash your hands?
Oh, yes.
I've already cleaned it, so please use it.
Oh, thank you.
Can I use it?
Yes.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm going out.
I'm sorry.
You have something on your face.
I'm sorry. It's a little hard to remove, isn't it?
I'll fix it because it's stuck.
Oh, yes.
I'm sorry. It's a little difficult.
But it's just tangled.
Master, don't look at me with such a sexy look.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Did I look sexy?
I have to clean the room before my husband comes back.
I'm home.
Oh, welcome home, master.
I'm still cleaning, so please sit down and wait.
Oh, yes.
Was it hot today?
It was hot.
Then please drink a lot of water and wash your face.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, it's a tea bag.
It's dusty.
Oh, I'm sorry. I've been busy lately.
I've cleaned your face.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, it's a tea bag.
It's a tea bag.
Oh, it's a hose.
You didn't clean at all, did you?
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's dusty.
Oh, it's dusty.
Oh, it's done.
Master?
What are you doing?
Did you go out?
Master?
No, you can't.
The tea bag is...
You can't do that.
I can't stand it anymore.
No, you can't.
Please go out.
Master?
No, I can't.
No, you can't.
I can't stand it anymore.
Please go out.
Master?
No, you can't.
You can't.
Master?
No, you can't.
Just a little.
Master?
Please go out.
Just a little.
Master?
No, you can't.
No, I can't stand it anymore.
I got hit in the butt.
You didn't get hit in the butt.
No, I didn't.
Why?
I get excited when I see this.
No, you can't.
Are you okay?
Just a little.
No, you can't.
I can't stand it anymore.
Master?
You can't lick the dirty place.
No, you can't.
Let me lick more.
Oh, great.
No, you can't.
You can't lick this place.
It's dirty.
No, you can't.
What are you doing?
I was looking at your beautiful butt.
No, you can't.
I can't stand it anymore.
Oh, great.
No, you can't.
Master?
Do you want me to calm down?
I'm calm.
Just a little bit.
I can't stand it anymore.
Please calm down.
I'm calm.
Oh, great.
Master?
What are you doing?
Just a little bit.
Oh, great.
What are you doing?
Just a little bit.
Master?
No, you can't.
Just a little bit.
Oh, great.
I can't stand it anymore.
Just a little bit.
No, you can't.
Oh, great.
Master?
What are you doing?
Oh, great.
I want to see this tea bag again.
Why?
You're wearing it because it's easy to see.
I heard that.
Really?
Yes.
Master?
Don't lick me so much.
Oh, great.
Master?
No, you can't.
Lick me more.
Oh, great.
Don't lick me so much.
Master?
No, you can't.
Don't do that.
Oh, great.
Master?
Don't do that.
Oh, great.
No, you can't.
You're so beautiful.
Oh, great.
No, you can't.
Master?
You're shaking.
Don't do that.
Master?
Oh, great.
No, you can't.
Master, please don't lick me.
Oh, great.
No, you can't.
You're so wet.
I'm going to die.
Master, I'm going to die.
No, you can't.
I'm going to die.
Oh, great.
Show me your butt more.
Show me more.
Master.
No, you can't.
You can't lick me.
Master, where are you licking?
Oh, great.
I'm going to die.
No, you can't.
Show me your butt more.
I'm going to die.
Can you stop?
Just a little bit.
Just one bite.
Just a little bit more.
I'm going to do it.
Just a little more.
No, you can't.
Please.
Just a little more.
No, you can't.
I can't reach it.
Please don't do this.
It feels so good.
It's almost over.
Just a little more.
No, you can't.
Please, just a little more.
Please.
I said, no, you can't.
If you don't do this, I won't be able to do anything.
I'll get in the way of cleaning.
Just a little more.
Calm down.
I'm sorry.
Please stop doing this.
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
Do you like this?
It feels so good.
Look at me.
It's taking a long time.
Just a little more.
No, you can't.
Just rub it.
Please.
You can't do this anymore.
No, you can't.
Just a little more.
I have to stop.
What do you have to stop?
I have to clean up.
Okay.
I'll stop soon.
I'll stop as soon as I get in.
No, you can't.
Okay?
Just a little more.
No, you can't.
Master.
I'll clean up as soon as I get in.
It's a promise.
You can't do this anymore, Master.
It feels so good.
When will you stop?
Just a little more.
I'll stop soon.
It feels so good.
You can't do this anymore, Master.
I'll stop soon.
No, you can't.
You can't do this anymore, Master.
I'll stop soon.
Master.
You promised to stop.
Just a little more.
No, you can't.
You promised to stop.
Master.
No, you can't.
You can't do this anymore, Master.
Master.
You can't stop.
No, you can't.
I'll stop soon.
Master.
It feels so good.
Don't do that.
It hurts.
I can't do this anymore.
Master, you promised to stop.
Please stop.
No, you can't.
It hurts.
Please stop.
Master.
It hurts.
It feels so good.
Just a little more.
I can't do this anymore.
Master.
No, you can't.
I can't do this anymore.
Just a little more.
It hurts.
I can't do this anymore.
Master.
No, you can't.
I can't do this anymore.
Just a little more.
Please stop.
I can't do this anymore.
It feels so good.
I can't do this anymore, Master.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's cold.
When is this going to end?
Just a little more.
I've been saying that for a long time.
Is that what you want to do?
Oh, it's hot.
Don't look at me like that.
Oh, my God.
It's so low.
Don't look at me like that.
Oh, my God.
I'm embarrassed.
Oh, no.
Master.
Just a little more.
No, I can't.
Let's get this over with.
Just a little more.
Is this going to end if I do this?
Let's get this over with.
I can't do this without you.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
It's time for you to go to bed.
I'm going to sleep.
You can't stay inside.
Oh, my God.
I can't do this.
Please take it off.
I can't stop.
No, I can't.
Master.
Just a little more.
No, I can't.
I have to take it off.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's OK.
I'm sorry.
I told you no.
I'm sorry. I couldn't help it.
I'm sorry.
I don't like you.
Ouch!
I don't know.
I can't get my back washed because I did such a thing.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm sorry.
I'm not angry anymore.
I'll wash your back today.
Don't look at me like that.
You're still angry, aren't you?
I'm not angry anymore.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
You're not angry anymore, aren't you?
I'm not angry anymore.
It means that your husband liked you so much, didn't he?
I'll wash your back.
Where are you washing your back?
I'm washing your back.
I'm just washing your back, so don't look at me like that.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel better?
No, I don't feel better.
But you're right.
What?
Don't look at me like that.
Okay.
I'm just washing your back.
My body is moving.
Please sit down.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Your husband was bullying you a lot, wasn't he?
No, he wasn't.
Did you feel so good?
No, I didn't.
Where are you washing your back?
Don't look at me like that.
Okay.
I'm just washing your back.
Do you want me to wash your back like this?
Do you want me to do anything?
No, I don't.
Okay.
Please put your arms behind your head.
You shouldn't look at me like that.
What are you talking about?
I'm just washing your face.
I see.
You have to keep your face clean.
Ouch!
Are you okay?
Didn't I wash your face?
I'm going to wash your hands, too.
Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay.
My body hurts.
Why?
No, I'm not okay.
This is blood.
You're not reflecting on yourself, are you?
No, I'm not reflecting on myself.
I can't help it.
Please raise your hand.
That's right.
You shouldn't look at me like that.
What are you talking about?
No, I'm not okay.
You shouldn't touch me like that.
Just a little bit.
No, I'm not okay.
Just look at me.
Master?
What's wrong with you?
I can't control my stomach.
Master?
Do you want me to wash your hands?
Yes.
I want you to wash my hands.
You have to tell me.
Please look at me.
Yes.
Look at me.
No, I'm not okay.
Just a little bit.
Master, you're not reflecting at all.
I'm reflecting.
Look at me.
Master, if you go in front of me, I'll go behind you.
No, I'm not going to go behind you.
I'm just washing your hands.
Yes.
It feels good.
Isn't it a little strong?
No.
What's wrong with you?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
I'm not washing my hands.
No, I'm just washing your hands.
You have to be clean.
No, I'm not washing my hands.
What's wrong with you?
By the way, you used my nose to clean your face.
Yes.
I'll do it for you this time.
What?
Please put your hand on it.
My hand?
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
What's wrong with you?
I'm fine.
I'm just washing your hands.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
Don't laugh.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
Oh, my God.
It's dangerous to be stimulated in such a place.
What's dangerous?
My hands.
What's wrong with your hands?
My hands...
I can't do it.
What's wrong with you?
I can't do it now.
Please look at me.
I want to get my hands out.
Let's wash your hands.
What?
I want to wash my hands.
Don't touch my hands.
Okay.
But if you touch my hands...
What's wrong with you?
Don't touch my hands.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
I'm just washing your hands.
I feel good.
I can't do it.
Oh, my God.
I feel good.
Can I wash my hands by myself?
No, you can't.
Do you want to wash your hands?
Yes, I do.
No, you can't.
I've never washed my hands.
Oh, my God.
What's wrong with you?
I want to get my hands out.
No, you can't.
Oh, my God.
I can't stand it anymore.
I want to get my hands out.
Please.
What should I do?
Oh, my God.
Why did you stop?
I can't help it.
I'll wash your hands.
You're not spoiled.
Please do it yourself.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Does this feel good?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Did you hear that?
Yes.
Does this feel good?
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Let's sleep.
Oh, my God.
Does this feel good?
You're not spoiled.
Oh, my God.
Please tell me when you feel like you're going to puke.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Does this feel good?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
You can't hear me.
Please let me go.
Please beg me more.
I want to go out.
Please.
It's hot.
It's dangerous.
I want to go out.
It's hot.
I can't stand it.
Do you want to go out?
Yes.
I want to go out.
I can't stand it.
It's hot.
Master.
You're energetic.
You're a naughty baby.
I'm sorry.
You haven't reflected on yourself at all.
I'm home.
Welcome back, master.
Do you want to have a meal?
Do you want to take a bath?
Or...
What do you want to do?
What do I want to do?
Well...
I want to have sex.
What?
What do you want to do?
I want to have sex.
You can't do that.
I'm still angry at you.
I'm sorry.
But...
I'm sorry to see you like that.
I came here because I thought you'd be happy.
I'll change my clothes.
No, no, no.
You can't disappear like this.
I see.
If you make me feel good, I'll think about it.
I'll do anything for you.
I'll lick you.
I'll put you in the bathroom.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
What?
I'm not hungry yet.
That's not food.
What?
Here you are.
Make me feel good.
Okay.
Do you use this?
Yes, of course.
Don't you feel better if I use this?
No, please use this.
Okay.
Then...
Make me feel good.
Okay.
Where do you feel good?
I feel good all over my body.
Here?
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
Don't do that.
Okay.
I'll do it here.
Wow.
Is this right?
Yes.
Wow.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Wow.
I'll go there because you're so good.
I want to see you go.
Wow.
I'll go there.
It's amazing.
What happens if you get in the way?
I can't.
I want to go.
If you get in the way.
Like this?
I can't.
Wow.
It's amazing.
I want to see you go.
Please look back.
You can go.
Please stick out your legs.
I can't.
Please don't shake me.
What should I do?
Please let me go.
Wow.
I'll push you while shaking you.
You're very low.
Wow.
Please let me go.
You're very low.
I can't.
What should I do?
Let's go.
I can't.
Wow.
I'm Soppy.
I want to use this, too.
Wow.
Please feel good.
Please put your face here.
Wow.
Oh, it's amazing
Oh, please put your tongue out
Oh, amazing
Please put your chest on your own
Oh, it's amazing
Oh, please put your tongue out
Oh, I'm sorry
Oh, it's amazing
It looks like your husband is licking your penis
Is it real?
Please put it here
Here?
Let's put it in
What?
It's not my penis
Are you okay?
My husband
I'll put it in
Oh, it's amazing
It's in
Is it okay if it's not my penis?
Do you want to put your penis in?
Yes
You can't
Oh, it's amazing
Can you see well?
Yes
Oh, it feels good
Can I get a reward if I make you feel good?
Yes
Can I help you?
What?
No?
Please make me feel good
Okay
Oh, it's amazing
Oh, it feels good
I'll go if you make me feel good
I'll help you
Please don't make me feel good
Oh, it feels good
Oh, it's amazing
Oh, no
Oh, it feels good
Please make me feel good
Okay
Oh, it feels good
It hurts
Does it hurt?
Do you feel good?
Oh, it feels good
You're good at it
Can I get a reward?
What?
Please
You made me feel good
Do you want a reward?
Please sit down
Okay
Please take it out
I'll take it out
My legs
Please sit down
Is this your reward?
Yes, you made me feel good
I'll give you a reward
Okay
Oh, you stood up
If you show me that, I'll stand up
Oh, it feels good
Oh, it hurts
Oh, it's amazing
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good
Oh, it's amazing
What's amazing?
If you stimulate me like that, I'll stand up
Do you want to stand up again?
Yes, I do
Oh, it's amazing
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
Nothing
Oh, you're feeling better
Do you want to feel good?
Yes
You made me feel good
But my husband
He got angry
Oh, I know
He's always angry
He's a bad father
Oh, I'm sorry
Oh, it's amazing
Oh, no, no
What's wrong?
Oh, I'm sorry
Oh, it's amazing
Did you go again?
Oh, I'm sorry
Your husband is a bad father
Oh, it's amazing
My husband
I'll give you a reward later
Come to my bed
Yes
A few days later
You can come in
Oh, you're here
Oh, I'm sorry
Don't come any closer
What?
I'm sorry
I won't forgive you
What?
I'm sorry
What are you doing?
Come on
Oh, I'm sorry
I won't forgive you
Your husband is noisy
Oh, I'm sorry
Does it feel good?
Don't touch him
Are you still angry?
Does it feel good?
Oh, I'm sorry
Oh, it's amazing
Your husband has round eyes
Oh, I'm sorry
Look at him
Oh, I can see
Oh, it's amazing
I thought you wouldn't let me do anything
Oh, it feels good
Oh, I'm sorry
Oh, it's amazing
Your husband has round eyes
Oh, I'm sorry
Oh, it's amazing
Why did you stop?
Oh, I'm sorry
How do you feel?
Oh, it feels good
Can I touch your butt?
No, you can't
I won't forgive you
But...
Oh, it hurts
Does it feel good?
Oh, I'm sorry
Oh, it hurts
Oh, it's amazing
Oh, I'm sorry
Oh, it feels good
Oh, it hurts
If you push me so hard, I'll be in trouble
What will happen?
I'll fall
You can't do it yet
I'm not satisfied
No
Oh, it hurts
Oh, it feels good
Oh, I'm sorry
It's okay
I can still stand
You can
It tickles
Oh, it hurts
Do you still want to do it?
Yes
Oh, it hurts
It tickles
It doesn't matter
Oh, it hurts
How can I help you?
I don't know
I'm really sorry
What do you want?
Do you want more?
Oh, my God.
Oh, it feels good.
It's been a while.
If you stimulate my neck like that, I'll get up.
What's wrong?
Oh, my God.
If you stimulate my neck like that, I'll get up.
Please do it gently.
Is it good?
Oh, my God.
It's okay if I touch you.
If you touch me like that, I'll get up.
You have to touch me together.
Oh, my God.
You're like a baby.
Look, Master.
Please come on my lap.
Like this?
Yes, that's right.
Oh, my God.
You're like a human being.
Is it good?
Oh, my God.
Do I look like an adult?
Yes, you do.
Can I kiss you?
Oh, my God.
Do I look like an adult?
One by one.
Oh, it feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it, Master?
Oh, my God.
It's not over yet, Master.
What's next?
Oh, my God.
Come on, lick me.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it feels good, doesn't it, Master?
Oh, my God.
Come on, lift your hips.
What's next?
Oh, my God.
You like this, don't you, Master?
Yes, I do.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, my God.
That's crazy.
It's like you're in there.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Won't you do it anymore?
I don't want you to do it anymore.
Oh, my God.
You like to be bullied like this, don't you, Master?
Yes, I do.
Oh, my God.
You're a pervert.
Please play with me.
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
Master, did you feel pain when you were beaten?
No, I didn't.
I have to put some medicine on you.
Oh, my God.
I have to treat you with this.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
I don't think you can do it yet.
What?
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
Master, you look like a pervert.
Oh, my God.
How long are you going to let me take care of you?
What do you mean?
Let the master do the work.
Please use it as much as you want.
It feels so good.
I'm sweating.
I'm sweating so much.
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
I can't stop.
Can I do more?
It feels so good.
I love you so much.
I love you too.
It feels so good.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it.
Come here if you love me so much.
I love you so much.
Do something more pleasant.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
I can't do it anymore.
It feels so good.
Do something more pleasant.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels so good.
Can I move now?
I can't do it anymore.
It feels so good.
It hurts.
Your butt is so strong.
I can't do it anymore.
I want to live with you.
I want to look at your face.
It's amazing.
It feels so good.
I want to live with you.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels so good.
I want to live with you.
I can't do it anymore.
It hurts.
It feels so good.
I can't do it anymore.
Do you want to do it again?
Wait a minute.
It feels so good.
You have a lot of hair.
You have a lot of hair, but it's thick.
Master.
Please serve me well from tomorrow.
Please subscribe to the channel.