I, Akari, am very happy to be with you.
You, my older sister, are always kind to me,
and you are a husband who I am proud of to my friends and my parents.
But I have a complaint that I can't tell my friends.
That is that you are too erotic.
I am happy because I can feel your love a lot,
but I can't hold it.
With this amount, I can have two babies soon.
You are always in a bad mood, so it's hard to wake you up.
It's morning.
You are really in a bad mood.
I don't know what to do.
The weather is so nice.
You are so lazy.
You are really in a bad mood.
Let's play a prank on you.
You don't wake up at all.
What? Do you want a more erotic prank?
You are so cute.
Let's kiss.
You don't wake up at all.
You will wake up when I do this.
You like here, don't you?
You don't wake up yet.
You wake me up like this in the morning.
You are happy, aren't you?
You should be in a bad mood, but you don't wake up at all.
What? You are getting bigger.
Is it because it's morning?
Or is it because you are really awake?
You are really awake, aren't you?
Which one is it?
You are still sleeping.
You are getting bigger.
Do you want me to touch you?
I will touch you.
You are getting bigger.
Does it feel good?
Let's play together.
You are getting bigger.
You don't wake up at all.
You are in my way.
You are like this.
You don't wake up at all.
I will touch you.
You like it here.
You don't wake up at all.
Ah.
I'm weak.
I'll do whatever you want.
This.
Do you want to hold hands?
Aha
Do you like it?
Well…
What should I put…
I wonder if you're having a good dream.
You're sleeping, but you're still awake.
I wonder if I'm a bother to you.
Hey...
Come on.
It's your boob.
You can't take it off even if it's your favorite boob?
Then I'll attack your boobs more.
Come on.
It's your favorite boob.
You're still awake, aren't you?
Does it feel good?
Oh, yeah.
It's getting harder and harder.
Come on.
It feels good, doesn't it?
If you don't get up, I'll take it off.
But if you take it off like this, it might be a little loose.
It might feel good to be rubbed.
I'm going to get you wet.
It's your favorite butt.
Come on.
It's warm.
It's hard.
It's really hard.
Come on.
I'm going to get you wet.
I can't do this.
It's okay, isn't it?
I can't.
It's your fault for not getting up.
I'm just rubbing it.
Come on.
It feels good to be rubbed.
I can't do this.
It's okay, isn't it?
Come on.
I'll wake you up.
It feels good.
Come on.
I can't do this.
Did you wake up?
What are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing?
Come on.
Don't you know what I'm doing?
It's too late for you to wake up.
And...
I'm going to make you hungry.
That's why you're in a daze.
Come on.
If you're awake...
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm sleepy.
It feels good.
Can I sleep?
You're so clingy.
It feels good.
I'm sleepy.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Come on.
I want you to do more.
Just a little more.
Why?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I'm sleepy.
It hurts.
No!
I'm sleepy.
It feels good.
I want you to do more.
Thank you.
No!
Don't tease me.
You're mean.
Take it back.
No.
I want you to do more.
It feels good.
I'm sleepy.
It's okay.
You like it, don't you?
It feels good.
Why?
I'm sleepy.
Let's go.
It feels good.
I'm sleepy.
Let's go.
It feels good.
You're going to be late from the morning.
I'm sleepy.
You're always flirting with me before you go out.
I'm happy, but I'm nervous every day because you're going to be late.
I'm sleepy.
If you take your time, you'll be late for work.
Here's your lunch.
Do your best today.
You can do your best, right?
Do your best.
One more time?
You have to get ready.
One more time.
See you later.
What?
Don't do that.
You're going to be late.
What?
Are you lonely?
You're cute.
What?
If you do that in the morning, you'll be late for work.
Just a little.
I'll give it back to you.
Don't do that.
It tickles.
That's what you like.
Don't do that.
What?
Are you trying to look at me?
Don't do that.
This side too?
No.
You're mean.
Don't be mean.
Do you want me to pet you?
You're mean.
It feels good.
I shouldn't have done that.
I shouldn't be too mean.
I feel weird.
I shouldn't do that.
What?
Here?
What's wrong?
This part is hard.
Wait.
It feels good.
It tickles.
Wait.
Don't do that.
You're mean.
I want to wipe your butt before we go out.
My butt?
It can't be helped.
It tickles.
You want to look at me?
Is that so?
You like this side of me.
It tickles.
What was that?
Are you playing with me?
It tickles.
Wait.
Don't do that.
It's embarrassing.
If you do that, I'll stop.
Wait.
Don't do that.
You're really mean.
No.
What are you doing?
Don't put your face there.
No.
It tickles.
You're really mean.
I told you not to be mean.
If you're going to do it, make me feel better.
It tickles.
Don't do that.
No.
More.
Do more.
It tickles.
It tickles a lot.
It feels good.
It's cold.
Let me go again.
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
I want to go again.
Let me go again.
It feels good.
It feels good to stay like this.
No, no, no.
I want to go again.
It feels good.
But you...
You can't go any further than this.
I'll continue after I go home.
I'm going to sleep.
The table with you...
It fills my stomach and my heart.
I guess this is what happiness is.
But you seem to want me to satisfy you with another thing.
Thank you for doing this for me.
You're welcome.
Anything tastes good when we eat together.
Do you like mandarin oranges?
I do.
Which one do you like better?
Mandarin oranges.
I'm annoyed.
I forgive you.
This is really good.
Do you want to try it?
Is it good?
I guess I'll try it, too.
The soup spilled.
What? Are you going to give it to me?
You're so kind.
It's good.
I can't stop eating mandarin oranges.
How is it? It's better than usual, isn't it?
It's good.
Really?
You should have said that from the beginning.
Oh, right.
I already took a bath.
Do you want to take a bath?
Yes.
Let's take a bath together.
Shall we?
No, no.
I can't take a bath with you.
I can see you.
This skirt is interesting.
Lower this zipper.
Oh, oh, oh.
You came out.
Don't sniff me.
Well, there.
Oh, oh, oh.
Thank you.
Hey.
What are you doing?
It's embarrassing.
Don't do that.
I'll take it off.
Here you go.
Let's take a bath together.
I'll take a bath.
It's warm.
You sound like an old man.
But I know how you feel.
You're cute.
It's fun to take a bath together.
I'll take a bath, too.
You can't go wild in the bath.
You're like a chicken.
It makes me feel nostalgic.
When we just started dating,
we often went to the hotel together.
We often went to the hotel together.
It makes me feel nostalgic.
It's floating.
Do you want to do it again?
Which do you like better?
You said it honestly.
I'm not good at breastfeeding.
I said it honestly, so I'll stop.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
You brought a pillow.
You want me to do it, don't you?
I'll do it for you.
It feels good, doesn't it?
By the way, I licked the Latte.
I thought it was a little salty.
You're greedy.
What are you going to do?
Let's get out of here.
It's going to be a lot of work if I let you sleep.
What?
I love you even if you're sweaty.
I love you.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
I'm glad.
I hope you feel better.
It's hot.
I really let it out.
I let out a lot.
I'm glad you let me out.
Next time, let's have a bath together.
What's wrong?
I'm glad.
Hmm?
What?
What's wrong?
Today's underwear is also good.
It's cute, isn't it?
This is my favorite underwear.
It's also wrapped in a bag.
Wow.
Is it cute?
It's cute, isn't it?
Really?
I'm happy.
Oh.
By any chance,
are you going to change into this today?
Hmm.
Does it look good on me?
I'll definitely wear it.
Okay.
Then I'll change.
At night,
change into the erotic clothes you chose.
Let's feel good together tonight.
What?
Ahh,
it's not good yet.
Let me change into the erotic clothes.
I wonder if I can put a pie in it.
Let's see...
Like this?
How is it?
Does it look good on me?
It does.
I'm happy.
Let's see...
What are you doing?
Is there a hole in it?
Yes.
What is this?
It's so dirty.
Let me see.
Wait.
It's sticking out.
It was small.
It's a little big.
It didn't fit.
You like the bigger one, don't you?
Oh no.
It's sticking out.
It feels good.
Oh no.
It's sticking out.
It feels good.
Oh no.
I'm going to rub it on myself.
It feels good.
Yes.
Can you see it?
It's so round.
Did you see something?
Oh no.
It feels good.
No.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
Again!
Oh, it feels good.
Why?
It feels good.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
Is my mango good?
Then lick a lot.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
It feels good.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
Let me go!
It feels good.
A toy?
Do you feel like you want to play with a toy today?
Okay.
Oh, it feels good.
It feels good.
Oh, my neck.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
It feels good.
I'm going to throw up.
I don't want to do that.
It feels good.
I can't do that.
I'm going to throw up.
It's embarrassing.
I'm going to clean up.
If you like me, you can lick me, right?
You love me, don't you?
I want you to lick me all over.
It's embarrassing.
Could it be...
I knew it.
It's fine.
It feels good.
I can't do that.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I can't do that.
I'm going to throw up.
It feels good.
What's that?
It's amazing.
I'm going to throw up.
It feels good.
Like this...
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I can't do that.
I'm going to throw up again.
It feels good.
I'm going to throw up.
It's embarrassing.
I can't do that.
I'm going to throw up again?
It's embarrassing.
I'm going to throw up.
It feels good.
It feels good
I can't do that.
It feels good.
No, it feels good.
I'm going to break it.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm going to put it in.
You like this one?
Don't tease me.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
I'm here.
What?
You still don't like it?
It can't be helped.
I'm going to do it for you.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
I'm going to tickle you.
I'm going to add two.
You're acting strange.
You're sticking out your teeth.
It's hot.
Do you like it here?
What's wrong?
Why?
It's cute.
It's puffy.
Here?
You can't eat it.
If you eat it like this, it's too mean.
Eat slowly.
You can't eat it.
Do you want to cry?
You really like it.
I'm sorry.
I have to do this.
Are you okay?
Can you stand this?
Be patient.
If you like me, you can stand it.
I'm going to tickle you.
You can't?
I'll hold it down for you.
You can't.
It feels good.
Be patient.
I want to do it.
You want to do it?
What are you doing?
Are you being mean again?
What?
You said it was amazing.
I'm sensitive.
Do you really want to eat it?
I'm getting excited.
Watch where you're going.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
One more time?
Let's do it together.
It feels good.
I'm tickling you.
Is it good?
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I'm going to do it.
It feels good.
I'm bleeding!
I feel good....
I feel good...
I feel good!
I can't get up.
It feels good.
Do you like me?
I love you too.
It feels good there.
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go!
It feels good.
Let's take this off.
Take it off?
Do you want to have sex with me?
I can still see you.
You wanted to see me.
I want to stay like this.
It feels good.
Show me your face.
I can't.
It feels good.
Do you do that?
I can't.
It feels good.
Let's go!
I can't.
It feels good.
Let's touch your neck.
I can't.
Let's go!
It feels good.
Don't stop.
I can't.
It feels good.
Shut up!
Kyoko, what did they do to you?
They beat me.
Don't worry.
Feel... feel so good...
I feel so good...
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! własfdimdit
Ahh!
Ah, I'm tickled, ah!
Ahh, It's tickling me
Ah... ah... ah...
I feel so good...
I feel...
I forgot...
I'm gonna cry...
It hurts...
I wanna go to the toilet...
I wanna go...
It's so hot.
It feels good.
Do you want me to pat you?
Okay.
Here?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Do you want me to pat your neck?
It feels good.
You have a lot of acnes.
You're tired, aren't you?
It feels good here.
It feels good here, doesn't it?
Do you want me to pat you?
Is it good?
I'm happy.
I'll pat you more.
It feels good.
More.
It's amazing.
I'm sweating.
It feels good here.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
Can I do more?
It feels good.
It's amazing here, too.
Look at me.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels good.
Do you like butt?
I like butt.
It feels good.
I can't do it anymore.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'm sleepy.
Can I do more?
It feels good.
I'm sleepy.
I can't do it anymore.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I'm sleepy.
I can't do it anymore.
It's dangerous!
It's no good!
It's still no good!
Hey!
When you go to school,
say you love Akari!
It's disgusting!
Are you going to fall asleep?
No, I'm not!
Akari! Akari!
I love you too!
Let's be together forever!