Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Teacher.
You couldn't see anyone?
Yes, for the time being.
You wanted to do it at school, didn't you?
No, that was a joke.
Come here.
Shut up.
Thank you for your hard work until late.
I can't take a break because I have more work to do.
Don't overdo it.
It's okay.
I'm glad I have a job.
Hey.
Sorry, I'm busy.
How busy are we?
You said you were busy with work.
I don't have time.
Please think about it.
You should go to bed early tomorrow.
I want to do it at school, too.
I'm the one who said it.
If you find out at school, I'll do it.
It's okay.
I want to do it.
Do you really want to do it?
It's getting bigger.
I love you so much.
If you do it like this...
No, teacher.
Do you really want to do it like this?
I'm sorry.
How does it feel to be choked at school?
It's really big.
Be quiet.
Teacher.
I want to change when I'm choked like that.
Is that okay?
I can't stand it either.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
Teacher, can I take this off?
I'm embarrassed.
It's really big.
Teacher is also embarrassed.
I won't do this.
It's really big.
What should I do if someone comes?
I can't stand it either.
If someone sees this, will they be jealous?
Of course.
Teacher.
I love you.
I can't stand it either.
I'm sorry.
I'll spit it out.
I can't stand it either.
Teacher.
I want to get you dirty.
Wait a minute.
I can't stand it either.
Let's go home.
Before that.
Let me return it to you.
It's embarrassing.
It's beautiful.
Teacher.
I can't stand it either.
It's here.
It's amazing.
I can't stand it either.
Hurry up and sleep.
Are you really going to sleep in school?
It's a secret.
Teacher.
I'm glad I met you.
Me too.
I'll put it in.
It's amazing.
Teacher.
What happened?
Please don't get me wrong.
I'm too excited.
I'm going to faint.
Please let me go a little.
Teacher.
I'm going to faint when I get wet.
It's amazing.
Teacher.
I'm going to faint.
Because the teacher is very strong.
Let me go.
I know you can do it.
If you make that much noise,
no one will notice.
It's okay.
If you like the teacher, do your best.
But...
It's not fair to say that.
I'm going to faint.
Teacher.
Ah!
Ah...
The computer was moving and shaking from the Gulf War!
Sorry!
Ah...
Ah!
Teacher...
If I don't blow the steam...
The baby...
Ah...
Today is a safe day, so...
Are you really okay?
Ah...
Teacher...
Ah, it's hot.
Ah...
Oh, no.
I can't breathe.
I'm sweating.
I'm sweating a lot.
Oh, no.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Are you moving this time?
It's a lie.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Oh my god!
Science teacher!
Z...z... slit my teeth!
I'm going to take a break for the afternoon.
I'll do my best.
I'm sorry.
I can hear the intense sound.
I'll do it slowly.
Please open the door.
Is there still time?
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
Please open the door.
It hurts.
Can I open the door?
I'm sorry.
I drank a lot.
I'll buy water and give it to you later.
It's all right.
It's a secret between us.
I'll keep it a secret.
I love you.
I love you, too.
The next day
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Teacher.
Why are you here?
What are you looking at?
Well, I'm a little...
Show me.
It's not now.
I don't know.
I don't want to play.
I'm not going to play.
What is it?
This is it.
It's cute.
Why are you hiding it?
I'm embarrassed to see the teacher's picture.
It's cute.
No one's coming.
I don't know what to do.
All right.
I'm sorry.
The next day
I'm sweating.
It's all right.
It's salty.
Can I eat a lot of this, too?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I want to make you feel better.
I'm sorry.
Are you really sorry?
I'm not.
I'm a teacher every day.
I'm sorry.
Let's start the 10 o'clock lesson.
We'll definitely do another lesson this time.
I'm sorry.
Don't smile.
I love you.
I love you more than anybody.
Me too.
I want to marry a teacher like you.
I love you.
Look after him.
You always take good care of me, don't you?
I'm so proud of you.
Do you do this every day?
It's not like that.
You do such a good thing with me.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
I'm so tired.
It's so delicious.
I'm sweating.
There is no smell at all.
It's getting tight.
I'm so tired.
What will you do if someone hears your voice?
I'm sweating.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm so embarrassed.
Can you do it before someone hears your voice?
I'm sweating.
It's amazing.
I love that the teacher helps me relax.
Please feel more comfortable.
I'm sweating.
I want you to move more.
Please relax.
I'm sweating.
I have to wipe it with a tissue.
I'm really sorry.
I went to the classroom.
I can go back to the classroom.
Can you still do it?
I want to do it, but I don't have time.
If I don't do it quickly, the next class will start.
It's okay.
Thank you.
I love you.
No.
You'll get caught.
I can't come.
Let's look for a lot of places to go.
It's probably okay here.
It's a library.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
If you're curious, look at the entrance.
Look at the teacher.
I'll look at it, too.
I'm sorry.
No.
If you enter the entrance, you'll be surprised.
I'm sorry.
The teacher's body is getting hot.
I'm really sorry.
Look here.
The cat is gone.
Look here, too.
I'm sorry.
I'm really going to get caught.
If you're with your husband, you can't do this.
No one's here.
You can make more noise.
Teacher.
You can lick it without using your hands.
I'm sorry.
You have a very mean face.
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
You told me to do it here, didn't you?
That's right.
Look at me.
Teacher.
I'm going to cry.
Teacher, no one's here.
You can put out a little more.
Teacher.
Can I go inside?
Ouch.
Don't do this.
It's okay because I'm here.
It's dangerous.
I've been in a lot of dangerous places.
If you were in the men's bathroom.
Teacher, I'm sorry.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's not funny.
It's not funny?
Go home.
Look, people are coming.
But it was okay a while ago, wasn't it?
But.
If only the teacher didn't make a voice.
I'm sorry.
The teacher has a very edgy face.
Don't do this.
Just put out your voice.
Okay.
Put out your voice.
Put out your voice, teacher.
It's like this.
Wow.
It's done.
It's almost done.
Teacher.
Can I do it too?
It can't be helped.
Look.
Teacher.
It's getting bigger.
I've been thinking about you all the time in class.
Wow.
Teacher.
I have to hurry up.
I don't have time.
Day off.
Tea first.
It feels good.
It feels really good.
Teacher.
Do you like the teacher?
I love you.
Teacher.
It feels good.
I want to lick it all the time.
I don't do things like that with teachers.
Can I have another cup of tea?
Teacher.
I'm going to lick you a lot.
I can't stop.
Teacher.
Do you do this to your husband too?
I don't know.
Teacher's cup.
It feels good.
I'll make it smooth.
It feels better when it's smooth.
Yes.
It feels really good.
Teacher.
It's cute.
It tickles.
Teacher.
The day break is over.
It felt good.
You wanted to lick it.
Yes.
See you.
Tomorrow.
Yes.
Teacher.
Can I put a scratch mark on it?
No.
Because.
If you don't do it with your husband.
You won't know.
No.
Because.
You're doing this.
See.
Teacher's hips are moving.
Amazing.
No one needs to come here.
You'll find out.
See.
The curtains are closed.
No one needs to come here.
No.
Yes.
It's painful.
Teacher.
Yes.
Amazing.
Teacher.
I love you.
One more time.
Teacher.
I love you.
Yes.
Today is the last day.
What?
Day off.
Yes.
Are you lonely?
But...
This is not the end.
But I'm lonely.
Listen.
Let's play after graduation.
Yes.
Let's play a lot.
Teacher.
I love you.
Me too.
It's the first time to play in the classroom.
Yes.
The classroom is...
It's not good.
Are you okay?
I can't see.
It's not good if I get caught.
It's okay.
I'll watch you.
But...
It's a classroom.
Shut up.
Yes.
Are you okay because the teacher is here?
If you don't hurry, the day off will be over.
Yes.
I'm tired.
Teacher.
If you touch me so much,
I don't want to do it.
Let's do it.
You have to hurry.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
I'll put it in my mouth again.
I'm really lonely.
I love you.
I'm tired.
I'm really good at it.
I don't want it to end.
It's lonely.
I want to be together with you forever.
Oh, someone's here.
Someone took it.
Teacher, I don't have time after all.
It's okay.
I'm done.
You like leaves, don't you?
I like your leaves.
I love your tits too.
Thank you.
I'm done.
It's okay, teacher.
Thank you for protecting me.
Teacher.
I'm done.
My knees hurt.
Get up quickly.
Get up.
I'm done.
What are you going to do when someone comes?
Even if they come, I can't bear it.
I'm done.
I have to hurry.
Teacher.
I'm done.
Hurry up.
Amazing.
I'm done.
Teacher.
I heard your voice.
I'm done.
I'm nervous.
Yes.
I'm done.
Teacher.
I like it.
I'm done.
I love you.
I love you too.
I'm done.
I love you.
Teacher.
I'm so tired.
I feel good.
Teacher.
I'm done.
Can you do it?
Me?
I'm fine.
Teacher.
Me?
Not yet.
I don't want to stop.
I want to be with you more.
Teacher.
I'm done.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I'm done.
I feel good.
I want to be with you more.
I'm done.
Teacher.
If I were a teacher, I would hit you as many times as you want.
Amazing.
I want to do it again.
Teacher.
Amazing.
I'm done.
I want to do it again.
Teacher.
I can't do it anymore.
I want to do it again.
It's time.
I'm going to end my lunch break.
Please call me again anytime.
I'll be there soon.
I'm lonely, but congratulations on your graduation.
Thank you.