She puts her hands on her shoulders.
His heart is beating faster.
She caresses his ears.
What?
You snooze, if she wakes up.
She is on right now.
She was like this when he was asleep.
so she puts her hands on her shoulder.
What am I supposed to do?
When she takes a nap, she rubs herself with his hair.
You have to flip it over, fold it, and put it out.
I don't want to do that.
I told you, you don't have to do that.
It's annoying.
It's not annoying. It's normal to make rules at home.
Do you have a house without rules?
You don't, do you?
Also,
tell me if you're going to eat on the way home.
I don't have to.
I've told you before.
It's useless to make it.
You won't eat it in the morning, will you?
Why?
I'm not asking why.
I'm cooking for you,
but you don't have to do that.
I'm doing what I like.
You don't have a part-time job,
but you're hanging out outside even though you don't have money.
I'm doing what I like.
Don't look at me like that all the time.
I'm tired of it.
Then make it yourself.
I can't make it.
You can.
I'm begging you.
You're going to be alone soon, right?
Then make it yourself.
I have to grow up.
When will you grow up?
You're going to save money and leave the house, right?
Do you have enough money?
Yes, I do.
How much do you have?
About 30,000 yen.
30,000 yen?
What do you think you can do with 30,000 yen?
I can make more money.
Do you have a part-time job?
You don't have a part-time job, do you?
Yes, I do.
I may not have anything to do with it,
but you have a lot of people around you.
You don't work at 6 o'clock.
You don't study.
What can you do?
I'm studying.
You don't have a girlfriend.
Make a girlfriend.
You're old.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I'm doing what I'm supposed to do.
You're kidding.
What kind of girlfriend?
Introduce her to me.
Is she cute?
Is she beautiful?
Where is she from?
I don't care.
Introduce her to me.
I'm not done talking to you.
What is it?
You said you didn't have much experience.
It's true.
If you're frustrated, make a girlfriend.
Introduce her to me.
I have a lot of experience.
I...
What is it?
Koji, what are you doing?
Wait.
I don't like it.
Let me go.
Wait.
Don't do that.
What are you doing?
Don't touch me.
I'm doing what I'm supposed to do.
I don't like it.
Are you crazy?
Don't do that.
Let me go.
Let's play.
She's cute.
She's just okay.
You want more?
Koji!
Ouch!
It's okay.
Do you understand?
Don't come here.
Do you need a girlfriend?
It's okay.
Don't use your head.
Don't do that.
It's okay.
Take back what you said.
Take back?
You said you had little experience.
I didn't say anything.
I only said the truth.
It's okay.
I'll make you feel better.
I can't.
I hope you feel better.
That's enough.
It's okay.
Don't do that.
Please.
It's okay.
It hurts.
Don't do that.
Please.
Please forgive me.
Forgive me.
Please.
I understand.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Please don't do that.
Please.
I won't stop until you forgive me.
Forgive me.
It's okay.
Please forgive me.
It feels good.
What should I do?
Please forgive me.
Does it feel good?
Do you want to breathe more?
Please breathe more.
Please don't do that.
You're getting bigger.
I'm sweating.
I don't like it.
I don't like the smell.
What?
You make fun of me all the time, and now you're talking about me.
I don't want to. You know that, don't you?
What?
I'm going to bite you.
Hey.
Bite me.
It's okay, isn't it?
There's no way it's okay.
It's not fair for you to feel alone at night.
That's not what I meant.
You didn't reflect on yourself, did you?
Reflect on myself?
Well, I'm reflecting on myself a little bit.
You're weird.
I know.
I'm nervous.
Is this okay?
Mom, I'm serious.
Serious?
I'm not playing with you.
Why do I have to go this far?
I don't know.
You've been bullied so much that you've grown up, haven't you?
We're both like that, aren't we?
That's not true, mom.
I want you to kill me again, mom.
Hey.
What are you saying to your parents?
I'm serious.
Is this okay?
With your mouth.
With my mouth?
Make it feel good with your mouth.
With my mouth.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
it's cold.
Do I need to help you with that?
The solution?
I see.
I'm going to sleep a little longer.
I'm getting bigger.
I'm glad.
Great.
Pamper...
Please forgive him.
I can't, Kuawasa.
He has insulted me to out of concise.
I need to teach him a lesson.
What did you say?
I, I think I know what I had to say.
Hey, can I talk to you?
I'm sorry.
Please.
You like it rough, don't you?
Forgive me.
I'm sorry.
What's this?
That's enough for today.
You're crying.
Koji.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
Don't do that.
Don't move.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
a harmful treatment
I'm sorry.
That's a lie.
Liar!
I didn't mean any harm.
This is my first try.
Come, let's eat.
This will be fine, right?
I can't do this anymore.
Oh−
Here−
I've been got the cold for a few days.
What was the time when you faced it?
It was all.
What do you mean?
Thank you.
Dama, are you ok?
I am fine.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Let me wipe your sweat.
It's okay.
Stop it.
I know.
It's okay.
It hurts.
But...
My body is going crazy.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Let me wipe your sweat.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
Please.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
It's going to break.
I'll rub it.
But I'm weak.
It's going to break.
Wow, Tai-chan...
Ai-kun...
Help me!
I can't do it!
It hurts so much...
What is this?
This is a lot of cosmetics...
It hurts so much...
My stomach is melting...
My hips...
I can't do this...
It hurts so much...
I'm sorry...
I can't do this...
Forgive me...