I was scared.
Hello, Aki.
The last time,
You were in a super office.
Your anko smelled really bad.
It was true.
You can't meet such a girl.
I always
It was serious.
Welcome back, Tamura-kun.
Ah, what should I do?
Hey, Tamura-kun.
Pick up the trash.
What?
You don't have to throw it away where I'm cleaning.
No, I thought it was just right because my wife was cleaning, so I threw it away.
What? Are you making fun of me?
Wife, if you're so angry, you'll get more customers.
Don't call me your wife.
Then what about me?
You're an old woman.
That's rude.
Why are you so angry?
Are you dissatisfied with your desire?
Or haven't you been treated by your husband?
What are you talking about?
Then I'll sit down for you.
Let's sit down.
You look like a woman.
See you.
Welcome back, Tamura-kun.
Thank you.
Hey, Tamura-kun.
Would you like to have some tea at my house?
Ah, yes.
There are also delicious sweets.
So I want to eat with you.
Is that okay?
Just a little more.
You like to eat a lot.
Here you are.
You son of a bitch.
You touched my chest yesterday, didn't you?
I used to be aiming for a woman's pro.
Before you become a woman.
If you like it so much, I'll let you taste it.
Hey, Tamura-kun.
Hey, auntie.
What do you mean by auntie?
I told you not to call me auntie, didn't I?
What?
If you say sweets, I'll pick you up.
Are you stupid?
Get up.
Don't fall down.
Where have you been?
What?
You've been making fun of girls.
You've been crying.
You don't have to be scared.
What do you think your parents will think when they hear this?
I don't know.
You don't know?
I'll let you smell the armpits of a woman you called an old woman.
Here you are.
What do you think?
The smell of an old woman's armpits.
Don't do that.
How was it?
I'm asking you how it was.
It's not painful.
How was it?
Tamura-kun.
People have been asking questions for a while, so you have to answer them.
It's not what it is.
It's what it is.
You learned how to talk to your superiors at school, didn't you?
Shut up.
What?
What is it, Tamura-kun?
What does it smell like?
The smell of an old woman's armpits.
It smells completely different from the smell of a woman you usually play with.
You bit my bad ear.
Hey.
I know how you feel when you want to be cool, but what are you doing?
I'll teach you how to talk to your superiors.
I'll teach you how to talk to your superiors and how to treat women.
You're not nice to girls, are you?
I know.
You don't know.
I can hear you on the phone.
I'm talking to you.
You don't know.
I'll teach you how to talk to your superiors.
Look!
Does it smell?
Please forgive me.
I thought I had to tell you.
I was holding back myself from taking a bath.
What?
I feel sick.
You feel sick?
Give up?
You have no guts.
You can only use it when you can't stand it.
What?
I can't stand it.
That's why young people these days have no guts.
How is it?
You've been wearing it for more than twice as long.
Does it taste different?
The taste of the kiss.
The kiss of an old lady who has been playing with Tamura-kun for more than twice as long is still persistent.
What?
Tell me.
More?
More what?
What is more?
What?
You.
You're standing with your back out.
I'm touching this.
No.
I'm not.
What is this?
What's wrong?
My boobs.
Boobs?
You have small boobs.
Right?
Wow.
What do you mean wow?
What?
Do you remember your mom's boobs?
Tamura-kun's mom is a beautiful person.
Your mom might cry when she sees them.
Your son is standing next to you with his back out.
He's about to suffocate you with his boobs.
What?
Your boobs are standing up.
Wow?
What do you mean wow?
You don't know until you say it clearly.
You don't know.
Right?
You don't say it clearly.
I'm going to stand up.
Does it hurt?
It hurts.
You keep saying it hurts.
Your boobs are getting harder and harder.
You stink.
I'm embarrassed.
You have a nice boob.
Tell me.
You're old enough to do it alone every day.
Show me how you do it.
Why are you doing that?
Is that how you do it?
That's how you do it.
Show me.
I'm going to smell your boobs.
You're as old as your mom.
Did I say it's warm?
You're good.
Does it feel good?
What are you doing?
You're being cheeky.
It smells.
Does it hurt?
You look so cute.
You're so shy.
You're going to do it, right?
You're going to do it alone, right?
You...
You're not going to do this to a girl you've been playing with, right?
Right?
You...
How do you feel?
It's the best.
It's the best?
You're suddenly so honest.
What's wrong?
It's the first time.
It's the first time, so it's the best.
You're so nice.
It's getting a little moist.
The smell has changed.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Let me smell the smell of a boy.
The smell of a boy who just got home from school.
It stinks.
It stinks, doesn't it?
It's bitter.
It stinks.
I can't help it.
Did I say that?
It's not a big deal.
Get up.
Come on.
What are you doing?
You look embarrassed.
I've been telling you.
Why?
Don't call me an old lady.
What did you say?
Do you know what I'm saying?
No.
Hey.
What did you say?
If you say it one more time...
Why are you panting?
You're panting.
Ochinchin is getting better again.
You look so cute.
You're a pervert.
I'll do this to your boobs.
I'll make your boobs shrink.
Wow.
Is it soft?
Ochinchin is getting better again.
You're honest.
You're so energetic.
You're good at kissing.
What?
What's wrong with your nipples?
I didn't do anything.
What's wrong with you?
You're suddenly honest.
I'm sorry.
I've never apologized to you.
You like this kind of thing.
You're old.
If you like this kind of thing when you're old, you'll have a bright future.
You're always bothering women, aren't you?
Let me take a good look at you.
Okay.
Excuse me.
You look like a ghost all of a sudden.
You're frowning.
Wow.
You're so sexy.
What's wrong?
You look like a different person.
You're so honest.
You're so beautiful.
You're so cute.
How does it feel to be pinched on the knees?
It feels good.
It feels good to be pinched on the knees.
Look.
You've never done this before, have you?
No.
Your body smells different from that of a young girl.
You don't like it, do you?
I'm going to pinch you if you're shy.
You're going to be pinched on the cheek and pinched on the knees.
I'm going to be surprised if a girl in my class sees this.
You're the only girl in my class who does this.
Look.
What's wrong?
I want to pinch you.
What?
Like this?
Yes.
Where did you learn this?
Look.
Your boobs and penis are kissing.
I'm sorry.
It's ridiculous.
My boobs are crispy.
Yes.
Your boobs are hard.
I'll pinch your boobs.
What?
It's a little damp, isn't it?
Your armpits are a little damp, aren't they?
What?
I'm sorry.
I'll make you feel better until you're hot.
You're so young, but you shouldn't come to the world of fetishes.
You're a pervert.
I want to be pinched.
How do you usually touch?
Like this.
You like to be strong.
I like to be strong.
You're good.
Your nipples.
Be strong.
I'm sorry.
Did you get addicted to your mother's smell?
You're like a different person than an hour ago.
Give me your tongue.
I'm sorry.
I bit your bad tongue.
Look.
How do you take off your panties?
Do you want to keep your panties on?
I'm sorry.
It's your fault.
You're wet.
Look.
Take off your panties.
What does it smell like?
Look.
You're getting aggressive.
You're suddenly losing your waist.
You're a strange boy.
Touch me.
How do you feel?
You're wet.
I didn't ask you to put your fingers in my panties.
Come on.
Get up.
I'll make you smaller.
I didn't ask you to put your fingers in my panties.
You're drooling.
I'll wipe your drool.
You're good.
Where did you learn that?
Do you want to put your fingers in my panties?
Look at me.
You're good.
I'm sorry I smoked in front of you.
I'll eat you like this.
You're good.
I took it out a while ago.
Don't say it easily.
Be patient.
I made you feel good.
You're good.
It's just the beginning.
You like to be tickled on your side.
You're good.
You have a great skill.
You're sweating a lot.
Is it painful?
It's painful, isn't it?
If you can't breathe, tap it.
You're good.
You're getting bigger.
It feels good.
It's getting hot.
I'll tighten it more.
You're good.
Don't do that.
Give me a bell.
You're good.
I want to do more.
Make me feel good.
How can I make you feel good?
What are you going to do?
From behind.
There.
Slowly.
It feels good.
You're good.
Hold my hips.
Put your hips in.
Turn around.
Turn around more.
More.
You're good.
Show me a cute face.
It's hard.
Cute face.
You're good.
I'll make you harder.
Put your feet on it.
You're good.
I don't know if I can do it, but I'm going to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to
do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best
to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best to do my best a
s nyon
what
pain
that
light
is
...
My sweet baby, You are waiting for me.
What should I do now?
It's so early in the morning.
I have to hurry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's disgusting.
Tamura-kun.
When I saw my stomach, it was so big.
I didn't expect it to be so hard.
I always say cheeky things.
You have a cute part.
I'm sorry.
When I got closer to my stomach, I didn't say anything.
But my mouth was swollen.
I was suffocating.
I'm sorry.
Surprisingly,
I'm honest.
I'm sorry.
I was suffocating.
I was suffering.
I'm sorry.
My smell.
I was suffering.
I'm sorry.
I'm suffering.
My butt.
I have a lot on my face.
I'm suffering.
I feel good.
Why?
What are you doing?
What are you doing in front of my house?
What?
Nothing.
What are you talking about?
Get up.
You've been lying down for a while.
It's suspicious, isn't it?
Forgive me.
I can't forgive you.
I've been watching you from the window.
Lie down for another 30 minutes.
Stop it.
You're not honest at all.
You keep saying, forgive me.
You look delicious.
But you're moving.
If you're waiting, tell me you're waiting.
I'm waiting.
What's wrong?
You're not honest at all.
I feel good.
I've been watching you from the window.
You're moving in front of my house.
I want to go home.
Do you want to go home?
I know it's a secret.
You're kind today.
Be kind to women.
You're ticklish.
You're sweating.
Does it smell?
It smells, doesn't it?
You're a pervert.
I can't run away like this.
It's painful.
I can't breathe.
It's ticklish.
You're a pervert.
It's painful.
It's ticklish.
You're a pervert.
Does it smell?
It smells, doesn't it?
You're a pervert.
You smell.
I remember you.
I'll touch you.
Is that okay?
It's ticklish.
I remember you licking me.
I've been thinking about you all the time.
It's ticklish.
You're amazing.
What should I do?
No!
You're amazing.
It's poisonous.
It's so poisonous.
I remember you.
You're amazing.
It's ticklish.
Ah!
Why?
No!
Ah! It's coming out!
It's coming out!
Ah!
No!
Oh!
It's coming out a lot.
Naive!
Ah!
I'm happy!
I'm going to crush you!
Naive!
It's hard!
Oh!
No!
I wanted to see you!
It's coming out!
Naive!
I wanted to see you!
Ah!
Oh!
You like it, don't you?
I love it.
Hm..
Ah..
I'll do it with your mouth
Even with my breast?
Yeah
Ah, it's amazing.
Ah, it's the best.
It's getting harder and harder.
I'm going to wake you up.
Ah, it's amazing.
You're erotic.
Am I erotic?
Are you erotic?
You're erotic.
Because...
It's getting hotter and hotter between your breasts.
Ah, it's amazing.
I'm happy that you reacted like this.
Me, too.
Ah, it's amazing.
You're erotic.
It's amazing.
Your haircut is wet.
You hate it?
We'd like your hair wet and soft.
Come on, hurry up and come here.
If you're going to do it, do it.
Show me your cheeky face.
Cheeky.
Ah, it feels good.
Put it on more.
Visual.
It's hard.
It hurts.
Ah, it feels good.
Put it on more.
It feels good.
Ah, it feels good.
It's amazing.
You're good.
It feels good.
No, no, no.
Ah, it feels good.
Come on, show me your cheeky face.
Open your mouth.
You drank it honestly.
It's amazing.
I've got a lot on my back.
I've lost my strength.
It's amazing.
I've got a lot on my back.
I've lost my strength.
It feels good.
I've got a lot on my back.
It's amazing.
Remember...
After you get home...
A lot...
Remember...
That you can do it alone!
Remember this important thing!
You idiot!
Don't manage...
Don't...
Impossible...
Oh, it's so wet.
What are you doing?
It's so wet.
It's so embarrassing.
But it feels good.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's wet.
No, no, no.
I feel like I'm going to die.
I feel so good that I'm going to die.
I'm going to die.
I'm going to die like this.
No, no.
I'm going to die.
You look great.
You should put on a lot of makeup.
I'm going to die.
I can't breathe.
It's painful.
It feels good.
It's moving.
I can't breathe.
It's painful.
It's the best.
Tamura, what's wrong?
Miki.
I thought you liked sweets, so I bought them.
Miki?
Sweets?
Yes, please.
It's disgusting to be called Miki.
Come here.
I can't breathe.