My name is Asuna Hoshi, I'm a female college student in Tokyo.
I'm having a drink with my friends at the club,
but I haven't had a drink in two years without my boyfriend.
I'm thinking,
it's not the right time to be having a drink in a place like this.
I'm drinking with my friends at the club,
but I haven't had a drink in two years without my boyfriend.
I'm thinking,
it's not the right time to be having a drink in a place like this.
I drink again when the drink I love comes in front of me.
Hey, you.
Yes?
You haven't had a drink at all, right?
No, I have.
It's pretty low.
What? But you haven't had a drink.
Please, give me a break.
Then, let's have a drink.
A drink?
A drink.
But you are strong.
Are you sure?
Don't run away like a man.
I'm weak.
Let's have a drink.
A drink.
Are you serious?
Wait a minute.
Close your eyes for a moment.
Close my eyes?
Yes, for a moment.
Okay.
Takeshi.
Come here.
Hurry up.
What is this?
It's okay. Wait a minute.
Sit down.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Wait a minute.
What do you mean?
You haven't had a drink yet?
Who are you?
Nice to meet you.
What's your name?
My name is Takeshi.
Takeshi.
Do you know me?
I'm Hoshiyasuna.
You know me.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm Hoshii, a drinker.
I'm a famous person.
What?
Did you finally wake up?
Where is everyone?
They left a long time ago.
What?
Takeshi doesn't drink.
He went to bed right away.
I'm sorry.
What time is it now?
I completely missed the last train.
Don't be depressed.
Do you want me to take you home?
Is that okay?
Yes, it's okay.
Thank you.
At this time, I drank too much.
I was going to stay at home as a senior.
But...
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Are you really okay?
Takeshi.
Yes?
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Then...
I'll do it.
This is good.
Takeshi is surprisingly strong.
Please hold on tight.
Senior.
Are you hit?
What?
Your chest.
I can't help it.
Are you a virgin?
What?
Hey.
Your voice is loud.
It's funny.
Please be quiet.
Are you a virgin?
I can't help it if I can walk.
It's funny.
Takeshi.
Wait a minute.
Are you depressed?
Do you want me to wipe your feet?
Don't wipe my feet.
You're a virgin.
Wait a minute.
Don't give me a weird name.
I knew Takeshi was a virgin.
For some reason, my heart was dancing.
I wanted to play a prank on him.
Excuse me.
What are you doing, Takeshi?
Hurry up.
I told you to stop.
You're doing it again.
Because it's funny.
You're reacting again.
No, I'm not.
You are.
I'm not reacting.
No, I'm not.
You are.
Let's drink.
I can't drink anymore.
By the way, why is Takeshi a virgin?
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Oh, my God.
Senpai.
Hoshi-senpai.
I'm embarrassed.
It's okay.
Why are you embarrassed?
Of course, I'm embarrassed.
By the way, Takeshi.
Do you want to play a prank?
Yes.
Where is it?
What?
I think I put it here the other day.
Where is it?
Is it a bullet?
What?
Why don't you attack me?
You've been staring at my panties and boobs.
No, I didn't.
You're lying.
I said I didn't.
If you want to see it, just say so.
Don't be so down.
I'm sorry.
I've never taken a test before.
I'll teach you a lot.
Show me your tongue.
Good job.
Like this.
It's very soft.
Do you want to touch your breasts?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's my first time to touch your breasts.
Is it your first time?
How is it?
It's very soft.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Do you want to touch it directly?
Yes.
It's amazing.
How is it?
It's totally different.
It's very soft.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
You're good at touching.
How is it?
It's very soft.
I want to see more.
It's okay.
It's amazing.
Can I touch it?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It's very soft.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
Do you want to touch here?
Yes.
How is it?
It feels good.
Do you feel good?
Do you want to lie down?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
You're good at touching.
Do you want to touch your tongue?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It's very soft.
Let me touch your tongue.
Okay.
It's amazing.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Thank you.
Touch it directly.
Yes.
It's very soft.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Touch here and lick your lips.
Okay.
It feels good.
What's wrong?
Do you feel better?
It's hard.
I can't bear it.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's okay.
It's amazing.
It hurts.
Are you okay?
It feels good.
I'll do it again.
Okay.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Takeshi.
I can't bear it.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I can't bear it.
It's okay.
It's still big.
Do you want me to do it again?
Not yet.
Are you okay?
Can I stroke you?
Yes.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
It hurts.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
It's big.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's coming out.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
It's still big.
Yes.
Do you want to do something?
I want to stroke you.
Do you?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Can you do it?
Why do you have it?
My ex-boyfriend left it.
Here?
Yes.
It's right.
It hurts.
Come here.
Are you okay?
Here?
Wait.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's big.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It hurts.
Wait.
It's gone.
Is it gone?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Let me see.
You have a lot.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It feels good, right?
Yes.
You have a lot.
Senpai.
I want to do it again.
Again?
It's okay.
I want to do it again with you.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I can't move.
It hurts.
It's gone again.
It's gone.
You're amazing, Takeshi.
Did it feel good?
Yes.
It's okay.
I want to do it again.
Again?
I want to do it with other people.
What do you want to do?
From behind.
Behind?
It hurts.
Takeshi.
It's coming out.
You're amazing.
You have a lot.
One more time.
You can do it.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Did it hurt a lot?
A lot.
Are you okay?
I feel so good.
You did your best to make me feel good, so I'll give you a reward.
What?
I'm happy.
You're amazing.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
I'll go.
It hurts.
You have a lot.
You can do it.
It feels good.
It hurts.
You're amazing.
You have a lot.
I'll give you a kiss.
It feels good.
You have a lot.
Did you wait for me?
One more time?
You're amazing.
I'm getting used to it.
I'm getting better than before.
It feels good.
You have a lot.
You're amazing.
Can you do it again?
I'll do it.
It hurts.
You're amazing.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
You're amazing.
You have a lot.
It feels good.
You're amazing.
You have a lot.
I'll do it.
I want to do it again.
You have a lot.
I have a lot.
Do you want to stop?
I want to do it again.
You want to do it again?
I don't have a rubber band.
Go outside.
I'm sleepy.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I told you to go outside.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't stand it.
I told you to go outside.
I'm sorry.
It's still big?
I want to do it again.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's still big?
I want to do it again.
I can't take it anymore.
It's been a while since I had sex, and it felt good.
But more than that, there were so many firsts for me.
My head was empty.
The virgin I had sex with was far more sexual than I imagined.
I was so happy.
Good morning.
I feel so dizzy in the morning.
Really?
My penis hurts a lot.
I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
I want you to take care of this swollen penis.
Well, if it hurts, I don't care.
Thank you.
Lie down.
Wow.
It feels good under the penis.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
I want you to touch my nipples.
Okay.
It's hot.
Please kiss me.
Okay.
It's hot.
My nipples are twitching.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
It's been hot since this morning.
Yes.
Senpai.
Yes?
To the back.
Okay.
That's right.
Oh, no.
It's hot.
I'll give you more.
To the back.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
It's hot.
I'll give you more.
I gave you a lot.
Thank you.
It feels good.
I'm glad.
Senpai.
I want you to touch my nipples.
Okay.
It feels good.
My nipples?
Yes.
My nipples are swollen.
I can't see your nipples.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It seems to be swollen.
Senpai.
Please let me touch your nipples.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
Please let me touch your nipples.
I can do it.
Oh, no.
Senpai.
I can do it.
You've been working out a lot since this morning.
No, I haven't.
Are you going to sleep until lunch?
I'm going to make lunch.
Okay.
I'm going to make lunch soon.
I'm good at cooking.
I drank too much yesterday, so I'm making miso soup.
I'm good, aren't I?
Your butt is very erotic.
What are you talking about?
Are you kidding me?
I'm kidding.
You're kidding.
You drank too much yesterday.
I'm sorry.
But my nipples hurt again.
But I'm still cooking.
Your butt...
Can I rub your nipples?
Sure.
Thank you.
Wow.
It feels good.
You've been working out a lot since this morning.
Your butt...
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I'm not good at cooking.
It feels good, doesn't it?
My butt...
I'm sorry.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm sweating.
You're so energetic.
I'm sorry.
But I can still do it.
What?
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I can do it.
I can't stand it.
What?
What are you doing?
I know.
I just rubbed your nipples.
I haven't taken a bath yet.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I'm sweating.
It hurts.
I can do it.
Senpai, do you want to eat something?
Yeah, which one should I choose?
I'm sorry for bothering you.
No, it's okay. I'm the one who's sorry for not being able to make it to the end.
But delivery food is delicious, right?
Yeah.
Senpai, I've been wondering for a while, but what is this trophy?
I was in the track and field club.
I used to be the ace of the track and field club, even if I look like this.
But I got injured and quit.
Do you still have the training clothes from that time?
I do, but...
What? Are you kidding me?
Senpai, are you done changing?
Yeah, but I'm embarrassed, so close your eyes and wait.
Okay.
You can open your eyes.
Senpai, you look great in it.
Really? But I'm embarrassed.
Senpai, can I touch your chest?
Sure.
It's so soft.
I want to touch you more.
Senpai, can I touch you directly?
No.
I'm embarrassed.
It's the best to have your boobs sticking out of your gym clothes.
It's hot.
Senpai, your nipples are getting harder.
Do you feel your nipples getting harder?
It feels good.
It's hot.
You're sweating.
No, I'm not.
Really?
Can I touch you?
It's hot.
You're sweating.
I'm embarrassed.
It's hot.
It's getting hot.
Senpai.
It's hot.
Can I touch your stomach?
You're sweating.
It's hot.
I'm sweating.
More.
Doesn't it feel good when I put my fingers in your mouth?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Senpai.
Did it feel good?
It felt good.
Please make me feel good.
Okay.
Senpai.
Give me a kiss.
A kiss?
It's hot.
Please lick my nipples.
Okay.
Does it feel good?
Please touch my nipples with your left hand.
Please lick my nipples.
It's hot.
Please touch my nipples.
Please touch my nipples directly.
Please touch my nipples while licking my nipples.
It's hot.
You're selfish.
It feels good.
Please do it faster.
It's hot.
I can't do it.
Did it feel good?
There's a lot coming out.
It's still big even though I patted it like that.
It feels good.
It feels so good.
Wait a minute.
If you lick it like that...
What?
I'm going to lick it.
How is it?
It's coming out again.
It's coming out.
I'm going to lick it.
It came out a lot again.
I put it in my mouth.
It's okay.
It's dirty again, so I have to clean it.
I'm still going to do it.
You look so energetic.
I want to do it more.
Would you like to do more?
Get on top of me, please.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
I don't want it...
I don't want to...
I...
don't want.
don't want to...
I...
don't want...
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't.
I could do it.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
Ouch!
I'm dizzy.
I can't get up.
It feels good.
I'm going again.
I'm going.
Do you feel better?
Ouch!
It feels good.
I can't get up.
I'm going.
Do you want to go out again?
I can go out again.
I want to go out again.
I'm scared.
Ouch!
I'm going.
I want to go out again.
Show me your boobs.
Ouch!
I'm going.
I want to do it again.
It feels good.
I'm going.
Ouch!
I feel sick.
I'm sorry.
I feel sick because I'm with you.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
Why is he so strong?
I don't care because I'm with him.
But I feel sick because of him.
Ouch!
What are you doing?
What?
I'm taking a bath.
Are you taking a bath by yourself?
I'm taking a bath by myself.
Yes.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
I was so excited.
I got this much.
Did you get bigger?
Is it hot?
Yes.
It's hot.
Are you going to take a bath?
It hurts.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'm going to take a bath.
Okay.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I'm going to take a bath.
It's hot.
You're still okay.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Are you glad?
It's hot.
Yes.
I understand.
Excuse me.
What's wrong?
My senior called me.
I'm going home.
Wait.
I have to go now.
Stay with me today.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'm going to take a bath.
Does it feel good?
It's amazing.
I hope you feel good.
Yes.
I'm going to take a bath.
It feels good.
Do it again.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I'm going to take a bath.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
I've never done this before.
Please...
please get up.
He is scared because I didn't raise him until now, and he is very calm.
I loved him until now.
It's not easy to like you, but I love you.
I don't know what to do.
Ah-!
Please get up.
Here we go.
Ah!
Why did you do that?
I did it.
But I can still do it because my first leg is big.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm sorry.
Ah!
Oh!
It's back!
AAAA!!!
Everyone, I can't do it.
You can do it.
Ah!
It feels good!
Wow!
Ah!
Take it with your hands.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Let's go!
Ah
Oh, oh, oh, oh......
What's going on?
I... I saw something.
Uh-oh...
Give it to me.
I can't do it!
Ouch!
How many times have I said it?
But, Senpai, I still want to do it.
I know.
Okay.
I...
Good morning.
Take lots of pictures of me today too.
Then I'll see you guys in my next video! Bye~!