3 years later
fine
Teacher,what's now Sakui?
I'm sorry.
Can I use your study room after school?
Sure, but it's going to rain tonight.
You can't stay late.
If you stay, I can't go home.
I see.
You have a boyfriend, don't you?
What?
Well, I have a boyfriend.
Do you have a boyfriend?
What? Did you guess it wrong?
Well, my classmates tease me that I'm childish.
But I have a boyfriend, too.
I see.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Excuse me.
I have a boyfriend.
I'm sorry.
It's raining faster than I thought.
Is it okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I had a lot of work to do.
It's raining, but can you go home?
The train has stopped.
So, you can't go home?
Yes.
It's not early.
I'm in trouble.
Well, do you want to walk to the teacher's house?
What?
Is it okay?
You have a boyfriend.
I can't help it.
I have to study.
I can't leave him alone at school.
It's Saturday tomorrow.
You can go home in the morning.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
I'll get ready, so wait a minute.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
The weather is bad.
Yes.
It's humid.
Come in.
Thank you.
Here you are.
Wipe your body.
You'll catch a cold.
Thank you.
You're sweating a lot.
What?
Yes.
Take it off.
What?
No.
This is for your boyfriend.
I brought you a t-shirt, so wear it.
No, it's okay.
Thank you.
But it's okay.
I don't care.
You go over there.
Okay.
I'm boiling a bath, so wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I don't care.
You'll catch a cold.
You're very kind.
No, I'm not.
You're kind to boring students like me.
I'm glad I met you.
Thank you.
I've been a teacher for two years.
I'm glad I met a good student like you.
Excuse me.
I'll answer the phone.
Okay.
Hello?
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to do today.
Wait a minute.
I explained the situation.
It's my fault.
You don't have to say that.
I'm sorry.
I'm apologizing.
Why don't you listen to me?
Don't say such a terrible thing.
I'm sorry for showing you a strange place.
No, it's my fault.
I'm not drunk.
I always drink like this.
I have to do what I want to do.
I'm going to take a bath.
Let's drink something.
I drank beer.
It's a secret.
This is your tea.
Thank you.
Cheers.
It's delicious.
I feel like I'm drunk.
That's right.
Excuse me.
Are you okay to drink so much?
Yes.
You are very kind.
I wish I had a boyfriend like you.
That's not true.
You are very kind.
Can I come closer to you?
Yes.
Thank you.
Are you happy to be with such a person?
What?
If I were you, I wouldn't make such a sad face.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to do this.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
I really like you.
So...
What are you talking about?
You are my student.
That's not true.
I'm sorry.
What?
Don't make such a face.
Because I'm going to show you.
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm sorry.
You are very soft.
I can't do this anymore.
We are teachers and students.
But I really like you.
I can't do this anymore.
Why?
I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
You are very soft.
You are very beautiful.
I can't do this anymore.
No...
Oh...
means
you already
You feel good?
Did you feel good to be loved by me?
I don't feel good
Stand up
Your voice is out
It hurts
It's hard here
It feels good
It hurts
I'm always in front of you
You show me like this
I don't
That's why I can't stand it
It feels good
It makes me feel good
That's no good
Why?
It makes me feel good
I'll do it again
That's no good
It's harder than before
Doesn't it feel good here?
That's no good
I want to see you
It's embarrassing
It's a little numb
Don't look at me
My legs are numb
That's no good
It's embarrassing
It's embarrassing to be looked at like that
That's no good
It's beautiful
Did it feel good?
That's no good
Again
Your lower back is moving
It's not moving
It's moving
That's no good
I want you to touch me
Yeah.
What's up?
Hmm
Ah
Ah, it feels good
Teacher
Can I eat it?
No, you can't
Please, teacher
No
Then
If I go to the toilet, will you let me finish?
I understand
This is the end
Then
Hmm
Ah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah Yeah
Oh , oh oh, oh, oh,.
um
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah , yeah, yeah
Ah ah
Daughter, are you feeling better?
Oh, my hair got in your hair...
I know, my lain...
Oh, that's right.
I could've washed you properly earlier!
I'm glad this is over.
That's right.
You're my only daughter.
I want you to rub it a little with your breasts
It's the last one
Does it feel good?
Why?
Touch me a lot.
I feel good.