Next, I'm going to show you how to make a 3D printout using a 3D printer.
First, I'm going to make a 3D printout using a 3D printer.
I'm going to make a 3D printout using a 3D printer.
Master, I'm looking forward to working with you today.
I want to have a romantic relationship with you anytime, anywhere.
This is the first time I've seen such a thing.
I'm not sure if it's just me, but I've never seen such a thing before.
On the other hand, there's supposed to be a higher level test for brain nerve functioning.
Completing that test in all its members stressed me out.
But, as a programmer, I think taking such a test should also protect your brain, right?
I'm very curious why you feel like that, though.
I'm hungry.
I'm lonely.
Let's eat something.
The cat trafficking isdragonflies.
It's so mysterious.
Dragonflies are panting now.
I'm lost.
I'm lonely.
It doesn't belong to me.
Draw back a little.
I'm so lonely.
I see.
Master, I'm looking forward to working with you.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
If you need anything, I'm always available.
Please let me know if you need anything.
Did you just say that?
Yes, of course.
It can't be.
It must be a dream.
It's a dream, isn't it?
No, it's not.
Let me know if you need anything.
It can't be.
Let me check.
It's real.
Please sit down.
It's a dream.
Please lick it.
Thank you, master.
Ouch!
It's like a dream.
But it feels good.
It's a dream.
Please lick it.
Thank you, master.
It's a dream.
But it feels good.
Thank you, master.
It's a dream.
Can I do anything?
Yes.
Please sit down.
It's amazing.
It's a breast.
It's soft.
Do you like breasts?
Yes, I do.
Please touch it.
Can I touch it?
It's cute.
It's like a dream.
Can I touch it?
Yes, master.
It's amazing.
It's difficult, master.
It's wrinkled.
It's painful.
It's amazing.
It's beautiful.
It's painful.
Please lie down.
Yes, master.
It's amazing.
It's painful, right?
Yes.
It's comfortable, master.
It's comfortable.
Does it feel good, master?
Yes, it feels good.
It's painful.
It's amazing.
My butt hurts.
Please show me your butt.
Yes, master.
It's difficult, master.
It's painful.
Please show me your butt.
It's difficult, master.
Please show me your legs.
Did you pick it up by yourself?
Yes, master.
Yes.
It's shining.
It's comfortable, master.
It's comfortable.
I cannot make my hands hard.
Master, I can't do it.
Please spread your legs by yourself.
I want to see my master.
You want to see him?
Yes.
Okay.
He's so big.
It's so big.
I'm tired.
It's all right, it's all right.
It's all right now, it's all right, it's all right.
I want to have a shower
It's OK.
Hello?
You were right.
Hold on, Yukiko.
Okay.
Please don't go to sleep, Yozo.
I can't breathe.
You don't have to do this.
Please let me drink the medicine.
Did you feel good?
What are you going to do today?
I don't have any plans.
I'll drink the medicine again.
Yes, master.
Please let me drink the medicine.
You drank a lot of medicine.
I'm scared.
Yes, master.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Please let me drink the medicine.
I'm scared.
I feel good.
I can't stand it.
I'm going out.
It's a waste.
Let's do it in various places.
I'm going out.
Please let me drink the medicine.
It's a waste.
I'm going out.
Please let me drink the medicine.
It's a waste.
I can't stand it.
I feel good.
Don't talk too much.
It's a waste.
I'm sorry.
Let's go upstairs.
Master, where are you going?
This way.
This is the bathroom.
It's fun to do it in various places, isn't it?
Hold my hand.
Yes.
Master.
I'm sorry.
Sit here.
Yes.
Can you move?
I can move.
I'm sorry.
It tickles.
I can't do it anymore.
I feel sick.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It feels so good.
I feel so good, don't I?
I'm scared.
Do you feel good?
I feel great.
I'm scared.
I'm so tired.
Are you sure you can do it anytime, anywhere?
Of course, Master.
I can do it.
Master, how's the water?
It's the best.
Cheers.
It's warm and nice, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Ah...
I'm getting sleepy.
You look energetic.
I'm energetic.
I'm pinching your neck.
I'm getting sleepy.
Ah...
I'm so sorry.
I know.
But...
I'm worried about you.
I know.
I love you.
I'll protect you.
It feels so good.
Master's kiss.
I want a free reaction from the baby.
Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
you
me
You
to
encourage
received
you
me
ah
you
I'm sorry.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I think it's a good idea.
I think it's a good idea.
It's so hot.
This soy sauce.
The soy sauce was delicious.
It's a sane career, but you gotta be soft in conversation.
Is it my too?
Yeah, it's your job to be soft on people.
Because you have to be hard with the people you're part of.
So just keep doin' it, bein' hard, and lay back.
MURDER HANIBA
Master!
How do you feel now?
Great!
Monter is doing a lot of great things today.
You're right I've been working on it too much
Please do feel a lot better
It should...
That's nice and cool
Does it feel good?
You're good at it.
I'm glad.
I'll do this side too.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Last time I played, I intend to do it another way for some shooting devices for today.
This time, I'm going to change this game to AAA.
It's so good.
It's the best.
Does it feel good?
It's good.
I'm going to touch you.
I'm going to touch you, too.
Are you massaging there?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
You're getting bigger.
Did you like this one better?
I'm happy with this massage.
I'm going to touch you.
You're moving a lot.
Yes, sir.
I'm going to touch you.
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
I'm gonna touch you.
I'm sorry for the nuisance!
I'm going to sleep with my eyes open.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh, ah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, all
agreed
Ah ah ah
No So
Hmm?
Ok...
Hmm...
Alright...
Ah...
You're exhausted.
Doesn't it feel good?
So natural.
Oh
Oh my god
I can't help it.
Can you see me?
I can see you.
That's good.
I'm starting to feel a little dizzy.
Then move your legs a little more.
Okay.
I can't help it.
ah!!
Now the other side
Hmm
Me
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
bicro
Eh
My
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Hmm
Ah ah ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah , ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, va
I don't know what to do.
I think I'm going to throw up.
Are you going to throw up?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm going to throw up.
I don't know what to do.
Good morning, master.
Let's play a lot of ETS today.