I don't know if I can do it, but I'm going to do my best.
Do you have to work so much at home?
I'm not good at making materials.
I don't know if I can do it, but I'm going to do my best.
It's nice to see you two get along so well.
I'm sorry.
I want to finish it today.
Natsu, go to bed early.
You haven't been with me at all lately.
We're at a good age.
I can't do that every day.
Okay.
I'm going to bed.
Good night.
I don't know if I can do it, but I'm going to do my best.
Ikarashi.
What's wrong?
You've been acting strange all day.
I'm sorry.
I had a lot of things to do in private.
Did you have a fight with your boyfriend?
It's not a fight.
That's about it.
Okay.
Let's have a drink today.
But I haven't finished my work yet.
You can't finish your work if you're like that.
This is an order from my boss.
I'm sorry.
Let's have a drink today.
You can work tomorrow as usual.
Okay.
Thank you for everything.
Can I treat you to a drink today?
I'm hungry.
You're really not in a good mood.
Let's have a drink sometimes.
Okay.
I don't know if I can do it, but I'm going to do my best.
Ikarashi, you're drinking too much.
You're the one who invited me.
I feel like I want to drink today.
I don't mind, but I'm worried about you.
I don't mind.
I have a lot of work to do.
And I haven't been in touch with you lately.
I see.
Let's have a drink today and work hard from tomorrow.
Let's do that.
Cheers.
Listen to me.
What?
You're always on your computer at home.
You don't look at me at all.
That's sad.
Ikarashi, you drank too much.
I don't know.
I don't have power.
I can't get a taxi.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I feel sick.
Are you okay?
I see.
I can't help it.
Ikarashi, can you hold on a little longer?
Okay.
Let's drink a little more.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I drank too much.
I'm sober now.
I see.
I'm glad to hear that.
I took a room.
Ikarashi, can you hold on a little longer?
Can I?
I'm sorry.
I'll miss you when I get home.
I don't think so.
I wanted to date a kind person like you.
I'm sorry.
You're kind.
I can't see you like that.
What?
You make me feel lonely.
I can't forgive you.
I wouldn't have made you feel that way.
Senpai.
It's my fault.
You didn't cherish me, did you?
You wanted to do this, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
I'm looking forward to it.
I can't.
I'm sorry I made you feel like this.
I'm sorry.
Senpai.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Senpai.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Do you feel anything?
No.
What's wrong?
Senpai.
Let me see.
I want to see your back.
I'm sorry.
It's getting bigger.
Do you feel good?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I made you feel like this.
Do you feel good?
I'm sorry.
I'm glad.
I can't.
I can't do this.
Let me see your back.
Do you feel good?
Let me see.
Don't hide it.
I'm embarrassed.
It's getting very hot.
It's embarrassing.
It's soaked into your pants.
Do you feel good?
Can I see what's going on inside?
Open your legs.
Let me see.
I'm sorry.
It's soaked into your pants.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Let me see.
I can't.
It feels so good.
Let me use my hands.
I can't.
It feels so good.
I told you I can't.
But you're spitting it out.
Because you...
You wanted to spit it out, didn't you?
I can't.
It feels so good.
I can't stand it anymore.
Can I put it in?
It's okay, isn't it?
Please put it on properly.
Oh.
Oh, my.
It's spinning.
I'll put it on properly.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I made you wait.
I'll put it on properly.
Okay, let's go.
Oh.
Oh, it feels good.
You're shaking a lot.
Does the glass feel good?
Does it feel good?
It's warm.
I can't stand it.
You're shaking a lot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I can't stand it.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
He's weak.
Are you wrinkled?
Okay, I'll put it on properly.
I'll put it on properly.
Oh.
Wait a minute.
I'm going.
Wow.
Your own waist is moving.
It's sad.
It feels so good.
It's the best.
It's hot.
No, no, no.
It feels so good.
Come on.
Do you want more?
It feels so good.
It's the best.
Let me do more.
It's ringing.
Isn't it your boyfriend?
I'm going.
Hello?
I went to drink with my friend.
I was a little drunk.
I'm taking a break at karaoke.
I'll be back in the morning.
I'm sorry.
Good night.
I think you're resting.
I didn't know you were doing that.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Look at me.
What's wrong?
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
Do you want to go?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's too bad.
It's amazing.
It's tightening.
It feels good.
I'm going out.
I'm going.
I'm sorry.
It's torn.
Why is it torn?
Something came out.
I have to pull it off.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Why did it break?
I'm going to take a shower.
I'm going.
Thank you for your hard work.
Igarashi.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I'm sorry, too.
I drank too much.
I'm sorry.
Please forget it.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Natsu.
I'm going to Hokkaido tomorrow.
Are you going on a business trip?
You're in a hurry.
I'm in trouble because I don't have a boss.
I see.
I have to buy a lot of things with bullets.
I can't buy souvenirs.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to bed early tomorrow.
Good night.
It's over.
I can't stop it.
I'm going to bed.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Igarashi.
Can I talk to you later?
What?
I want to apologize for the other day.
If you keep doing this,
you'll have trouble at work.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I don't regret it.
Can we talk to each other?
Yes.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
You're living with your boyfriend, aren't you?
He's on a business trip from today.
He won't come back.
I see.
If he's near the office,
he might be seen by someone.
That's right.
What are you doing?
You said you wanted to talk to me.
I wanted to see you again.
I wanted to see you and Igarashi.
I'm sorry.
If you react like that,
everyone will be serious.
And...
Even if you say you don't want to talk to me,
I want to talk to you more.
Tell me.
You said you didn't want to talk to me.
You said you didn't want to talk to me,
but you're trying to kill yourself.
I'm sorry.
Igarashi.
If your boyfriend is on a business trip,
that means...
That's what it means, right?
No.
Igarashi.
You're already dead.
You couldn't forget what happened the other day, could you?
Did you imagine it?
I'm sorry.
Today,
I want you to blame me.
That's what I think.
Please lick my body.
Igarashi, it feels good.
You like to be licked here.
Please do it.
I'm sorry.
It feels so good.
Please lick this side, too.
Come here.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Please touch this side, too.
It feels good.
Do you want me to do it, too?
It's hard.
Please touch this side, too.
Please do it while drinking this.
I'm sorry.
Please lick this side, too.
It's hard.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Do you like shabu-shabu?
I don't like it.
I'm sorry.
I'll take off your underwear.
I'll rub your chest.
It feels good.
What's wrong?
I'll make you feel better.
I'll rub your chest.
What's wrong?
You're doing a great job.
You're still here.
You have to wear it.
It's okay.
I brought it today.
You're wearing it now.
I'll rub your back today.
Good boy, good boy.
I'm going to put it from behind.
Let's go.
Great!
Oh, it feels so good.
You like to be hugged from behind, don't you?
Come on, more.
No, no, no.
No, more.
Oh, it feels so good.
No, no.
I want to shake you more.
Senpai.
My hair is a mess again.
Oh, it's true. I wonder why.
What should I do? I only have one piece of rubber.
I'm in trouble.
Oh, it feels so good.
Well, I broke it last time, so it's the same.
No, no.
Come on, let's go.
Oh, it feels so good.
I was taking care of it, but it's a mess.
Wouldn't it feel better if the rubber was torn?
Wouldn't it?
Oh, it feels so good.
Wouldn't it feel better if the rubber was torn?
What's wrong?
Let's go.
Oh, it feels so good.
What's wrong?
Let's move it.
Oh, it feels so good.
That's a good massage.
That sounds good.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
!
Ah ah ah
Ah,
Why would they listen to sounds like that?
It provides a chance for them tolation.
Ok, it's done.
Senpai, I want you to drink a lot today.
Ah, kimchi...
Did you want it so much?
No...
Ah, kimchi...
Please make this kimchi harder.
Please turn around.
Turn around?
Ah, kimchi...
Do you lick such a place?
Does it feel good?
Ah, it feels good.
You just got out of bed, but you're very energetic.
It feels good.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it feels so good.
ah
Wow
amazing
so good
Inhale
Please sleep with your head on your side.
Ah...
It feels good.
We don't need to go to Japan anymore.
It's warm because the afternoon air is refreshing.
It's time to say goodbye to the kids.
The family is lonely.
The damaged hair found in the cooking closet is a waste.
So it would be great to make good use of the clothes we threw away.
So that you can't wash them right away with just a new dryer.
As I thought, you are a pervert.
Senpai.
How do I look?
You look great.
Senpai.
How do I look?
Please tighten your teeth.
Do you like this kind of thing?
I love it.
How do I look?
Please sit down.
It feels good.
It's getting harder.
It's getting harder and harder.
It's too hard.
It feels good.
It feels so good.
I'm going to use my mouth.
I want to eat more.
It's the best.
It feels so good.
Ahh...
Ah...
Your feeling?
This feels good.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Straighten up.
I can't stand it if I lick this kind of thing.
I can't stand it.