I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to cry.
Suzuki-kun, there you are.
Senpai.
Good morning.
Here you are.
Thank you.
You were scolded by the store manager, weren't you?
I saw it.
You have to open your eyes and talk.
Yes.
That's it.
How's your part-time job?
Do you get used to it?
I'm still a little nervous.
I can't do it well.
I see.
You don't have to think so hard.
Let's make eye contact again.
Yes.
Let's practice eye contact.
Look at me.
Yes.
Sorry, I laughed.
I'm serious.
Thanks to you, I feel better.
Really?
Yes.
Let's go out for a drink next time.
A drink?
Yes.
Let's go out sometimes.
I see.
I'll call you later.
Don't forget your schedule.
Yes.
I have a test at the university.
I'll wait for it.
Yes.
I can do it.
I see.
I'll call you later.
Okay.
Let's exchange LINE messages later.
I'll get my cell phone.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for making you wait.
It's okay.
Do you usually wear this?
Yes.
It looks good on you.
Oh, really? Thank you.
The sashimi at the restaurant we're going to today is really good.
Oh, really? I like sashimi.
You do? That's great. I like it, too.
Let's have a drink.
Don't you usually drink a lot?
I don't really have a fixed drink.
Shall we have a beer for now?
Okay, beer.
Let's get drunk today.
Okay.
Shall we go this way?
Yes, let's go.
Let's go this way.
Okay.
I'm so hungry.
Me, too.
By the way, is the last train okay?
The last train?
Yes.
Oh, it's still okay.
Oh, really?
Oh, I see.
That's good.
So, it's okay.
Wait a minute.
Oh, yeah.
The last train was early, wasn't it?
I'll look it up.
Okay.
Oh, no.
The last train has already left.
What should I do?
Is your house near here?
No.
My house is in Chiba.
Chiba?
Yes.
Then, you can't go home by taxi, can you?
I don't have enough money.
Oh.
What should I do?
Well.
I can't afford a hotel room.
Oh.
Then, do you want to come to my house?
What?
Can I go to your house?
Yes.
Then, let's drink again at home.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's almost there.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Are you sure it's okay?
Don't worry.
It may be a little messy.
No, it's okay.
Then, let's drink again.
Okay.
Let's go.
The next day.
Come in.
Oh, yes.
Your slippers.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Oh.
I'm so thirsty.
Me, too.
I drank a lot.
I think I drank too much.
Oh, it's hot.
What's wrong?
Oh.
Come in.
Oh, yes.
Please sit here.
I'll sit here.
Okay.
I'll change my clothes.
Don't look at me.
Oh, yes.
Oh, it's hot.
Hey.
Oh.
Ah, it's hot.
It's hot.
Did you see it?
No, I didn't.
Really?
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Thank you.
Well,
Yes.
Try it.
Cheers.
It's good.
This snack is good, too.
Try it.
Okay.
It's my favorite snack.
Really?
This one is a little spicy.
I like spicy food, too.
Really?
Then,
I'll try this one first.
Okay.
It's good.
It's really good.
It goes well with this snack, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
I love this snack.
Do you often drink this at home?
Well,
I drink this every day.
I see.
Do you drink this at home?
I drink this at home sometimes.
I see.
You drank a lot just now.
You're a strong drinker.
Really?
I want to be strong, too.
Then, let's drink a lot today.
Okay.
By the way,
Yes.
The manager is noisy, isn't he?
Oh,
Is he like that to you, too?
Yes.
He asked me to increase the shift.
I see.
Maybe it's because he relies on you.
Is that so?
I'm studying to be qualified, too.
I'm not just working part-time.
You're studying, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
What kind of qualification are you studying?
Well,
I'm studying to be a waitress.
You don't know much, do you?
Well, maybe.
I want to know more about you.
Thank you.
I forgot my cell phone.
Where is it?
What?
There it is.
I found it.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Look at this.
Yes.
This is my dog.
Isn't she cute?
Yes, she is.
But she's a grandma.
Is that so?
I'm worried about her.
I see.
She's always been small.
Yes, she is.
I haven't seen her lately.
I have to go home.
I think she wants to see you, too.
Do you have a pet?
No, I don't.
But I have a stray cat.
I have a cat.
That's great.
You're so kind.
I feed her.
Are you attached to her?
Yes, I am.
That's great.
I think you can use her as a pet.
What are you talking about?
Maybe.
Are you okay?
I think I drank too much.
I ate a lot.
You've been acting strange lately.
What are you talking about?
You're acting strange.
What are you doing?
Really?
I thought you might be lonely.
No, I'm not.
Really?
I'm fine.
I'm relieved to hear that.
Let's eat.
It's not good to eat too much.
You're so kind.
I'm worried about you.
Let's eat.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I was drunk.
I'm relieved to hear that.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for listening to me.
You're welcome.
I realized that I have a lot of things in my mind.
I'm glad that you like me.
I wish I had a boyfriend like you.
I'm glad to hear that.
You're so kind.
I'm always grateful to you.
Really?
I'm a little drunk.
Are you okay?
You were drunk.
I'm not drunk anymore.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I want to go out with you again.
I'm glad to hear that.
Can I go out with you again?
I want to go to the next restaurant.
Will you go with me?
Of course.
Really?
I haven't been there yet.
I went there last month.
Really?
Let's go.
Okay.
Can I kiss you?
I'm sorry.
Your lips are soft.
Yes.
Yours is softer and fresher.
Let me see.
Let me see your tongue.
Okay.
More.
Smile.
It feels good to kiss, right?
Yes.
I don't know what to do.
I want to touch your boobs.
Boobs?
I want to touch them.
Okay.
Touch them gently.
It's very soft.
It feels good, right?
Yes.
Are you nervous?
I'm very nervous.
Your face says so.
It's very hot.
I want to see them directly.
Do you want to see them directly?
Yes.
You're very sexy.
Can I?
Yes.
You're very beautiful.
Don't look at me.
I'm sorry.
You're very beautiful.
You can touch me.
Okay.
I'll touch you.
It's very soft.
Can I touch you?
Yes.
It feels good, right?
It's very soft.
Can I touch your nipples?
Okay.
What's wrong?
I'll touch you.
Okay.
It's hot.
It's getting harder and harder.
It feels good.
Doesn't it hurt?
No.
It feels good.
I want you to touch me harder.
Harder?
Yes.
Can I?
Touch me as you like.
Okay.
I'll touch you.
You're getting better.
Okay.
It feels good.
What's wrong?
I'm curious.
About what?
Well...
You...
You're getting better.
Do you want me to take it off?
Yes.
I want to see it.
Okay.
You're a pervert.
Don't say that.
I didn't think you were a pervert.
I'm curious.
I'll take it off.
Look at me.
Okay.
It's embarrassing.
Look at me.
Do you want to see it?
Yes.
Please.
Can you spread your legs?
Okay.
You're looking at me too much.
Do you want to touch me?
Can I touch you?
Yes.
Touch me gently.
Okay.
I'll touch you.
Like this.
Can I touch you like this?
It feels good.
Touch me.
Okay.
It's amazing.
I think I'm going to cry.
Let me move.
Let's go.
He's gone.
He's gone?
He's standing.
I'm nervous.
I'm excited.
I'll make you feel good.
Okay.
I'll make you warm.
I'll take off your panties.
Okay.
You're cute.
I'm embarrassed.
You don't have to be embarrassed.
I showed you my panties, didn't I?
I'm ticklish.
Are you ticklish?
Yes.
I'm ticklish.
I'll make you feel good.
Okay.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'll give you a lot.
It's very hard.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
It feels good.
You can't stand it anymore?
Yes.
Do you want to do something more pleasant?
I'll put it on you.
It's my first time.
What should I do?
It's okay.
I'll teach you.
Okay.
I'll put it on you.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Wait a minute.
Yes.
It's ticklish, isn't it?
Wait a minute.
Why did you do that?
I'm sorry.
You're cute.
It's ticklish.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't stand it.
So I put it out.
But you can still do something.
It's ticklish.
Wait a minute.
It's getting hard.
It's ticklish.
Stand up.
Okay.
I'll take it off.
Try putting it in.
Okay.
It's ticklish.
I'm sorry.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
I'll do it harder.
Okay.
It's ticklish.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
You're very good.
I'll move it for you.
It's ticklish.
It's getting really hard.
It feels good.
Wait a minute.
It's ticklish.
It's getting really hard.
I did it.
Wait a minute.
It's ticklish.
You're ticklish, too.
It feels good.
I'll do it from behind.
Okay.
It's ticklish.
I don't know where it is.
Senpai, it's very tight.
It feels good.
It's ticklish.
I can't move because it's too tight.
Come here.
It's ticklish.
I'll do it again.
I did it.
It's ticklish.
It's amazing.
I'll do it again.
It's ticklish.
I did it a lot.
I did it a lot, too.
It felt good.
I felt good, too.
I'm glad.
I'm sweating a lot.
It's hot.
I'll take a shower.
Let's go.
I'll wash your hair.
Thank you very much.
Doesn't it hurt?
It's hot.
It's better to throw it away than to use it.
It feels good?
Yes.
It's hot.
I have to make it clean.
It's ticklish.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'll make it clean.
Thank you very much.
It's ticklish.
You haven't washed your hair.
I'll give you a bath.
I want to wash your hair.
Look at me.
It's hot.
It's getting hot.
I'll wash your hair.
Is it hot?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
It's ticklish.
It's cute.
Hey.
Yes.
I have to wash your hair.
Please stand up.
Yes.
I'll wash your hair.
I'll make it clean.
Thank you very much.
Can I lick your hair?
Yes.
It's hot.
I'll wipe it for you.
It's cold.
Ah
Are you feeling good?
Yeah
Ah
Mmm
Show me a more pleasant face
I'm sorry.
Senpai, do you feel good?
Senpai, wait.
I think you can do it.
You can do it.
Wait.
He is standing up.
Senpai.
I was surprised.
What's wrong?
Let's take a bath together.
It's hot, isn't it?
Senpai.
Did you want to touch me?
Yes.
Touch me more.
It hurts.
It's soft.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
You stood up again after I touched your boobs.
I'm sorry.
I'll make you comfortable.
Yes.
It's hot.
Look at me when I'm licking your boobs.
Yes.
It's hot.
Look at me.
I'm weak.
Yes.
It's hot.
You look like you feel good.
You're cute.
What are you doing?
You look like you feel good.
It's hot.
You're cute.
You look like you feel good.
It's hot.
Wait a minute.
I can do it.
It's hot.
Wait a minute.
Don't look at me.
It's hot.
Senpai.
You look cute even without makeup.
Thank you.
I'm embarrassed.
I told you to look at me.
Show me more.
I'm not wearing makeup now.
You look cute.
Thank you.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I brought ice cream.
This is mandarin.
This is peach.
I'll have mandarin.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Ice cream is delicious.
Do you want to eat peach?
It's okay.
Ah.
It's delicious.
Senpai.
Do you want to eat this?
Thank you.
Can I eat this?
Mandarin is delicious.
It's hot, so it's good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I won't hold back.
Ah.
Wait a minute.
Don't look at my face.
You look cute.
Thank you.
Don't look at my face.
I was surprised.
What?
It's nothing.
Don't you have a stiff shoulder?
I have a stiff shoulder all the time.
I carry heavy things.
My arms are tired.
That's right.
It was the same when I started.
Ah.
Hey.
Do you want me to give you a massage?
Is that okay?
Yes.
I'll do it for you.
I don't want you to do it.
It's my job.
Ah.
You have a stiff shoulder.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Ah.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
I brought oil.
Oil?
Yes.
It's better to put this on.
It feels good.
It feels better than before.
Right?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Do you massage here, too?
Yes.
I have to massage here, too.
Ah.
All right.
Your whole body is stiff, isn't it?
Yes.
I'll give you a massage.
Ah.
Yes.
Lie down here.
Senpai.
Yes.
Are you a blue-faced person?
Yes, I'm a blue-faced person.
I see.
Ah.
You move a lot.
It feels good here.
Yes.
I'll give you a lot of massage.
Ah.
I see.
Let me see your face.
All right.
Ah.
It tickles.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
Ah.
When I see your reaction, I want to bully you.
Senpai.
What are you talking about?
Ah.
Your voice is getting hoarse.
It feels good.
Ah.
I told you to look at me.
Yes.
Ah.
I'm sorry.
It tickles a lot.
Ah.
I didn't touch you. Why?
I'm sorry.
Senpai.
It tickles.
Ah.
Do you want me to take off my panties?
Yes.
Ah.
I'm embarrassed.
Why?
I just took a bath.
Ah.
I'll massage here, too.
Here, too?
Yes.
Ah.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Ah.
I'll go again.
I'll go.
Ah.
Can I go now?
No.
Ah.
I can't go yet.
Oh.
Ah.
No problem.
What should I do?
Ah.
It's sweet.
Do you want me to lick it?
Yes, please.
What should I do?
Please lick my lips.
It's sweet.
Yes.
Wait, Senpai.
Why?
It's coming out.
Is it coming out?
I'm not serious yet.
It's coming out.
Wait, wait, wait.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
It's so hard.
Wait, Senpai.
I can't wait any longer.
Please, Senpai.
Can I go now?
Yes, you can.
Let's go.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
It's coming out.
I can't wait any longer.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Ouch, wait.
I'll squeeze it all out.
Wait, wait, wait.
Why?
You can still do it, can't you?
I can't wait any longer.
You can do it.
It's so hard.
I'm sweating.
I'll take a bath again.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Senpai.
Good morning.
I was surprised.
What were you going to do?
I was going to look at your face.
That's all.
That's all?
I'm sorry.
You're cute from the morning.
You're cute, too.
What?
Don't look at me.
I'm not wearing makeup.
You're cute.
Thank you.
What?
That's strange.
You're cute when you're embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
It feels good to kiss you.
It hurts.
Please lick me.
It's embarrassing.
Your sleeping face is cute.
It hurts.
You're good at licking.
Really?
You're getting better than yesterday?
I'm glad.
I'm thirsty.
Are you thirsty?
I can't help it.
I was surprised.
Was it good?
Yes.
Did I do well?
Please lick me more.
Does it hurt?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Does it hurt?
Please lick me more.
Does it feel good?
It's hard.
It's hot.
Why are your hands here?
It's embarrassing.
I'm taking a video.
I haven't touched you yet.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It's cute.
I'll lick you and make you feel better.
Wait a minute.
What?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I almost died.
It's hot.
Let me hug you.
Touch me.
Okay.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Do it harder.
It's amazing.
Wait.
No.
I might die.
It's hot.
You did a great job.
Ai-chan.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
I cried a lot.
I can't stand it anymore.
Me, too.
It's hot.
Please lick my hand.
You're getting bigger.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
I can't stand it anymore.
Me, too.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
You're getting bigger.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm tired.
It's hot.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'll start from the back.
It's hot.
You're really good at this.
I'll be happy if you say that a lot.
I'll do it harder.
I can't stand it anymore.
What's wrong?
It hurts.
It's hot.
I'm sweating a lot.
It tickles.
Give me a kiss.
It's hot.
I'm sweating.
Give me a kiss.
I'll do it again.
I want you to give me a kiss this time.
It's hot.
You can wear it now.
Yes, thanks to you.
It's hot.
I'll do it now.
It tickles.
It's hot.
Does it tickle?
It tickles.
I can't stand it anymore.
You can do whatever you want.
It tickles.
I can't do anything.
You can do it.
It tickles.
I'll do it again.
I'll do it.
It tickles.
I have a shift today.
What?
Don't tell everyone.
Okay.
I might look funny.
Don't do that.
It tickles.