Cheers!
It's been a while.
It's the best.
It's been 6 years.
I miss it.
We used to drink every day.
I've been working overtime.
I haven't been drinking at all.
Takeshi is a social person now.
Yuko got married before I knew it.
I'm the only one who hasn't changed since then.
I'm just calling you.
I haven't changed at all since then.
No way.
I heard that you're getting along well with your husband.
Who told you that?
Everyone told you, right?
What?
You look happy.
It's been 5 years since then.
You've grown up.
Don't say that.
Yuko, how's your new marriage life?
It's fun.
I cook every day.
Isn't it amazing?
You didn't like cooking that much.
Didn't you burn the bread?
Don't make fun of me.
It's different from that time.
It's about time.
Let's go for the second round.
Your husband is waiting for you.
You're going, right?
I have to go to work tomorrow.
I'll go home after I drink this.
You're not in a good mood.
Let's drink again next time.
Let's drink again.
I'll put the money here.
Thank you.
See you.
Take care.
Thank you.
He's gone.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
You have to go to work tomorrow.
Yes.
I cook every day.
Yuka.
Can you stop using honorifics?
I don't like it.
I'm sorry.
Where do you live now?
I live in the suburbs.
Really?
Is the power outage okay?
No.
It costs about 15,000 yen by taxi.
It's the worst.
Let's go.
Takeshi.
What?
Do you want to come to my house?
But...
My husband is not at home today.
Okay?
Was it really good to come?
Yes.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This is for you.
Thank you.
I feel strange.
Takeshi is here.
Wow.
I miss him.
He hasn't changed.
No, he hasn't changed at all.
When was the last time you came to my house?
Since we broke up.
I see.
Takeshi.
This snack is delicious.
Do you want to eat?
I'm going home.
What?
Why?
I have to stay at my husband's house.
Let's have a drink.
Okay.
Cheers.
Album.
I took a picture with Takeshi.
Do you still have it?
What's wrong?
Takeshi.
I can't stand being with you anymore.
You can't stand it anymore.
It's ticklish.
It's hot.
Did you want to do that?
Sorry.
Look at me.
It's hot.
I can't stand it anymore.
Stand up.
It's hot.
Takeshi, it's ticklish.
It's ticklish.
Takeshi, can you do this for me?
Can you do this for me?
It's hot.
It's ticklish.
It tickles.
You like it, right?
I like it.
It tickles.
It's ticklish.
Use your hand.
It tickles.
This?
Do you like it?
It tickles.
Do it with me.
Take this.
It tickles.
Takeshi licked me.
I want to put you in a blanket.
Takeshi is very excited.
Yuko, too.
It tickles.
I'm happy.
I'm excited.
What should I do?
Show me your butt.
Open your legs.
What?
Is it okay?
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
It tickles.
I can't do it.
I ran away again.
I ran away.
I can't do it.
It tickles.
You can't run away with this.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I can't do it.
It tickles.
Were you waiting for me?
Did you want to do it with me?
Did you really want to do it with me?
I wanted to do it with you.
It tickles.
I'm happy.
Are you okay?
I think I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
It tickles.
What's wrong?
I'm not moving.
It tickles.
It's amazing.
I'm not moving.
It tickles.
It's hard.
It's getting harder.
It's amazing.
It's hard.
I'm not moving.
It's amazing.
I can't do it.
My head hurts.
It's amazing.
It's hard.
It tickles.
It's amazing.
I can't do it.
It tickles.
Don't look at me like that.
Your reaction is getting better.
I can't move.
It tickles.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Do what you like.
I'm so happy.
It tickles.
It feels good.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
Did you say something?
I said something.
I don't know what I said.
It's amazing.
Do it again.
It tickles.
You did it.
Do you want some water?
No.
Can I borrow your shower?
You know where it is, right?
I know. Thank you.
It tickles.
What am I doing?
Can I join you?
No.
Don't you like it?
I don't dislike it.
Excuse me.
Takeshi is a kind person.
He wrote what he thinks on his face.
I'll give you a hint.
It's a secret.
What is it?
I'm getting better.
No.
Wait.
Why?
I want to see it.
It tickles.
What is it?
I can't help it.
It tickles.
This?
You like it, don't you?
I like it, but...
It's getting harder.
What about this?
It tickles.
You're making a lot of noise.
I can't help it.
Do you like it?
Do you want me to tickle you more?
No.
It tickles.
It tickles, doesn't it?
I'll give you a lot of this.
It tickles.
It's hard.
It's getting so hard.
It tickles.
Do you know you have a runny nose?
You have a runny nose.
It tickles.
You're getting better.
I'm glad you have a runny nose.
It tickles.
It's hard.
It's getting so hard.
It tickles, doesn't it?
It tickles.
I'll give you a lot of this.
It's amazing.
It tickles.
I washed you, but you're dirty again.
You look good in a T-shirt.
Thank you.
Hey.
Do you want to drink again?
No, I'll quit.
I have to work tomorrow.
Do you want to sleep?
Can I borrow your sofa?
Don't you sleep with me?
I can't.
You don't have to.
What are you talking about?
I can't.
Good night.
What are you doing?
I can't.
You can't?
Wait.
I can't.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
What do you like?
It's not that I like you, it's that I hate you
Why are your ears so hard?
Wait a minute, stop it
Why?
Stop it
I said stop it
Why?
Wait a minute, it's going to come out
It's going to come out
It came out
I'm sorry Yuko
Let's go home
What?
I don't want to
Wait
Let's go home
I don't have sex with my husband
What?
Because I'm busy with work
I haven't been with him for about a year
But when I see Takeshi's face
I wonder if I can go back to that time
That's not fair
I'm sorry to bother you
Just tonight
I want to go back to that time
Because I'll forget
I'll forget everything that happened today
Does it feel good?
I haven't done it at all
I'm sorry
Do you still like it here?
It's fantastic
It's hot
I want to lick Takeshi's whole body
It's fantastic
It's hot
I'm being licked
I can't do it
It's hot
It's fantastic
It's been a long time
I smell Takeshi
It's hot
It's fantastic
I can't drink it
Can I drink a lot?
Drink a lot
It's fantastic
I can't do it
You know I'm very weak
It's fantastic
It's embarrassing
I'm weak
It's fantastic
I haven't licked you yet
I can't do it
It's fantastic
Don't make me do it
I can't do it
More
It's...
It's fantastic
You know it feels good, don't you?
Do you like it?
It's fantastic
It's been a long time since I slept
It feels good
It's fantastic
I want to do it more
It feels good
It's fantastic
Give me a kiss
It feels good
I like it
It's fantastic
Yuko is weak
Wait a minute
Let's drink together
How is it?
I can't do it
It feels good
Again?
Ouch
I can't do it
You can't do it?
Yes
Did you put it in?
If you put it in now, it will definitely hurt.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it's in there.
It's in there.
Ah, it feels good.
How about this?
Ah, it's no good.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it's in there.
Ah, it's no good.
It might go away soon.
Is it okay?
Ah, it's going away.
Move.
I can't move.
You can move, right?
Don't be mean to me.
Ah, it's no good.
It's in there.
There's a lot of white stuff coming out.
I can feel it.
Ah, it feels good.
It's amazing.
It's hitting me.
You like it, don't you?
I love it.
Ah, it's no good.
It's amazing.
Ah, it feels good.
It's no good.
Ah, it's no good.
Ah, it's really hurting.
Ah, it feels good.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Turn around.
Ah, it feels good.
This?
I'm going in.
Ah, it feels good.
It's in.
It's in deep inside Takeshi.
Ah, it's hard.
Ah, it's amazing.
Ah, it feels good.
Hey, look at me more.
Look at me.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it's gone again.
Ah, it hurts.
It's no good.
Ah, it feels good.
It's going again.
Ah, it hurts.
I'm going to move.
It feels good.
It's no good.
Ah, it hurts.
Ah, it feels good.
It feels good.
It's no good.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's no good.
Ah, it's amazing.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it's no good.
Ah, it hurts.
It feels good.
Help me.
It's no good.
Ah, it hurts.
It feels good.
It's no good.
Ah, it hurts.
It's hard.
It's no good.
I want to lose it.
My mouth...
My mind...
I want to lick it.
It feels good.
Ah...
Hey, Takeshi.
Hmm?
Don't go home until I wake up.
Nana.
Takeshi.
A letter?
To Yuko.
I'm sorry I couldn't keep my promise.
When I'm in this room,
It was like a dream when I was alive.
But now I'm in pain.
I'm sure this is for you two.
But five years later,
You were beautiful.
Thank you.
But...
Goodbye.
PS.
What are you thinking now?
Idiot.
I'm sorry.