Oh, I'm sorry.
Yes.
Then I'll have a single.
Single.
One serving.
Yes.
No, two servings.
Two servings.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Please wait a moment.
What?
Brother.
Chizu-san told me not to smoke.
No, that's right.
But I drank alcohol.
What?
If you forgive me, I'll be scolded by Chizu-san.
Satoshi.
Please say something to Nene-chan.
You really can't speak.
At times like this, you should say,
Nene-chan, I'm tired, so please be kind to me.
Brother.
Don't involve my people.
Oh, Maido.
Maido.
Oh, Sachiko-san.
Nene-chan, can you join us?
Yes, I can.
Sachiko-san's brother?
That's right.
He recently came back from Tokyo.
I'm Nene.
Sachiko-san is always taking care of me.
I'm sorry.
This girl is quite dark.
You don't look like me at all.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Please use that table.
Thank you.
I'm going to meet Haruko-san.
Okay.
Nene-chan.
Who is that dark girl with Sachiko-san?
Sachiko-san's brother.
I see.
You don't look like him at all.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
If you're looking for a part-time job, please work for us.
After you get a part-time job, you can drink alcohol at the store.
And now, the cute boss will guide you gently.
What?
Are you slipping?
Thank you, Nene-chan.
This girl doesn't have a job now, so I'll help her.
Right, Takeshi?
I'm really looking for a part-time job, so please think about it.
Nene.
Please serve this.
Okay.
Takeshi.
Why did you do that?
It's Yoshitaka salad.
What?
I'm a girl.
I'm sorry.
You're dark.
One Yoshitaka salad, please.
Thank you.
Hey.
You're dark.
Do it with a smile.
With a smile.
E-chan.
Don't bully me.
It's my important part-time job.
Is it more important than me, a regular customer?
Both.
What's that?
Are you drinking alcohol?
Is it good?
It's good.
Who is it?
Yasumiyan
I'm pleased that Yasumiyan came here.
He's the director of the class reunion.
I thought he was not gonna be here.
It would have been nice if he was in good spirits soon, but he is absent.
I think you don't know how lovely he is.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm a married woman.
A wife shouldn't look at her husband like that.
I don't know.
Hey.
Stop it, Takeshi.
What are you doing?
Hey.
Don't do that.
What are you doing?
Hey.
Don't do that.
What are you doing?
Hey.
Don't do that.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
I know.
Hey.
Someone is coming.
Don't do that.
Do you know what you are doing?
Hey.
Stop it.
I'm married.
You know that.
Hey.
Don't do that.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
No.
Can you hear me?
Hey.
Stop it.
I know.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
No.
I feel good.
What are you saying?
Why are you so angry?
I feel good.
Do you know what you are doing?
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
I know.
Please stop it.
Stop it.
I know.
I feel good.
Let me see your tongue.
You like it.
I feel good.
I don't know you like it.
Oh!
Ouch!
That's enough, really.
Spit it out.
I can't help it if you don't stop!
Stop!
Takashi!
Hey!
Hey, what are you doing?
Come on!
Hey!
Stop it!
Ouch!
Hey!
Stop it!
How long are you going to do this?
Ouch!
Hey!
Stop it!
Come on!
Hey!
Stop it!
Ouch!
What?
Let's do it again.
No!
Ouch!
Can you hear me?
Stop it!
Ouch!
What?
Stop it!
Hey!
Ouch!
Stop it!
I'm really angry.
No!
Hey!
Ouch!
Let's forget about today.
I'm going to change at home.
Please clean up.
What?
I told you to clean up.
Stop it!
What?
What are you doing?
It's been a long time since you had sex, right?
I put you in the shelter.
And you kissed me.
It's been a long time, hasn't it?
Hey.
What are you talking about?
What?
Stop it.
I remembered.
I got excited again.
That's enough.
Let me do it.
I don't want to do it.
Stop it.
I said I don't want to do it.
It feels good.
Look at me.
No!
I said I don't want to do it.
Your nipples are up.
I'm really angry.
It's okay.
I know I'm doing it.
If you don't do it, I'll tell everyone that I made you do it.
Is that okay?
What do you really want to do?
I said I don't want to do it.
Hey.
It's beautiful.
You can feel it.
No.
Stop it.
I said I don't want to do it.
Move your tongue.
No.
Stop it.
Move your tongue.
No.
Stop it.
Move your tongue.
Hey.
Stop it.
You did it just now.
Hey.
Stop it.
What's wrong?
Why did you do that?
Stop it.
Hey.
It's good here, isn't it?
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Please stop it.
Do you feel good?
Stop it.
Let's drink together.
I don't want to talk with you.
Hey.
Stop it.
Do you feel good?
Hey.
Move your tongue.
Stop it.
I love you.
Did you say something?
Hey.
Can you hear me?
Don't talk to me.
Move your tongue.
Do you feel good?
Stop it.
Look at this.
I don't want to.
There are two.
Here?
I said don't talk to me.
Why?
What?
I know.
Stop it.
This part is weak.
You've been doing this for a while.
Stop it.
I said I don't want to.
What are you doing?
You're crazy.
You're wet.
You're excited.
Do you feel good?
Shut up.
You've been doing this for a while.
No.
You should say no.
Shut up.
Do you feel good?
Stop it.
I said stop it.
I said no.
You've been doing this for a while.
Do you feel good?
I said I don't want to.
I said no.
I said stop it.
Don't move your waist.
Stop it.
I said no.
I said stop it.
Stop it.
Do you feel good?
Shut up.
I said stop it.
Do you feel good?
You have beautiful legs.
I said stop it.
Do you feel good?
I don't know what to do with myself.
You don't look well today, Nene-chan.
Did you do something to Nene-chan?
Ii-chan, that's not true.
I just have a slight headache due to low blood pressure.
That's why you're worried.
Did you take medicine?
Thank you for worrying about me.
I feel better when I look at Ii-chan's face.
If you say that, I'll go ahead of you.
This is delicious.
I'll grill the meat.
Nene, help him.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Hey.
I didn't want to hit you.
Hurry up.
Hey.
Stop it.
Are you listening to me?
Hey.
There's someone over there.
Hurry up.
Stop it.
Hey.
What are you doing?
No.
No!
You can't.
I can't.
No!
I really can't.
I told you not to.
No!
What are you doing?
Someone's coming.
Be quiet.
No!
I told you not to.
What are you doing?
I really can't.
Wait a moment.
I can't.
Go back to the store.
What are you doing?
Wait a moment.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
Did you finish knitting?
Yes.
I'm home.
What's wrong?
Hold me.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
I bought you a souvenir.
Let's eat together.
Thank you.
Hey.
What's this clinic?
I don't know.
What's this?
I'm going to treat you.
Thank you.
It may not heal soon.
But I'll do my best.
I can't.
I can't do this.
Why?
Nene's birthday
What?
Nene, happy birthday!
Thank you!
What's going on?
I don't know.
This is a private house.
If you're scared, hold your voice.
Stop it.
I don't know.
I'm over there.
Stop it.
I don't know what's going on.
I don't know.
I'm over there.
Go home.
I don't know.
I told you I don't know.
Are you listening?
I don't know.
Stop it.
What are you thinking?
I don't know.
Pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant,
pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant,
No...
Why?
Look at me.
No...
It's cold.
Look at me.
I don't understand anything.
Can I put my hand on your stomach?
I'm going to cry.
Why are you doing this?
I'm getting goosebumps.
I'm looking at a beautiful woman like you.
I want to break you.