It's a good atmosphere, isn't it?
Which one do you like?
I like this one
I really like broccoli
What do you usually do?
Do you have any hobbies?
My hobby is...
Actually...
I'm sorry if it doesn't make sense
Please tell me your favorite clothing style
It's pretty good, isn't it?
I go to Hokkaido
That's great
I want to go to the sea
I also want to go to the sea
Where do you usually go?
I usually go to Fujiyoku
Fujiyoku?
Where do you usually go?
I only go to cheap places
Cheap places?
Where is it?
Is it in Shimokitazawa?
No, it's not
I see
Cheers
It's hot
Are you interested in younger people?
I'm not interested at all
I see
She is like a child
Tomoko
I'm sorry
It's time to go home
I see
It's too early
See you at school
Bye
I'm going home
I see
Let's drink
Cheers
This is my boyfriend Hideki
Hello
This is my sister, Remo
Nice to meet you
Chiyuki, I'm going back to my room
I see
Take care
Thank you
I see
What are you looking at?
What?
What's wrong?
Nothing
Hideki
Are you listening to me?
Sorry, what?
Were you afraid of my sister?
No, I wasn't
Thank you for introducing me
You're welcome
I can't do it today
Why?
I want to kiss you
Then, let's do it
No, I have a period
Period?
Until when?
I can't do it for 5 days
5 days?
Then, my parents will come back
I see
I'm sorry
I'm going to the bathroom
I see
What?
What are you doing here?
Come here
Okay
What are you doing?
I'm sorry
What?
I can't kiss you
That's...
Do you always do this?
No, I don't
Anyway
You want to kiss me
That's...
I want to
It's a period
Good job
What?
Anyway
I'm going to drink it
Good job
What?
I can't do it anymore
I can't
You can't?
I want to do it more
What?
Hideki?
Where did he go?
He came back
Good job
I'm going to kiss you more
What?
I can't
Hideki doesn't come back
He has a bag
What are you going to do if he finds out?
Tell him I'm okay
What?
Let's go back
Go back?
What?
I want to kiss you more
I can't
What should I say to Chiaki?
I have a good idea
What?
Why don't you tell her you kissed her?
What are you talking about?
I can't do that
What should I do?
Please forgive me
Good luck
Bye
What?
I'm home
Chiaki?
I'm going to the convenience store
Okay
Welcome back
Good luck
How was the kiss with your sister?
Well
Tell me
It was good
Why are you so shy?
I'm shy
I'm sorry
How was it?
Well
I don't know
What?
It was good
You grew up
What?
Well
I'm home
Can I overwrite the scar on your face?
What do you mean?
I'm home
Am I worse at kissing than my sister?
No, it's not like that
Okay
I'm home
Open your eyes
Okay
Look at me
I'm home
Open your eyes
Okay
I'm home
Chiaki said she's home
Will she get mad if I tell her?
I'm home
Why are you closing your eyes?
I'll kiss you
Look at me
I'm home
What kind of kiss did you have with Chiaki?
I can't tell you
Why?
I'm home
What are you doing?
Show me your tongue
I'm home
It's okay if you don't like it
What's wrong?
You have a stiff neck
I'm sorry
It's okay
Make it look like you're kissing Chiaki
What kind of kiss?
Chiaki
Show me
Okay
Do you always do it like this?
Yes
Don't you do it harder?
Well
Do it like you always do
It's not like that
I'm home
I'll move my legs
I'm in trouble
What's wrong?
You have a stiff neck
I'm in trouble
Lick my arm
Okay
What's wrong?
You were licking my arm
No
I wasn't
I was too excited
I'm sorry
Do you lick here?
No
I'm going to give you a shot.
You're breathing heavily...
It quickly turned yellow.
Who is it?
I thought you hadn't given me your blood yet.
I'm getting sleepy.
My stomach is hard again.
Hurry up and take your pants off, or I won't kiss you.
What's wrong with your tongue?
Oh, I see.
I'm getting sleepy.
I'll touch you.
You'll touch me?
I'll kiss you.
I'm getting sleepy.
I want to get my pants dirty with my saliva.
Do you want me to touch you?
I want you to touch me.
Yes.
No, you have to touch me.
How do you usually do it?
Is that so?
I do it like this.
You're doing it so fast.
Show me your face.
Your hands are frozen.
I'm getting sleepy.
What are you doing?
I'll put my hands on your head.
Then I'll tickle you a lot.
Put a lot of my saliva on your head.
How do you feel?
Yes.
I'm tickling you a lot.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
I'm tickling you a lot.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to do it for you?
Yes.
I'm tickling you a lot.
It's very hard.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
I'm tickling you a lot.
Are you sleepy?
I'm sleepy.
You can't.
Why are you looking at me?
Do you want me to tickle you more?
You're very sleepy.
Look at me.
I'm tickling you.
Do you want me to tickle you more?
Yes.
Are you okay?
You're very sleepy.
Look at my hands.
Did you feel good?
You're very sleepy.
I'm sorry for doing this to you.
It's okay.
I suddenly feel sick.
I think this is a rust.
If you take this off, you'll feel better.
I'm sorry.
Can I go out?
Hello?
I'm at home now.
What time do you get up?
1 o'clock?
I'll make you a dessert.
I'm hungry.
Apply French breadcrumbs of your preference.
The croquette is done!
It looks scrumptiously delicious.
I'm trying to make spicy braised pork.
Well, my pork belly is still back in place.
I like raw pork better than sirloin.
I felt totally equivalent today.
But this is nothing compared to the pork ribs I ate yesterday.
It's been a while since I've been here, so I'm a little nervous.
I'm going to take a look at the inside of the building.
It's a big building.
I'm going to put it in my mouth.
I want you to touch me a little.
Do you want me to pat you?
Directly?
Yes.
But you might wake up.
Can't you stand it?
Yes.
Then, put it down.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I do.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I do.
Can't you stand it?
Yes, I can.
Do you feel good?
Then, I'll do something more pleasant.
It's hot.
Ouch!
Can you lick here?
No, it's hot.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
I can't lick here.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I do.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
It's hotter than before.
It's hot.
Can't you stand it?
Don't do that.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
Do you feel good?
Yes, I do.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I do.
It's hot.
I'll give you a lot more.
What should I do if you come back now?
Don't say that.
What?
Will you stop?
I want you to say that.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
Wait a minute.
Do you like it?
It's hot.
Don't do that.
Do you feel good?
I'll give you a lot more.
It's hot.
Wait a minute.
I'll give you a lot more.
It's hot.
All right.
See you.
She's not here.
What are you doing?
Hideki was there, so he was talking.
I see.
Hideki, can I see the light bulb in your room?
Sure.
Wait, don't open your eyes yet.
Not yet?
Wait a minute.
Okay.
You can open your eyes.
Can I?
Yes.
What do you think?
It looks good on you.
Really? I'm glad.
I'll take it off, so wait a minute.
What?
Are you going to take it off?
Yes.
I'm going to go on a date with Hideki next.
I see.
I got it.
Chiaki, I'm home.
I found the sesame pudding.
Chiaki.
Are you sleeping?
You're wearing it after all.
Chiaki.
Are you inviting me?
Chiaki, you smell like an adult today.
Do you think so?
It's the same as usual.
What?
Why do you say that?
Anyway,
you've grown up.
No, I haven't.
Are you excited because of my smell?
What?
Chiaki.
I went to deliver something to my friend, so I won't be back for a while.
By the way,
does this suit you?
Is that yours?
Yes.
I thought you'd like it.
Does it suit me?
I don't think so.
Yes, it does.
Let's do it again.
But...
Why don't you do it?
Can't I do it with you in your clothes?
No, it's not like that.
Let me take it off today.
Take it off?
Okay.
Do you like it?
Do you get it?
How do I take it off?
Let me take it off.
Like this.
I have to put it back.
Don't mess it up.
Did you fart?
No, I didn't.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel sick?
No, I'm not sick.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel sick?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Do you feel sick?
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel sick?
I want you to touch me more.
Here.
Here?
Do you always touch me like this?
Is that so?
I'm embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
You've grown up a lot.
Do you feel sleepy?
What?
I don't feel sleepy.
What should I do?
What's that face?
Wait a minute.
Do you feel good?
You've grown up a lot.
Wait a minute.
I thought I shouldn't do that.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
What's that face?
Do you feel good?
Wait a minute.
That's not good.
That feels good.
Do you want me to do it?
That's not good.
I'm jealous.
Do you feel good?
Do you want me to do it?
Next is my hair
It feels good
Feels good
What are you laughing at?
You look like you're in a good mood
Can I lick your teeth?
Feels good
That's...
Does it feel good?
Feels good
Wait, wait, my fingers are weak
What's wrong?
What?
What did you eat?
I'm at my limit
You're at your limit?
Does it feel good?
I'm at my limit
Your limit?
Can I touch you?
You can't?
Can I?
Is it itching?
Look at me
There
My fingers are weak
Feels good
It's okay
My fingers are weak
It hurts
Why does it feel so good?
It hurts so much
I can't see anything
I can see a lot
It hurts
What?
Let's go
I can't
It's hard
It feels good
4 o'clock...
What's going on?
Does it feel good?
4 o'clock...
Baby...
Hiei-kun?
What?
Towel, put it here.
Thank you.
Today is your birthday, so take care of your body.
I got it.
I'm going out with Ten-chan, but wait for me.
OK.
Yes.
What?
Power outage?
I can't see you with the light on.
Power outage...
At this time...
Breaker...
Smartphone...
Where is it?
Don't be surprised.
I'm scared of power outage, too.
What?
That's right.
What shall we do today?
What do you mean?
The last time you had sex was very pleasant, wasn't it?
No...
But you're going to have sex with your sister today.
Why?
I'm going to break your bones so much that you can't have sex with your sister.
But...
Come here.
The lights are back on, aren't they?
Yeah, it's so bright.
Are you going to continue?
Yeah.
It's so hot.
It's hot.
Can I eat this?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
I'll do it from behind.
From behind?
It's hot.
It feels good.
Come here.
It's hot.
It feels good.
What do you want to do?
It's hot.
Let go of my hand.
Hey.
Will you go out with me?
No.
Why?
Because I'm only interested in human things.
So, be someone's man forever.