This is the story of a few years ago, when I took my husband and son, and went home and back home.
At the end of the year, I also came to show my close relatives, Hiroshima, and his family.
See you, Vega, it’s been a long time.
meet for a long time.
How many years.
My son, look, I am you.
Hi to you.
It is awkward, hello.
One of them, husband.
Go to shopping.
Please bring a cell phone.
Sorry, I can’t leave now, can I get you?
understand
Sorry please
Okay is?
I have not met Nico for a long time, so I will talk to you.
My son, have you grown up?
Sorry, I will say hello later.
In high school I was very excited.
You have grown up, and you have grown up.
Do not be too noisy.
Oh yeah
Can you go out and play out?
There was even superior.
The right man?
Instead of my brother’s son.
Hi to
My childhood acquaintance.
Assad is okay.
Yes, you are always well.
Are you soon?
Yes, because I’ve been on vacation for a long time.
You can slow down.
Yes is.
Oh, and then, Reika, let’s play.
to play?
Let us play together.
Let’s play, let’s play.
Reiki is troubled.
I am very much here, come here.
Let’s play there.
Want to go play?
Fuck to
Yes, next is
differently is
Oh differently.
I do not know.
It looks like a hacking.
Like a hack, this is.
Do you bet?
No to no.
It is scary.
Somewhere anyway...
Next time, next time.
It is awesome, well.
did it
Yes, next
I want a little.
The opposite.
I take well.
This is
Oh is
This cousin
Why Why?
Oh this
No, no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
No to
Is it not here?
No different different.
No to
has been
It has been.
If you lose, you will be punished by a game.
Yes is.
Is it so?
This is more fun.
Oh, it is me.
did it
I did!
This and
Oh I hit!
greatly
Oh, this has hit.
It is awesome.
I have 7 pairs.
I have 8 pairs.
Who is N?
I have 3 pairs.
Or lose yours.
We lost because it was a punitive game.
The punitive game is the strongest, so decide the punitive game.
Oh, yes, so close your eyes.
Have you not closed your eyes?
Are you close eyes?
Yes, it is shut.
What is?
Now what?
Keep your eyes closed.
Oh I am scared.
Do not cry.
What to do?
A punitive game?
The punitive game?
What are you doing?
Oh, a little
Her breasts and hair.
Give it to me.
It is a punitive game.
What are you doing?
10 seconds
I was sick.
properly
Her breasts and hair are hair.
No to
No longer
Oh, fuck, right, right, right, right, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now?
No, not more than that.
A bit of fucking.
Not ten seconds.
Fuck, no more, what are you saying?
It is not over.
The punitive game?
Yes, do not open your eyes.
not ended
It is over.
The penalty game is not over.
Time to prepare dinner.
soon to
The internet and the internet are coming back.
What are you doing, you?
Is it a game of bats?
Be too much.
The game is not over.
How was it? how was it?
It was very big.
Okay okay okay.
by Nirappuga
Very soft.
You had a great resilience.
I am jealous.
is hard.
No what.
But it was awesome.
You know, your breasts are awesome.
not to
As much as his own son.
I thought of such a master.
I could not imagine it at the time.
That day, again, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the brother, the
He is already sleeping in his room.
It is early.
What about the Dude?
Now she is taking a bath.
So, it is already time.
Time to go home.
Do you not stay?
No, I just didn’t intend to.
Did you not hear?
My mother stayed in Hiroshima.
If you pull it up above.
No need to be in a hurry, I was studying.
You have swept.
My father said he wants to go to the temple tomorrow.
Okay, so let’s get the car out.
I became with you.
All in all, thanks
When the girls came out, they took a bath.
So, let’s get it first.
Then, we will take a bath.
Oh, it is dumb.
All day long, it’s full of dirt.
If you do not take a bath, you will not be allowed to put the cloth in.
Oh yeah
Oh, and I got a bath.
Sorry to.
Do you dry your hair and sleep?
OK is
again
So we both go for a bath.
Three people can’t, but small.
So what do you do?
So, I can get in.
Oh is?
Okay, then we’ll take a taxi.
Wait a little.
What is.
I want to go in with you and I want to go in with you.
Okay you are stupid.
It really mixed, you.
You are a mixed fucker.
Because I do not.
Go to you.
No, it is okay.
Sorry to say, baby.
No, I and I too, my brother.
Okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay.
Why is.
Okay, and you are.
I am.
No to oh.
I want to prepare later.
Yes to.
Oh yeah yeah.
Take off your clothes.
Yes to.
Yes
How did school have fun?
Yes, it is fun.
well was
Is there something shit inside?
And really, football.
Oh, they are playing football.
Yes
Okay, it looks fun.
Yes, it is very fun.
Take it off quickly.
Yes
Do you study well?
It is hard to study, but I try hard.
What do you like?
Maybe chemistry.
It is awesome.
Boys are better at that.
Experimentation is very fun.
Yes is.
well is
I got a lot of friends.
Oh yeah yeah
well was
go out.
Oh yeah yeah
Nico is always.
Are you going to go in the bathroom with me?
Yes, I usually go to the bathroom.
Oh yeah yeah.
You always go in the bath with your mom.
Yes, I always stay with my mother.
Yes, they are together.
Do very harsh.
Oh yeah yeah?
Okay, you are very friendly.
Yes, I have to get back.
Yes, you have to be rough.
Does your mother do one?
Mostly when we come in.
Oh yeah yeah.
What happened?
Yes, nothing is anything.
Going to bath?
Yes
Great, big toast.
What are you saying now?
It is completely different from my home.
With her mother?
No so is.
Very big.
I will take it off soon.
Maybe a little different below.
Maybe it is.
I will take a bath.
But it is great, it is big.
No to.
Was it so big ever?
Oh is?
Talk about breasts?
Why are you watching?
Can I touch it a little?
Do you want to touch?
such a way.
Amazing, it is like this.
What are you doing?
It is awesome, soft.
Is this not heavy for Ricky?
Maybe a little heavy.
Oh yeah, that is.
greatly
No longer
This too something.
here here?
What is?
Are you bad?
Not so, even the girls.
Oh yeah, that is.
It is only my son.
Not your mother.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
What are you saying.
Try to touch it a little.
I did a little.
No to no.
The girl will be angry.
When I touched.
Because he is completely different from me.
That is it.
Because girls and boys are different.
No to
You understand?
No, do not touch it here.
Can I touch it a little?
for a second.
A second is long.
What are you doing?
It is awesome, something.
No to see.
I am not really calm.
That is yes.
No more no.
See also, end of.
No, I can touch the other kids.
Oh no, can you?
No to No.
I will be hated.
It was awesome.
Just a little more.
I will take a bath.
I understand
I’ll wash you behind.
really is?
You will not reach.
thanks to
Sorry to
Please please.
Take a bath.
Do you always wash your mom?
Because I always wash.
You are already good.
Yes is.
Good to you.
The previously
My house is always washed.
Is it so?
They wash well.
Viva the.
Do you live?
Yes
I washed it for my mother.
My mother washed and washed.
Do this so.
You should wash it clean.
Yes is.
by themselves.
Maybe they can’t wash properly.
Right on both sides.
Are you washing?
Do you think it is OK here?
Are you washing all the time?
here here?
I washed it myself here.
Oh yeah yeah.
Your mother too, isn’t it?
Yes, because it is not so big.
Is it so?
My mother is also very big.
Tomorrow is school, you are still on vacation.
Yes, I am still on vacation tomorrow.
This does not hurt?
Maybe it will be a little googling.
Can I wash my hands?
Yes, thank you
Then get a full bubble.
Yes
Oh, Mr. Dude, what are you doing on your holiday?
Or maybe go shopping.
With all of you?
Yes, or go to the movie.
It is great.
What are you always doing?
What is it.
Like a trick before.
It was strong.
You are doing a lot.
Because we can’t be all.
Yes is.
You must have friends.
Are you washing well?
Yes, they are washing well.
I am good.
Yes, I always wash it.
It is very big.
I guess so.
Okay, so much so big.
Would you like to be big?
Something is awesome.
My mother’s house is not so big.
and so.
It is large and very soft.
It is soft.
It feels good.
Yes, it feels good to wash.
Yes is.
It has become less.
At that moment, I felt how Massa touched his chest.
A little child’s hand over my chest.
It was a touch that sometimes made me want to touch the chick and doubt whether it was intentionally touched.
I was married for 10 years, and my husband and his family were not in a relationship, but despite the child, they were long-standing.
It is great, big.
Do you wash your hair with this?
They won’t wash so well.
I was the one who washed it every day.
I will wash it too.
I can wash it myself, okay.
It is OK.
I will wash it again.
Wait a little.
Until I wash it.
I can wash.
Yes, thank you
Spit it a little.
So I will wash it.
I will wash it tomorrow.
Are you washing well?
Yes, it feels good.
You have to wash it well too.
Oh yes
It will be dirty.
Maybe you washed it already.
Wash it a little more.
But
It is still dirty here.
No to
If this happens.
What are you always doing?
Oh that.
If you are, you will always be healed at home.
Oh yeah yeah.
Wash it a little.
So I washed it, so I will take it.
Are you okay? are you running?
Yes it is okay.
Wait a little.
It is always easy to get it, if you get it, you will be healed.
No matter what, I will not cure.
Can you cure?
It always heals, but it doesn’t cure.
I will cure you, so you shouldn’t get anybody.
Yes I understood.
You understand?
Yes to.
You can promise.
Do you cure?
Yes, I think it will cure.
How did you get older again?
It is okay, I will heal.
What this.
Oh Mr Rika.
Is this this?
Great this.
I feel weird at home.
It becomes pan.
Yes, it is okay.
It will cure well.
Yes to.
This will cure.
Really?
It is awesome.
Can your breasts be cured?
Yes, I will cure you.
It is so.
I did not know.
Your breasts are big,
I will be my thumb.
Yes is.
Oh well ooo.
Yes to.
Great, feel good
Feel good
Soon it will flow.
Look at my face.
Then go out sooner.
Feel good
I will lick you again.
In my case, it became harder quickly.
I am becoming more and more rough.
Okay to.
My own.
It feels good.
Something will come out.
go out
stimulated by the body.
Maybe I lost my calm too.
by Mr.
The joined shares.
Adults without losing.
I was erect.
Now I am confessing.
Even my office already.
I think he was nearby.
whatever it is.
I would say to be a slug.
Asha with you.
No relationship around.
I took it.
Something very clear.
Thanks to the man.
Maybe healed.
Yes is.
Then heal it.
A shameful story.
by Mr.
I will not forget that bathroom.
I comforted him alone.
This was my first time experience.
What happened?
Oh, I thought I would play with you.
Oh yeah yeah.
Well go up.
Oh, I will hinder you.
What, you are going to do?
I’m sorry, I’m out with Uncle Yuki today and we’re not going to come back until evening.
It is so.
Wait a little while and I will give you some fruit.
Oh yes yes.
Oh is?
by Mrs. Reika
A little, what happened?
What happened?
If not both, then okay?
No, but not so, right?
and right.
Do as in the previous paragraph.
No, that is a little.
The breast of Mica is very large.
It is large and very soft.
Right now.
Okay is it?
There is no Yuki.
Yes but not.
Reika’s breasts are so good.
I want to touch a lot.
It feels good, because it happens.
I feel so good to touch Reika’s breasts.
I love Reika’s big breasts.
I want to touch a lot.
What are you doing.
I cannot.
Show me more.
Her breasts are very large.
I can’t see more.
No to no.
Not a little.
Okay is.
There is no one.
Yes but
Oh, it is awesome.
I want yours.
Very large and beautiful.
A little
My mother touched her here.
You feel good.
Yes
You are a great blonde.
Mike’s breast is delicious.
Very delicious.
I want to drink.
It is okay, look.
Because there is no one.
Show me it.
difficult is
It is getting very hot here too.
Is it warm?
My heart is getting hotter.
Take this out.
To get out?
I want to see more of the umbrella.
I want to see better.
I am ashamed.
Spread it and show it.
Oh here?
difficult is
Awesome cat here.
It feels great.
The cat is great too.
It is damp, it is coming out.
It is wet.
It is down.
Also a cat.
It was so nice to be licked.
So, this is fine.
Ricky would feel good too.
It is dirty, something.
Something warm and awesome.
Tagged as  M.
Oh my sister.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
You are doing it while laughing.
Can you make it so? do not make it so much.
It is awesome.
When will I speak.
But
I will go down.
So feel good again.
Oh is?
I will leave.
You are getting bigger here.
Do feel good.
Do you want to feel good?
Yes
It feels very good.
Want to feel better?
I want to be more.
Sit here at me.
Feel good
Feel well.
Okay to?
OK is.
well
Feel good
Oh awesome.
It’s so great behind.
Oh Oh Oh
Stay full of.
Oh awesome.
It feels good.
Oh Oh Oh
Feels good?
Very strong, feel good.
Oh, awesome, oh, you are very good.
Feel good
Oh awesome.
It feels good, right?
Very good feeling.
You are very good.
It feels good.
I slept in the bed.
I feel good too.
Feel good
– to
and
You felt so good.
It felt very good.
Not great.
Can I feel better?
OK is.
Feel much better.
The Wife’s scream.
The voice of mother.
Overall and Sexual trash
Go to the purpose
Rain to ride.
by
The Devil is.
Eye Stack
Go out.
The EFI.
Act as a friend
Go to the North together.
O O O O O O O O O O O O
You are angry.
I felt good already.
Again the Mason.
I looked big down there.
Can you say that you have a fire in your body?
Do not go beyond.
I have surpassed myself.
That night again.
Mason was coming to stay with me.
I could spend a little while with Mason.
Mr. Masal also approached me actively.
My uncle is sleeping in the next room, and there is a young man there.
But I’m sleeping, so it’s okay.
I can’t forget my big breasts.
Okay to.
So make sure you don’t wake him up.
is big
It feels so good.
It feels good, my brother’s breast.
It is great, very big.
The house is soft.
It feels good, and we will fill it.
Mr. Shane said he felt good.
It is acid.
This is shit, awesome.
It felt good.
No longer was it.
by Tite.
Yes, great
stupid there.
I am doing nirvana here.
It feels good, you like it.
Eyes, and so on.
No to
Oh well
by
Feel badly
Oh awesome.
hurtly
Two fingers in.
It feels good to drink a cup.
Drinking is
Heat is
It hurts.
The voice came out.
Heat is
Oh yeah, I am sleeping.
Oh well feeling.
Do you hurt?
Yes to.
Okay is it?
It is OK.
If you are quiet, it will be okay.
4 days, feeling good.
This is great, 4 days.
Great, feel good
No, not so much.
Why, so great, so good.
Broken on his back.
If so, I will voice.
Why not already.
It hurts, it hurts.
greatly
Feeled
Why and why.
No, no no
What is happening?
Move to
Liked it.
greatly
It is inside.
Feeled
is bad
Sorry to
Feeled
It is awesome.
greatly
Oh... oh... oh...
...oh...
Oh no, no no no. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
Oh yeah, now yes...
... no...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh well...
Oh...
It feels good...
... no...
Oh well...
It feels good...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, it feels good
Oh yeah, yeah yeah yeah
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh yeah
Oh oh oh
This is this?
Put it out.
by breast.
OK is.
by Brist
Go out.
Oh my dear, you can.
I love my breasts.
Breasts smell good.
It smells good.
I really like my breasts.
My mother and her breasts.
Okay, I love it so much.
So much so.
It smells very good.
Feel good
I want to see directly.
A lot of sleep.
I love
Do you love it?
Yes
Feels good?
Yes, it feels good.
This is also very good feeling.
Drink a lot.
It is becoming more and more tough.
It feels good.
This too.
It is getting very soft.
This will be so.
Can I see?
It is very dirty.
The book is also very exciting.
Feel good
Something very good.
Be careful.
Feel good
Oh no.
Oh yeah
Feels good.
Oh oh oh oh
Oh is
Oh no
Feels good.
Oh yeah
Oh is
by
Drinking on your feet.
Great is
Rick, your ass is very big and soft.
The ass is great.
My ass is so soft.
Feels good?
Yes, it feels great.
Damn, you looked so good.
Shamefully shame.
Just the eyes of Pacquiao are so big.
Tastefully
It feels good, lick more.
Lick it again.
I was excited.
You are excited.
Feel good
Very good feeling.
Is it great feeling?
Let us do.
It will feel better together.
It feels good.
Mother, can I go to sleep?
My mom is very wet, too.
Feel good
Oh awesome.
It feels good.
Oh yeah
Oh oh oh
Oh is
Feel good
Wait a little.
I got it.
More below
Feel good
Feels good?
than feel good.
greatly
Feel good
Very good feeling.
Bombs on Milly when it burned.
Oh yeah
No to No! no to No!
Oh oh oh oh oh!
Oh well! oh well!
Feels good?
Yes
I feel so good.
already great
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
Oh oh oh
Then
Look at it and look at it.
Yes
Do you see properly?
Very well seen.
In her mother’s house,
There is blood in them.
greatly
I went to the back well.
Go to.
The mother’s breasts.
I want to move.
What is not what is not what is not what is not what is not what is not what is not what is not what is not what is not what is not what is not.
No to no.
More of
Feel well.
Feels good?
I will go.
Okay is?
Put a lot inside.
Feel much better.
greatly
Let me sleep.
Go out, go out.
Oh yeah yeah
Oh go out.
It felt great.
Let us do again.
Next time, when I come.
Yes is.
Okay is.
Oh, I went away.
Has Mason come?
Yes
Oh well, and you guys, Jinn?
I think I will be back soon.
I just went to buy dinner materials.
5th, the best of Lita.
Yes, yes is
Oh sorry.
You will be attached to your arm.
It is fun.
What is it, today.
and Hamburg.
I’m also happy with hamburgers, but what?
Curry is curry.
I don’t want to eat curry, I don’t want to eat curry.
But it is a hamburger.
See, Hamburg. – You are a kid, Hamburg is a kid.
Decide in Hamburg!
It is no longer my decision.
I think it’s already Thailand.
Yes, because they have already bought it.
It is Hamburg.
Oh how about.
I don’t know, you were told.
What are you good at?
Now it has decided.
This is the only time you have a ban on your relatives Masal.
Definitely so.
I want you to come home, I want to play.
Yes, I was hungry.
Thy there.
You are there.
I am hungry, so make it fast.
A shameful story.
I remember now.
Totally
Soon to soon.
I can never tell people.
Is it a meeting?
must come in.
Wait to wait.
Yes, I said, I bought it.