I heard from the teacher that you smoked at school and tried to rape a girl in your class.
Koudai, why did you do that? Tell me the reason.
Shut up. It's none of your business.
Wait.
What?
I'm not done talking.
Shut up.
Koudai.
Don't come out.
What man?
Huh?
What?
You called Koudai?
I did.
This is the first time I've ever seen a cat like this, so I'm a little worried.
I'm going to have to get used to it.
The sound is being recorded, so I think it'll be too loud.
Yokojima
Let's do our best!!
Hello! I'm Saki Mochizuki!
Oh! Yoshinobu san!
What happened?
Yes, I do.
Torima in this neighborhood?
Oh no, I'm scared.
Stealing underwear of a woman walking?
Wow, that's scary.
I understand. Thank you very much.
I don't think it's her.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Is this...
Kodai, come here.
Kodai
Hey
Wait a minute.
What?
This underwear came out of your room.
Shut up.
It's none of your business.
Explain what's going on.
It's none of your business, isn't it?
Explain it to me.
Shut up.
Wait.
Explain it to me.
Let me go.
Please explain it to me.
Please, Kodai.
Let me go.
It's none of your business.
Explain it to me.
I did it.
It's none of your business.
Really?
I didn't want to imagine it.
I didn't want to imagine that you and I were together.
If it's a death sentence, it's a death sentence.
Don't take your life so lightly.
What are you doing?
I can't forgive you for doing this to me.
If you're interested in women, you shouldn't commit such a crime.
You should kill me first.
What are you doing?
I was wrong.
If you want to hurt people, you should kill me first.
What are you talking about?
Kaoru.
You wanted to do this, didn't you?
I guess so.
Kaoru.
What's wrong?
You wanted to do this, didn't you?
Kaoru.
It's okay.
You can do it to me.
Kaoru, stop it.
It's okay.
Kaoru.
Kaoru, stop it.
Stop it.
Kaoru.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I didn't kill you.
I'll tell you everything.
I'm sorry.
Touch me.
It's soft.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Kodai.
Mom.
I didn't tell you this.
Touch me.
Mom.
Can you pet me?
I don't know what to do.
I don't know.
It's so hot
How about this?
It'll be fine.
Watch me.
Because you're so big.
Oh, my God.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
Not again.
Koudai.
This is what you wanted to do, right?
I'm sorry.
Fuck!
I don't know what to do.
I dont' know what to do.
And I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do
I don't know
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Anuk
Ayayyang
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Ah, ah ah ah
Is not it
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Yeah yeah yeah
I don't know what to do.
I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to throw up if I don't wash my face.
Here's your salad.
I'm going to take the exam.
What? Why so suddenly?
I go to school, but I'm worried about what people think of me.
So I get frustrated.
So I'm going to think about it.
No.
You won't change even if you take the exam now.
You won't change.
I'll make you realize it as a mother.
And I think you should give up.
What are you talking about?
It's your responsibility.
Mom.
What are you doing?
It's not too late to reflect on yourself.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
You can take it out.
You have to reflect on yourself.
I'm sorry.
Mom.
Are you going to sleep?
Yes.
Oh no.
All right.
What's wrong with you?
Don't be afraid.
Let go.
Mhm.
It goes...
like this...
Good boy.
He's coming out.
I'll make you reflect on yourself as a mother.
Good boy.
How long are you going to do this?
Until you reflect on yourself.
I'm reflecting on myself.
I don't know.
Only mothers know.
Good boy.
More.
There.
A little more.
Good boy.
Mom, I'm reflecting on myself.
I told you it's not enough.
Why don't you listen to me?
Kodai, lick him properly.
Good boy.
Kodai, I can see you.
Kodai, look at me.
Good boy.
Do you want it?
Do you want me to lick you?
What should I do?
Kodai, look at me.
Good boy.
You are so tender.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Good boy.
Show me your face.
Kodai, you have to be considerate of your mom.
Good boy.
Kodai, show me your face.
I'm going to lick you.
It feels good.
Good boy.
I'm going to lick you.
What's wrong?
Do you want more?
Cute.
Good boy.
Baby...
Come here.
I'm gonna take you now.
Shintani is so strong.
Yes, you're very strong.
He'd make good wife.
Good boy.
Come.
What did you do?
Baby's so nice.
Let's take Peggy home.
Come here.
baby needs pampering.
I see.
Let's go.
Come here.
Her belly must beel convincing.
Level up, shintani.
I don't believe it.
I don't know what to do with myself.
Did you fall asleep?
I understood.
Can you lick me?
Can you lick me a lot?
You are cute.
Head?
Shoulders?
Head and head?
All of them?
Can I lick you?
Can you lick me?
Can you lick me a lot?
You are cute.
I love you.
Good girl.
Oh, the ancient flower is hitting Puri-chan.
Oh my goodness
Oh my gosh, you are licking my nose.
Tana-kun
Give me your tongue
Come here.
Are you hot?
I'm sorry.
Can you see me?
Come here.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Ah!
I lost it!
You lost it?
There's nothing to go to.
Your mom isn't healthy enough yet!
Ah!
Aaaaaaa Aye Oh Rar
Eee Ah Ah Ah The
fossils while
Ouch!
You make a funny sound.
I have to clean up properly.
Ouch!
I have spoiled you a lot, so I want to raise you with love.
It's your fault.
You tried to deceive me and go out.
Ouch!
You will go out and do bad things again.
It's too late if you commit a sin.
Ouch!
I'll suck out everything.
You don't have to put up with it.
Ouch!
Does it feel good?
Ah...
What's wrong?
Don't be patient.
It's delicious.
I have to clean up.
Don't be patient.
I'm still standing up.
I want to put you in bed.
Don't be patient.
I'm still standing up.