I'm going to the library.
I see.
Take care.
Bye.
That was my classmate, Kousuke's mother, Yurika.
She's the woman I admire.
As you can see, she's beautiful, has a great style, and has a kind smile.
I've been in love with her since I saw her for the first time in class.
And when I look at Yurika, I always get a tingle.
Yurika's father, Kousuke.
Where should I put it?
Here?
Okay, here.
Hey!
It's your turn next.
Hurry up.
What's your mother doing today?
She just came back from shopping.
I see.
It's your turn next.
Can I go to the bathroom?
Sorry, I'll be right back.
Hello.
Welcome.
I was just about to bring you some sweets.
Really?
Wait a minute.
I can't wait.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
I can't breathe.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
Yurika.
What?
It's okay.
I'm sorry for what I did to you all of a sudden.
I'm sorry for having sex with my long-time husband.
Stop it.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry for what I did to you.
Wow.
You're strong.
You're so brave.
You're so beautiful.
I'm tired.
Calm down.
Let me see.
You're strong.
Calm down.
What's wrong?
I can't stand it.
Can't stand it?
It's getting harder.
I can't stand it.
Calm down.
Let me see.
What's wrong?
I can't stand it.
It's so hot.
You're drooling.
I'm not.
It's so hot.
I can't stand it.
Calm down.
You're drooling.
Let me see.
Wait.
You're drooling.
Don't make a sound.
It's embarrassing.
I can't stand it.
It's so hot.
Wait.
It's embarrassing.
I can't stand it.
You're drooling.
It's embarrassing.
I can't stand it.
I understand.
It's so hot.
It feels good.
It's hard.
You've grown up a lot.
What?
Make a sound.
I understand.
Calm down.
It's so hot.
I understand.
Calm down.
It's so hot.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's so hot.
It feels good.
It feels good?
Does it feel good?
Come here.
Give me a kiss.
Does it feel good?
Come here.
Calm down.
Give me a kiss.
I'm embarrassed.
It's so hot.
Don't put your finger in my ear.
Can I put my finger in your ear?
Take your time.
Don't put your finger in my ear so soon.
It's so hot.
Does it feel good?
Wait.
Wah!
Ahh!
Ahhhh!
He's out of breath.
Give him a break.
Ah! Wait, wait, wait!
Ah!
Wait!
Don't put it in so soon!
Ah!
Wait!
Don't put it in so soon!
Ah!
It's getting hot!
My shoulders are getting hot!
Ah!
Hmm!
It's true.
Let me cut this, too.
I got a cramp in my stomach.
Don't put it in without permission.
I'm sorry.
Help me.
Get up.
I got it.
Calm down.
I'm sorry.
I got a cramp in my stomach.
You have a lot of cramps.
I got it.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I can't hold it.
I don't want to sleep.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
I got it.
I can't hold it.
Don't put it in without permission.
It feels good.
I can't hold it.
Wait a minute.
Do more.
It's amazing.
I can see it.
It feels good.
What is it?
Touch me.
Do you want me to touch you?
It's getting hot.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
What's wrong?
I don't know.
It feels good.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
Don't move so much.
I can't hold it.
I'll do it.
Wait a minute.
Don't move so much.
It's embarrassing.
It feels good.
Do you want me to touch you?
What is it?
I understand.
It feels good.
Do you want me to touch you?
Let me touch you.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I can't hold it.
Let me touch you.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I came to my house because of my relationship with Yuki.
At first, I avoided it as an adult, but I couldn't control my desire.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
What's wrong?
I can't do it.
You did it last time.
You can do it, right?
Please.
I can't do it.
I'll make you feel better.
You can do it, right?
I can't do it.
What's that?
It's getting hot here.
It's not like that.
I can't do it.
It feels good, right?
Your voice came out.
No, it didn't.
I'll make you feel better.
I can't do it.
It feels good, right?
Why?
You did it last time.
That's right.
Do you want me to touch you?
You want me to touch you, don't you?
I'll touch you.
I can't do it.
I want to stay here a little longer.
But...
I can't do it.
Why?
You did it last time.
That's right.
It feels good, doesn't it?
How about here?
Or here?
I can't do it.
How about here?
Wait a minute.
I'm embarrassed.
I can't do it.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm embarrassed.
I can't do it.
It's amazing.
I'm hot.
I'm not hot.
I can't do it.
I'm embarrassed.
Can I look closer?
I can't do it.
I want to look closer.
I understand.
It's amazing.
I'm hot.
I can see it.
I can't do it.
I'm embarrassed.
I'll make you feel better.
I understand.
You feel good, don't you?
I feel good.
I feel good, but I'm embarrassed.
I understand.
Don't push me so hard.
I'm hot.
I can't do it.
I'm embarrassed.
I licked you.
I feel good.
I can't do it.
What are you doing?
I'm embarrassed.
I can't do it.
I feel good.
I licked you.
I can't do it.
I feel good.
Did you feel good?
I can't do it.
I feel good.
Did you do it again?
I told you I can't do it.
I couldn't stand it because I felt good.
I can't do it.
Let's eat.
Eat a lot.
It looks delicious.
It's delicious.
Do you like it?
Is it delicious?
Eat a lot.
How about you?
Is it delicious?
You are not cute.
It's delicious.
You are eating a lot.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
You are careful.
You are rude.
It's delicious.
Is this a salad?
Both pasta and salad are delicious.
Thank you.
You are rude.
You are eating a lot.
I'm hungry.
It was delicious.
Are you still eating?
You can eat.
I will bring dessert.
Wait a minute.
KOSUKE.
I will help you.
I don't need it.
I will bring dessert.
It's okay.
KOSUKE is here.
I don't need it.
It's okay.
I don't know what to do.
I'm sorry.
Calm down.
It feels good.
I'm going to give you a shot, so calm down.
Wow, it's getting bigger.
It's amazing.
I'm going to give you a shot, so calm down.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Don't make a sound.
Kosuke is here.
Can I make a sound?
Yes, you can.
I'll take care of everything.
I'm going to give you a shot, so calm down.
It's a good exercise.
I gave you a lot.
Come back soon.
I'm going to give you a shot, so calm down.
Buy me some bread and eggs.
I'll pay for it.
Buy me the cheapest bread.
Show me your receipt.
Do you understand?
You can't buy me a snack.
I can't?
Can I have one?
No, you can't.
Only bread and eggs.
Do you understand?
Okay.
This is enough, isn't it?
Thank you.
I'll buy it.
Don't buy anything extra.
Okay.
See you later.
At this time...
Yuuki-kun may have asked me for help.
I'm too young.
I can't stand a young man.
I tied my son's eyes and continued our relationship.
Don't get upset.
Ahhhh!
It feels great
What?
You can don't move so much like that.
Ah, it feels good.
More, more.
Before you come back.
It feels good, doesn't it?
No, no, no.
Don't get so angry.
I'm going to leave.
No, no, no.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's so hot.
I'm going to get bigger.
I'm going to get bigger soon.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're getting bigger.
Does it feel good?
I want to sleep.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's so hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I want to sleep.
Do you want to sleep?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I want to sleep.
I've never done this before.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I've never done this before.
How do you do it?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Let's go to bed.
Go to bed.
It feels good, doesn't it?
The next day
On this day, Yuuki-kun
wanted to stay at my house
and asked Kosuke to stay
He was sleeping in Kosuke's room
But
on that night
Yuuki-kun
came to me
while I was sleeping
It's okay if you stay quiet
It's okay
You won't be found out
That's not the problem
It's okay
It'll be bad if dad finds out
It's not okay
Please
It's not a favor
I want to do it
It's not good
if you say you want to do it
It's okay
I'm here
How do you feel?
It's good
I'm here
It's time
I know
Do you like it?
Do you want more?
It's time
today
Good night
It's your room
I'm so happy
Are you leaving?
We will take my hand off.
Slowly.
Are you worried that you will make a noise?
I can't take my eyes off of you.
Calm down.
Will you do something for me?
I'll do something for you.
So be quiet.
Can I hold my voice?
I told you not to speak.
Be patient.
Are you licking your husband's?
I haven't done that for a while.
You can lick him as much as you want.
I know.
If you speak, I'll stop.
Calm down.
Stop it.
I'll go ahead
Behave yourself
Mhmm
Right side
Okay
Aha
So dying
I understand
Good morning
Ava
I'm sorry.
I understand.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I want you to sleep.
It feels good.
I'll do it slowly.
I want you to sleep.
It feels good.
My relationship with Yuuki
gradually
escalated.
Even now,
I'm looking for a thrill.
In a forbidden relationship,
I felt
intensely.
I'm sorry
for being a
dirty and sinful
mother.
I can't stand it anymore.
I like this.
I'm sorry.
I'll be found out.
Then shut your mouth.
I want you to sleep.
I don't want you to speak.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Give me a hug.
I'm scared.
I don't think you can stand it.
Are you hungry?
Give me a hug.
I want you to lick my neck.
Does it feel good?
Give me a hug.
I want you to touch my neck.
I love you.
Ah...
It's so good.
I want to eat it.
Ah...
Can I put it in?
Um...
Ah...
Oh my god.
I feel so good now.
I'm going to sleep.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'm going to sleep.
It feels good.
You are worried.
It's scary.
I'm going to sleep.
It makes me feel great.
Sleep.
Can you come up slowly?
I don't know what to do with myself.
I can hear you.
I can hear you because I feel good.
I want you to feel better.
I'm sorry.
Wear the earphones.
It feels good.
Center of gravity feels good too.
Please feel relaxed.
I do as well.
When I take a deep breath, I will speak.
I can't stand it.
It feels good.
I can't speak.
It's okay.
It feels good.
Press a lot.
I like it.
It feels good.
Show me your belly button.
Are you okay?
It feels good.
It's over.
I can't move from the bottom.
It feels good.
I can't speak.
Let's do more.
Look at me.
It feels good.
I can hear you.
Don't move too much.
Be patient.
I can hear you.
It feels good.
Let me see your stomach.