I'm going to put it in a plastic bag.
Please put it in a plastic bag.
Welcome.
Thank you.
70,000 yen?
Yes, 70,000 yen.
Would you like this one?
Yes.
Cash?
It's 700 yen in total.
Yes.
Here you are.
I'm not sure if I can go home this year.
I don't have anyone.
100,000 yen?
No, I'm not in that kind of situation.
I might be in that kind of situation.
I'm not in that kind of situation.
I'll think about it when I calm down.
We're talking about it.
I see.
I got it.
I'll hang up.
Mom?
I want to go home soon and see my grandchild's face.
I want to do everything I want.
I want to do everything I can.
I don't know what to do.
I want to go home soon.
I'll do the rest.
You can go home and take a rest.
I'm fine.
You're tired, aren't you?
I got it.
I'm sorry.
I'll go home.
I'll leave it to you.
I'm sorry.
I have to go back to my hometown when I graduate.
I can only work for half a year.
It's tough, isn't it?
No, no, no.
I can work for a short period of time.
My wife doesn't have a husband, so she's helping me.
He's Suzuki Kazuyuki.
He's inexperienced, so he can teach me a lot.
I got it.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'm sorry.
The product is...
The product with a fast foot is in front of you.
Foot?
The expiration date.
The product with a fast foot is in front of you.
The product with a long foot is in the back.
Okay.
I want you to be careful.
The product name should be visible to the customer.
Like this.
This way.
Yes.
That's the basic.
Let's try this.
Yes.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Yes, yes, yes.
You're polite.
Thank you.
You look good.
Hey, Kazuya.
Yes?
I'm managing the shift.
Can you send me the expiration date?
Now?
Yes.
I sent it to you.
This much?
I hope you like it.
You don't have to put it in.
No, it's very helpful.
But...
Don't you have to go on a trip or something for the summer vacation of a fourth-year college student?
You're done with your job, aren't you?
I thought I'd do my best at my part-time job and send her a present.
You have a girlfriend?
Yes, at the same college.
I was so busy with my job that I couldn't meet her.
I thought I'd give her a present to cheer her up.
Thank you for today.
I look forward to working with you again tomorrow.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Here you are.
Thank you.
It's 398 yen.
With cash.
Yes, please put it here.
Yes, it's okay.
It's 100 yen.
I got it.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you very much.
Kazuya, can I have the cash register?
Yes.
Excuse me.
I'd like to pay 70,000 yen.
70,000 yen.
Hey.
Kazuya is not in a good mood.
What's wrong with him?
Well...
He broke up with his girlfriend.
I see.
Thank you.
Here you are.
Hey.
He's not in a good mood recently. Is he okay?
Well...
His girlfriend decided to work here.
Then...
He broke up with her because of a long-distance relationship.
I don't know why.
Because...
Isn't it harder to break up than a long-distance relationship?
So...
I think his girlfriend didn't like me that much.
I don't think so.
Because...
The bigger the feeling of love for a woman,
the more anxious and lonely she is.
I think it's a big deal.
Excuse me.
Kazuya.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Come here, please.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Those products don't sell well.
Is that so?
Yes.
How can we sell them?
What should we do?
Well...
Oh, it's okay.
Thank you.
Hey, Kazuya.
Yes?
Can I have your tea?
Yes.
I'll change my clothes.
No, it's okay.
I just want you to have my tea.
Oh...
What?
Nothing.
Okay.
Oh, and...
Yes?
Can I have your tea?
Well...
My husband is tired, so I want him to rest.
Oh, I see.
It's okay.
Thank you.
It's very helpful.
Can I have your coffee?
What?
What is it?
Can I have your coffee?
Oh, yes.
Here you are.
Thank you.
And your tea.
I don't have tea.
What?
You don't?
No.
Oh, I see.
Do you still have coffee?
Yes.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm going home.
Okay.
Thank you.
See you later.
Thank you for your hard work.
You're sweating a lot today.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I sweated a lot when I went to throw away the garbage.
If you had told me, I would have done it.
You're taking a break at home, aren't you?
Well...
I'm sorry.
You should take a break at times like this.
Yes.
It's so hot.
My underwear is wet.
I'm going to look around the store.
Okay.
I'm taking a break.
Did you see it?
No.
No, I didn't.
Really?
It's hot, isn't it?
Huh?
Hey.
Can I not look at it?
Yes, you can.
You were looking at it, weren't you?
It's hot.
Hey.
Are you nervous?
No, I'm not.
My husband is here.
But I want to comfort you.
What?
So...
I want to comfort you.
I'm sorry.
Can't I say I'm fine?
You want to see a lot of things, don't you?
We broke up, didn't we?
What do you usually do?
Huh?
Don't you feel uncomfortable?
Oh.
I'm sorry.
Don't you want to go to the store?
It's okay.
I'm free anyway.
Huh?
It's okay.
I really want to see it.
Huh?
It's okay.
It's okay. Look at me.
Look at what I feel.
Huh?
Your panties are really tight.
Do you want to see more?
More.
It's wet.
It's cute.
Touch me.
Huh?
It's hot.
It feels good.
You have long fingers.
It's hot.
Oh.
Move a little more.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
You're excited, aren't you?
Well...
But...
You're honest.
No...
What?
I can't take it any more.
What do you think?
I saw it, so show me.
Isn't it unfair?
Wait a minute.
Your panties are stained.
What's this stain?
It's stained.
Was it that good?
It's hot.
You can't do that.
Can I have the rest of the break?
Give me a break.
It's hot.
What?
I don't think it's a bad idea to make it this big.
What are you going to do after this?
What are you going to do?
What do you want to do with me?
I don't want to do anything.
You don't want to do anything?
You don't want to?
It's hot.
I think I'm going to puke.
You put it in, didn't you?
You don't have to put up with it.
Don't put up with it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Which one of us is moving now?
Me?
Kazuya?
Which one of us is moving?
It's hot.
I like that room, so don't stop me.
Stay still.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
Have you ever been inside?
No.
That's right.
You're a student.
I won't get angry even if you make fun of me.
It tastes good.
You can still do it.
You can do it, can't you?
Go to sleep.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's hot.
Stay still.
You're sweating.
It's hot.
You don't have to put up with it.
I told you before.
Don't put up with it.
It's hot.
You can still do it.
Touch my boob.
It's hot.
I wanted to come here.
Did you have a fight with the manager?
No.
I didn't.
I wanted to cheer him up.
I don't think this is good.
Don't you think we should be exposed?
No.
Let's enjoy it.
That's...
I didn't like it the other day.
Which one?
You didn't like it?
That's...
It looked like you were having fun.
I had fun.
It's hot.
Wait a minute.
It's hard to be exposed to the manager.
You don't have to be exposed.
It smells good.
I'm sweating.
It smells different from that person.
You don't have to put up with it.
I'm not putting up with it.
You're not putting up with it?
Don't be embarrassed.
It's hot.
Are you really going to do it?
What do you mean?
Is that what it is?
Is it erotic?
No.
You don't have to put up with it.
I'm not putting up with it.
I'm sorry.
You can't put up with it?
I don't want to be exposed.
You have to put up with it.
You look like you're in a good mood.
I'm sweating.
Show me a more erotic face.
That's amazing.
You're not putting up with it.
It's hot outside.
I'm sweating a lot.
It smells good.
What does erotic mean?
Does it mean it feels good?
Excuse me.
Don't make a sound.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I bullied you because you were cute.
Did you want to go?
Yes.
I'll do it for you a little longer.
I'll look inside the store.
I can't.
Why not?
I might be seen.
Don't you want to go?
I'm sorry.
Can you see me?
Yes.
How do you feel?
I feel the same as before.
I might be seen.
I can't.
I'm fine.
Look at me.
I'll be in trouble if someone comes.
No one is here?
Well...
What?
There's a customer.
I'll go.
I'm sorry.
Let me see your tongue.
What?
More.
Let me see your tongue.
It's hot.
I'm worried about you.
Sit down.
What?
What are you going to do?
What do you think?
Do you think so?
No.
Don't you think so?
I'm sorry.
It's good to be young.
It feels good.
It's hot.
What?
What are you looking at?
You know what I'm looking at.
It feels good.
Good morning.
Kazuya.
Can I take a shift tomorrow?
I have to write my graduation paper at the lab.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for today.
Yes, please.
Nina?
What are you doing?
I'm not used to being alone after the summer vacation.
You can't do that.
Well...
Thank you.
You know, I have a client.
Just a little bit is fine, right?
Well...
What did you do during the summer vacation?
Were you alone?
No.
Are you in trouble?
Nina...
Are you so worried?
Well...
Just a little bit is fine.
But...
If Nina finds out...
Nina will be in trouble.
Yes.
That's all for today.
Nina...
Look.
Aren't you excited?
This is 230 yen.
Thank you.
I've been wanting to do this for a long time.
I'm sorry.
I'm in trouble.
I'll give you a VIP seat.
Kazuya?
Yes?
Can you clean the bathroom?
Okay.
Please.
Nina...
I can't clean the bathroom.
Concentrate on me now.
But...
Do you want me to clean the bathroom?
No, that's not good.
Let's continue what we were doing.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I can't do it.
You can't?
No, I can't.
I can't do it.
You can.
I'm sorry.
Breathe into my ears.
I'm sensitive now.
It's because you didn't do it with me.
Touch my head like you did before.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It's hot even though summer is over.
It's my fault, isn't it?
It's hot.
Don't speak.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
You wanted to do it, didn't you?
Look at me as it is.
Okay.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I've done it.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
I've done it.
Yes.
Come in.
You were in a hurry.
Yes.
I was in a hurry, too.
What?
Nothing.
I was wondering if it would be okay if the manager came back.
He's sleeping, so it's okay.
I think you're bold.
Yes.
Look.
It's beautiful.
What?
Say it again.
Everyone is very beautiful.
Yes.
Won't you come?
You can come.
Yes.
It's beautiful.
It's a good sound.
Yes.
I have to do it directly.
It's beautiful.
Yes.
Let me do it.
It's beautiful.
Don't do it.
Yes.
It's beautiful.
Don't do it.
You can do it as you like.
It's beautiful.
It's hard.
It's because everyone is mean to you.
Am I that mean?
You don't hate me, do you?
It's hard.
Hey.
Come closer.
Yes.
You don't have to do it.
I'll do it.
It's hard.
Come closer.
Don't cry.
It's hard.
You were crying.
It felt good.
Is it over?
What?
I'm still working.
Is it over?
I can't finish it like this.
I want to do it more.
Let's do it again.
It's hard.
It came out.
Let's do something more pleasant.
Yes.
It's hard.
What should I do?
Yes.
It feels good.
I feel good, too.
I want to do it more.
I'm pushing here.
One more time.
I want to do it while looking over there.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
No.
I'm sorry.
I can see it.
I didn't notice the number of customers.
That's not good.
My waist is getting bigger.
Did I make too much noise?
I think so.
I'm sorry.
I didn't notice the number of customers.
I'm sweating.
I'm sorry.
I like this place.
I like it.
I'm sorry.
What is it?
It hurts.
I can't get up.
Let's go this way.
Can you still sleep?
I can't move.
Can't you move?
Can you move?
You may be found out.
It's too late.
I can't move.
I thought you could work until February.
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid I'll need to renew my contract when I get older.
I'm really sorry.
I wish I could work a little longer.
I didn't mean to bother you.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I see.
Actually,
I got a call from my girlfriend.
I'm going to retire.
I'm going to work,
so I decided to go out with you again.
That's why I decided to go out with you.
I see.
When I'm with you,
I can't stand it.
I'm going to quit my part-time job.
What?
I see.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you for everything.
Don't mention it.
It was fun.
I see.
Give me a kiss.
Let me sleep a bit more.
Let's do a lot of things that'll be a problem if people find out.
Stronger.
Touch it harder.
Yes.
Use a lot of your eyes.
All right.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
Take it out yourself.
I'm sorry.
Show me a lot.
I want you to be careful.
What should I do?
I'm sorry.
You can practice hard so that you won't be disappointed by me.
I want you to be happy.
Can you bear it?
I'm sorry.
I love your face.
I want you to be satisfied with me.
I want you to be satisfied.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I want you to be satisfied with me.
More.
More?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I feel uncomfortable.
More.
I'm sorry.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, come on epidemic
Hmm
Me
It's hot.
Look at me more.
It feels good.
It's hot.
If you don't listen to me, I'll quit.
Yes.
It's hot.
If you don't listen to me, I'll quit.
What do you want to do next?
Do you want to go to this store?
Yes.
It's hot.
Do you still have it?
I still have a lot.
It's hot.
You can still do it.
Can you do it?
Yes.
If you can, come to me.
It's hot.
Welcome.
Kazuya.
I'm going back to my hometown, so I came here to say hello.
I see.
Take care.
Okay.
Where's Mina?
She's working in the office.
I can't force her to work while she's pregnant.
It's her second month of pregnancy.
Congratulations.
Welcome.
I can't force her.
I told you she's fine.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
Did you come here to say hello?
Yes.
Mina, well...
I wish you happiness with your girlfriend.
Thank you for watching.