Yes to.
thanks to.
I am suddenly sorry.
He lives next door,
I say to be.
Oh yeah thank you.
I am pleased.
What did I do.
and that,
The air conditioning house.
The remover is unusable.
Oh to ah.
I am very sorry.
It is the same building.
I think the air conditioner is with you.
If you wish.
Can I borrow it now?
Okay, but okay
Oh, and if you should.
Let’s look at the air conditioner.
Oh, what a knowing one.
True, it is okay.
It will help you a lot, so let’s come.
Please I am sorry.
Yes, I could not press the button.
True is
I thought it was a remote.
I do, but I cannot.
Actually
There is a thoughtful section.
I cleaned the air conditioner a while ago.
At that time, they were dropping parts.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah.
It’s a season-like one, and I’ve never used it since.
If I had been waiting for a long time, I would not be able to find him.
and parts.
I’ve put it inside, so I don’t need to look for it.
Sorry, thank you very much.
I can’t see it from above.
I don’t want to look for this, really.
I can’t see this back.
Sorry, but I have to ask my master.
Oh yeah, it was so.
No, I am on a trip home.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Sorry, but really
Yes to.
Can I take it?
No, but this is not connected.
Is it really okay?
Let me take care.
Yes yes yes
Totally
If you said yourself.
Very helpful.
Thanks to.
Oh is
Get out of.
I feel like it has fallen too.
of this part.
I just can’t find the board.
Yes
Yes is it.
What to do.
If you don’t hit me, I won’t fix it.
I cannot lift it up.
Oh yeah
difficulty seems.
I know
You cannot see.
Oh yeah
Yes is.
Oh and where to go.
Was it?
It is true.
Oh myself
Let’s see.
Then
Can I look at it a little?
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Please please.
Sorry a little.
Sorry to.
Sorry, thank you very much.
Thanks to.
Yes to.
It helped greatly.
At least if you want this.
Anytime anytime.
No, really already.
Oh sorry to.
Please go.
There is only this thing.
No to no.
Give me some tea.
Thanks to.
This is this.
Sorry to please.
Please please please.
I never did it anymore,
I always take care of my master.
Well, yes is it.
This is something mostly a man does.
Yes is what.
So if you want to try.
With a little work, your body gets tired.
You can’t be sure, you’re tired.
Yes is what.
Is it okay?
As if something is sitting.
And this year, it has become worse and worse.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah.
So long ago, I couldn’t sit anymore.
If you want, I can massage a little.
No, not until then.
No, I’m not so bad, I’m also a massage worker.
Is it yes?
Do it often with your mother.
Parents are on the other side.
Yes, I’ll let you do it a little bit.
Is it?
If you sit on the other side, I’ll push it a little.
Thanks to.
Yes is
Can I do this?
Where is it, it hurts.
Really already
on the back below.
Oh yeah
around here.
Suddenly something around.
exactly to say.
It may hurt.
A little down or up.
I will slowly do it.
Please please.
Yes is
Oh is
You are very tight.
Yes is.
Oh yeah
Does it hurt?
The above is okay.
Oh is
You are good.
Okay okay
Are you not hard?
If it were good.
Normal on the sofa.
Oh yes?
Yes is
Thanks to.
It feels better here.
Oh well well.
well is.
No, not at all.
Thanks for the tea.
No, that is
You have done nothing.
I also watched the air conditioner above.
No No No No
Really sorry.
Does it hurt here or there?
is okay.
I think it’s good to have muscles on your ass.
Yes is
It seems like he has pain in his back.
Is it yes?
Yes is
I first time knew.
Why should you just leave it on this side?
It is getting easier.
is true?
Yes is
that
If you change a little, is it okay?
A little more
Four times the size.
4 times
I do a massage here.
Sorry to
This is
If you are not hard.
rather than this way.
Please please.
Yes is
How about?
well is
Press it a little stronger.
Sorry a little.
Sorry to sorry.
that
Yes is
Sorry to
Was it hurt?
No is
Not that way though.
Okay, but the strength is now.
is okay.
Then make a little more massage.
Do you hurt?
The massage is almost over.
What are you doing?
The massage
No trouble a little.
No problem.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
No to
Is it okay?
Are you okay?
Oh is
I am in Zelda’s ass.
Oh yeah
Oh well delicious.
Oh is
A little one.
Oh, and so
Oh awesome.
Oh is
Yes
well
Okay, it is shut up.
by
Oh yeah yeah yeah
by ilo
Oh the highest.
Oh well shit.
Once, once and once.
Oh yeah
Thanks for the air conditioner.
It is delicious, I make it.
Sit down a little and wait.
Oh yeah
Yes is
Wait a little longer.
Oh yeah yeah
I haven’t done that with my husband lately.
I was so excited about my ass.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
I am doing it.
It is a really good ass.
Drinking will come out.
Oh yeah
The year I drank.
I fell so down again.
green is
2nd
Oh whole
1 is
It looks comparable.
No more
It hurts.
Oh oh oh
Sorry to
again
I was excited.
Sorry, here there
Oh yeah
If if
Yes
Are you drinking again?
Wait a little.
I am on vacation today and I drink from day to day.
I am drunk, but wait a moment.
So then?
No to?
No but.
Yes to.
Nothing is anything.
It happened.
It is awesome.
Do not drink too much.
It happened.
It is OK.
OK is OK.
I get a call at this time.
Not difficult.
Be careful.
When is the color?
Have a good job.
Is this OK?
thanks to.
Try it to.
Yes to?
I was there, S.
I thought I would start again soon.
Maybe because his arm fell.
Can I help you a little?
Oh yeah yeah
How is?
Come to me.
Oh yeah
But
today is
What is?
There is a bit of a scratch.
Oh is?
Want to know?
Oh yeah
Yes is
Do you like it? I know.
Oh yeah
See also
Oh that?
It is awesome, right? sorry
Oh yeah
Oh well no.
greatly
Oh yeah
I really like your ass.
Yes because
Not a great echo.
by footage
Oh that
Can I get her hand?
Oh yeah
Laughing
I don’t always wear it like this.
Not so is it.
No to
I am sleeping, I want to lick.
No, no, no, I have to work hard.
Oh...
Heat is
No longer
I have not yet been operated.
Oh yeah
Yes is
What should I do?
Then
OK is
by Tanya
Take this head.
Yes is
Let it go.
This is
Yes is
thanks to
Then then
Using hot water.
I will go.
Oh yeah
Please please.
Yes is
Usually very tired.
Or maybe even.
Oh well
On the shoulder or here.
The Shoulder
And in oil.
by Warm
I will massage.
Oh yeah
But you have a very good body.
Is it so.
Is it okay to be stronger?
It feels great.
Are you tired of sitting around?
Well, of course it is.
Or?
What do I do, I am hungry?
Hungry and yes.
Okay then then.
Oh yes yes.
Please care about this.
Yes, yes is well.
Yes is
Mostly easily tired.
I have touched.
Oh awesome.
And also very good feeling.
here
Oh is
You are sensitive.
Yes is
Add a little oil.
Is this feeling good too?
Yes is
Oh yeah
It is a fucking.
Oh, oh
You are watching.
Oh yeah
Oh sorry, again
Good thing.
This too
It seems to be getting tough.
Oh yes yes
is
Can I see directly?
Oh yes yes
Do you feel good?
Yes is
Good was
It will become more and more hard.
Wait to.
It feels good.
Feels good?
Yes it is great.
Is it not hard?
No, it hurts a little more.
Does it hurt?
Yes, it feels too much.
Would it hurt?
Okay, it looks like it hurts.
Really be bitch.
Okay, I am up.
Would I wake up?
No and no.
Can not be?
Oh is?
Do you want to go with your ass?
The ass.
You like it, right?
Yes to.
Seriously
Do you not like being tricked?
This is good, right?
How is?
Oh the best.
It was hot.
Not well.
I can no longer endure.
Can I bear it anymore?
Oh well feel.
I like to watch you press.
Yes is
It really gets hard.
It feels good.
thanks to
Thanks to it, I grind.
Oh is
Yes
Or my own.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
and more
2nd
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Yes
No to
O wow wow!
by w w w w w w w w w
Ike is
Woody is pleased.
No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No
No more, no more
Not drinking too much.
Oh yeah
Is it okay?
I shall die.
I drank and came home.
A little, a little
Sitting and sitting.
Oh yeah
I just drank this and came home.
3 beer or 4 beer?
Drinking too much, as usual.
Do you have any gifts?
It is not a tourist trip, it is not a tourist trip.
A little.
If you sleep here, you will get a cold.
Please wait a little.
by Bad
You have to endure.
2nd
and more
No to no. No to no.
I will make a drink again.
Oh yeah
A little
Let me drink.
Yes yes
Oh well
Wait a little.
What to do.
Feel good
Oh well
Oh yeah
Wait to
Oh is
Oh yes, proof
Yes Yes Yes Yes
Oh yeah yeah yeah