I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
I told you to rest.
Okay, I'm going to tell you today.
Help me.
Give me some water.
It's so painful.
Hey, do you usually do that sound...
Oh, no.
Oh, what's next to you?
Nothing.
I'm just...
Oh, no.
Oh, you just had a blood test.
A blood test?
Yes.
Oh, sorry.
We're going to wrap it up with a warm-up set.
Please wait a moment.
No.
Oh, is there anything else?
No, I'm just a little...
The sound is noisy.
It's okay, it's okay.
No. 8 is fine.
Thank you.
Oh, Hizuki-chan, I'm sorry.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Please sit here.
Oh, well.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
If possible, a little more...
I want to focus on the story later.
I'm sorry.
No.
Oh, no.
Mom, mom, mom.
Wait.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
What is it?
It's going to be a
white lie.
Oh, come on!
It was refreshing.
This is it.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What do you want to talk about?
Do you always do this?
Well, yes.
It's not easy for a man to train his muscles.
Muscles?
Are you interested in it?
What?
No.
Oh, I know.
You came here to teach me how to train, didn't you?
What?
I'm sure you did.
You should have told me earlier.
I was the only one who taught you.
But it's okay.
I'm always training.
I can do 8 more sets.
Let's get started.
What?
There is a pair training that can be done by two people.
What is it?
It's a professional term.
It's called sex.
Sex?
You can do it with two people.
Wait a minute.
You can do it with one person.
You have a gentle kiss.
No.
You're good at it.
Really?
Do you do it?
No, I've never done it.
Really?
Yes.
You're very gentle.
You've been kissing like this for a long time.
When did you start kissing like this?
When did I start?
Do you train alone?
No, I don't.
You don't?
No.
You don't have to do so much?
It has something to do with training.
No, it does.
I've worked hard to get here.
I see.
You haven't worked hard.
This is the bathroom.
You haven't done anything?
No, I haven't.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
How is it?
It's beautiful.
It's amazing.
I always watch your videos,
but I've never seen such a beautiful
How is it?
You're listening, aren't you?
Are you listening?
I don't know.
You haven't done any training, have you?
If you start now, you'll be even more embarrassed.
Is that so?
Don't you need training anymore?
I don't need it anymore.
It's enough. It's beautiful.
It's delicious.
Isn't it soft?
Is this training?
It's amazing.
What is it?
I don't know.
You came here to do training, didn't you?
Then why did you come here?
What is it?
I don't know.
You're listening, aren't you?
I'm listening.
It's getting hot in here.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
Are you done?
I can't touch you that much.
You haven't been able to do any training.
Did you put on this much?
You're inviting me, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Why are you wearing this?
Do you always wear this?
Yes, I always wear it.
You always wear it.
That's amazing.
You're so beautiful.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you really embarrassed?
Yes, I'm embarrassed.
I can't see you being embarrassed.
You're beautiful.
You're so beautiful.
How do you feel?
I don't know.
You have to breathe.
Breathing is important in training.
Breathe in and out repeatedly.
That's great.
You're so beautiful.
It's hot.
Aren't you tired?
You have to train.
It hurts.
You can't do it easily.
You're so beautiful.
You have to train hard.
Training?
You have to move your hips.
How do you feel?
You're so beautiful.
Open your mouth.
I have nothing to say.
How do you feel?
It's hard.
It's different from a normal man.
It's juicy.
You're so beautiful.
Why are you drooling?
I don't know.
It comes out on its own.
That's good.
It makes a man happy.
You're so beautiful.
I can't stand up.
How do you feel?
You're so beautiful.
You like to lick your lips, don't you?
I don't hate it.
I can feel it.
Come on.
I want a pretty boobs.
Can I have boobs?
What?
I've never had boobs.
What a beautiful boobs.
Oh, it feels good.
It feels good.
It feels really good.
That's right.
Let's lick it together.
It feels good.
It's moving on its own.
How is it?
Great.
It's amazing.
It's big and hard.
Do you like it?
I do.
It's good.
I don't know why, but I'm not sure if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it's because I don't like it or if it
isn't it that, but when I see it, I think I don't have to worry about it, but I don't have to worry about it,
but
I'm going to have to praise my
Chiang Yen would have been lucky if he was not an extra teacher.
She had Globe'cheering for herthana when she knew she wasn't a teacher for so many years.
She might have to have gotten used to it.
She must have started offering them for the class which might have been big for trimester school,
but it was good for Chiang girl.
She was very happy.
She was going to need a teacher at the private time.
I'm so hot that I can't breathe.
I can't bring myself to do these things so easily.
I nuan to exercise when I want to be fit.
It is soager, so I was put under a coat !!
I was senzaering and made a santé cream instead !!
I want you to do the next step of the training.
Should I shake it like this?
You don't have to.
I want you to do it.
That's right.
That's great.
It feels good.
You can do this.
I feel good.
It hurts!
No!
No, no, no!
It hurts!
No!
No, no, no!
It hurts!
It's a little different from before, right?
It feels so good.
I feel like I'm going crazy.
It's okay, it's okay.
It hurts!
I can't do it anymore.
Ouch!
My head hurts!
It hurts!
It hurts, it hurts!
Don't cry!
It hurts!
I'm so tired.
I think I'm gonna cry if I do this.
Wait a minute.
It's so hard.
No.
I can't do it anymore.
Help me!
My back hurts.
How do you feel?
Oh no!
My back hurts.
That felt good.
Here's your tissue.
Thank you.
Here's your protein.
Protein?
It's really good.
Cheers.
How is it?
It's good.
It's good, isn't it?
It's different from usual.
It's for exercise.
When you're done drinking this,
let's go on a date.
On a date?
I'm so excited.
The next day
Please take a seat in the back.
We'll start the interview.
I'm Aoki, the manager.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Okui, the therapist.
Do you have your resume today?
Yes, I have it.
Thank you.
Here you go.
I'm 24 years old.
What do you usually do?
I'm a housewife.
Did you have a job before you became a housewife?
I was an accountant.
Have you ever worked as a housewife?
No, it's my first time.
I've never worked as a housewife.
I see.
Housewives don't have to be full-fledged.
It's not difficult.
It's not difficult at all.
Before we start,
we're going to do a proper training.
If you have any questions,
please feel free to ask us.
I understand.
First of all,
the reason why I want to work at home.
What kind of words?
Recently, my husband has changed his job.
My income has decreased.
So I want to make a living.
When I saw the job,
I thought my salary would be good.
So I applied for a job.
I see.
Do you have a target amount?
I'd be happy if I could get about 200,000 yen a month.
Number 20.
How many times a week do you work?
I think twice a week.
Twice a week?
Yes.
When do you start working?
If I can work right away,
I'd like to work.
I see.
How about next week?
Yes, I'll be fine.
When do you start taking pictures?
I see.
Do you have time after this?
Yes, I'll be fine today.
I see.
I think it's better to take pictures after this.
I think I'll be able to take a short break.
I can join this week.
Really?
Yes.
I see.
I'll ask Okuri-san.
Please let me join this week.
Yes, please.
What time are you free today?
My husband is coming home at about 7 or 8 o'clock.
Then I'll be fine.
I see.
Let's get started.
I'll be your client.
If you have any questions, please let me know.
I see.
Here it is.
Is it a little hot?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Here you go.
First of all,
there are towels and other things in here,
so please take them out.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Today,
I'm sorry that I'm the only woman
wearing a man's shirt
instead of a woman's shirt.
I see.
I'm the only woman wearing a man's shirt.
Are you all right?
I see.
I'm fine.
That's all.
Thank you.
I'll give you this.
Yes.
Then,
I'll change your clothes here.
I see.
It's a little...
Well,
it's hard to see at first,
so I'll hide it at first.
Yes.
Here you go.
Please change your clothes.
Yes.
Here you go.
Is it your first time
to wear a man's shirt
without a man's shirt?
Yes, it is.
It's my first time.
I see.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm worried
if I can do it myself.
But our customers
are pretty good at it.
I'm sure they'll be able to do it.
You know,
I'm inexperienced,
and I like amateur girls.
I see.
I'm sure they'll be able to do it.
But I'm a little nervous,
so I'm sure they'll be able to do it
for those who want to be healed.
Oh, it's upside down.
Please wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
Please take a seat here.
Actually,
I was asked to come to the shower
after I got my hair done.
I was asked to come to the shower after I got my hair done.
When you get out of the shower,
you can keep your back wet.
You can keep your back wet.
That's right.
I walk a lot.
That's why I wipe it off here.
It's like this.
Yes.
First of all,
I'm going to start with that side.
Yes, please.
At that time,
it's okay to wipe it off.
Oh, great.
It's the position of the throat,
and the back.
Yes.
It hurts a little when you get on top of it from here.
Oh.
If you put it on the big muscles of the buttocks,
it doesn't hurt,
and it feels good, so it's good.
Yes.
Can I come in?
Yes, it's okay.
Yes.
Excuse me.
How was it?
Did you get it from the nurse?
I have too many things to learn,
so I haven't got it yet,
but she taught me one thing.
Oh.
Yes.
Then I'll play the role of the customer next time.
Let's do what we learned so far.
Yes.
Let's do it.
Yes, let's do it.
Well,
then,
this is it.
Please change your clothes with this.
I'll wipe it off.
Yes.
Are you okay?
Well,
then,
can I do it?
Yes.
Can I do it?
Can I do it here?
Yes, it's okay.
Well,
then,
let's do it right away.
First,
please wipe it off.
Yes.
Please wipe it off.
Okay.
I wonder if it's okay.
I'm a little nervous.
Yes.
Oh,
I forgot the towel.
Excuse me.
Well,
you look strong.
Oh, really?
I've never
done a massage
by myself
before.
I don't know.
Well,
that's the standard.
Oh, I see.
I see.
I'll remember it.
It looks good.
Oh,
it looks good?
Yes.
Well,
so far,
it's done.
Yes.
Let's do it right away.
Next.
Yes.
It's done.
Let's do it right away.
Next.
Yes.
It's done.
Oh,
it's done.
Yes.
It's done.
Let's do it again.
Okay?
Yes.
It's done.
Let's do it again.
Yeah.
It's done.
Okay.
Next.
Yes.
Oh,
It's done.
Yes.
Next.
That was
I'm going to apply the cream.
Are you going to apply it?
Yes.
I'm sorry that I can't show you the oil.
I'll apply it.
I spilled the oil.
Let's move on to the next one.
Okay.
The next one is...
Was it the foot?
Let's see...
The foot...
Which one is still flowering?
One loaf...
One loaf, please.
I think it's better to do it more tightly.
It's quite difficult.
Really?
I think it's better to do it more tightly.
I understand.
It's better to do it more tightly.
Because men will be happy.
That's right.
Did you get any advice from your parents?
I don't think it's a good idea to touch it too much.
I see.
It's a serious matter.
That's right.
It's easy to get angry when I get a lot of advice.
I think it's better to do it more tightly.
Because men will be happy.
I see.
It depends on the customer's business.
That's right.
Yes.
It's a good idea to touch it more tightly.
That's right.
Shall we move on to the next one?
Yes.
Let's move on to the next one.
It's a little far.
Yes.
Let's move on to the next one.
Let's go.
Here we go.
What's wrong?
Because there are people like this.
That's right.
It's not good.
If you say that everything is bad, the audience will be sad.
That's right.
You have to cut it a little.
Cut it.
Let's cut it a little smaller.
But a little.
A little smaller.
No.
No, but.
It's nothing.
This is.
I heard that it's not good.
That's why you can't die.
You can't live.
That's right.
I see.
You haven't heard about it, have you?
I haven't heard about it.
Why don't you try it with fruit?
Fruit?
Yeah.
That's a little.
That's true.
200,000 a month.
Was it 200,000?
That's right.
200,000 a week.
I think it's a little difficult.
That's right.
How much does it cost to wash?
But.
It's a little.
I don't know.
But.
It's good to work at the same time.
That's right.
That's what we're all counting on.
That's a little.
It's the first time.
Let's put it under the clothes.
It's under the clothes.
It's not full nude.
That's what we're going to do today.
That's right.
I hope you can do full nude when you work next time.
Practice, practice.
I understand.
it may be
It may be
Can I do this?
Yes.
Let's continue.
You have a big nose.
Yes.
What?
You have a big nose.
Yes.
What?
You have a big nose.
Yes.
You said you would hold my hand if I touched you.
No.
You would be sad if I touched you.
Really?
Yes.
I think it's important to have a good relationship.
I think so.
What?
You need it.
No.
Yes.
You need distance.
That's the distance between you and the audience.
Yes.
What's next?
Didn't you get closer to me?
No.
I didn't get closer to you.
Wait.
What should I do?
Massage.
Yes.
I'll put more on the center.
Okay.
Yes.
I'll put more on the center.
Okay.
Yes.
What's next?
I'll put more on the center.
More?
Yes.
More.
I'll rub it.
Rub it?
Yes.
That's...
I'll rub it with my hands.
More.
I'll put more on the center.
More?
Yes.
I'll put more on the center.
I'll be happy.
On the center?
Yes.
Just like this.
Touch it.
Yes.
Like this.
I'm going to put more.
Um...
Like this?
I'll rub it.
Can you hear it?
No.
Okay.
I'll touch it with my hands.
Oh, my.
It's good, isn't it?
This is an option, isn't it?
Didn't you say it was hard to make money?
That's right.
If you make an option, you can earn 400,000 or 500,000 yen a month.
Is that so?
I don't think so.
That's good, isn't it?
It's a good option, isn't it?
You should put it on.
I understand.
Did you understand?
Kiss?
You've done it before, haven't you?
I've done it before.
Isn't it an option?
It's an option.
You can't touch it directly.
I think I'll take it out.
The distance between customers is the most important.
What is this?
I'm a massage shop.
You have to massage here, too.
This is also a massage shop?
I'll massage you directly.
It's easy, isn't it?
It's an extension of massage.
You can massage with this.
It's amazing.
Is it cheap?
I'm worried because I can do it for all customers.
You can do it yourself.
The way you hold it is important.
What's wrong?
Let's use your mouth.
I can't use my mouth.
If you use your mouth, you can get 10,000 yen.
10,000 yen?
Let's practice.
I don't have to practice.
It's a wrap.
Let's practice.
Such a good mood.
It's great.
Here you go.
It's a wrap.
Is it cheap?
What are you talking about?
That's...
That's the same as Fudogaku, isn't it?
30,000 yen per floor.
30,000 yen?
30,000 yen.
Oh, you need it, don't you?
No.
What?
Well, then...
No, wait.
Stop it.
Please stop it.
It's a practice room.
No, wait.
Yeah.
No.
Go to sleep over there.
No, wait.
No.
Stop it.
Please stop it.
No.
Wait.
It's just a little bit.
No.
It's about 30,000 yen per floor.
No, no.
It's okay.
No.
Wait.
Please stop it.
What's wrong?
No.
It's 30,000 yen per floor.
No, but...
It's delicious.
No.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
Really?
It's impossible.
No.
It's just a little bit.
No, it's impossible.
What?
It's impossible.
Impossible?
I see.
I'm sorry.
I really can't do this.
I'll give you 30,000 yen.
No, but...
No, wait.
You can help me.
No, but I can't do this.
Really?
It's just a little bit.
No, wait.
What?
No.
No, wait.
No, I can't do this.
Please stop it.
Really?
I don't know.
I see.
You can't do this?
I think it's wrong.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I'll go to the back and think about it.
Okay.
You should rest.
It's dry here.
I'll put some humidifiers.
Thank you.
You should rest.
Okay.
Bye.
Hi.
Hi
😥
It really hurts.
Be patient.
Don't cryzed.
She's not crying.
Yeah, not crying.
Even on the par sticky into him.
I don't know what it means to Reiki.
I don't care at all.
I'm not sure if I can do it or not, but I'm sure I can do it.
I'm not sure if I can do it or not, but I can do it.
Oh, it's sticky.
I'm nervous.
I'm not sure if I can do it or not, but I'm sure I can do it.
I've never done it before.
Oh, really sticky.
I'm sleepy.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not,
but I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not,
his rump seems like fine.
Oh my god.
I'm not sure if I can do it or not, but I'm sure I can do it.
I'm not sure if I can do it or not.
The baby was all the rage again, but it was all lawyer's fault, not necessarily a pregnant woman's fault.
A recent baby boy used to say several times that the kid kept thinking that he was a child, but didn't really realize why the
situation didn't go well.
Is it okay?
Are you okay?
I'm not going to die.
I'm going to die.
Definitely die.
i have really to get up tonight
i can't anymore, i have to go home microfiber
they just can't do any job.
They just can't see eyes,
they can't sign in everything you want them to do.
One mistake,
one mistake is crazy!
So...
I wanted to reflection your opinion to know
how did you make it get to this point?
Regionally!
I can feel it.
I'm full!
I'll put in applying the cream.
Wow, see that.
The cream is ridiculous…
I'm going to take a shower.
I'm taking a shower.
I haven't heard the sound of rain.
What's wrong?
Can't you open the door?
Where's the key?
Hasn't Mom come home yet?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to wait for Mom at your house.
I'm going to take a shower.
You can take a bath first.
I'll put your clothes in my basket.
Are you okay?
Do you want me to take it off?
Okay, good luck.
Okay.
Are you embarrassed?
Turn around.
Lift your legs.
Can I take a bath?
Can't I take a bath alone?
Okay, I'll go to the bathroom.
Okay.
Okay, let's go in.
How is it?
Did you warm up?
If you catch a cold, you won't be able to go to school.
Is school fun?
It's fun.
That's good.
You liked school, too.
Okay, let's go.
Okay.
I'm going to take a bath.
It's warm.
It was cold, so I changed my clothes.
I'm sorry I got in the way.
It's warm.
Did you wash your body?
It's dirty in the rain.
If you don't wash it with soap, it will be dirty.
I'll wash it for you.
Take it off.
It's big.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Yuto.
I think it's a good thing to have a big penis.
I think Yuto's penis is good.
I like it.
Really?
Yes, it's true.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to wash my body.
It's embarrassing.
I'm going to turn around again.
Aren't you embarrassed?
I'm going to wash my body.
I'm washing my body.
Stay still.
It's a really good penis.
Really?
It will be popular in the future.
I'm going to wash my body.
Turn around.
What are you doing?
It's dirty.
I'm going to wash my body.
What's wrong?
It's dirty.
I'm going to take a bath.
Please wash your body.
What?
I'm going to teach you how to use your penis.
I'm going to wash my body.
What are you doing?
Do you know what I'm doing?
I'm going to teach you how to use your penis.
How do you feel?
I feel weird.
Do you feel weird?
Don't you feel good?
I feel weird.
That's what you feel good about.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
It's getting harder.
Your penis is getting harder.
You're sensitive.
Good.
So cool.
Don't touch my buttocks, okay?
Do you feel good?
Amazing.
I want to eat Yuta's food.
Can I put it in like this?
I don't know.
I'll do something nice for you.
I'll put it in like this.
Amazing.
It feels good, right?
I want to eat Yuta's food.
Come in front of me.
Come over here.
Try moving with this.
You're good.
It feels good.
Amazing.
It's cold.
It feels good.
Can you move faster?
You're good.
It feels good.
I feel like I'm going to die.
Move faster.
It feels good.
Can I put it in like this?
Move faster.
Go, go, go.
It feels good.
Let's go to a different place.
Let's go.
It feels good.
I'm going to give you another drink.
It's harder than before.
It feels good.
Come here.
Try to put it in from behind.
There.
It's easier to move than before, right?
It feels good.
If you move too fast, I'll go.
No.
It hurts.
It's moving.
Try to sit here.
I'll move you.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Try to touch the cup.
Try to touch it.
It feels good.
Amazing.
I'm tired.
It feels good.
Try to touch the cup.
I'm tired.
It feels good.
Did you fall in love with me?
Try to lie down.
It feels good.
Do you feel tired?
Amazing.
What's wrong?
I feel like I'm going to fall asleep.
Try to touch the cup.
It feels good.
Amazing.
Did you feel good?
It's a secret from your mother.
If you fall again,
If you fall again, come to your aunt.
Come to your aunt.
Thank you for watching.
Good morning.
Is this all you have?
Oh, my hair is sticking out.
Oh, sorry.
See you later.
Could it be...
Mr. Namase...
Oh, it smells so good.
Oh, my hair is sticking out.
I said it's wrong.
It's a misunderstanding.
I wanted to send it to you.
You wanted to send it to me.
Yes.
Why did you sniff it?
Well, it's...
It looked like that from an angle.
I don't know.
You were sniffing my panties.
What?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You're interested in my body.
Yes.
Mr. Namase is pretty.
He has a big chest, too.
So?
Were you satisfied with the smell?
Yes, it was.
Hmm...
You're satisfied?
What?
I can't stand it when a guy who gets excited for me is in front of me.
What do you mean?
Hmm...
But you're already satisfied, aren't you?
What a pity.
Well...
It hurt, didn't it?
Hmm...
Are you okay?
You were so excited, weren't you?
Hmm...
Put your tongue out.
Where do you feel it?
Does it feel good?
It's getting really stiff.
Are you feeling better?
Yes, I am.
I can't believe it.
You did this to me.
You didn't want to be like this?
Yes.
I've been watching you.
I see.
I've never felt this stiff before.
This side is getting stiff too.
I haven't touched anything yet.
Come here.
It's getting really stiff.
Is it?
How long have you been doing this?
I've been doing this since last year.
You're such a pervert.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to lick me.
You want me to lick you?
Yes.
You're so sensitive.
Amazing.
It's like a dream.
It's getting really stiff.
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
It's getting really stiff.
Where does it feel good?
Everything feels good.
Everything?
Here too?
Yes.
It's getting really stiff.
I can't take it anymore.
It's been a while since I've done this.
I've never done this before.
You've never done this before?
I've never been licked like this before.
Really?
Yes.
This is my first time.
Stand over here.
It's getting really stiff.
Is it good?
Do you do this often?
I don't do it often.
Don't ask me that.
I'm sorry.
It's getting really stiff.
Can I pinch you with my boobs?
What do you mean?
I'm going to pinch you with my boobs.
Is this your first time?
It's getting really soft.
It's my first time seeing such a big boobs.
No way.
It's really soft.
It's getting really stiff.
It feels so good.
It's my first time seeing such a big boobs.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels so good.
It feels so good.
It's amazing.
It's getting really stiff.
It feels so good.
Stand over here.
I'm going to do it properly.
It's amazing.
I can't see anything.
It feels so good.
It's getting really stiff.
Can you see my wrist?
Yes.
It's getting bigger.
It's because of my boobs.
Really?
It's getting bigger.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels so good.
It feels so good to be alone.
Please calm me down next time.
What should I do next time?
I'll calm you down.
Give me a kiss.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Be careful.
It's so heavy.
Can I lick it?
Calm down.
Lick it slowly.
Slowly.
Is it like this?
It feels so good.
You did a great job.
It's good.
Is it good?
What are you saying?
I want to be an adult.
It feels so good.
It's so heavy.
My face is getting hot.
You did a great job.
Are you sure?
Have you ever licked a mango?
What?
Here?
Can you see it?
Yes.
Please lick it.
I can see it better than before.
It's so beautiful.
Is it your first time seeing it up close?
Yes.
It's my first time seeing it.
It smells good.
It's embarrassing.
Don't smell it.
Can I lick it?
Yes.
Here?
It's so good.
It smells so good.
It feels so good.
What?
What did you say?
It feels so good.
Do you feel good?
Why are you licking it so much?
You're good at licking it.
You're good at licking it, aren't you?
It's delicious.
Can I lick the inside, too?
The inside?
Sure.
It's delicious.
I want to lick it more.
Can I lick it?
Don't lick it.
Sure.
Tell me to lick it.
It's delicious.
Can you feel the tickling?
Sure.
I'm going to lick it.
It's delicious.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's getting harder.
It's amazing.
It's delicious.
It's my first time to lick it.
Is this delicious?
Yes.
It feels good.
Try to lick it.
Can I do it from the back?
Put it in from the back.
From the back.
Do you know where to put it?
Right away.
Don't make a mistake.
Here?
Is it okay?
It hurts.
It feels good.
Can I move it?
Try to move it.
What should I do?
It's really the first time.
It's okay.
It feels good.
Try to touch it.
Try to put more on me.
It feels so good.
It hurts so much.
Oh, no!
It hurts so much!
Is this really the first time you've done this?
Yes, it feels great.
Let's stand here then.
You can do it here, right?
Wait, wait, wait.
Where is it?
You don't know? You just did it, right?
Please hold it.
It's here.
Do you really like boobs that much?
I want a lot of boobs.
Then please make me feel good.
Please touch me more.
It feels great.
I can't do it anymore.
Are you okay?
Please do it here.
You want to try this, right?
Are you okay?
I can't do it anymore.
Just do it.
It feels great.
It's hot
This is the first time, isn't it?
Give me more.
I want more.
You are very good.
Then, please sit here.
You can still do it.
This feels good.
Give me more.
You love me, don't you?
I love you.
This feels good.
Do you want to cry too?
Then, turn around.
This feels good.
Try to move your body.
You can move until it feels good.
This is amazing.
This feels good.
You want to move more, don't you?
Move more.
This feels good.
You want to move more, don't you?
Yes.
This feels good.
I can't hold it in anymore.
Are you okay?
Did you put it in your mouth?
It came out comfortably.
It felt good.
Did you feel satisfied?
I'm very satisfied.
I'm not satisfied yet.
What is it?
What happened?
It's okay.
Just a little more.
It's okay, right?