The switch sound.
Good morning to you.
Tired of you.
It was quick today.
I have a little lesson from James this morning.
Will this foot break out?
The building after the war.
Because it moved well.
It was decided before.
Oh but
Shibuya graduated from school.
I’ll be here until March, so be sure.
Instead, graduate well.
I don’t know if you stay.
A little bit okay.
They almost reached the range.
So I will go.
Come to go.
by Mr.
I protected this apartment with you.
Next year, they finally destroyed.
I want students to relax and create a relaxing space to encourage the school.
Sometimes I will be a father, a mother, and support their lives.
After you died, I still took that thought over here.
Finally, we will be here.
Only one thing is restrained.
The 2045 Room, Shiguyam.
I will never see you again before.
I want to feel the warmth at once.
You are a guilty woman.
Yes is
Mariner, what is it?
I made meat for dinner.
I made too much.
I cannot eat alone.
If you want, please give me a little sham.
Okay okay to?
It looks good, thank you.
Wait to wait.
Shivam, is this the hot water?
Oh well
No, so it is fine.
Oh, and a little, a little.
Now I’m going to go for something, so let’s eat with the potatoes.
No, it is a bit dirty.
Can I eat it, can I eat it?
Please eat it.
Oh well well! This is very good, Mr. Curry.
really is? happy to
So, you still have two habits.
I wish you had pleased him.
It is very good, really.
Do you not make her?
Then you can make a delicious meal every day.
I am not fashionable.
And there are people who like.
Who is who?
by Mr.
Oh is?
here here
Oh yeah
by Mr.
No to
Oh yeah
Going, Going and Going
No to
It hurts.
Oh is
Oh yeah
still is
A little more.
Oh oh oh
Oh yeah
No to No.
from behind.
No to
by
Yes
No to
Oh yeah
Try to cut.
I was struck.
Sorry to
I am going to do this.
by Mr.
Yes to?
What are you doing?
I do not know.
I was asked for waste.
Oh how much.
If you want, go down to me.
Okay is?
Can I ask for it?
of course is.
Thanks for the package, be careful.
Oh well okay.
Is it okay?
So I’ll take it down.
thanks to.
Thank you very much, Mr.
Thanks for drinking coffee.
Is the time okay?
Time is okay, but
I have not done much,
Not to let me get here.
Okay so okay.
It is instant, but there is a good coffee.
Oh, where did you go?
I am alone, I cannot get it fast.
I want to go, but where?
That is?
Where did you do it?
Where is it, oh?
I cleaned it, it’s gone somewhere.
Okay to?
So what happened?
Stop it.
I am looking for my voice now.
Sorry to
Could it not be?
Give me, I can’t find you.
Can I tell you after here?
An unknown child.
You are so cute, Kate’s ass.
The frog is also chasing.
How can you protect yourself, which one do you like?
Which of you like?
Frog, which one do you like?
Which of them.
Which of these.
This is
here here
No, why
It is already growing.
Why is
Thank you very much for watching it until the end.
Oh... That world...
too hard.
Drinking
I know this apartment in half a year.
Thinking so is lonely.
What if you graduate?
I will continue my work and return to my country.
I graduate and go to university at the same time.
I was crying at Okayama.
Do you want to go there?
Yes...
Something is lonely.
When graduating
A little closer to Gideon.
Can we meet again?
Okay so has.
here and
by
I brought Caesar.
Oh well done, Hygge
Kyle, we’re going to have a good party.
Drink with Caesar.
Sorry, but I drink a little.
Do not talk about the office.
because last
Let us all make happy memories together.
Yes to Mrs.
Oh yeah yeah
The brother is going like this.
Enjoy here and here.
here and here and here.
Sit and sit.
Sit to
Mr. Kyle, is Bill well?
I drink a little...
Oh, oh, oh, I say that.
Not one drink.
In our celebrated sense.
Why?
What is happening?
Eat more.
still remains.
disappeared
Have you bought just that now?
is enough?
by? Yes to?
Yes is
Not bad, what is it?
Oh yes right.
Oooo Oooo
Why stop?
Oh yeah?
Why?
Buy this.
Oh yeah?
Oooooh
Please please please
I this
You have to look at the butterfly.
Oh yes right.
thanks
I know
Goodbye to you.
Come here and drink.
Drink to drink.
Do this.
Why suddenly drink?
Have you drunk? Have you drunk? Have you drunk?
The comparison?
Suspiciously
Why that water?
water is
Not the water.
Is it okay?
I am not lying.
Lying is
The pot is dangerous.
Lots of water...
Why?
Why no water?
A bit tasty.
Buying lemon.
Lemonly
Consciousness is too high.
Very shaken
Drinking is weak.
Do not eat.
Mr Kyle is
You are not eating?
This is quality.
I cannot get rid.
I want to celebrate.
Kimmy will return.
will return.
But here he does not return.
I think I know.
I want to make fun memories.
Yes, yes
Not sad though?
A little...
and? What are you doing?
Really ignored
The graduation?
Yes is
I have not decided anything yet.
Try that.
I said you want to travel abroad.
Oh yeah yeah?
On the road, right?
And really?
Public life.
But I did not decide anything.
What about? Our student
as our student.
Foreign student arrives.
pleasedly
Not too much contained? Are you okay?
Go with us?
I bring Shiraz.
and Shirataki?
This is good?
Isn’t this good?
Oh this thing?
Oh, but...
That is more of a junkie.
by Jade
I ask for something.
No request is.
No the most requested.
The request, the request.
Request, request
Request, request and request
Annie and Annie.
Annie, A
Annie is
One, two and three.
It tastes!
is taste?
Oh, very delicious
Even if I made.
Can I eat?
Yes, it is okay.
What do you want to eat?
have two
The two?
by Duba
Not a bit tired?
by Ido, Ido
very much like.
It is decreasing.
Two of them, two of them.
several times water.
hurt is
by
Stop the Dart?
Sorry to
entered in
Usually in violin.
cannot sit.
Is it okay?
Another knife?
Let me sit?
Do you see a lot of legs?
Do not see.
Why?
Want to go home? Want to go more?
Want to go home?
I want to go home.
Want to go quickly?
If only the boat can be rented.
The ship stops.
Is it okay?
Where is?
is here?
It cleared up.
Drinking
Is it clear?
What do you?
The dog?
is cute?
What do you?
The face
The face is different.
The face of Eros?
Not to Kitty?
The face different?
Really is?
The face of Eve?
The frontal
The face of Eros?
Her face is E.
Look at your face.
See also
Not not not? Different from?
The face is different.
Look a little closer.
What about?
What is?
What to do?
be quiet.
My legs are now very large.
not yet seen.
No more like me.
No to meet.
You really...
not found
Oh to!
Too sick.
The screen disappears again.
disappeared.
Really disappeared.
Doing this.
to sleep?
Where to Rise?
Not yet seen.
When sleeping... I am sleeping.
No to no.
Too good.
No to
A bit scared.
See that.
as primary school.
Someone know.
The pants!
See the pants?
and? Not attacking it?
Not attacking it?
Yes together.
Oh what.
and? some
Oh the color.
The same color.
Is there?
there from
I am afraid, afraid
Oh oh oh oh oh oh
Oh, oh oh
I can, I can, I can.
too shameful
To be honest, what do I feel?
I now...
Continue to the boss...
I think beautiful.
Really is?
I am brother.
And suddenly?
I am not brother.
Yes to?
The Sosa?
Sossy
No, a little
is real? Not the weather.
Not the weather.
is okay.
The weather answered?
Sorry to
You are more aggressive.
The hearts
by
ah is
I too
A cup of 4...
Sorry to.
This cannot. not can.
I hope you don’t believe too much in animators.
A little...
Oh no nonsense.
and
Come here here.
Oh yeah?
Now broken.
broken is
I am kissing.
Are you kissing?
Come here and here.
Oh, so good
Oh, oh oh
Oh, the big
here here here
Sleep only.
Sleep only
Mom, just sleep
The hands, the hands.
A little
A little, a little
Oh...
A little...
That... A light sound...
I hear it.
No such sound.
What should I do?
No, no can
Forgetting is
I want drink.
Not drinking
Drinking is
Oh yeah?
cleansed it.
Oh yeah yeah.
When did it?
Feels good?
Feels good
Do not wash.
too hard
Too much pain.
Do not stop.
Why do you do?
The body of such a person.
Cement is coming.
Go to my life.
Go to M.
Tagged personalities
Mithra
Miko is
Mickey Circle
and Miko
It is near.
Approaching me.
Oh no no.
Chickby Case
What is Chick Case?
Really not know.
Try a chick box.
The new word.
Really not know.
The Chick?
Napoleon is
Uploaded
It’s
Up it’s
up up
It’s
cannot endure.
Oh, it is hot
The hot?
Heat is
No, no, this is never going to be.
It is the hottest.
not hot
Wait a little.
was hot.
is grown?
not grown.
Oh...Oh...
Oh thank you.
Oh yeah, all of you!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Me and Me.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh!
I, I, I, I, I and I, I and I.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Ah Ah...
Oh, oh...
The car, the car...
I wanted to try...
My...
and better.
Now is better.
Oh...Ended
Just me two.
Written by
My clothes tweet.
Sorry to
calmly
Where to sit, where to sit.
by
Where do you come from?NNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNN
What is happening?
Totally different thing.
A little... Stop to.
Something happened.
by?
What happened?
What is? What is?
Oh great
Always worrying.
OK is
Helping someone is hard.
is okay.
On the ceiling.
Where is?
The wound...
Oh...
Down to...
Feels good.
Why do you?
Not to differentiate depiction.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
So many birds.
Yes is
by
Oh... Sorry..
I ate...
Sorry..
A little like that.
Thus...
Oh...
A little like that.
Oh... What is that?
Oh...
by?
and? Why to me?
Oh, a little... somewhat.. A bit ashamed.
Oh, the big
Oh, I am...
somewhat..
Why? Why to me?
Tell her.
What is?
What do you want?
to me...
Ehehehehehe
Funny to do.
One more
Yes, that is
and
Oh that side.
No is
So feel good.
Danced
Come to
come to
by
Pithy
Oh yeah yeah
Oh, oh...
by
Oh well...
Oh...
Oh, oh...
Luckily he
I and I die.
I cannot die.
The presentation
The mountains
Baby, why is this?
Why is this?
Oh sadness.
Are you okay?
Oh baby, babyAs to
Let your own leg move.
Sorry to
The Viking came out.
Luckily
Fortunately do not escape.
The hungry head.
Old Jenang
My praise
Ahaia escape
Ahaia
Oh, I have won.
Oh yeah
Oh... I am...
I am too tired...
I am a dividecheer.
A is
100 is
L is
both of
Oh...
by  by Hass!
No to go.
Oh to!
Oh...
Why a cook?
by A-
Oh well...
I am doing my ass.
I am doing ass.
Oh...
DuckSome
Oh oh oh oh
Oh yeah yeah
by A.
The Contract
This child is so worried.
This child
Stay still more.
I am Umber.
You have tried.
child
by
Ua is
The hour!
A is
by Doctor
Looking at
How about?
by Mack!
Why?
Otherwise?
otherwise
Is it okay?
is okay.
Put in hand.
The voice is huge.
Oh well...
I want to hear...
annoyingly
PITing
Forced will be over
Oh yeah yeah
I slept a lot.
Oh, it happened.
Oh, I followed the same.
Okay okay
and pain.
Speaking with mouth?
You are a fucking kid.
Do you drink?
The wine?
Drinking? drinking? drinking? drinking? drinking? drinking? drinking? drinking? drinking? drinking? drinking? drinking? drinking? drinking? drinking? drinking? drinking?
The wine? the wine?
You have broken, you have broken.
I broke up.
Has it broken?
I will get it.
Yes
Tastefully
Good night and so.
Chouchou
by
No to
Oh yeah
Tagged as: Tea Tea
by TN
Oh yeah