I'm sorry.
Yuji wants to find a job here.
It's only been a few weeks, but I think he'll be fine.
I know.
Yuji was worried about his mom.
I see.
It was like his mom was in love with him.
But after that, Yuji had to take care of him.
I wish we could have a new store here.
You don't have to worry about it.
I'm sure they'll feed you.
I'll be fine.
You and your family are Yuji's only family.
You came at the right time.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Yuji.
Please ring the doorbell.
I'm sorry.
I'm from the countryside.
Thank you.
Please use this room.
It's so warm.
You're late.
Why are you always so late?
I have a lot of work to do.
Really?
I thought you were playing.
I see.
Let's have some beer.
Sounds good.
But I'm sure you're really serious about your work.
Or are you washing your hands at work?
Since you were a kid?
I've been doing it since I was a kid.
I've been eating all the sweets you dropped.
The sweets I dropped?
It's a three-second rule.
I'm home.
You're home.
Welcome home.
I'm going to take a shower and get changed.
I thought this was my house.
Take your time.
Thank you.
I'm going to look for a room as soon as I get a job.
I understand.
I hope you find a good job nearby.
Tokyo is so big.
You'll be surprised.
Let's eat.
Let's eat more.
It's good.
Right?
I'm glad.
I was praised.
Hey.
You're always like this.
Don't do that outside.
You're good at it.
I'm going.
Take care.
You too, Yuuji.
Do your best.
Like this,
my husband's younger brother
and my life with Yuuji
began.
But
Yuuji's job-hunting activities
didn't stop there.
It was the first time
that Yuuji
and my husband
were together.
Yuuji's job-hunting activities
didn't stop there.
I'm sorry.
I don't know.
I guess I shouldn't have said that.
That's not true.
You'll definitely find a good place.
At first,
Akane encouraged me like that.
But
Akane
was worried about
his mother.
It's a shame
that I said that.
I'll do my best.
Yuuji?
Hey...
My pants good though.
Oh, no!
One year later
Boss, I am sorry about that.
No, that's not true.
I...
...love you!
Wait!
I hate it!
I hate it so much...
No! No! No!
No! No!
Stop it!
You are a good girl!
No! No! No!
No!
No! No!
I'm gonna save you warm
Please...
Just hang on for a bit more.
I want to lick all of you.
No!
Don't lick that part.
I want to lick all of you.
No!
Don't touch me!
I want to lick all of you.
No!
Stop it!
I'm sorry.
I love your cute ears.
No!
I'm sorry.
I love your back.
No!
I want to lick all of you.
I'm sorry.
Don't do it!
I don't want to!
That's the best part about you, sister!
No!
I can't stand the side of you, sister!
I can't!
No!
I love you, sister!
What a beautiful boobs!
No!
Let me go!
Sister...
I can't stand the side of you, sister!
I'm sick of you!
No!
You've been licking me so much!
You haven't licked me, have you?
I'll lick you a lot, sister!
No!
I can't!
Sister...
No!
Stop it!
Stop it, sister!
No!
Stop it!
It's getting really hot, sister!
No!
Stop it!
I want to lick all of you, sister!
Don't lick me!
No!
I can't stand your feet, sister!
It's dirty!
It's not dirty at all!
You're beautiful, sister!
Stop it!
No!
I want to lick all of you, sister!
Stop it!
No!
I love you, sister!
Please understand me, sister!
Stop it!
No!
Don't look at me!
I hate you!
Stop it!
Don't lick me!
I can't stand it!
It's not dirty at all!
You're being licked by me, brother!
Sister...
I'm sorry...
You're not being licked by me...
You're such a beautiful baby...
I'm going to lick you, sister!
You smell disgusting!
You smell good!
Don't bite me!
It's disgusting!
It smells good and it's delicious!
No...
I'm sorry...
Let me go...
No...
It's delicious...
Stop it...
No...
I'm sorry...
I can't stand any of you licking me.
Stop it...
I'm sorry...
I can't stand it...
No...
Ah
Seriously?!
She has low blood pressure.
We don't like that.
No, how could I be like this...
I've never been bullied by anyone.
Me neither.
I'm the only one who's been bullied here.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
I can't do this anymore.
Please don't make a noise.
It's such a shame that you can't eat such delicious food.
I've already eaten a lot of your food.
Please don't make a noise.
Please don't put it in my stomach.
Please don't.
Please don't make a noise.
It feels so good.
Your mouth is the best.
Please don't make a noise.
Please don't.
It feels so good.
Your mouth is the best.
Please don't make a noise.
Are you playing with me?
You're not playing with me, are you?
Please don't make a noise.
Please don't.
What are you doing?
You're pulling my thread.
Please don't.
It feels so good.
This is the best.
Please don't.
I'll lick all of you instead of my brother.
My brother's mom scolds me a lot inside.
Please don't.
This is embarrassing.
I want to lick all of your embarrassing parts.
Please don't.
Yuuji, was it bad again?
I'm sorry.
It's been a while.
Don't rush.
There's always a place for you to meet.
If I were the president,
Yuuji would be right.
I'm not the president.
That's right.
Let's drink.
Did you finish drinking?
It's a three-second rule, so it's okay.
Are you going to use it as it is?
It's dirty, wash it.
It's okay.
There's always a place for you to meet.
It's a three-second rule, so it's okay.
I want to lick you again.
You just have to lick it, please.
You just have to lick it.
You can't do that.
You just have to lick it, please.
Put your hand on my finger.
Get on here.
You just have to lick it, please.
I'm embarrassed.
No, no, no.
You just have to lick it, please.
I wanted to lick it.
Do you feel good?
And
knowing that I can't go
Yuuji-san and
sex
Do you feel good?
I'm going to put a lot of oil on it.
It's full of oil.
It's amazing.
I'm so happy.
Let me taste it.
It's amazing.
It hurts.
I'm so excited.
My heart beat faster.
It's so soft.
So soft.
It's hot.
It feels so good.
I'm so happy.
I can't stop.
It feels so good.
I can't take it anymore.
I can't.
Congratulations.
I knew you'd do it.
That industry is still growing.
You're the best.
Don't give me that.
Don't come back here.
I know.
All I can do is thank you.
Thank you.
That's good.
You should drink too.
Thank you.
Cheers.
It's so good.
I'm happy.
I'm so happy.
I can't stand it anymore.
I can't do it.
It's so hard.
Wipe it off with a toothpick.
Lick mine too.
It's so hard.
Show me your back.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh
Eh
Yeah
Ah, I'm stuck.
Amazing...
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
ahuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
the
uu
Oh, it's
Oh, it's so cold.
Hold me more.
I'm so hot.
Oh, it's so cold.
Hold me more.
I was struck by the force of an icebreaker.
I was struck by a yellow ocher.
I'm going to die.
Come on.
Oh.
So the job was decided,
Yuuji left the house.
Two months after that.
Take care of yourself.
Kanna.
It's hard to say.
What?
You've been sweating lately.
I'm sorry.
I started jogging in the morning.
I had to take a shower after you left.
I see.
I'm busy in the morning.
It's okay if you know.
I'm going.
Take care.
I'm going to die.
It smells good.
Really?
It smells so good.
Thank you for your viewing.
Please subscribe to my channel.