Cue the music!
I was feeling a bit serious that day.
It's been a long time since my husband went on a business trip, and I spent my free time at my friend's bar.
I had a lot of work to do, and I was in a good mood.
I was depressed because my boss, Hachino, gave me a bad proposal.
I was on my way to the station to buy a can of Chuhai.
Is the proposal over?
Yes, just a little more.
The rest is the same as the same price.
You don't have to explain.
If it's over, do you want to go for a drink?
Are you sure?
I'm sure. You're full of motivation to get drunk.
Let's go to a regular izakaya.
Cheers!
Let's not talk about work from now on.
Let's eat, drink, and have fun.
Do you often come to this izakaya?
I don't think so.
I think so, too.
I think you look good in a bar.
Sometimes I drink alone.
I can't drink at my company.
But I'm happy to drink like this.
Isn't it hard?
Drink it all at once.
It's hard.
I can't drink anything.
Here you are.
This is a handmade powder.
It looks delicious.
I'll have another one.
I'm glad to hear that.
The first manager I met outside the company was kind and kind.
But he was a little mean.
And he was very beautiful.
You're a good boy.
You're interested in small things.
It's a funny story.
What kind of sex do boys like this have?
What am I thinking?
I'm looking at the manager with erotic eyes.
The more I look at him, the more erotic my face and body are.
Maybe it's because I saw a pornographic video of a mature man last night.
I can't believe my wife is erotic.
I have to calm down.
He is my boss.
Can I eat this?
No, you can't.
It's a little late.
It's already 12 o'clock.
It's already 10 o'clock.
I don't want to drink anymore.
I'm going home.
Are you drunk?
No, I'm fine.
Did you drink too much?
Did he leave?
I was late.
I'm sorry I made you wait so long.
What should I do?
You don't have to worry about it.
Are you going to the bathroom?
Do you want to come to my house?
That's...
It's okay.
My husband won't come home today.
Let's go to the office together tomorrow.
But...
I'll give you a greeting from my husband.
The taxi is here.
Taxi.
My husband won't come home.
Did he think I was having sex?
What should I do?
What if he suddenly pushes me down?
But...
No.
If I tell him to stop, he'll stop.
This child.
My husband won't come home.
What does that mean?
I'm scared.
My husband will come home.
He'll show me his house.
I don't care about that.
I just want to drink.
I'm sure.
Hey.
I got off the taxi and held your hand.
And you're sweating.
What's going on?
I'm so excited.
My hands are sweating.
I'm embarrassed.
He knows I'm excited.
Here you are.
I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
Why?
It's okay.
I won't push you down.
Okay.
I pushed you down.
Can I kiss you?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Did I ask you to push me down?
Don't push me down.
I'm sorry.
I drank too much.
My body is hot.
It's hot.
It's like I'm naked.
Are you okay?
It hurts.
Take it off.
Hurry up.
Can I take it off?
I'll take it off.
It hurts.
Do you want to take a shower?
Yes.
No.
It's hot.
I love your sweat smell.
So, you should sweat more.
I'll lick all your sweat.
It's hot.
Why are you so sensitive?
Are you okay?
You're not sick.
I'm fine.
You're lying.
It smells good.
It smells like you've worked a lot.
It's hot.
Look at me.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Let's go to bed.
It's hot.
Can I kiss you?
You have a nice body.
It's hot.
Don't do this to me.
I'm excited.
Do you want to be more excited?
Yes.
It's hot.
Why are you so sensitive?
It smells good.
I know.
You've been excited since you got in the taxi.
I'm sorry.
You had a bad breath.
I'll clean your ears.
It's hot.
It's embarrassing.
It smells like you've worked a lot.
It's hot.
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
You have a good body.
Did you see me crying?
No.
I like you more than anything else.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Do you want to touch me?
I want to touch you.
It's hot.
You wanted to touch me, didn't you?
Did you say you could lick me?
I couldn't do it.
I have to beg you.
I beg you.
Let me lick you.
Okay.
It's hot.
Do you want to lick me?
Yes.
It's hot.
It's dirty.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It smells like tea.
It's hot.
I can't do it.
It hurts.
It feels good.
My legs are moving.
It's hot.
Do you want to lick me?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
Let me lick you.
It hurts.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Let's do something more pleasant.
I'll move a lot.
Are you sure?
Do you want to go home?
I don't want to go home.
You want to do something pleasant, don't you?
Come on me.
Slowly.
You're sleepy, aren't you?
Yes.
Wait.
I'll do it.
My stomach is full.
It feels good here, too.
I'm nervous.
Don't move.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
I don't want to move.
You don't have to move.
But...
I want to do it more.
Let me do it slowly.
There.
It's warm.
What's this?
You want to move, don't you?
I'll do it.
I'll move you a lot.
Let me do it now.
My head hurts.
It hurts.
My neck hurts.
It's hot.
I'll do it.
Can you see it?
Look at me.
It's amazing here.
It feels good here.
It's the best.
I can't stop.
I'm sorry.
It must hurt a lot.
It feels good here.
It's the best.
I'm sorry.
Don't move.
It must hurt a lot.
Let me do it again.
Okay.
It feels good here.
I'll do it.
What are you going to do?
Can you move?
I can move.
I'll do it.
Put it in from behind.
From behind?
Why is it so hard?
I'll do it.
It must hurt a lot.
I'll do it slowly.
Can you see the part where I'm in?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
You're good.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Me too.
That's good!
There!
Let's go!
Don't cry yet.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Stop it!
It tastes good.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Let's go.
Can I move?
You can't stand it anymore, can you?
You want to move.
You can't help it, can you?
It feels good here.
It feels good here for me too.
It's amazing.
Don't cry.
I'm sorry for making you cry.
Come here.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's completely different from before.
It feels good for me too.
You don't want to move, do you?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Do you know how to close it?
I'll close it.
It's amazing.
Let's go.
It hurts.
Hurry up.
It's so hot that I can't stand it.
It smells good.
It feels good for me too.
Are you going to leave?
You can't.
It feels good when I hold it in, right?
It's okay.
It's amazing.
I'm going to cry.
My jaw is going to break.
Let's go.
My head hurts.
Did you feel good?
I'm worried about the company.
I'm sorry.
Is this the director's house?
I stayed at the director's house last night.
Really?
What should I do?
I'm bored.
I'll pretend to sleep.
Koume?
I'm drunk.
I can't tell my husband about this.
But you're cute.
You're big and you lick me a lot.
I want to do it again.
What should I do?
Should I wake up?
I missed the timing.
What should I do?
What are you going to do?
I can't believe it.
I'm going to sleep.
Did you wake up?
What are you doing?
What are you talking about?
I love you.
That's why I'm licking you since this morning.
Did you wake up?
It feels good.
Let's take a shower.
I'll wash your hair.
I'll wash your hair, too.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'll wash your hair.
Your hair is wet.
I'm going to sit here.
You were sleeping, but you woke up in the morning.
Don't say that.
I'll wash your hair, too.
I'll wash your hair.
It's dirty.
You licked my hair, too.
That's right.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Will you lick my hair?
I'll wash your hair.
It feels good.
Wait a minute.
I want to take a shower.
I'll be right back.
Can I wash your hair?
It hurts.
It's embarrassing.
Do you want to wash your hair here?
Yes.
Don't look at me.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'll wash your hair.
I'll be right back.
It's dirty.
Don't look at me.
It's heavy.
It's delicious.
It's hot.
Your body is cold.
Can I wash your hair?
Yes.
I'll wash your hair.
You're amazing.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Why are you licking me?
I told you.
I like to be licked.
It's hot.
Manager.
Can I call you Tsubasa?
Do you want to call me?
Yes.
It's okay.
It feels good.
Tsubasa.
It's hot.
Don't look at me.
It's delicious.
Tsubasa.
You were amazing.
Yes.
Did you feel good?
It's good.
It's perfect.
Is it really good?
What?
I borrowed your shirt.
You did a great job.
I see.
I'll make dinner for you.
Okay.
Let's go.
I don't want to go with you.
I don't care.
I'll go out from the back door.
I'm home.
Come in.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm home.
Please wait a little longer.
What's wrong?
There's beer in the closet.
You can drink it.
What's wrong?
Please wait a little longer.
Tsubasa is cold at work.
You can't flirt at work.
Koume said so.
But I was a manager.
I did my best.
I wanted to play with you.
I wanted to lick you.
I licked you a lot.
I'm not in a good mood.
I thought that would make you happy.
Please wait a little longer.
It's still dinner.
Can you wait a little longer?
Yes.
Please wait.
Thank you.
Please eat a lot.
Let's eat.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
But it's delicious.
Please eat a lot.
Yes.
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's really delicious.
Tsubasa.
What's wrong?
The food is delicious.
But Tsubasa is cold.
I'm eating now.
I haven't taken a shower yet.
Tsubasa.
I'm sorry.
You're sweating a lot.
You smell bad.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
The food will be cold.
I want to eat this too.
It's hot.
I can't eat if you're cold.
You're not full, are you?
It's hot.
I'm going to cry.
I can't.
I want to sleep.
Me too.
Don't look at me.
I want to sleep.
I'm sorry.
It's delicious.
It's cold.
Sit down.
What?
Okay.
What's wrong?
You want to take it out, don't you?
It's embarrassing.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm embarrassed when you say that.
But it's delicious.
It's delicious.
It's hot.
It's getting bigger.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
It's delicious.
I drank it all.
It's hot.
Are you satisfied?
It's delicious.
Let's continue eating.
Okay.
It's hot.
Do you like it?
It's delicious.
It's hot.
You just took it out, didn't you?
But...
It's already hard.
It's hot.
Are you going to let me go?
Yes.
It's hot.
Shall we go in?
Yes.
It's hot.
I'm embarrassed.
You're still big.
It's hot.
I've never done this before.
Do you feel strange?
Yes.
It's strange to take a bath.
It's hot.
You're still big.
I think so.
I'm going to take a bath.
Do you lick me?
Yes.
I want to lick you.
It's hot.
My hands are wet.
My butt is wet.
It's hot.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm wet.
It's hot.
I can't.
You're warm.
That feels good.
It's hard, isn't it?
You're purring, aren't you?
Let's leave it like this.
It's hard, isn't it?
Put it in.
It's gone.
It's hard, isn't it?
That's good.
That's great.
It hurts.
It's hard, isn't it?
I can't do it anymore.
Sit down.
Can you stand it?
It's hard, isn't it?
It's warm, isn't it?
That's great.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's warm, isn't it?
That's great.
Let's go.
It's hard, isn't it?
Let me go.
It's coming in.
It's hot, isn't it?
You can do it, can't you?
That's great.
I'm so happy!
Calm...
It's OK.
You are right.
Please don't cry!!!
It doesn't look that bad, but...
There's a lot generally in there.
I'll just try not to laugh.
The water is boiling and slooowly this is getting hot.
Oh, yeah, there's the movie...
Are you guys okay?
Can you see me?
I'm sorry.
You're beautiful.
Thank you.
This is your pajamas, right?
Yes.
Don't you have sex with your husband?
I don't.
Why?
I don't know.
Maybe I'm bored.
Look at me.
I don't know.
Will your husband come back tomorrow?
I won't see him tomorrow.
You should feel better.
I want your wings.
Give me your wings.
You're amazing.
I'm sorry.
I'll be full until tomorrow.
I want to see you soon.
I feel good.
It's warm.
It's hot.
It's delicious.
I feel good.
Wait.
You're amazing.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's hot.
I feel good.
I have to lick you.
Let's lick together.
It's hot.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'll do my best.
It's so slippery.
It's the biggest one.
It's amazing.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
I'll do my best not to forget it.
Look up.
I'm sorry.
It's so slippery.
I can't move my legs.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
Don't make me give up.
Can you do it?
I can do it.
I can do it better than you.
Make me feel better.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I can do it.
It's amazing.
I want to move, too.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
It's dirty.
It's not dirty.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
I'll move it for you.
Stay there.
It's good, isn't it?
It feels good.
It's getting bigger.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
It's dirty.
It feels good.
It's getting bigger.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
What is this?
It's amazing.
I'll go.
It's hot.
It's getting bigger.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Lie down here.
Can I lie down here?
It feels good.
You can see my legs, right?
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I want to cry.
It feels good.
I'll go.
It's hot.
You won't forget our sex, right?
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
I'll go again.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's hot.
I'll never forget our sex.
I love you.
Let's go together.
I'll go, too.
I'll go.
It's hot.
It's all out.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'll go, too.
I want to do it more.
I want to do it, too.
I can't do it.
I want to do it more.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I want to do it more.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
Let's meet at the office again.
I'll pretend to be a stranger.
I see.
I'll go.
It's hot.
The last train has left.
Then, will you come to my house?