Shiori Inoue, 22 years old
What happened?
I don't know...
To decide, we'll analyze the love between two people!
I'm going to try hold on...
Good morning, Yuta-kun.
Good morning.
Are you going to work part-time from now on?
Yes, I am.
Good luck.
Oh, this is what I left for you.
Eat it if you like.
Is this a lunch box?
Yes.
Yuta-kun, you always go to the convenience store at noon, right?
It's a part-time job, so I have to eat nutritious food once in a while.
Thank you.
Well, thank you.
Well, I'm going.
Good luck.
Huh?
A letter has arrived.
This is...
Huh?
It's annoying.
It's a part-time job day.
What is it?
Huh?
Reika-san?
What's wrong with your outfit?
Well, Yuta-kun...
I...
I'm going to be Yuta-kun's maid from today.
Huh?
Well, in other words...
Reika-san's mother's family was a maid for generations?
Does this mean that I am the descendant of that master's Kurosuke?
No, no, no.
Because I'm Aoki.
That's your mother's last name, right?
Your real name is Kurosu Yuta.
I was born between the master's Kurosuke and his beloved mother.
Huh? Wait a minute.
I heard from my mother that my father died in an accident.
I think that's the only way to put it.
My mother thought that her existence would be a burden to her family.
That's why she left the master's Kurosuke before Yuta-kun was born.
The reason why I haven't had any contact with the master's Kurosuke until now...
I think it's because I have such a mother's feelings.
Huh?
If that's the case, why is Reika-san my maid now?
That's the thing.
It seems that Shinpei-sama passed away the night before yesterday.
What?
Yesterday, I received this from the mansion.
It seems that Shinpei-sama left a will before his death.
If I die, I will give Yuta-kun a part of my property and a maid.
I was also surprised.
I didn't know that Yuta-kun, who lives next door, was the one I could use.
Huh? You didn't know either?
It's a great coincidence, isn't it?
This is the first time I've been a maid.
Until now, my mother has done everything about the mansion.
But now, my mother seems to be full of things about the mansion.
That's why I was chosen.
I see.
Hey, Yuta-kun.
I think this is at least a compensation from Shinpei-sama.
Yuta-kun may not be able to organize his feelings suddenly.
I wonder if you can accept it.
I will do my best to help Yuta-kun as a maid.
Well, that's...
From my point of view, it's not a bad thing.
Um...
Reika-san, what are you going to do with your own house?
Because Reika-san is getting married, right?
If that's the case, it's okay.
If you do it well, you can get along properly.
But I think it's better to keep this a secret from my family for a while.
Why?
They won't believe me even if I tell them a lie like this.
I don't want to be misunderstood badly and cause trouble to Yuta-kun.
So for a while...
I come here every morning after he goes to work.
I'm thinking of leaving here before he comes back at night.
What do you think?
I understand. Let's do that.
Okay.
If that's the case, let's get started with today's work.
What should I do first?
Cleaning? Washing?
Let's see...
This letter is about a maid's job.
Can I ask you to do this too?
What? Which one?
This one.
I can do it.
Yuta-kun, do you want to do it?
Yes.
I want to do it.
Yuta-kun, I...
Reika-san, you're my maid now.
Yuta-kun...
Maids listen to their masters, right?
So...
Let me see your tongue.
Hurry up.
It feels good.
Let me see your tongue.
Reika-san, you're my maid now.
It feels good.
Let me see your tongue.
I don't want to.
Why?
Maids can't resist, right?
It feels good.
Hurry up.
I don't want to.
Wait.
Let me see your belly.
Hey, Reika-san.
I don't want to.
Yuta-kun...
Maids can't resist, right?
Maids listen to their masters, right?
It feels good.
Let me see your tongue.
Reika-san, you're my maid now.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm wearing a mask.
Let me see your tongue.
Your nose is so smooth.
It's so beautiful.
It feels good.
Why?
You're still naked.
I want to see you naked.
Let me see you naked.
Yuta-kun...
It's so beautiful.
I don't want to.
Reika-san...
It's so hot.
Your neck is so cute.
Does it feel good?
What do you want me to do?
Does Reika-san always wear underwear like this?
Don't look at me like that.
Can I look at you?
It's so beautiful.
What do you want me to do?
You're wet.
Let me see what you're doing.
Let me see.
You're wet.
What's going on down there?
Let me see.
Don't look at me like that.
Open it yourself.
Open it.
You're wet.
It's so warm.
You're so wet.
It felt so good.
This morning...
I hope you feel better.
You're a maid, right?
You can do it, right?
Come on.
Touch me.
Make me feel better.
You can lick me.
The other side.
It feels good.
Touch me.
You have to do it properly.
Touch me directly.
Don't touch my pants.
It's embarrassing.
If you're a maid, listen to me.
You have to do it properly.
It feels good.
Let me lick you.
Push me.
It hurts again.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's okay.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's warm.
It feels good.
It's okay.
It hurts.
What's wrong?
Nothing. Why?
Nothing.
Do you want a drink?
Okay.
Let's go.
Good morning, Yuta.
Ruiko.
Yuta, are you going to do it again today?
Okay.
It hurts.
Ruiko.
Yuta.
It hurts.
Ruiko.
Show me your butt.
Ruiko's butt is very beautiful.
Don't look at me like that.
Show me.
It hurts.
Let go of my hand.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Ah ah ah ah
resemblance
Yeah war
Pao
Uh-huh
Hmm
Hold on to my hand.
a
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
pus
Yeah
I have been
doing this
Ah, it feels so good.
The other side too.
Ah, it's getting harder and harder.
Hey, lick my balls too.
Ah, it feels so good.
I can't hold it anymore.
It's painful.
Shake your hips.
Shake your hips more.
Ah, it feels so good.
More, more.
Let me do it from behind.
Ah, it feels so good.
Oh, my God.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Yuta-kun?
Don't go, Reika-san.
I can't, Yuta-kun.
I'm going to bed.
Good night, Reika-san.
Good night.
Hey, Reika.
I have something to tell you.
What?
You're moving out?
For the sake of his job,
I'm going to stay in America for 3 years.
Maybe I'll become a hero.
That's...
I don't want that.
What?
Oh, right.
The will.
My dad's will...
Reika-san, you have your dad's will,
so you can't go to America, right?
What?
I like you.
I...
I've always liked you.
About Reika-san.
But you...
You're the wife of someone other than me.
I thought I had to give up.
At that time,
this suddenly happened.
I...
I embraced you,
and I fell in love with you more.
And yet,
the result is...
I can't believe it.
For Reika-san,
I don't want to leave you.
I wish I was lucky.
Me too.
I don't want to leave you either.
I want to be with you forever.
Reika-san...
I was confused at first,
and I was about to break his heart.
But...
While he was loving me,
something beyond that
began to grow inside me.
That is...
In other words...
I think I like you.
About Yuta-kun.
Then...
But I can't.
I'm your wife.
I can't betray him.
My relationship with Yuta-kun
is just a maid
and his master.
I was just following
the mission of the clan.
I thought so.
Let's forget about it.
Yuta-kun...
I...
don't want to forget.
I want to remember
Reika-san's warmth
forever.
Yuta-kun...
Are you really going to take it?
Yes.
I want to remember it.
Reika-san's warmth...
Is it warm?
Smell it.
Yuta-kun...
From the end...
It's hard, isn't it?
Here...
A little...
Is it close?
Because...
It's so beautiful.
I don't want to.
This too.
Hey...
Hey, give me a kiss.
Give me a kiss.
Hey...
I can feel the space here.
I want to see this too.
Hey...
Show me your tongue.
Yuta-kun, you like this side, don't you?
Hey...
Can you peel it off?
Sit down and show me more.
Hey...
Open your mouth.
It's hard.
It's the last one.
Hey...
Hey, Reika-san.