Thank you so much for watching this video.
Please subscribe to my channel and give it a high rating.
See you in the next video.
You look like someone.
Thank you.
Please eat.
What kind of person are you?
Do you look like someone?
I don't think there's anyone who looks like me.
But I'm really serious.
I'm too serious.
It's okay.
Seriousness is the best.
Is that so?
You've found someone.
I'm sorry.
Welcome back.
Tsubasa-chan, you're back.
It's been five years.
I didn't see you when I came here.
Really?
How long has it been?
It's been eight years.
Is that so?
Say hello to your husband.
It's been a long time.
Tsubasa-chan got married.
And I came back to this town with my husband's money.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Are you married now?
Of course.
I got a job as a videographer.
I got a job there.
It's a good city.
It's not good.
It's good.
When did you come here?
My husband is coming back next week.
I came first and packed my luggage.
Is that so?
I'll go get my luggage.
You must be lonely for a week.
It's not like that.
Why don't you eat dinner at home?
Is that okay?
You haven't opened your luggage yet.
It's lonely to eat alone.
It's hard to make it.
Is that so?
I'll remember your words.
Thank you.
I'll make it with my own hands.
I know.
You say nice things.
Yes.
It's been a long time.
You like me as usual.
The room hasn't changed at all.
You got married.
Shock?
Why?
I'm in shock.
I wonder.
What's that?
Do you have a salary with your husband?
Yes.
The company is a good bridge.
It's a little far.
It's okay.
But I have more than you.
Besides, you are here.
What?
Do you like meat?
Yes, I like it.
I'm sorry.
I'll go to the bathroom.
I forgot my card.
Really?
I'm going to get it next time.
I see.
Bye.
I'm going home.
I'm sorry I didn't notice.
Today?
I'm going to sleep with my friends.
I'm going for a walk.
No.
I'm going to sleep with my friends.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to work today.
Hello?
I'm going to take it home.
I wanted to give it to you when I moved.
What about the one you cleaned up?
I don't care.
I'll buy you a present.
I won't hold back.
Where is it?
I found it.
It's only in the elementary school.
It's strange.
Do you remember?
Somehow.
What is it?
It's so small.
You're right.
What is it?
Nothing.
I'm curious.
I'm sorry.
No.
I think it's okay.
Bye.
Ok, good for you!
I'm going to stop the camera and quickly edit
It's kind of noisy
I can't wait to eat it with rice
I'm going to have a cup of tea with my friend.
I can't wait to eat it.
I'm so hungry.
This is the entrance to the station.
I don't know if I can do it or not, but I think I can do it.
It doesn't tickle.
Thank you.
Miss...
I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to die if I don't do this.
Touch it.
I'm going to take a break and get ready to go to bed.
He wanted to sleep.
If loved...
I don't think that person should leave.
I shouldn't talk to you all knowing that I've
been in love...
what should I do?
I'll just let it slip through your خ .
Oh, it's hot.
Take it easy.
I can't stand it anymore.
Oh, it's hot.
You're kind.
Wait a minute.
Oh, it's hot.
I'll put it on for you.
Really?
Don't you want it?
I can't stand it anymore.
What are you talking about?
I'll put it on for you.
Oh, it's hot.
The other way around.
Ah...
Ah, I see...
I'm walking...
It's so hard...
Ah, it hurts...
It's too painful...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
, yes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh
, oh,
yes.
Oh
, yes.
Oh, yes,
yes.
Oh, yes.
I want to go home.
I wanted to do this.
Are you embarrassed?
I'm very embarrassed.
I want to go home.
What happened?
Did you wake up?
I have a plate.
I'm hungry.
Let's go somewhere later.
Is it okay to go out later?
Let's go now.
Let's go.
What happened?
I want to go home.
It's completely different from the beginning.
What?
I can't hear anything.
I want to go home.
What happened?
I can't hear anything.
What?
I wanted to do this.
It's completely different from the beginning.
It's okay.
I want to go home.
I can lie down.
Can I?
It's not hard again.
Why?
I just put it out.
It feels good.
Show me closer.
Are you happy?
I knew it.
I can't help it.
Are you happy?
Have you ever seen me like this?
Don't look at me.
I want to look at you if you don't look at me.
What is this?
Look at me.
It's getting harder.
It's amazing.
Aren't you hungry?
I'm hungry.
Have you ever been touched by a kiss?
No, I haven't.
Why are you acting like that?
But
I started it.
There is no kiss bigger than this.
Aren't you embarrassed to say it yourself?
I'll play with you.
How is it?
What's wrong with you?
Is it soft?
It's soft.
Is it delicious?
It's delicious.
I think I can still do it.
I can still do it.
Did you feel good?
Did you get drunk?
I got drunk.
It's not good, is it?
It's not bad to go.
What are you going to do today?
Are you going to stay?
Can I stay?
Yeah.
Let's go to bed.
Are you hungry?
You just slept, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
You can't sleep yet.
Please stay awake.
It smells good.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
I'll give you more.
You don't want to give me more?
Just a little.
I'll give you more.
What?
It's warm.
It's messy.
I'll give you more.
It feels good.
I've always wanted to do this with you.
Really?
It's hot.
Do you know it's hot?
I'll give you more.
It's hot.
It's moving a lot.
Look at me.
Hey, Yuu-kun.
Will you lick mine, too?
Yes.
I hope you feel better.
It feels good.
How do you feel?
It's hot.
Here you go.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Why are you so mean?
It feels good.
I'll lick yours.
It's hot.
Here you go.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Can I put it in like this?
Sure.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Yuu-kun, touch it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Yuu-kun.
I'm happy to be with Yuu-kun.
It feels good to be with me.
It feels good.
I don't want to stand up
That's dangerous
I can't stand up
Come here
I wanted to do it
I can't stand up
Wait
It feels so good
I can't stand up
Look at me
Does it tickle?
It feels so good
I can't stand up
Mom
I'm going out
Where is your dinner?
This meat sauce is so good
Really?
I made it all by myself
No way
You made it all by yourself
Really?
It's my favorite taste
I've liked meat sauce since I was little
The food is good
Isn't it?
I'm still eating
I'm not happy
What are you talking about?
There is still a lot of flavor
Really?
There are two more dishes
I'm going to eat
Wait a minute
Aunt
Hello
How was Kanazawa?
Is it a souvenir?
From now on
I'm sorry
Can I do it tomorrow?
My husband will come home at night
When you say hello
Dinner?
I have to ask my husband
I'm sorry
Excuse me
Eat more
I'm sorry
Will you come tomorrow?
Yes
Then
I have to do it today
No
Will you come tomorrow?
I'm sorry
hahahahahahahahahahaha
Hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha
Push.
Push
I'm going to have a cup of tea to relax my mind and body.
I don't want to know what will happen today because when I have a cold, there is a slight temperatureO
I don't want to know what will happen tomorrow because when I have a cold, there is a slight temperatureO
Tsukasa-chan, you're home too, aren't you?
Let me put this on you.
Tsukasa-chan...
It feels good.
What?
I'm sorry.
It's okay, it's okay.
Is it okay?
Tsukasa-chan...
It feels so good.
Do you want to try it?
I want to try it.
It's so hard.
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
It feels so good.
Tsukasa-chan...
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
No.
I...
I love using this product!
Ah, this is nice.
Oh, it's hot.
It's getting hot.
I love you.
What did you say?
It's embarrassing for everyone.
It is.
I love you.
What about you?
Look at me.
Om recursos!
Sexy.
Cos it's my first time drinking such big packaged
I'm sorry.
I don't want to
I told you I don't want to
I shouldn't
I don't want to
It's good, isn't it?
It's good.
Give it to me.
What?
It's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
It's beautiful.
It's good.
It's delicious.
Ryuko.
Are you done?
I'm done.
Are you going to climb up?
It's good.
It's amazing.
It feels great.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's amazing.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Hurry up.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
What is this?
Yuka-sama...
Feels good...
Yuka-sama is really...
Ah!
Oh my!
Ah, wait!
Ah, Yuka-sama...
Yuka-sama...
Ah!
My loose leg.
It's not a bad thing when you're still rifle comparing to before.
Now I'm still got it in…
It suits you well.
You already needed aoi some massage, right?
I'm sorry.
Like this?
It feels good.
Give me a hug.
It hurts.
It hurts too much.
I can't get used to it.
It's dangerous.
It hurts too much.
Give me a hug.
It's dry.
It hurts.
Give me a hug.
It's true.
This is a souvenir.
Thank you.
This is my husband.
Nice to meet you.
You look like an old man.
Thank you.
I've known you since I was a child.
You're like a daughter.
You're a nice person.
This is Yuichi.
Nice to meet you.
I'm going to sleep a little tonight.
Really?
I'm going to sleep.
Thank you for watching.