Do you smoke black?
Yes, I am the O.
Do not worry about smoking.
Oh yeah then.
This is the smoking room of the shop.
You smoke something delicious.
Smoking in Tokyo is good.
Wherever you smoke, you are not with me.
Is it better to eat in the countryside than in the air?
It’s just the smell of cow shit.
Oh yeah, that is so.
Is Tokyo too gas-powered?
No, is it not cute?
Is smoke really better?
Don’t worry, because your husband is always smoking.
You are good with your husband.
I probably love the guy who smokes.
Every child was a smoker.
Did you meet in a smoking room without smoking?
You thought I was a man, right?
No, it is no longer so.
Is she there? is she there?
No, she no longer has any friends.
I am so missing you.
So be with me.
No, they are not together.
You have a husband.
Because my husband doesn’t love me at all.
Is Sasha free today?
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
We’ll go out to the shop and drink after we’re done.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Sorry, I have waited.
The manager stopped him.
The manager talks about Black.
They are married, they are like each other.
So let’s go!
Tastefully
This is delicious too.
What do you usually eat?
Lunch at the supermarket, ram and cow rice.
Selfishness? what is it?
In fact, it’s like a cup of pasta or retort curry.
I do not say that true.
Yes, or not too.
No, I have a cooking machine.
I am getting pretty much too much.
What about laundry?
Washing is OK.
It is dry in Coinland.
Do or do.
Because I am with his old man.
If you do, be my boyfriend.
What are you saying?
Are you joking?
Seriously Seriously Seriously
I’m not talking about the former manager, but Mr. Black, you’re married.
It doesn’t mean you can’t love anymore, right?
No, some people may think so, but in general...
No is no?
No, I don’t like it, but...
So, I’ll do my homework without you, so make me a little.
Oh well he?
So, it is OK, toast!
Toast to!
You have been excited.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah.
It is good to buy beans here.
Okay really?
I have to go home early today, so I have my husband.
Let us go home.
Yes, be careful
Just now
The room is so clean, it’s not ours.
You are hungry, eat something.
Yes
I made it deliciously today.
I will eat.
Tastefully
really is?
Eat a lot.
Good luck, I made it.
I will eat.
is delicious?
Very delicious.
Previously pastel is delicious.
Glad to be messy.
I told you I liked Sasha.
Good luck, I made it.
I didn’t think it would come out so great.
really is?
Good luck, I said.
Many thanks.
Because I took care of her life.
Not an exchange condition.
Yes, well well
If I could do what I can.
Take care of sex.
Oh yeah
Okay is?
Yes, do it
Good luck to you.
Oh, it is very big.
Yes
Well, be good.
Succeed to.
Yes yes yes
Okay really?
It is so great, so hot.
Oh well...
Feel good
Oh well feel.
Oh, yes, I didn’t take a shower.
I just want to smell that.
A lot of sweat.
I was nervous.
Full and delicious.
Sleep to
It feels good.
Oh...
Oh, something...
Next, make a sync.
Lick it.
Oh awesome.
Can I drink?
Feel good
Very very beautiful.
No to no.
No, this is good.
Yes, yes... well...
The next shit came.
Feel good
Another one will enter.
Asc is
Feel good
No, it feels good.
Oh, stop to
Feel good
by
You may not have been able to endure.
No to
It is painful, all the time.
It’s great, I can endure it.
Full of out.
I was excited.
Very big.
Oh well feel.
greatly
In the mouth of tears.
Very good feeling.
Feel good
Ta Hua and Len are dying in the same position.
easily to break.
Why once?
I am wrong.
No to
Me is
Oh yeah yeah yeah
No to
and ve
It feels good.
Air Conditioner eyeshadow
Oh I cried.
I am going now.
No to No.
Oh really
Very good feeling.
Go to sleep? I don’t know.
Feel good
Skeletonists
I have it.
hurtly
It is so lovely.
Oh, so great feeling.
Feel good
Very good feeling.
Okay, it is cheap.
Feel good
Very good feeling.
immediately feel bad.
What am I doing so much.
I quickly escaped,
Check that the person is running away immediately.
Make sure they run away a little.
Monk, it feels great.
No more, no more stop.
I’ll get out of mine a little.
Can I clean your rubbish face?
Monk is fine.
Del, Del is Del!
by Ryo Gaya
It would be hard to find a girl.
I want to kiss.
It is romantic.
Really to?
I will hit.
I was back in the hustle.
Just now, I can’t wait.
Wait until they make it.
I can do it in a moment.
Oh awesome.
Oh my dear, wait a little.
It is delicious, Mommy.
I am a laurel, so I’ll wait.
Tastefully
No to no.
Nami, I ate the nuts.
No to
Wait a little.
Yes
I want to cool the food.
Do it from somewhere.
I also ate coconut.
I ate everything.
What to do.
It smells very hungry.
I was hungry.
Oh well cute.
It seems to be getting hot.
Are you going to be a pantsubishi?
Show me your ass.
Your kind child.
I will cool.
No, because it will cool.
No, no, no no no no no.
Oh yeah, it is great.
Keep your ass and show it a lot.
Oh, oh, it is awesome
Great, I know
No, I am ashamed.
Show me, no.
I am ashamed of college students.
Very well well.
No, no more
No more not.
No to no.
Show me more.
It tastes good here too.
No to no.
It smells good.
No more no.
Tastefully
Really good now.
No longer sleep.
No more no.
I have done it all twice, but I have done it in a different way, socially.
I am talking about the Pacific.
I think of my good world.
No to
Go to
Great to eat.
I will go away.
More of
Now hold your fingers.
and meat.
Yes
Great
Mother and Mother.
It feels good!
Oh! is awesome!
The taste is out.
Oh well delicious!
It looks sounding easily.
Feel good and can’t eat.
Tastefully
here to here.
I slept.
I cannot go to sleep sooner.
What is your mother?
Mother, can you sleep?
I want something more.
I want more.
greatly
It feels good.
Very good feeling.
Feel good
Oh yeah yeah yeah
something
Mr to Mr.
I want to drink.
Do not stop?
I feel tired and tired with Miki.
I am going to get hungry.
Things I Illusions
Mr Nami
Oh well, oh well, oh well
Come on!
You are blacky.
Do not hide.
Tears are fun.
Ton to
Explain to
Oh is
Put it in.
Enter it in.
Oh is
Oh, the feeling
Why is
Oh, it feels good.
No, let me go.
hurtly
and
It feels good.
Oh is
Feel good
Oh yeah live
Oh yeah yeah
Oh yeah yeah yeah
No to
I took it next to you.
was next to you.
Instead of doing homework.
I will have sex.
With the male student he met at the part, such a relationship is also quickly going through the four-year period, and he is trying to end with his graduation.
He returns to his local area and tells the family business.I live with my unhealthy husband as I always did.I have no place to go.
Finally a farewell.
If you want to meet again, you will meet again.
But I can’t see you here anymore.
I don’t want to shower today as I did the first time.
I have written a lot.
I said a lot.
The smell of Nami, I don’t want to forget it all.
Let’s go a little.
Tastefully
No to
He is already sweating.
Sorry to
What are you doing?
by Tia
by
Full of stomach.
Tastefully
It is cold.
My stomach hurt.
Oh to
They bite everything.
Orange is delicious.
Feel good
It smells there.
The best.
I no longer sweat.
sweat is
The tears
Today is dirty.
It feels great.
You have to push in.
Fuck me, no
What? what? what? what? what?
A little, no more.
Oh well, oh well.
No, yes is
No to
It is dirty, so it is not.
Tastefully
Mommy, it is so delicious.
No to
Dirty...
It is no longer cold, it is dirty.
I will drink too.
No to
It is awesome.
Mrs. Nathalie, extend the rope.
No to
Oh yeah
extend it.
again
Oh well
No to no.
greatly
Sunny is awesome.
I am in a mess.
must be great.
It has become easier to eat.
Full of stomach.
A little more.
is sleeping
Oh yeah finished
Come to Feel
It is doing.
DJ is
Oh yeah yeah yeah
by
I will return you.
I had really good feelings today.
As I thought, she came home.
I think I have returned to her home.
And I thought I was back at her house.
And again!
I am very angry.
I hope you dream my dream.
I can see this to get people to like me.
I want to compete with my favorite guy.
I can see her love the guy that she is.
I will be her favorite guy and the woman she likes and she likes.
Be careful.
well is
He is hungry.
No to
Oh oh oh
HFFF
No to
Oh oh oh
Oh oh
Thanks to feel good.
It is cold.
something
Feels good.
Oh and so.
Boe
No longer
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh, oh oh, oh oh
alone...
I read you, coin.
Coin
You, this sister
by vom
is similar
Pruch is
This too
very much
Oh yeah
Feel good
It hurts.
hurtly
Feel good
Hi to
A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A
Feel good
Oh awesome.
Return to
Feel good
Okay okay okay okay.
Oh yeah
Yes Yes Yes Yes
J is
Oh yeah
Feel good
No to
cannot be
Oh, I continue
Tagged as  Tagged
Why is!
Have money.
well well
See it?
The Guardian