5 minutes later
Ah, I fell asleep
It's been a while since I've done this, so I'm a little nervous.
But I'm going to do my best.
I'm going to do my best.
Now that I've put on my sociali, I'm going to start starting.
Each time I put down six eggs, we figured out we should put them all injar together.
I don't know what to do with myself.
I don't know what to do.
Ah, feels good!
I'm sorry.
Yuki
What's wrong?
You look blank.
Maybe I overslept.
You're weak in the morning.
Hey, Yuki.
Are you still eating?
You're relaxing.
Have you decided on your career path?
I'm thinking about it.
If you don't do it now, you'll have to study more when you get old.
I've been thinking about it since this morning.
You're a little off.
Thank you.
I have a meeting today.
Really?
I don't need dinner.
Don't you need a little?
I don't need a little.
Okay.
I'll be a little late.
I'm counting on you.
Okay.
I took a bath.
Take a bath.
I'll take a bath in a little while.
Yuki, what's wrong with you today?
What?
You've been blank all day.
Do you have any worries?
I think so.
I don't have anything.
Are you in puberty?
What are you talking about?
You had something, didn't you?
I don't have anything.
Did you have a crush on someone at school?
What are you talking about?
I've never had that before.
I thought you had something.
It's not like that.
Really?
It's hard to say to your mother.
It's not like that.
Can I tell my father?
Don't do that.
I don't have anything.
Then I'll change my hair.
Wait a minute.
It's popular to use hair wax.
Don't do that.
I think it looks good on me.
It's okay.
It's cute, so I'll make it cool.
I'll put out my forehead.
Look at me.
Mom.
The center part is cool.
Why don't you try this?
It's okay, mom.
You have a beard.
Why don't you trim your eyebrows?
It's embarrassing.
It's okay.
I think it's cool to trim your eyebrows.
What's wrong?
Are you angry?
It's not like that.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I'm sorry.
It's snowing.
It's nice.
It feels good.
Isn't it a little too much?
It's because there's a set-up.
Don't you think it's too much?
You're angry.
It feels good.
My fingers get in.
Do it gently.
Push it hard.
Yes.
It feels good.
You're a little fat, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
You're cute.
You make delicious food for me.
That's it.
Is it connected to the lower back?
That's it, too.
I think it's better over there.
Really?
I'm in trouble.
You should buy new shoes.
I think so.
I like that.
Do you want to buy the same shoes again?
I think so.
I'll have you choose the shoes for your face.
You're always like that.
You always leave it to me.
Yes.
It feels good.
Isn't it good?
It felt good.
Thank you.
I think I'm a little better.
You're not angry.
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Did you hear that?
What?
I'm a little older than you.
Really?
I may be a twin.
I want to congratulate you.
I thought you were the same age as me.
I'm a little older than you.
I'm about ten years older than you.
Really?
You did your best.
I did my best.
I want to congratulate you.
Really?
That's great.
I'm alone.
Don't you want a younger brother or sister?
I think so.
I want to think about it now.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
That's right.
By the way,
Didn't you do it recently?
Aren't you tired?
I had a massage today.
Thank you.
Mom.
What's wrong?
You're acting strange.
I like you.
I'm serious.
What's wrong?
Mom.
Get away from me.
What's wrong?
I like you.
What?
What's wrong?
It's painful.
Mom.
Get away from me.
I like you.
I love you.
Get away from me.
Mom.
I'm serious.
What are you talking about?
I'm thinking about you.
I don't like it.
Mom.
Touch me.
You're getting worse.
I don't like it.
Mom.
I can't control you.
I don't like it.
What's wrong?
Mom.
I don't like it.
What's wrong?
I can't control you.
Mom.
I don't like it.
What's wrong?
I can't control you.
I don't like it.
Mom.
I won't get angry.
Look at me.
Close your eyes.
I can't control you.
Please.
What?
I can't control you.
Touch me.
I can't.
Mom.
What's wrong?
Touch me.
I can't control you.
I can't.
Mom.
What's wrong?
I can't control you.
Mom.
I can't.
Please.
Just a little.
I can't.
What?
What's wrong?
Mom.
Mom...
Stop it.
Please.
Mom, please.
Mom...
No!
I'm scared.
Mom...
I'm lonely.
I have to make you my favorite.
Mom...
Mom, I like you.
Stop it.
Mom, look at me.
Come on, come on, touch me, touch me.
I really can't.
Come on, hold me.
Touch me a lot.
What should I do?
I can't do it.
Do it yourself.
I love you, mom.
I really can't.
Hurry up.
You know I can't do it, right?
No, you can't.
I can't stand it.
You can stand it, right?
No, you can't.
I can't stand it.
I can't stand it, mom.
You can do it yourself, right?
I can't stand it.
I can't stand it, mom.
Mom, mom.
Does it hurt?
Yes.
Just a little bit.
Okay.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
Does it feel good, mom?
Mom.
Just a little bit.
I'm a little angry.
I love you, mom.
That's enough.
I want to drink with you.
Let's drink together.
Then let's call it a day.
Is this okay?
You're like a baby.
It's so good.
Does it feel good?
Oh no.
It's gonna come out.
It's coming out.
Oh...
I'm sorry...
I felt so good...
Really?
Yeah, I felt so good...
Oh...
I can't do this anymore...
Mom...
Dad...
Stay away from me...
What's wrong?
Please...
Mom...
What do you want me to do?
I want you to do more.
What?
You did it with your hands, didn't you?
I can't stand it.
Mom...
Do you want me to do it?
Yes.
No matter what?
No matter what.
Okay.
Don't look at me like that.
You don't have to touch me.
Okay.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Okay.
I want you to lick my lips.
What?
My lips?
Okay.
I want you to lick my lips.
It's just for today.
Okay.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'm going to...
I cried a lot.
Mom...
It's amazing.
This is the end.
Yes.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I didn't touch you.
Do you want me to wash your face?
Yes.
I'm going to wash your face.
Thank you.
I'm going to be late today.
What about dinner?
I don't have dinner today.
Really?
I hope you will be able to study.
I'm doing my best.
I see.
Good morning.
You're here early.
What's wrong?
Mom.
Will you do it for me today?
What?
Okay.
Mom.
What's wrong?
Okay.
I'll do it for you.
Mom.
What's wrong?
Dad might come back.
Will you do it for me on the day he doesn't come back?
No, I won't.
I won't.
I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to die if I don't eat this.
I ate this.
I'm going to take a bath.
Do you want to take a bath?
Hurry up.
I'm going to take a bath.
It's not good to do this.
It's hard to stay overnight.
You look happy.
Did you put the golf bag properly?
You did it again, didn't you?
I'm fine.
Are you going to take a bath?
I'm going to take a bath.
Study hard.
I know.
I'm going to take a bath.
Be careful.
See you later.
Mom.
What's wrong?
I'm alone.
I'm alone with my mom.
What are you talking about?
Mom.
I'm not going to do anything.
I'm sorry.
What?
I've become like this.
So?
Please lick me.
I can't.
I've become like this.
Mom.
I can't do it myself.
I know.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
I'll just lick you.
Okay.
Mom.
I'll just lick you.
Okay.
Mom.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Mom.
Mom, I'm tired.
It's okay.
Mom.
I'll just lick you.
Okay.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'll just lick you.
It's okay.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'll just lick you.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I've done a lot of bad things.
Did I do this much?
Come here.
Mom.
It's okay.
Come here.
I love you, Mom.
It's okay.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
Come here.
I'm sleepy.
Let me see your body.
I'm sorry.
Your body is so wet.
You've grown up.
You're amazing.
You're so wet.
I'm sorry.
You're amazing.
I can't stand it.
I want to do it.
Put this on.
You can put it on.
Do you want to do that?
I love you.
It's just a little bit.
It's hard.
I love you.
You're amazing.
It's just a little bit.
It's hard.
I'll do it again.
It's just a little bit.
I want to do that again.
I want to keep doing that.
You're amazing.
I can't stop crying.
It's okay.
It feels good.
I'm stupid.
It's okay.
I can't stop crying.
There's a lot in here.
Gum.
I can feel your pain.
I'll put some gum on you.
No.
Why?
Be a good boy.
I can feel your pain.
It feels good.
I can't stop crying.
It's okay.
It feels good.
I can't stop crying.
It's okay.
It's not a misunderstanding.
I'm serious.
I can't help it.
It's okay.
I'll take you outside.
Mom, thank you.
I love you.
Mom, I love you.
Mom, thank you.
I love you.
mom....
oh no
mom, let's go
Oh, no.
Ah...
Let's go.
Go go go go!
Ah!
Oh, gosh.
I'm sorry.
I rushed too much.
You got myself in trouble.
I...
Stop it.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
It's so uncomfortable.
Hurry up.
I have to do this.
I'm afraid I'll fail.
It's in.
I can't take it out again.
I have to take it out quickly.
I love you.
No, no.
I can see your back.
I'm sorry.
I know.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
It's hard.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
It's in.
Don't cry.
Don't rush.
What should I do?
I'm tired.
I can't do it.
I love you.
Mom.
I can't do it.
Come here.
Lie down.
Mom.
I can't do it.
What should I do?
Mom.
I'm sorry.
Don't blame me.
I told you I can't do it.
I'm tired.
Do you want to do it so much?
Yes, I do.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Don't you regret it?
No, I don't.
Really?
I can't do it.
Mom.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Mom is moving.
I can't do it.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
I can't do it.
Do it more.
Do you like me?
Mom.
Look at me.
I can't do it.
I want to do it again.
Do as you like.
I can't help it.
I can't do it.
Do as you like.
It's overflowing.
I didn't feel good.
I didn't feel good, either.
I can't do it.
Did you let it out again?
Get up.
I can't do it.
You're still awake.
You're awake, aren't you?
I don't know what you're doing.
I'll leave you alone.
I can't do it.
What's going on?...
Calm down, please.
Hold on...
Woman moaning
You can't do that.
I can't do it?
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's been a while since we took a bath together.
You're getting older.
It's hot.
I just took a bath.
You're getting older.
Thank you.
You got taller.
It's hot.
Ah-
Pepper...
Ah...
I see.
It feels good, doesn't it?
What are you expecting?
Mom, this is amazing.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's really big, isn't it?
Do you want to put it in your mom's mouth again?
Yes, I do.
It's really big, isn't it?
I want to do more.
It's okay.
Good morning.
Good morning, mom.
Did you wake up?
I just woke up.
What time is it now?
It's 5.45 am.
It's really big, isn't it?
Dad will come home today.
It's the last day.
It's hot, isn't it?
I'm so happy.
Today is the last day.
I've put a lot of things in my mind.
What would you do if you had a baby?
I love my mom.
I don't mind if I have a baby.
Look this way.
Mom.
I don't mind if I have a baby.
Look this way.
Don't you regret?
No.
How much do you love me?
I love you more than anyone else.
I love you, too.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
I thought today was the last day.
So I prepared a surprise for you.
Look at me.
Mom.
It's different from usual.
I prepared a special day for you.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I love you more than usual.
I love you.
Do you love me?
I love you, too.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I love you more than usual.
I love you.
I'm going to hug you.
I'm going to put you in my arms.
I love you.
Yeah, sounds like a lot of fun
Do you want tea, man?
Okay, that's it.
I'm going to lick you.
Did you feel good?
I feel sick.
You're the only one who knows.
I want to lick you more.
You like your mother, don't you?
I feel sick.
I want to lick you more.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
More.
Put more effort into it.
Deeper.
I'll put more effort into it.
Are you okay?
It's so hot.
It's so hard.
It's getting worse.
I can't do it anymore.
It's so hard.
You have to stretch it.
I'll put more effort into it.
It's so hard.
I can't do it anymore.
Give me more.
You can still do it, right?
I can do it.
This is the last one.
It's so hard.
My legs are shaking.
I'm tired.
How was it?
The sun was so strong.
I think I got tanned.
Do you have anything to wash?
I'm sweating a lot.
I think I have a lot.
How was it?
Did anything change?
I was the same as usual.
I was a little lonely.
It's good to be gone once in a while.
Do you remember the conversation we had before we left?
Do you remember?
You were next to me.
I'm glad you remember.
I haven't talked to you for a long time.
I'm going to miss my brother.
I said that I wanted a brother while I was waiting.
Is that so?
I'll think about it.
Well, I've eaten a lot of food, so I'm full.
You're full?
No, no, no.
Yes, I'm full.
That's good.
I'm looking forward to it.
You're getting excited.
I don't want to.
I'm going to take a bath.
I'll leave this here.
Oh, yeah?
Yes.
I want to do it again.
Shall we do it again?
Yes.
Thank you for your viewing.