That's where we did it last time.
Yes.
Let me see.
That's where we did it last time.
We did it last time.
I'm sorry. I just remembered.
Look at my body.
Yes.
That's where we did it last time.
Do you remember?
No.
I remember the shape.
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
Do you want me to do it again?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
That's where we did it last time.
Remember it.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
That's where we did it last time.
I can remember it now.
Wait a minute.
That's where we did it last time.
Do you remember?
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
Why?
Can I do it again?
I want to impress you.
Do you want to impress me?
I'll remember it.
How is it?
Can you remember it?
I can remember it.
Do you remember?
Yes.
I can remember it.
Let's do it again.
I'll remember it.
Do you remember?
Yes.
I'll remember it.
How is it?
I can remember it.
Really?
Do you remember?
Yes.
I'll remember it.
You're good.
Don't forget it.
Yes.
Wow, you got it all right.
Really?
Thank you.
That's amazing.
Yes.
It's really easy to remember when I use your body.
Really?
Yes.
But you forgot the last time.
No, the last time was a little less stimulating.
What?
This time it was more stimulating and easier to remember.
Don't forget it.
Yes.
Then I'll give you a reward for getting it all right.
A reward.
Yes.
You can take it off.
Can I?
I'll never forget this.
Yes.
How is it?
I can remember it better.
Can I do this one?
Yes.
And this one.
Did you really remember it?
But if you touch me, I'm sure I'll remember it.
Then it's okay if you remember it.
Can I do this?
Yes.
Thank you, doctor.
Wait a minute.
This is X, and this is P.
This is P, and this is P.
You remember it very well.
Yes.
I'll teach you how to study and how to be sexy.
Yes, thank you.
It's getting into my head.
That's it.
Just a little more.
Wait a minute.
If you get it right, I'll give you a reward.
Really?
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Isn't the test coming soon?
The test is coming soon.
Get 100 points.
100 points.
You can do it, right?
Yes.
I'll definitely get 100 points.
I'm looking forward to it.
If I get 100 points, will I get a reward?
Of course.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
100 points.
If you get 100 points, I'll give you a great reward.
A great reward?
Yes.
Okay.
Hello, Ueda.
Hello.
What's the matter?
I got 100 points.
That's great.
You really got 100 points.
Yes, I got 100 points.
That's great.
You got everything.
Yes.
That's great.
I remembered everything about you.
I got 100 points because I didn't stop even once.
Wow.
Yes.
I could feel your boobs.
Really?
Yes.
Did you see my boobs?
They came out.
It's all thanks to you.
I'm glad.
I promised to give you a great reward.
A reward?
Yes.
I promised to give you a great reward.
I remember everything.
I'm glad.
I was surprised.
What's the reward?
Wow.
Thank you.
You got 100 points.
I'll give you a lot of rewards today.
A lot?
Really?
Did you remember?
Yes, I remember.
It's a reward, isn't it?
Yes.
I got 100 points, so I'll give you a lot of rewards.
Okay.
What's the matter?
I can't stop thinking about you.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Do you want to go to bed?
Bed?
Yes.
You're too lazy.
What's the matter?
My shoulder hurts.
It hurts.
I'll show you more.
I'm glad I did my best on the test.
I'll give you a lot of rewards.
Really?
It's amazing.
It's soft.
Can I touch your shoulder?
Do you want to touch it?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It's wet.
Are you excited?
Yes.
I'm so excited.
It's hard.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'll show you more.
More?
Yes.
You have to study the body of a woman.
I'll study.
You've never seen it, have you?
Look at it.
This is also a study.
It's amazing.
You can touch it.
Yes.
It's warm.
Is it warm?
Yes.
It's warm.
Why is it so wet?
It's because it feels good.
Touch me more.
Yes.
If you let me touch you, I'll give you a reward.
Reward?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Will you lick me?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
If you let me touch you, I'll give you a reward.
Reward?
It's amazing.
Will you let me touch you?
Don't do that.
Why?
It's amazing.
You're very excited.
Yes.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Your waist is moving a lot.
Does it feel that good?
It feels good.
I'll make you feel better.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I want you to stop.
Does it feel that good?
Yes.
It's amazing.
I'll give you a reward.
How do you feel?
I can't do it with my hands.
I think you'll be able to remember this better.
Yes.
When will I be able to remember?
How do you feel?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
You love my boobs, don't you?
Yes, I love them.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Do you want to feel better?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Is it okay?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
Look at my body more.
Okay.
I'm getting excited.
It's amazing.
Look at me.
Look at my belly.
Okay.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Look at me.
It feels good, right?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Look at my belly.
Okay.
It feels good.
I'm getting hot.
I'm going to go.
Wait a minute.
I'm going.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry that I couldn't help you.
Come here.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'm just singing.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
This time, you move.
Me?
Okay.
I'll move.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
You forgot to study, didn't you?
I want to do this more now.
No.
Yes.
Remember this.
Can you remember some formulas?
If you do this, you'll be able to remember about five.
That's right.
I'll remember more than before.
Remember this.
It's amazing.
It was very dirty again.
Is it in your head?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
If you don't feel good, do it slowly.
It hurts.
Doctor.
Did you remember?
Yes, I remembered.
If you remember, write a formula on my butt.
My butt?
I got it.
You remembered, didn't you?
Yes.
I'll try it.
Are you writing a formula?
Yes, I'm writing a formula.
I'll remember more and more.
Did you remember everything?
Yes.
Did you remember?
Do you remember?
Yes, I remember.
Y equals B tangent.
Shit.
I got it.
It hurts.
Great.
You remembered everything.
Yes.
I wrote a formula.
It feels good.
Doctor.
I can't do it anymore.
What about you?
Why?
I can't do it anymore.
Ah.
Doctor.
Is it okay to write a formula?
You'll remember, won't you?
Yes.
I forgot this.
I'll learn from you.
Well.
Did you remember?
Yes.
It's easier to understand.
You'll get a perfect score next time.
Yes, I'll get a perfect score.
If you get a perfect score, I'll do something better than today.
Something better than today?
Yes.
Better than today?
You did a good job.
I'm glad.
I'm sure I'll get a perfect score.
Yes.
It's easy to get a perfect score.
Ah.
If you can do that, I'll make it easier for you when you get a harder one.
This one, too?
Yes.
Try this one.
This one?
Yes, this one.
Well.
What was this?
You taught me this the other day, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Yes.
I remember it somehow.
You taught me the same thing the other day.
Yes, I did.
Yes.
I remember it somehow.
You did it a lot.
Yes, I did.
Yes.
Well.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
Try to remember it.
Well.
Do your best.
Can you stretch your back a little?
Yes.
Well.
I don't think you remember it.
No, no.
Well.
Ah.
What?
You did it.
You did it a lot.
Tatsuki.
Well.
What?
Ah.
At that time.
Yes.
Well.
Oh, no.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Well.
I thought you remembered it well.
Ah.
I know where it is.
Well.
Ah.
I'm sorry.
I can't remember it.
Ah.
I have a lot to remember before the test.
I'm sorry.
Well.
It can't be helped.
Ah.
Do you want to remember it again?
Please.
I'll never forget it this time.
You'll remember it this time.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
You'll remember it this time.
Yes.
Oh.
I'll never forget it.
Yes.
Ah.
Well.
I equals.
X minus 1.
Yes.
X plus 2.
Oh, no.
Ah.
X plus 2.
Yes.
X minus 1.
X plus 2.
Look carefully and remember it.
X plus.
Yes.
Well.
You said you remember where it is, didn't you?
Yes.
I put it in the same place as last time.
Ah.
I'll never forget it.
Yes.
This formula.
If you forget it next time.
Ah.
I wonder if the teacher will be angry.
I'll never forget it.
Yes.
X plus 1.
Ah.
Try it.
Yes.
I wonder if you remember it properly.
I remember it.
Yes.
I did it.
Wow, you remember it.
Well.
Yes.
Using that formula.
This is the same, so let's solve it.
Yes.
This.
Remember this formula, too.
Yes.
I'll never forget it.
I'll never make the same mistake again.
I got it.
Wow.
You remember it properly.
I did it.
Wow.
You did it.
I did it.
I'll never forget it.
This formula is perfect.
Yes.
Okay.
This is perfect for the test.
Yes.
Well, let's solve the next problem.
The next one?
Yes.
This is the same, so...
Well, I remember too many things now.
Yes.
Let's take a break.
A break?
Let me calm down.
Okay.
Let's take a break.
I'll never forget it.
Well, if you forget it, I'll be angry and I can't show it to you many times.
I know.
I'll never forget it.
Yes.
Okay.
You're great.
You remember it well.
Because you teach me so hard.
I can't forget it.
You can't forget it just by talking.
Yes.
Of course.
Well, let's make a promise.
A promise?
Yes.
Okay.
Let's make a promise not to forget it.
It's good.
Yes.
Did you make a promise?
I'll never forget it.
You must.
Yes.
It's good.
Okay.
Now that we made a promise, let's solve the next problem.
Ouch!
Doctor.
What?
It hurts.
Oh, really?
Yes.
I can't go on.
You should get used to it.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't stand up every time you remember it.
Because I can't get used to being kissed by such a beautiful doctor.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
Take it off.
Oh, dear.
I'm sorry.
Your face is covered.
It won't get better.
What?
It won't get better?
No, it won't.
I can't do it anymore.
You just touched it a little.
Oh, dear.
I'm sorry.
You always do it.
You always do it, don't you?
Just a little.
Oh, please.
Oh, doctor.
I'll never forget it.
Oh, dear.
I'm sorry.
You should get used to it.
I'll never forget it.
Tatsuki.
I don't want to waste your time.
So, I'll ask you to read this.
Read it.
When you read this, remember that the doctor licked you.
Then, you'll remember it.
Yes.
13x-1
1 over 2
3 over 4
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
Oh, dear.
You shouldn't say that.
Say it.
I'm sorry.
When I was concentrating, I could do it.
Really?
Yes.
But I could remember it all.
Really?
Yes.
That's a lot.
Isn't it a lot today?
I think so.
Is it okay to concentrate so much?
It's a proof that I could remember it well.
You can concentrate now, right?
Yes.
I'll do it all.
Then, I'll do it all today.
I'll do it.
I can remember it all.
You're concentrating well.
Really?
Yes.
You can remember it all.
I can remember it all.
By the way,
Yes.
You have a test next week, right?
I have a test next week.
Can I look forward to it?
Please look forward to it.
Really?
I'll get 100 points.
100 points?
I'll get 0 points except 100 points.
With that feeling?
Yes.
Let's challenge the test.
I'll definitely get 100 points, so please look forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
What should I do?
Hello, Mr. Tachibana.
Oh, hello.
Let's study hard today.
Please.
Let's do it.
How was the last test?
Yes.
It's over.
What's the result?
You haven't got the result yet?
Yes, I have.
Oh...
You were so confident.
No.
What?
98 points?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't remember the formula for the last test.
Oh...
You taught me so much, but I couldn't get the result.
I see.
I'm so sorry.
I couldn't get the result at all.
I was so impatient.
You taught me so much, but I could remember the formula.
You were so confident.
I'm so sorry.
It's the same as 0 points.
Well, well, well.
You could remember the formula, so you don't have to be so depressed.
You taught me so much, but I couldn't get the result at all.
I see.
But, let's be careful next time.
There is no next time.
I can't do anything.
I'll drop out of college.
I'll fail to get a job.
You're so depressed.
It's okay.
Let's do our best next time.
I don't know what to do.
Don't be so depressed.
You can study hard again.
I don't know if I can study hard.
You taught me so much, but I couldn't get the result at all.
I'll ask my math teacher to give me 0 points.
It's not like that.
You can study hard.
Let's do our best next time.
You're so depressed.
I'm sorry.
You can't study hard.
Okay.
Look at me so that you can do your best next time.
I'm not motivated.
Don't say that.
Miss...
I'm sorry.
Don't be depressed.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
You're getting better, aren't you?
Yes.
Cheer up and let's do our best next time.
I'm sorry.
You're getting better, aren't you?
I couldn't get the result at all.
Don't be depressed.
You're always doing your best, aren't you?
You know me the best.
Miss...
I'm sorry.
Cheer up.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't get the result at all.
You couldn't get the result at all?
I'm going to take off your clothes.
It's too tight.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to make you feel better so that you can do your best next time.
Do you want to see the result?
Yes.
I'll never forget it.
Never.
I wonder if you can overcome it.
I'm sorry.
You're amazing.
You're getting better.
I'm sorry.
I wonder if you can overcome it.
How is it?
Can I touch you?
Yes.
How is it?
Can I touch you?
You're depressed today.
It's special.
It's good.
Does it feel good?
Are you okay?
You're depressed today.
I'm going to make you feel better so that you can do your best next time.
I'm sorry.
Can you stand it today?
I don't know.
You can't?
No.
It's hard.
You should study when you're depressed.
And read the reference book.
The reference book.
I love it.
Do you think you can memorize it?
Yes.
It's hard.
You should concentrate on the screen.
I'll do my best.
When the teacher is doing something, you should remember it.
Does it feel good here?
Do you feel good?
Concentrate and memorize it.
It feels good.
My head is going to pop out.
Did it pop out again?
Yes.
It popped out.
What?
It's amazing.
It's stronger than usual.
I ate it for a week.
It's been a while since I ate it.
I see.
You did your best for a week.
Yes.
I ate too much.
This is your effort.
Effort?
I guess so.
I'll put it on your face.
What?
It's amazing.
I'll put it on your face.
It popped out a lot.
It's loud.
What's wrong?
Tatsuki.
Please get up.
I can't get up.
It's amazing.
It popped out.
I can't get up.
I'll use your body and learn a lot.
You'll learn a lot.
It's amazing.
I'll learn a lot.
Enjoy it so that you can remember it well.
It's amazing.
Hey.
What?
I think it's better to write it directly on my body.
On your body?
Yes.
Write it with this.
Can I?
Let's write it with this.
Okay.
I want to see it well.
Let's see it well, write it, and remember it.
Can I?
Write it on your body and remember it.
It's amazing.
I can remember it.
How is it?
You can remember it if you write it directly.
Your body is amazing.
Can I remember a lot?
Yes.
Remember what you can't remember.
Okay.
If you write it here, you can remember it.
It's amazing.
Can I lick it?
What?
If you look at it from here, you will never forget this view.
Wow.
I'll burn it in your eyes while licking it.
Okay.
Can I burn your stomach and fingers?
Remember it well.
Okay.
It's amazing.
Remember it with your senses.
Okay.
You'll never forget this.
It's amazing.
What are you doing?
Are you doing well?
You're doing great.
It's amazing.
You'll never forget this.
Write everything you want to remember.
It's amazing.
I remembered it.
Did you really remember it?
It's perfect.
Is it perfect?
Yes.
Really?
I'm sorry about earlier.
Tatsuki.
Yes.
If you don't remember this, you'll be the most shocked, right?
So, if you get closer to me, I think you'll remember it better.
Closer?
Yes.
I think I'm going to burp.
It's too close.
It's okay.
Closer.
I want to remember it closer.
Come here.
I'm going to burp.
In the toilet.
I think you'll remember it better if you burp.
Yes.
I want to burp.
What do you think?
I'm going to burp.
Can I shake your legs more?
I can feel the warmth in your back.
Can you feel it?
Yes.
I'm going to burp.
Can I see your back?
I can see it well.
Wow.
I'm going to burp.
Can I shake your legs more?
Yes.
I feel good.
I'm going to burp.
Wow.
Can you see it well?
Yes.
I'm going to burp.
Can I shake your legs more?
More?
I'm going to shake your legs more.
Can I see your back?
Yes.
I'm going to study while doing this.
You can burp like this in this difficult exercise.
I'm going to burp.
Keep going...
What's wrong?
My...
I think I'm going to puke.
Puke?
Yes.
Okay.
Let me see.
I'm going to puke.
Really.
You'll remember it when you see it.
Doctor?
Yes.
I'm going to puke.
Okay.
It's hot.
I'm so nervous.
I'm going to puke.
I've puked.
I have a lot of puke.
We can't forget it.
We have to remember it.
I'll do my best to remember it.
I'll never forget it.
You'll never forget it, right?
Of course. I'll remember it for the rest of my life.
Can I put it in again?
Again?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
I'll never forget it.
That's right.
That's great.
I'm so sad.
I have a lot to remember.
You have a lot.
I'll remember this feeling.
It feels so good.
How do you feel?
Let's go.
Your butt is so easy to remember.
My butt?
Yes.
Do you like my butt?
Your face.
Your butt is moving a lot.
It's easy to remember, isn't it?
I'm done.
It feels so good.
Studying like this is the best.
But it's easy to remember, isn't it?
It feels so good.
It's easy to remember.
It's coming out.
You have a lot.
Look at me.
I put it out here.
Did you remember what I told you?
It's okay.
Let's remember a lot and do our best.
Thank you for your continued support.
I'll follow you forever.
Here?
Yes.
It's smoother than before, isn't it?
You should have told me.
I'm glad.
What's wrong?
I want you to tell me the way you taught me before.
The way I taught you before?
It was very easy to remember.
That's right.
I've learned a lot since I've been able to do that.
Yes.
Every month?
Let's do it again today.
Yes, please.
You have to move your hands.
Yes.
Do you remember the formula before?
When I look at your boobs, I remember the formula.
You're good at writing.
You can see the formula, right?
Yes.
It was very easy to remember.
I'm glad.
You have to learn a lot.
I'll give you a pen.
Yes.
You're amazing.
It's all thanks to you.
When I look at your boobs, I remember the formula.
Is it easy to remember?
Yes.
You're good at writing.
You're smart.
It's all thanks to you.
Today's formula is this.
Can you see it?
It's hard to see from this side, isn't it?
Yes.
Can you see the curve?
Yes, it's easy to see.
Do you remember the formula?
Yes.
Can you see the curve?
You're a boy, so you have to remember the formula.
I'm sorry.
It can't be helped.
It's very easy to remember.
Is it easy to remember?
Yes.
Can you write the formula?
It's a long formula.
You're good at writing.
Really?
Can you write the formula?
Yes.
You're good at writing.
It's easy to remember.
Yes.
It's all thanks to you.
It's because you look at my boobs.
It's easy to remember.
I'll give you a reward.
Are you sure?
Yes.
What should I give you as a reward?
I want you to remember my boobs more.
I'll put a pen here.
You're tired, aren't you?
Yes.
I think you'll be more relaxed if you touch something soft than a hard pen.
I'll put this on your forehead.
Yes.
You can remember it with both hands.
I think you can remember it.
Can you remember it?
Yes.
You can remember my boobs.
You remember all the rules of the lottery I put on your forehead, don't you?
Yes.
It's amazing that you can remember such a long thing.
Thank you very much.
How is it?
The softness.
It's very soft.
It's amazing.
It's a big thing.
It's really amazing.
Well, teacher.
What's the matter?
I have a test next week.
In that test, there is a girl who has good grades and is smart.
Her name is Sakuma.
Her name is Sakuma?
Yes.
I want to beat her.
She is your rival.
That's right.
You have to beat her.
Yes.
So you have to touch her more firmly.
You can remember only what you touch.
Yes.
Don't lose to Sakuma.
Remember this formula and other formulas.
Let's aim for the first place.
Yes.
I'll do my best.
Masakazu is the only one who is studying like this.
Yes.
You'll be fine.
Your teacher is with you.
Thank you.
Your teacher and your boobs are with you.
Yes.
You'll be fine.
You may be nervous during class.
Take a deep breath and remember your teacher and your boobs.
Yes.
Then you should be able to do well in the exam.
I'll remember your boobs during the exam.
I'm glad to hear that.
Do you want Masakazu to remember your boobs?
Yes.
So remember your boobs.
I'll remember my boobs today.
Yes.
Take a deep breath and remember your boobs.
I won't lose to you.
Yes.
Hello, Masakazu.
What?
Hello.
It was a test, wasn't it?
Yes.
It was a test.
Let me see.
I was looking forward to it.
Yes.
Here it is.
It's great.
100 points.
It's perfect.
And the handwriting is beautiful.
It's easy to read.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
By the way, how many points did you get?
I got about 70 points.
70 points?
Yes.
You did it.
You won.
Yes, I did.
Why?
You won.
You got 100 points.
Yes.
I was the best in my class.
I was the best.
Congratulations.
That's great.
What's wrong? Are you sick?
No, it's not like that.
Actually, I won the test last night.
Yes.
But my girlfriend was there.
Your girlfriend?
Yes.
I thought she wasn't there.
So, I didn't feel like I won.
Masakazu.
You got so many points in the test.
Think back to the beginning.
Yes.
This is your talent.
You got 100 points because of your study method and your talent.
But you're worried about Sakuma because he's your rival.
Yes, I don't want to lose to him.
Sakuma got about 70 points in the test.
But he looked so happy.
He got 70 points in the test.
Why?
I enjoyed it because my girlfriend was there.
I see.
I thought it wasn't good to get only good points in the test.
You have to praise yourself for getting good points in the test.
But...
Masakazu.
You want a girlfriend.
I want a girlfriend like her.
I see.
A girlfriend...
You have to give her a reward.
Masakazu and you...
What do you think of me as your girlfriend?
You mean me as your teacher?
Yes.
I don't want to date you.
I don't think so.
Because...
I'm touching your boobs with my hands.
I see.
Couples do that.
But you're studying and touching my boobs.
I see.
That's how you learned it.
I want a serious girlfriend.
I want a girlfriend like her.
I see.
You don't want a teacher?
No.
I mean...
You don't want one?
What?
Tell me.
Well...
I'm happy to have a teacher, but...
Give me your tongue.
Okay.
I see.
How do you like having a teacher?
You're getting older.
You can learn from her.
I like that.
Do you?
Yes.
I can learn and I can have a girlfriend.
Isn't it great?
Yes, it is.
Then you have to climb up the adult stairs a bit more.
Oh, okay. The adult stairs.
The adult stairs.
Sakuma-kun, you haven't studied yet, have you?
Huh?
This isn't going to change your reward for last time, is it?
Yes.
Come on, look closer.
Okay, let's leave it as it is for now.
It's okay, you can learn a lot.
This is amazing.
If I do this, I think I can learn a lot.
You think you can learn a lot?
Yes.
Are you okay?
Look at the teacher's boobs.
Yes.
I want you to look at all of them.
Look.
Huh?
This is amazing.
If you do this, you can concentrate, right?
Yes, I think I can concentrate.
Masakazu-kun, look.
Look, it came out.
Yes.
Look more.
More.
Look closely.
I'll look at them a lot and learn a lot.
Don't just look, touch them.
Yes.
You're her boyfriend, right?
It's going to overflow.
The teacher's boobs are big.
It's amazing.
Amazing?
Yes.
Masakazu-kun is amazing.
It's amazing to grow in such a short period of time.
Yes.
Look more closely.
This side too.
Look.
Yes.
Look closely at every corner.
Touch them.
The last one was long, so I think it's hard to remember.
Focus more.
I'll put it here.
It's amazing.
I was able to remember it in an instant.
Did you remember?
Yes.
When I was touched by Masakazu-kun, the teacher's boobs came out.
Look here.
Yes.
Just touch them.
I think you can do more with this.
Yes.
I think I can do more with this.
But it might come off.
Masakazu-kun.
Yes.
Why don't you take notes of my boobs?
What? Take notes of your boobs?
If you write it here, you can remember it.
I want you to like me more.
What?
Yes.
I have something good.
Something good?
I brought it.
Look at this.
This pen.
With this...
I'll write this formula on your boobs.
I see.
Like this.
Write it well.
You can write it like this.
You have a good face.
I see.
I think I can remember this.
You can?
If you take notes of my boobs, you'll be smarter.
Yes.
This is a good way.
Write it well.
Yes.
I wrote it.
You did?
Yes.
It's beautiful.
Observe it well.
Yes.
Touch it.
X minus 1 is 2.
Root 2 X minus 3.
Wow.
I can remember it.
It's long.
Yes.
Look closer.
Can't you see it because it's too close?
Yes.
I can remember it.
You can?
You have to memorize it.
Yes.
Wow.
Memorize it with your mouth.
With my mouth?
Yes.
Wow.
You can concentrate better if you lick my nipples.
Don't you think it's better to do it while chewing gum?
Yes.
It's your nipples.
Masakazu.
Yes.
Memorize more formulas.
It's a little narrow here.
Yes.
Do you want to use your whole body and write it down?
Where do you want to write it?
Come to the bed.
Yes.
Where do you think is better?
Here.
Then...
Here?
Yes.
Try writing it.
Okay.
Yes.
Look at the textbook carefully.
Write it big.
Wow.
You're so active.
Masakazu, you have a good face.
Yes.
You're studying hard, aren't you?
It's thanks to you.
I'm having a lot of fun studying thanks to you.
I'm glad.
You're not alone.
You have a girlfriend.
That's right.
Try writing it bigger.
Yes.
Write it big.
Wow.
Take a closer look.
Yes.
Trace it.
Not only there.
Here, too.
Yes.
Here.
It's easier to remember if you trace here, isn't it?
Yes.
Trace it closer.
Touch it and remember it.
Come closer.
Touch it closer.
Wow.
Smell it and remember it.
Yes.
Wow.
Masakazu.
Yes.
Have you ever touched here?
No.
Let's take a closer look here.
Yes.
Take a closer look.
See what kind of structure it is.
Yes.
Take a closer look through the official website.
Open it.
Yes.
I'll remember it, too.
You have to remember the structure of the doctor.
Yes.
Then...
Do you see the hole in the flat part?
Yes.
Trace it with your finger.
Here?
Yes.
Wow.
It's amazing.
Don't just trace it.
Put your finger in it.
Yes.
Look at the official website carefully.
Temperature, smell...
Masakazu has a lot of memories.
Put your finger in it.
Wow.
It's inside the doctor's room.
It's amazing.
I can remember the structure of the doctor.
Yes.
Wow.
It feels so good.
That's where the doctor is.
Yes.
I remember it.
You do?
Yes.
It's been a long time since I saw Masakazu.
Wow.
It feels so good.
The sky is shaking.
Look at the sky.
Wow.
It's so beautiful.
Check your mouth.
My mouth?
Yes.
Wow.
Look at your side.
It's Masakazu.
Wow.
It feels so good.
Masakazu's eyes.
Wow.
He moved.
It feels so good.
That's where the doctor is.
Yes.
Do you know the doctor's answer?
Yes, I do.
Then, show me the answer in the center of Masakazu's body.
Wow.
I have to put a flower here.
I'll put a flower here.
Wow.
Congratulations on your 100th birthday.
Thank you.
Wow.
There's a nice pen here.
Are you excited?
Yes.
It's cute.
Then, I'll look at this pen.
Wow.
Wow, it's great.
I have to get my lower body to remember it.
How is it? Can you see it with this?
Yes.
Can you remember it with this?
Wow.
I have to get my lower body to remember the formula written on your boobs.
It's easy to remember because the doctor's boobs are broken.
Is it easy to remember?
Yes.
Wow.
I think it's better to put it between your boobs like this.
It's great.
Yes.
Wow.
Oh, my lower body is crumpled.
It's very stiff.
Yes.
Wow.
Then, I'll take off the lid of this pen.
Yes.
Please.
You have to study more.
Yes.
Wow.
It smells good.
Then, I'll put the ink on your boobs.
Wow.
It's amazing.
I'll wipe it off.
It's wet.
Wow.
It's amazing.
Salty ink is coming out.
I'll take off the cap.
Wow.
Remember this.
Eat the ice cream you had in your head.
Yes.
Wow.
Then, I'll put the ink on your boobs.
You can see it clearly with your outlook.
Yes.
An X is drawn in the valley.
It's drawn.
Yes.
Wow.
Did you draw an X here on purpose?
No, I didn't.
By chance?
Yes, by chance.
You're good at taking notes, aren't you?
It's a mess.
It's a little cramped.
Then...
Look at everything.
Teacher's, Masakazu-kun's, Kana-chan's...
Body.
Everything.
There.
Hold on tight.
It's no good if it's just a little cramped.
Teacher, it feels so good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Teacher, I can't take it anymore.
You can't take it anymore?
What if I hug you like this?
It feels so good.
I see.
You can't take it anymore?
Masakazu-kun.
While remembering the formula,
do something that feels good.
Okay.
Look at the formula.
Look over here, too.
Look.
The part where you put your finger in earlier.
Put it in here.
Teacher's...
Boobies...
Body...
The formula you wrote yourself...
Don't look at it too much.
There's a lot to look at.
You can't just smile like Sakuma-kun.
Do you understand?
I'll remember it.
Can you remember it?
Yes.
It's a promise.
Look at this.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's a promise.
Write it down.
Okay.
Write down the formula you wrote the other day.
The formula I wrote the other day?
You can write it down here, too.
Okay.
You're writing it down.
That's amazing.
Okay.
It's really hard to write.
Did you write it down?
Yes.
My boobs are big.
I can't see the bottom.
I can see it well.
Can you see it?
It's for you to remember.
You just have to look at it.
I'm sorry.
Come closer.
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it all at once.
I can do it.
It feels good.
It's a promise.
I told you earlier.
The answer is right.
It's a promise.
Do you know what it means?
Yes, I know.
Is this the right answer?
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It feels good and it's easy to study.
Come closer.
I'm sorry.
You can write it down whenever you want.
Do you understand?
It's your privilege.
It feels good.
Can you move?
Yes.
Can you do it from behind?
Let's add a formula.
A formula?
Can you write it on your butt?
Put the textbook on your back.
Okay.
I'll write it.
I can't believe you're writing it.
I'm so excited.
I want your pen.
Not the one I brought.
You can write it down.
Did you write it down?
Yes, I did.
Then, remember it.
I want your pen.
My pen?
I might be selfish, but can I have your notebook?
Yes.
Look at the textbook I wrote.
Look at it and remember it.
This time, it's your butt.
It's easy to remember.
If you remember it, I'll give you a reward.
So, remember it.
I can't do it.
I'm so sleepy.
You can sleep.
Did you remember it?
Yes, I did.
Okay, put it in your stomach.
I'm so sleepy.
Did you fall asleep?
Yes, I did.
Can you remember more?
Yes, I can.
I'm so sleepy.
Can you write more?
Yes, I can.
Write here and here.
I'm so sleepy.
You can write more, right?
Yes, I can.
I'm so sleepy.
Did you write it?
Yes, I did.
You're still energetic.
I'm so sleepy.
Can you see me?
Yes, I can see you well.
I can see you well.
I feel so good.
Let's study with this.
Let's become an adult with this.
I feel so good.
I'll be scolded if I write more.
I'm so sleepy.
Did you memorize it?
Yes, I did.
I memorized all of them.
Great.
Then, put all of them in the teacher's room.
I'm so sleepy.
I feel so good.
More.
Sakaguchi-kun.
You're amazing.
I think you'll get a good score in the gym class.
Sakaguchi-kun.
In the future,
your study will definitely help you.
Let's study with Mr. Nippai.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Also, since you're my girlfriend,
I'll teach you more things that you don't know.
Yes, I want you to teach me more.
But it's a secret.
Yes, I'll keep it a secret.
I'm your secret teacher and girlfriend.
Nice to meet you.
Yes.
You should be happier.
I'm so happy.
Let's solve this problem, Suzuki-kun.
Yes.
Y equals...
This is the value of T, right?
Yes.
Well...
What was it?
It's difficult.
When you want this value, you use this formula.
This formula?
Yes, this one.
What's wrong?
Well...
Ms. Sakaguchi.
Yes?
I want you to teach me how to memorize that formula.
What?
That formula?
Yes, that formula.
I can't memorize it without that formula.
I see.
Then, can you memorize it?
Yes.
It can't be helped.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
Well...
Today...
I'll use this one.
And this one.
Okay, I got it.
Then, memorize it properly.
Yes.
Well...
Then...
Solve this problem.
This problem?
Yes.
You can do it if you use this formula.
This formula?
Yes.
Solve this problem.
This problem?
Yes.
You can do it if you use this formula.
This formula?
Yes.
I see.
First, memorize the formula.
Memorize the formula?
Yes.
Then, solve this problem.
Okay.
This problem?
Yes.
First of all...
Well...
If you solve this problem...
If I solve this problem?
Yes.
I'll give you a reward.
A reward?
Yes.
I'll give you a reward.
Okay.
If you solve this problem, you can turn this over.
What?
I see.
Do your best.
Okay.
I did it.
This is it.
You are amazing.
You are correct.
Thank you.
I owe it to you.
You can study by connecting the formula with your boobs.
This is a good thing.
The formula comes to my mind.
Really?
I'm glad.
Then, let's solve this problem.
Teacher.
Before solving the next problem, I want to see the formula.
I see.
I forgot it.
You said you would show me the formula if I was correct.
Yes.
Okay.
Please show me.
Excuse me.
It's beautiful.
This part is like this.
Yes.
If you remember the formula on your nipples, you can solve the problem easily.
I'll remember it.
Let's do our best together.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
Keep it up.
Let's move on to the next problem.
The next problem.
This formula is on this page.
Teacher.
I solved it.
Yes.
You're correct.
Oh, no.
It melted.
I'm sorry.
No problem.
I'll give it to you because you're correct.
I want to solve it by myself.
I see.
I got it.
Here you are.
I'll do my best.
Okay.
I memorized it perfectly.
Yes.
Keep it up.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
What should I do next?
I think this is good.
Okay.
The next problem is on this page.
The formula is on this page.
Okay.
Let's solve the second question.
The second question?
Yes.
It's important to memorize the formula now.
The formula?
Yes.
Look at this formula and solve it.
This formula?
Yes.
You can't look at the formula in the exam.
Okay.
It's important to memorize the formula now.
I'll do my best.
Okay.
Keep it up.
I got it.
Did you get it?
Wait a minute.
Wow.
You're correct.
Thanks to you.
Good job.
You can take this exam again.
This exam?
You solved the most difficult problem.
Thank you.
I'll give you a reward.
A reward?
Yes.
Here you are.
From now on, I'll watch your program and study harder.
I'll do my best.
Okay.
I'll give you a reward for studying hard.
It's been a long time.
Here you are.
Wow.
By the way, Suzuki-kun.
Yes?
I want you to review the formula again.
Review?
Yes.
So, can you put a sticker here?
I got it.
Excuse me.
Is this okay?
Yes.
Then, take a good look at the formula and memorize the formula.
I got it.
You have to take a good look at the formula.
Excuse me.
Ah.
You need to do one either of the above.
Oh.
That means.....
One either of the above plus one either of the above.
Oh oh oh!
Oh oh oh oh
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Can I take off the bandage?
Yes.
I'm glad that I can learn a lot from you.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you very much.
The exam is coming soon.
Let's do our best together.
I'll do my best.
I'll be more strict from now on.
Let's do our best together.
I'll do my best.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Let's continue the exam.
Let's do it here.
Okay.
Here.
That's right.
I'm not afraid of the exam.
Okay.
What kind of exam is this?
Which one?
This one?
I don't remember the name of the exam.
Where did you put this?
I put it on your boobs.
That's right.
You remember it.
Your boobs and memory are in good condition.
You'll be fine.
My body and my memory will be in good condition.
You can remember my number.
Your body and my memory will be in good condition.
Okay, it's a deal.
Okay.
For example, how about this formula?
What?
What was it?
Did you forget?
I'm sorry.
In that case, you have to remember it right away.
You can't forget the formula, so you have to remember it right away.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Now you know that revenge is important, right?
This is the formula.
Suzuki-kun.
Among them, put the one you don't remember here.
Here?
Then, this one?
Yes.
You can remember it if you put it on your body like before.
Look at it carefully and remember it again.
Yes.
Suzuki-kun, did you remember?
Yes, I remembered.
Really? Then, I'll test it.
Then, tell me the formula here.
Yes.
Y equals A, X minus P.
Correct!
That's great!
You're great.
You did well.
Thank you.
Then, you can take this pen.
Then...
You can do it if you do it.
Yes.
Keep it up.
Then, I'll give you a reward.
A reward?
Can I?
Yes.
I'll give you a reward if you remember it well.
A reward?
I'll take it.
Then, remember it well.
Yes.
The math test next month is perfect, right?
Yes, it's perfect.
Yes.
Keep it up and remember it well.
I'll remember it.
Ah!
If you get a reward like this, will you study more?
Yes, I will.
Then, what should I do next?
I want to remember it with my body.
I can't help it.
Then, I'll do my best for you.
Yes.
Look at this and remember it.
What?
3, 4, 5.
B equals F.
A equals F.
This is the formula that A equals F minus B.
Formula?
Yes.
This is also a point that is often used in the test, so remember it well.
F?
B equals F.
Ah!
It's getting better.
That's good.
Then, today is the final test of next month, so you can study with your teacher's body as you like.
Let's do our best for the final test.
Yes.
I'll do my best.
Phew.
You can't do it yet.
Study hard.
I'll study hard.
Yes.
Then, put the formula that you studied the other day on your teacher's body as you like.
What?
Yes.
I got it.
Then, I'll put it on here.
Yes.
This one.
Put it on here.
Teacher, if you put it on here, it will come off, so can I write it directly on your body and study it?
Yes.
That's good.
Then, use that pen.
Yes.
Then, I'll write it with this.
I'll study with this.
Yes.
FF is equal to X minus B.
Y minus G is equal to 0.
Then, I'll write this formula on your teacher's body.
Yes.
Then, remember it well.
FF is equal to X minus B minus Y minus G is equal to 0.
Yes.
This formula is also easy to write.
I still have a lot to write, so write it well and remember it well.
Yes.
This one, too.
X minus B minus G is equal to Y minus G is equal to 0.
Yes.
B minus G is equal to 0.
I memorized this formula perfectly.
Yes.
Keep it up.
More.
Yes.
This area is not enough.
I think I can memorize this area more.
Then, I'll take this out of the way.
Yes.
Then, I'll write a lot.
I'll write it.
Then, I'll write this left V.
Yes.
X minus B minus G is equal to Y minus G is equal to 0.
Look at this.
Yes.
X minus B minus G is equal to Y minus G is equal to 0.
I'll tie it with a rubber band.
It disappeared.
I'll write it again as soon as it disappears.
Yes.
I'll write it again.
Next, I'll take this out of the way.
This is X minus B minus G is equal to Y minus B.
Oh, my God.
X minus B minus G is equal to Y minus B.
This is F cup.
Yes.
I've memorized this area.
Me, too.
X minus B minus G is equal to Y minus B.
I can't finish it.
I'll write it on my butt.
On your butt.
Yes.
Then, I'll write it on this side.
It's easy to write on my butt.
Yes.
Then, you can memorize a lot.
This is B.
Yes.
Fill my body officially on that side, too.
This is 1.
Oh, my God.
X minus B minus G is equal to Y minus B.
This is 1.
I see.
Keep it up.
Yes.
More.
I'll write it on my butt.
Yes.
On your butt.
You see?
Memorizing is the most important thing.
Oh, my God.
You have to memorize a lot.
Yes.
It's hard.
Let's have fun studying.
Yes.
You're sweating a lot.
Then, remember this.
Yes.
Then...
What did you write here?
The answer is 0.
That's right.
Then, this formula is...
Here you are.
What's this?
This formula is X plus Y plus R plus 2.
That's right.
Keep it up.
I'll give you a reward if you memorize it.
A reward.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
It's hot.
Can you see the formula here?
Yes.
You have to memorize it.
I have to memorize it.
I have to write it here.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
It's hot.
You're not good at it.
I'm sorry.
You have to concentrate on studying.
Yes.
Keep it up.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
I want to lie down.
Do you want to lie down?
Then, you have to look at the formula here.
Oh, my God.
It's hot.
You have to concentrate on studying.
Oh, my God.
X equals B plus 2.
B plus 2.
Oh, my God.
That's right.
Y equals X.
Y equals 2B plus 2.
That's right.
You're right.
Oh, my God.
Hey, Tsuzaki.
You have to study a lot.
I'll study with you.
Yes.
Then, I'll give you a reward.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Now, you'll be able to study with me, right?
Yes, I'll be able to study with you.
One more.
Oh, my God.
You have to study hard.
Yes.
X equals B plus 2.
I'll give you a reward.
Yes.
X equals B plus 2.
You have to remember the feeling of touching me.
Yes.
X equals B plus 2.
Oh, my God.
Can you see it?
Here?
It's not enough.
Oh, my God.
Look at me.
Can you see it?
Yes, I can see it very well.
Look at me.
Don't look away.
You have to study hard.
Look at my back.
Yes.
Then, let's draw this.
This?
Yes.
Can I draw this?
Is this okay?
Yes.
Look at me.
I can't see the characters on your butt.
Oh, my God.
If I do this, you can't get close to me, can you?
Yes.
I can't get close to you.
Then, you can remember it well.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
Yes.
You have to remember the characters on my back.
Oh, my God.
Here, here.
I'm doing my best, so I can get more than 80 points.
What are you feeling now?
I want to work together with the teacher.
Oh, I see.
I see.
You can draw as much as you want.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Let's draw the X.
X.
I see.
X, right?
X.
I see.
Please help me.
I feel sick.
Can you draw as much as you want?
Yes.
I feel sick.
I can't stand it.
You can't stand it?
Do you remember the rules?
I'll do my best.
It's okay.
I'll let you in.
Are you sure?
I'll do my best.
I promise.
I can't stand it.
Thanks to you, I was able to finish the back and the buttocks.
This time, I have to remember the front, too.
What?
Don't you remember this part?
I can't help it.
Look at me.
Can you see it?
I'll practice half-and-half.
I've said it many times, but half-and-half is very important.
Touch the buttocks from behind and remember what's written on your back.
Can you do it?
I can't do it.
I'll do my best.
I'm not good at this.
I'm losing consciousness.
I can't do it.
Look at me.
Move.
Does it feel good?
Do you want to go out?
I don't want to.
Put the hot water in me.
I'll put the hot water in you.
Remember that.
I can't do it.
You're doing your best.
But you still have a lot to learn.
Let's do our best together.
I'll do my best.
In order to do that, you have to write the formula, erase it, and write it again.
It's important to repeat that.
First, lick this and erase it.
Do I lick this and erase it?
Yes.
I can't do it.
Remember that.