This is a souvenir I got when I went on a business trip to Fukuoka the other day.
Oh, thank you.
I'm sorry I didn't notice.
No, no, no.
Please eat it if you like.
Thank you.
What is this?
Fukuoka mentaiko.
Isn't it a famous one?
I like it.
Thank you.
I know.
That's right.
I'm glad.
I know.
Let's eat it for dinner.
Yeah.
Will you eat dinner properly today?
I will.
You don't come home recently, so you don't eat dinner.
I'll eat dinner today.
No, no, no.
Don't you have a brother at home?
Will you listen to me?
Yes.
You don't come home recently because you have a lot of work to do.
I go on my day off.
I had a lot of plans to go out.
But it's all over.
I can't help it.
I'm busy now.
It's been a long time.
When will it end?
It will end next week.
It's been a month since I said that.
Don't make time with Yuri.
It's okay.
You're kind.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
What kind of work are you doing?
The project was over the other day.
I'm busy now.
What are you busy with?
I have a lot of things to do.
How is your company?
You have a lot of overtime.
How is my company?
My company is white.
I heard that.
My company is also white.
Where is white?
It's a very clean company.
You're stupid.
I told you to get a job.
I'm sorry.
You're always like that.
You're busy.
I wasn't like this before.
Did you change your department?
My boss has changed recently.
That's where it starts.
Is that so?
I should go home.
Don't you think so?
Did you change your department?
That's right.
I'm 30 years old now.
It's not strange to change your department.
That's right.
I think it's possible.
You don't have much time with me.
What do you think?
Tell him.
I'm sorry.
What do you think?
I'm in a hurry.
Are you in a hurry?
I'm going to the company now.
You came to the company.
I'm sorry.
I'm in a hurry.
I'll change my clothes and go.
Let's eat together.
Don't you eat?
I'm sorry.
I bought a meal.
I can't eat dinner alone.
I bought a lot of ingredients.
I bought good meat.
Good meat?
Do you want to eat dinner at my house?
I have a lot of ingredients.
I bought a lot of rice.
I'm glad to hear that.
Really?
By the way.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
Is that so?
I thought you were popular.
That's not true.
I've been popular since I was a kid.
Is that so?
I don't have a girlfriend.
How are you doing recently?
I'm fine.
I'm fine at this age.
That's normal.
That's right.
I'm in my mid-twenties.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
I don't know if I should tell you this.
What is it?
Can you hear me?
Yes.
Actually.
As you can see.
Ichiro is busy at work.
So.
I don't have much time for my husband.
I'm 29 years old.
I'm 30 years old.
I'm in a hurry.
I've always wanted a child.
Is that so?
Yes.
I have to make a child soon.
I may not be able to make it in time.
But I want a child.
Please.
Will you have sex with me?
We are brothers.
We have the same genes.
Please.
No.
I don't think that's good.
But.
No.
Well.
I'm sorry.
But.
I want a child.
I can only ask you.
Please.
Excuse me.
I can't.
I really want a child.
Please.
Well.
Are you sure?
Are you sure you want me?
No.
I can't.
I'm Ichiro's brother.
And.
I don't think anyone will notice us.
I won't tell Ichiro.
Just once.
Please.
Just once?
Just once.
Anyway.
Let's do it.
Please.
I won't tell anyone.
Are you sure?
No?
I'm sorry.
You're sweating a lot.
Yes.
Well.
I've been sweating a lot.
But.
I see.
You can look at me a lot.
Yes.
You don't have to be shy.
Okay?
It's been a long time since I saw you.
It's been a long time.
Ichiro.
Well.
It's been a month.
A month.
I see.
Ouch.
You're twitching.
I'm not used to being touched by a woman.
I hate it.
Can't I do this?
No.
You may like it.
Really?
Yes.
You'll feel better.
Can you pull it out?
Yes.
Ouch.
Wow.
It's hot.
This is it.
Can I look at you?
Yes.
Ouch.
Wow.
Can I lick this?
Yes.
Okay.
You're twitching.
Wow.
Can you do this?
Yes.
Can you do this to me?
I'll do my best to make you feel better.
Hey.
Can I do this?
Yes.
Hurry up.
Wow.
It feels good.
Really?
Yes.
I'm glad.
It's hot.
You'll feel better.
Ouch.
Wow.
It's hard.
You like boobs, don't you?
Yes.
Look at this.
I'll use it a lot.
Okay.
Wow.
Do you like it?
Yes.
It's important.
Really?
Are you excited?
Yes.
Wow.
It's really hard.
I'll use it a lot.
Use it as much as you like.
Excuse me.
Wow.
It's hard.
You have a pimple on your back.
I'm excited.
That's good.
I'm glad.
Wow.
I'm glad that you like it.
Can I hold this?
Yes.
Touch it.
Wow.
You don't have a pimple on your back, do you?
Don't worry.
You don't have a pimple on your back at this time.
So don't worry about it.
Okay.
Let's have fun.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Wow.
I'll play with you.
What?
I've never done this before.
Really?
This is the first time I've ever done this.
Then I'll do it a lot.
Hold me.
Okay.
How do you feel?
I don't feel good.
Don't do that.
Please.
Hold me.
Okay.
Just hold me.
I'll hold you.
Okay.
I feel good.
I'm glad.
Do you like this?
Yes.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Really?
Wow.
I'm getting sleepy.
Hold me.
I feel good.
Do you like this?
Yes.
I feel good.
Hold me.
I'm getting sleepy.
Don't do that.
Okay.
Can you touch me?
Come here.
Touch me.
You don't need this, do you?
No.
Okay.
Can you touch me?
You don't need this, do you?
I want to touch you.
I'm sorry, but I can't do this anymore.
I told you, didn't I?
What did you say?
I'm sorry, but I can't do this anymore.
I'm going home now.
Don't go home.
Hikari?
I'm sorry.
Akira has been busy lately.
What's wrong?
As I said earlier, he's always working.
He doesn't take care of me.
I want to have a baby, but I can't.
I see.
Please wait a little longer.
I don't know when I'll have a baby.
I'm getting old.
I don't think so.
If you're going to have a baby, you should be young.
Maybe.
I don't have time.
You don't have time?
Shun.
Yes?
Can you have sex with me?
What?
I'm sorry.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
Hikari.
Yes?
It's a secret.
Of course.
It's embarrassing.
Are you okay?
I'm 30 years old.
It's been 4 years since I got married.
I can't do it.
It's hard if you're over 30.
I'll tell you.
I'm nervous.
It's hard if you're over 30.
It's amazing.
It's hard to say.
I told you earlier.
I'm sorry.
I want you to keep it a secret.
Is that so?
I feel good.
Can I take a break?
I want to drink water.
Why do you take a break?
Please let me take a break.
Please.
You can do it.
I feel good.
This is the end.
Please let me take a break.
I feel good.