I'm looking forward to it.
Welcome.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you very much.
It's beautiful.
Is there anyone else?
I'm looking forward to it.
I wanted to show you a tea bag before taking a bath.
I'm looking forward to it, so I'll do some warm-up exercises.
How many men are here today?
I'm looking forward to it.
I can't wait to take a bath.
I'm going to show off my body.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to take a bath.
There is nothing important.
You can just pay for it.
I'll talk to him over there, so please come in.
Here's the 3 million yen you owe me.
I'd like you to give it back to me.
I'd like you to pay me back in installments.
In installments?
Yes, in installments.
No, please don't.
I don't think it's a bad thing.
Did you pay for the admission fee?
What?
If you were nice to me, I'd go out with you.
Did you pay for the admission fee?
First of all, you have to pay me back.
No, I can't help you if you don't pay me back.
I'm not going to pay you back.
No, please pay me back in installments.
Who are you?
I'm a customer.
What?
Of course.
Can you make it bigger?
It feels good.
What are you doing?
It feels so good.
You're so energetic.
Slowly.
It hurts.
Tissue.
I'm sorry.
It's strange.
Are you satisfied?
Thank you.
What's going on?
That customer paid for the admission fee.
Pay for the admission fee?
Again?
Excuse me.
Can I have the lower mouth?
The lower mouth?
Yes, I understand.
Lower mouth?
Is this okay?
Yes.
Excuse me.
It feels good.
I'm glad.
You're so energetic.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Can I have the lower mouth?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You're doing a great job.
It hurts.
Please help me.
I'll do it again.
Again?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I see.
Please use it a lot.
It hurts.
Excuse me.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
Please do it more.
It hurts.
I see.
It feels good.
Please use it a lot.
It hurts.
Did you use it a lot?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm not dirty.
I'll wipe it off.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It hurts.
It says you're done.
You're done.
Excuse me.
Hello.
I see.
It's dangerous.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
I think there's a staff in the front.
Please explain to them.
Let's go.
It's hot, isn't it?
Can I touch you?
Of course.
Go ahead.
Please touch me a lot.
Okay.
Can I put my finger in your mouth?
Of course.
I did it.
It's amazing.
If you pay the fee, you can do it for 24 hours.
Really?
Of course.
You can do whatever you want.
Can I do it again?
Of course.
It's hot.
I see.
I love you.
Please do it a lot.
It's hot.
Can I put my tongue in your mouth?
Of course.
You can do whatever you want.
Excuse me.
It's hot.
Please do it a lot.
You can do whatever you want.
It's amazing.
Your tongue is coming in.
I see.
You are weak.
It's hot.
Can I put my finger in your mouth?
Yes, please.
It's hot.
Do you like the upper lip?
Yes.
That's good.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
Do you want me to put them side by side?
Excuse me.
Thank you for using it today.
Please enjoy it a lot.
Thank you.
Do you want me to put them side by side?
Excuse me.
Thank you.
ちゃんとここにしよ
つづいて
ん
反応
ね
あった
Yup
Ahaha...
You're awake.
Ah, um...
Here you go.
I wanted to put it in my mouth...
You can put it in your mouth for 24 hours, so you can use it whenever you want.
Yes, I'll put it in my mouth again.
Damn, why did I put it in my mouth?
Thank you.
Ah, excuse me.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Mori, the director.
I'm Mikuru Tezuka, the gravure idol.
Nice to meet you.
I'm sorry I'm late because my car was packed.
No problem.
Can you show me around?
Yes, I'll show you around.
Yes, please.
Please be careful of your feet.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Thank you.
The atmosphere here is nice.
Yes, it is.
I'll go in here.
Okay.
Tezuka-chan.
Yes?
After the shoot is over,
You're going to shoot a movie, right?
Yes, I am.
You don't have a schedule tomorrow, right?
No, I don't.
I heard from the manager that you can stay overnight.
Yes.
Do you want to have a party in your room?
All of us?
What?
Yes, all of us.
I see.
Or you can have a private party.
I want to have a party at the next onsen.
I see.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Take your time.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
The atmosphere is great.
Thank you.
Tezuka-chan's onsen
I'd like you to tell us about your onsen.
Okay.
You don't have to look at the camera.
But, please look at the camera and smile.
Like this.
Yes.
Please.
If you have any information about the onsen,
you can come in.
Thank you.
You two look great in the video.
You look beautiful in the video.
Thank you.
You are beautiful in the video.
No, no, no.
Thank you.
Okay, let's get started.
If you don't want to test the camera, let's get started.
Okay.
Let's get started.
5 seconds before the start.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
I'm here at Girepo Onsen.
This onsen was established in 1948.
This is the hall.
This onsen is good for your skin.
It's good for your skin.
Can I drink this?
Yes, you can.
I see.
It's good for your skin.
Let me drink it.
It tastes like normal hot water.
It's good for your skin.
This onsen is open 24 hours.
You can use the onsen as much as you want.
You can use the onsen as much as you want in the facility as well.
You can use the facility as much as you want for 24 hours.
It's wonderful.
I think it's very attractive.
It's good for your skin.
Is my face in my video?
Don't kill my face.
I'm glad that you say so.
Did you
crack up?
Yes I did.
Can I touch you here?
Please finish here.
Woah, that's great!
So there's more?
Oh, moreれたね
There are a lot.
Thank you.
You said it's cute!
Oh, that's great.
Oh, I see.
Oh, what is it?
It's amazing.
It feels so good.
I'm glad I came here.
It's my first time here.
Oh, it's my first time, too.
It's been a while since I've been here.
Yeah, it's been a while since I've been here.
Can I touch it, too?
If you don't mind, I'll go this way.
Oh, thank you.
I'm glad I came here.
Can I wash my body?
Oh, thank you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Let's wash our bodies.
Oh, please.
I'm sorry.
You have a lot of boobs.
Oh, thank you.
Please wash them well.
Can I wash this part, too?
Oh, it's hard.
No.
Washing is difficult.
Shall I wash my hands?
I see.
I think it's good to wash it thoroughly.
If you like.
Then, I'll wash your back.
Can I?
Yes, you can.
It's good to wash your back.
I want to wash my back, too.
Please.
It's hot.
Is it okay?
Yes, it's good.
It's hot, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Then, I'll wash your back.
Okay.
Please.
I have this.
Can I wash my back?
Yes, you can.
Are you washing your back?
Yes, I am.
Can I wash your back more?
Yes, you can.
Is it okay?
Do you want to use this?
I'll do it for you.
It's hot.
It's good to wash your back.
Really?
Yes.
It's hot.
Then, I'll wash my back, too.
Okay.
It's hot.
I see.
Is it okay?
Yes, it is.
You are good at washing your back.
You are used to washing your back.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Can I wash this side?
Yes, you can.
It's better to wash this side.
I see.
I'm not good at washing my back.
It's hot.
I think it's better to wash your back with a towel.
I see.
It's good, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
How is it?
It's good.
I think it's good, too.
Really?
Yes.
I'll wash this side, too.
Okay.
Can I wash this side, too?
Yes, you can.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
I think it's better to wash your back with a towel.
Yes, it is.
I'm not good at washing my back.
Can I wash this side, too?
Yes, you can.
I think it's better to wash this side, too.
Can I wash this side, too?
Maybe?
It's hot.
OK.
That was OK.
Well,
you know,
there are some delicious fish,
such as river fish.
So,
could you tell me
what kind of fish
there are
for dinner?
What should I do?
Oh, wait a minute.
Ms. Otei.
There is a strange voice.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
I'm not doing my job.
I'm sorry.
I'm waiting for the camera.
Could you be quiet?
OK.
I'm sorry.
I can't turn the camera.
OK.
I'm sorry.
Ooh.
I was stuck.
Peek-a-boo.
I'm sorry.
Ah.
Oh.
Ha ha ha.
Ugh.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Ahhh, also, I regret I couldn't go a little more
I'm sorry I couldn't behave, so please forgive me
Ahhhh, again
Ah!!!
Ah ~~~
Ahhh
The doctor was injured in parts of my body.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh ~~
Fryer
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, ah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Can I have a drink?
Oh, it's okay.
It's okay.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's in.
It's a hot spring, so it's natural that it's in.
No, it's not natural.
No, so it's natural that there are guests in the hot spring, right?
Stop it.
It's hot.
It's a really annoying guest.
Come on, come on.
Go, go.
Stop it, stop it.
Stop it?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
It's a little late.
It's hot.
Well, I'd like to ask you to come to Ieho Hot Spring.
Okay.
Let's take a picture together.
Don't turn it around.
No, no, no.
What?
Don't turn it around.
It's hot.
Okay, let's take a picture together.
Okay.
Let's take a picture together.
After that,
Let's leave it for a second or two.
And then,
We'll say,
Ieho Hot Spring, come on, everyone.
And then,
We'll leave it for a second or two.
Let's do that.
Yes.
Good.
Then,
Three, two, one.
Everyone, please come to Ilefontein.
There is a penis.
What? What did you say?
What are you doing?
What is this?
What's wrong with you?
Are you tired?
I'm sorry.
I said something strange.
What should I do?
I'll tell you about the three of you.
Are you all right?
I'll cut it out.
I'll edit it.
It's a public bath.
If a male guest comes in, let's have an interview.
Do you come often?
Are you a local?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
May I have an interview?
Do you come to this hot spring often?
Yes.
Are you a local?
I'm from Hiroshima.
Is this hot spring famous?
Yes.
This is a very good hot spring.
This is a very good place.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good in many ways.
In many ways?
For example, this?
That's right.
Did you hear that?
I heard a lot.
What did you hear?
If you come in, you'll feel it.
Can I feel it now?
You can feel it right away.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
You.
Are you going to be an AD all the time?
Yes.
You're aiming for a director, aren't you?
What did you say?
Can I take a look at you?
You're so cute.
Do you always feel like this?
Yes, I do.
I thought I could hear a lot of things.
I think you're feeling good.
I think you're in a good mood.
That's right.
I see.
There are a lot of people from all over Japan.
I think you're in a good mood.
You're not going to be an AD all the time, are you?
Yes.
You're aiming for a director, aren't you?
What did you say?
I think you're in a good mood.
Thank you.
When I was an AD, I was working under you.
Yes.
I'm sorry about that.
I think you're making excuses.
Yes.
I'm sorry about that.
I think you're in a good mood.
I can't believe you said that.
I'm sorry about that.
Uwaa!
Wow!
What is this?
This is good, isn't it?
It's good, isn't it?
It's really good!
What is this?
What do you mean?
No, I mean...
I told you, didn't I?
No, but...
This is amazing.
It's a big scoop!
Oh, a big scoop.
It's really hard.
It's beautiful.
It looks disgusting in the outdoor bath.
Don't take it off.
It hurts!
Can I take it off?
Take it off.
Do it properly.
Properly?
It looks beautiful.
I won't take this off either.
I'll...
What are you doing?
Mori-san, wait a minute.
You're already looking that way.
I'll...
You came to the onsen, didn't you?
I came to the onsen, but...
I'll...
No, I won't!
You won't!?
Mori, I won't take it off.
Please, let me take it off!
It's mine...
It's mine.
You don't mean...
I'll take it off then.
Thank you.
It's not mine.
You won't take it off?
It's not.
Theres, there
Ihave been here during my shift
During his shift, one of you will fall
Who is it
Go on
Ouch...
Oh, my!
Please accept my apology.
I'm sorry...
My frustration...
What's this?
I'm sorry.
A girl is always evil!
What's she trying to do?
What's this?
What's wrong with that girl?
I'm sorry.
Ma'am.
What does this mean?
I don't know.
Can you explain?
Camera.
This is a TV.
Do you want me to explain?
All of this...
Like all of my guests...
In this room, these guests...
Have been put in bed for 24 hours.
Oh, my back!
This is out on the table!
I was put up?
This is a sign made of wood, but isn't it called all-you-can-put-it-in?
No, it's not.
Of course, it's all-you-can-put-it-in, but it's all-you-can-put-it-in, isn't it?
The hot springs are also all-you-can-put-it-in.
There are also all-you-can-put-it-in guests and staff in this building.
So please enjoy it.
It's really amazing here.
People like me, people who have tattoos like this guy, everyone is all-you-can-put-it-in.
This is the only dormitory.
The girls in the hot springs are also all-you-can-put-it-in.
It's the best, really.
Wait a minute.
You can take it off.
I can't take it off.
It's amazing.
Let's go.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Wait a minute.
Let me help you.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
I was going to help you.
This is a good hot spring.
You're crying.
Can I put you in?
Of course.
You're in deep water.
It's good.
It feels good.
It's fine.
Oh, no.
She's in a hole.
Thank you very much.
Wow, there's a lot in there.
How many are you going to take out?
Please let me out a lot, too.
Thank you very much.
Turn it around.
Wow, there's a lot.
Thank you very much.
It's a lot.
Wow, there's a lot.
Oh, here's one.
Thank you very much.
Wow, there's a lot.
Can she go a little faster?
She's coming.
Oh, it's hot.
I'll do it again.
Anyway, this is a hot spring that can be used by both women and men.
Please come to this hot spring.
Oh, it's hot.
Cut!
3, 2, 1
Good morning.
Let's go.
She's sleeping.
I'll check if she's really sleeping.
She's really sleeping.
Oh, it's hot.
Wait, wait, wait.
Girls don't go to hot springs like this all of a sudden.
Come here and film this.
I'll show you a video.
Oh, it's hot.
I wonder if she's wearing underwear.
Let's check it out.
What kind of clothes is she wearing?
Is she sleeping?
Oh, she's got legs.
Beautiful legs.
What does this mean?
It's a yukata.
Her legs are in the shape of 4.
Is it a message?
It might be a message.
Okay.
It's a yukata.
I couldn't find her underwear.
I wonder if she's wearing it.
Excuse me.
She's wearing it.
Did you check it out by yourself?
It's amazing.
She's wearing it.
She's got a hair.
I wonder if it's a message.
Wait a minute.
She's got a hair.
Maybe she's never been to this hot spring.
She's never been here.
What does that mean?
Maybe she's never been here.
It's a beautiful voice.
She's got a nice face.
She has a nice voice.
Is she really a virgin?
Please touch her.
She's grabbed my hand.
She's so soft.
Good morning.
She's not angry.
I wonder if she's moving.
Good morning.
She's nodding.
She's not angry, is she?
She's not angry.
She's just a rude virgin.
She's a bit grumpy.
Maybe she'd like plenty of advice.
She's in a bad mood.
Is that okay?
Isn't that so good?
Maybe she's pure?
Oh, I see.
How far have you done it?
Actually, this one is also the same.
Double Bakidon?
It's a hard one.
Oh, it's shaking.
I don't think he would do it if I didn't teach him how to do it.
Oh, I see.
It's cute just by looking at it.
This is how you do it.
Do you like the boobs of the two of you?
Do you like it?
Yes, I love it.
Are you okay?
How do you like the boobs?
I want to touch them forever.
You can't just hold it like this.
You have to do it here, too.
Do you want to lick it?
Yes, I want to lick it.
Come here.
Oh, you're so cute.
Do you like it?
Is it your first time licking the boobs?
He's licking it a lot.
I don't think he's licking my boobs.
Do you live here alone?
No, I don't.
Because this is a famous place.
Is that so?
I enjoyed taking a bath during the day, but I didn't think I'd be able to enjoy it all at once.
What is this?
I've touched a lot of boobs.
I didn't know a virgin could be so energetic.
Aren't you both in a tight spot?
Take it off.
I'll take it off for you.
I wonder which of you will take it off first.
Oh, you're so cold.
Oh, you've already taken off your underwear.
You're both so nice.
It's a waste of boobs.
Come closer.
Come here.
Wow.
Your mouths are open wide.
It's my first time touching a woman.
Is it your first time?
What do you want to do? Tell me.
I want to flutter.
Flutter?
Then I'll take it all at once.
Until the end.
Don't let it out.
I'm out of breath.
Already?
Then I'll go first.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Don't pull my waist like that.
Or I'll do it like this.
Ah.
Oh.
Hey, AD, what are you doing?
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Hey.
It's okay, it's okay.
I can't help it.
I was surprised.
It's a waste to wipe it off.
Just your hand.
Why?
Since you're here, why don't you do a six-nine?
Six-nine.
Have you ever seen it?
69.
That's right.
Like this.
Asou-chan, look, look.
Let me take off my panties.
Panties.
Excuse me.
Ah.
Can you see it?
I can see it.
Look, look, look.
Ah.
Wow.
How is it?
Ah.
It's really tight.
Do whatever you like.
Ah.
Look.
Hey.
I told you I can see it.
Ah.
Ah, this side, too.
Ah, what a waste.
Both of you are so cute.
What were you thinking?
You're so cute when you're like this.
Are you satisfied now?
No, not yet.
Ah, not yet?
But it's not good to do this.
What should we do?
Let's do what we did just now.
We have to take care of each other.
Let's pull it together.
Let's do it together.
One, two.
Ah.
You're so cute.
Eh?
Is that so?
Ah.
Ah, another kiss.
You're amazing.
This side, this side, no matter how you look at it, you're not a virgin.
I'm just so-so.
Ah, I see.
That's why he squeezes his mouth.
Ah, this ear is still amazing.
This ear is still amazing.
Ah, well, the virgin is still alive.
I'm so hungry...
Then watch, I'm going to take this rice out.
Do you want to get in?
Lie down.
You don't know how to get in, do you? I'll do it.
Look at me.
I'll do it.
It's still hard.
I'll dry it right away.
What do you think?
Hey, you don't know how to get in, do you?
It feels good.
Wait a minute.
It's still hard.
I've been doing it for a long time, so it's hard.
What do you think?
Do you like it?
She seems to like it.
What do you think?
You're so cute.
Is it warm inside?
Do your best.
I can't do it yet.
It feels good.
I can't do it anymore.
You did it again, didn't you?
My heart was beating so fast.
It feels good.
You did it again, didn't you?
I graduated.
I said I couldn't do it yet, but I can't help it.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You saw it, didn't you?
This is in the way.
Please call me Daisuke.
What?
My name is Daisuke.
Daisuke?
Which do you prefer, Daisuke or Dai-chan?
I like Dai-chan.
Dai-chan?
You're so cute.
Look at Haru-chan.
I'm going.
Dai-chan is hard, isn't she?
Cute, isn't she?
I can't do it anymore.
It's not over yet, is it?
It feels good.
Can't you do it a little more?
You can do it, too.
Can I do it, too?
Haru-chan, look at this.
I think I can rely on you a little.
I'm sleepy.
You're amazing.
That's what it was like.
That's how cold it was.
Give me your hand.
Harder.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm going.
It feels good.
Yes.
Tap my butt.
Your butt?
Like this?
It feels good.
Lower your head.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels good.
It's as intense as before.
It's intense, isn't it?
It feels good.
I can't do it anymore.
Wait a minute.
Something warm is dripping.
It feels good.
Open your legs.
I can't do it anymore.
You're amazing.
Let's change the camera.
I can't do it anymore.
Can you do it?
Try something else.
Something else?
Try it.
It's here.
You're amazing.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels good, doesn't it?
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Try moving it.
Forward and backward.
Like this?
That's good.
It feels good.
I can't do it anymore.
You're amazing.
Let's do it again.
I can't do it anymore.
You're amazing.
You're amazing, aren't you?
Put your hands behind your back.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm going to cry.
It feels good.
I can't do it anymore.
You're amazing.
It hurts.
I can't do it anymore.
You're amazing.
I'm going to give you a kiss.
Wait a minute.
Not yet?
I can't do it anymore.
Did you give it all out?
It was hard work.
Thank you very much.
It was great.
It's like the morning now.
We might make you come again at the cafeteria.
I'll be back again.
Thank you very much.
See you later.
Thank you.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I feel good, too.
Oh, no.
Oh, it feels good.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Mike.
Let me help you.
Oh, no.
Oh, it feels good there.
Here?
Yes.
It's very crunchy.
Here?
Does it feel good here?
It feels good.
Look this way.
Oh, no.
Mike.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Let me help you.
Here?
Yes.
Oh, no.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I feel good, too.
Let me help you.
Can I help you?
Of course.
Oh, no.
Let me help you.
Can I help you?
Mike.
Oh, no.
I'm so full.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so full.
Oh, no.
Oh, it feels good.
It's hot.
You're clean now.
Thank you.
It's amazing.
It felt good.
You, too.
Then, I'll take your shoes.
I'll take your shoes.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm so full.
Really?
You're so full.
It feels so good.
I'm glad.
It felt good.
Thank you.
If you're satisfied.
I'd like to do it later.
Of course.
May I?
Yes.
I'm going to be addicted.
You can do it for 24 hours.
Really?
Yes.
I want to do it again soon.
Yes, please.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Good morning.
Where's your mom?
She went to pick up the sheets.
Is it okay if I don't pick up the sheets?
It's okay.
Really?
You look young.
Do I?
How long have you been doing this?
I've been doing this for two years.
Two years?
You look young.
Thank you.
You're so beautiful.
Do you enjoy this job?
Yes, I do.
That's good.
I'm so grateful to you.
I've never seen such a cute girl.
Is it good?
What cup is this?
It's a G cup.
A G cup?
Yes.
Is it okay if I brush my teeth?
You have white teeth.
Do I?
You have a lot of teeth.
What kind of person is she?
She's my ex-girlfriend.
You're cute.
Thank you.
Where are you from?
I'm from Yamanashi.
You're from Yamanashi.
Yes, I am.
I want to do something for my hometown.
You're young, but you're great.
Thank you.
You don't have a boyfriend, do you?
I had a boyfriend before I started working.
It's not good to work in a place like this.
I'm sure you're going to hate it.
That's right.
I don't hate it.
Is that so?
I can't stand such a cute girl being my girlfriend.
Thank you for your kind words.
It's a G cup.
This is great.
I'll show you this.
Your teeth are beautiful.
Thank you.
Can I lick your teeth while I'm brushing my teeth?
Does it feel good?
Thank you.
It's a refrigerator hot spring.
Yes, it's a 24-hour refrigerator hot spring.
Is anyone in the hot spring now?
That's right.
It's the best.
You're a genius.
That's right.
Do you like slippers?
I love it.
Do you usually wear sexy underwear when you work here?
That's right.
It's warm.
It's pierced.
I think I'll go home.
I can hear you.
I think so, too.
It feels good.
I think everyone who stays here feels good.
That's right.
Does it feel good here?
Yes, it feels good.
That's good.
You'll feel better when you sleep.
It hurts.
Would you let me lick your teeth?
I'm happy.
It's the best.
You can put anything in your mouth.
That's right.
When I went to the hot spring, there were other female guests, so I let them in.
I see.
You were happy.
I'm satisfied with everyone.
You're amazing.
You're popular with female guests, aren't you?
What do you think?
I'm sure you're popular.
Would you like to put it in your mouth?
Yes, please.
Would you like me to put it in your mouth?
It's the best.
It feels good.
I'm happy.
That's good.
I can't.
Let me hear it.
It's the best.
You have to wear this when you're at work.
But...
It's okay, isn't it?
Yes.
That's good.
I'm glad I was able to get it.
Is that so?
I'm glad.
It's the first time I've had this size.
That's right.
The main purpose was to go to this hot spring.
But I wanted to buy it.
Where is it?
Is there a good place?
It's close.
Is there a waterfall?
Waterfall?
The weather is good now.
There's a mountain here, too.
Yes, there is.
Inoue!
Come here.
Let's decide where to go today.
There's Nakai over there.
Come here.
What are you doing?
Did you see a woman?
Yes, I did.
I didn't see her at all.
I let a woman who was walking in here.
That's good.
You saw a sightseeing dash, didn't you?
Bring that.
I'm going to throw up.
I let her in here, too.
That's good.
What are you doing?
You came to the inn.
Let me let you in here.
Is that okay?
Yes.
You don't have to go there.
This is a hotel.
Let me let you in here.
Let's decide where to go today.
Can I put a magazine here?
Yes.
I'll put a magazine in my mouth.
I heard that the waterfall is famous here.
Was it Kouyou?
Kouyou.
This is it.
Where was the waterfall we saw earlier?
Over there.
I don't know where it is.
It's deeper.
Is it deeper?
It's not deep.
Is it deep in the mountains?
I don't know.
Is there anything delicious?
What is delicious?
Fish.
Fish?
It looks delicious.
It's hot.
It's a fish.
I wonder what it is.
I heard that there is a famous castle here.
My ears hurt.
Can I let you in here?
Please let me in.
What?
What's wrong?
You seemed to be in a good mood.
I want to go in there.
You should let her in.
That's right.
You paid for her admission.
I wonder if I can really let her in.
What will you let her in?
I can't believe that I can go in there with such a beautiful lady.
You want to let her in, don't you?
I want to let her in.
I wonder if it's easy to let her in.
Do you want to let her sleep?
Thank you very much.
Can I let her sleep?
Of course.
Can I really let her sleep?
Thank you very much.
I'm going to put this in her mouth.
I put this in her mouth.
You made her feel good.
You can do that.
That's comfortable.
Is that true?
It's comfortable.
Let's go, let's go.
You made me go.
I told you to take a walk with Okami-san.
No, Okami-san and I...
We had an accident.
What? You didn't go out?
We couldn't go out.
What's going on?
We are staying in this hot spring.
It's time for you to change your personality.
I know, but I'm here.
I'm here, so I have to have fun.
Please have fun.
It's written here that it's good for constipation.
Is that so?
Yes.
You can lie down.
I feel sick.
I can't do it anymore.
You can do it.
I feel sick.
I can't do it.
The food was good.
It was very expensive and delicious.
Was it?
It was delicious.
I'm glad. Thank you very much.
You should say thank you to Itamai-san.
Yes, I will.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I can't do it either.
Please do it.
Can I really do it?
Of course.
I can't do it.
Please do it.
You're sweating a lot.
You can do it.
It's very warm.
I'm glad.
Of course.
Excuse me.
I'll get your yukata dirty.
It's okay.
I'll bring you a new one.
Did you come here to get a sheet?
Yes, I did.
I'll bring you a new one.
I'll take this.
Thank you very much.
Can I push it?
Yes, please.
Excuse me.
I'll bring you a new one.
Is it okay?
You're good at this.
I think so.
Let's go to the next room.
Okay.
I can't do it.
The next day.
You're cute.
You should go to the next room.
I think so.
You should attack.
I may not see you for the rest of my life.
But...
It's big.
What is it?
It looks soft.
You should go to the next room.
There is a trash there.
Really?
You should tell them.
What should I tell them?
You can tell them anything.
It's your chance.
Tell them your name.
Tell them your age.
Tell them where you're from.
Are you Matsumoto?
Yes.
How old are you?
I'm 20 years old.
You're 20 years old.
What do you usually do?
What do I usually do?
I'm a university student.
Where do you live?
I live in Nagasaki.
We live in Nagasaki.
How long will you stay here?
I don't know.
How many days are you going to stay?
I think I'll stay for a week.
Do you want to go on a date?
Yes, I want to go on a date.
Can I go on a date?
It's not a date.
I want to go on a date.
I want to go on a date with a girl.
What kind of girl do you like?
I like a girl who is like a cat.
Oh, that's good.
Do you live in Nagasaki?
Yes, I do.
If you don't mind,
would you like to go out for a meal?
Would you like to go out for a meal?
I'm sorry.
I have a boyfriend.
I have to go out for a meal.
I'm sorry.
There's a trash can here.
Really?
How do you do?
Can I help you?
Shake it all off.
Ouch!
Take it all out.
How is it?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Ouch!
Take it all out.
Shake it all off.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels great.
I like it.
I'm sorry, but I can't help it.
You need more strength.
I can't, I can't.
I can't.
You can do it, you can do it.
Thank goodness.
Can I ask you to do this?
I'll do it.
We can do as much as we want.
You have a boyfriend, don't you?
How long have you been dating him?
I've been dating him for half a year.
Does your boyfriend know about this part-time job?
No, it's a secret.
You're working part-time for your boyfriend?
That's right.
If your boyfriend finds out about this...
I'm sorry.
I'll do it, too.
Can you buy me another one?
You want to do more, don't you?
Come in.
Is it okay for you to do this much?
But it's your job, so it can't be helped.
You chose this part-time job, didn't you?
You want to do more, don't you?
It hurts.
It feels good.
Be careful.
Are you okay?
Let's send this picture to your boyfriend.
Don't do that.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I'll do it, too.
You've been doing this all day.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it, too.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
Yamada-kun.
I'm sorry.
There's a lot of blood.
Thank you very much.
Can I talk to you?
Mr. Nagasaki, please.
It's in.
Thank you very much.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's in.
Let's do it here.
Here?
It's in.
Can I take it off?
I can't stand it.
I'm losing it.
It's in.
Can I do it here?
Can I kiss you?
Come on.
Please tell us about us.
Let's introduce ourselves.
Mr. Enose.
Please open your mouth.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
No, no.
It's in.
I'm Yamada.
It feels good.
No, no.
It's in.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
No, no.
How about me?
I'm Taniguchi.
Don't forget about us.
Please kiss me.
Please.
Do you remember?
Do you remember who we are?
Please close your eyes.
It's in.
Don't open your eyes.
How do you feel?
He is...
Mr. Shimizu.
I'm sorry.
Did you make up?
Yes.
You made up.
Please close your eyes again.
Who is it?
Please close your eyes.
I'm sorry.
Am I wrong?
You can look at me now.
I'm sorry.
Please close your eyes.
I can see next time.
You shouldn't look at me.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
Do you know who it is?
Who is it?
Do you know who this is?
This is...
Um...
Taniguchi-san.
Taniguchi?
Wait a minute.
Taniguchi.
Can I see it?
Go ahead.
I made a mistake.
Ah...
This is the last one.
The last one.
You know who this is.
Close your eyes.
Okay.
Come here.
A little more.
Ah...
I don't know.
I don't know who this is.
I want to drink the last one.
Me, too.
Yamada-san.
Ah...
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
You look happy.
So, you can drink anything.
Yes.
Please remember who I am.
I'm Inoue.
I'm Yamada.
I'm Shimizu.
I'm Taniguchi.
Do you remember me?
Yes.
I'm Yamada.
I'm Inoue.
I'm Shimizu.
Ah...
I'm Taniguchi.
I'm Yamada.
Ah...
It's amazing.
She's crying.
I really enjoyed this one night and two days.
It's all thanks to you, Ms. Matsunaga.
I didn't feel fulfilled when I was alive.
I was able to come here and change.
It was the most fulfilling two days.
Really?
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Please come again.
Yes.
I'll be waiting for you.
Thank you for watching.