What do you want to eat today?
Eat or what?
I am studying hard and I like to do what I do.
Do you want to ask the Crow?
I want to eat tofu.
Is it hard?
It is hard.
Did you like the crap?
Listen to the taste.
Today, I want to eat the cabbage.
I feel a little Chinese.
Chinese, I understand
Think about Dad.
It was in the refrigerator, secondary.
Well, I don’t have to go at all.
Because I am going shopping.
really is?
Maybe you will buy more.
Do not buy too much.
Do not go to the supermarket first.
But I haven’t asked for it lately.
Let me come and say something.
by HEBK
Sit for a moment.
Sit down or sit.
My mother has an important story.
No, it is not so important.
Honey, what do you want to eat today?
My father said he wanted to eat Chinese.
What important story?
No, about the food.
Oh, and Chinese
It is Chinese, and not Chinese at all.
Oh no, the spring.
The Spring Wrap?
The freezer.
Maybe a little hot.
with spring.
So you like your dad.
with tofu.
Not enough as much.
If there is a salad.
Do you really need anything else?
I study hard, I like to make it.
But
The food that my mother makes.
Everything is delicious.
Anything is
You are well told.
Thanks to the Rush.
I think you really want to be a bit of a bitch, my mom will cook.
Speak strange words, really.
Happy mother.
I am pleased too.
You really are a good boy.
I am glad you really made me happy.
Is it okay, is it bad?
No, no, but in general, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well.
really is?
Maybe well.
Oh yeah
Your voice is reversed.
Oh is?
You have been nervous so far.
Oh no, I’m a little nervous.
I think that such a beautiful woman will suddenly become a mother.
Now, he is a beautiful person.
One and a half, now.
I am so happy, Mr. Ken, if you can do that, I will be able to cook today.
If you buy it, you will have a delicious meal.
Thanks to Mr. Hiro.
You can eat one thing.
I go back to my room and study.
Let us go.
What happened? is it bad?
So get used to it, really.
I hope you stay nervous.
No, no longer you
Enjoy the Chinese meal.
Yes, you listen to it.
What happened.
My neighbor has a baby.
I wish to congratulate.
Looks like I could.
Did you wear a party shirt?
But it should be after it comes in.
Just a little greeting, you are me.
Please note, the opposite.
So, it is time for me.
Yes, I want to, because I am busy now.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah.
You think it will be okay, right?
Yes to.
So think how it goes.
I’m going to the supermarket, but I’m going to the supermarket first.
Oh is?
So let me talk a little.
But still not,
Go and go.
Oh well.
Yes, I am going to.
Yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
Oh well, the rooster.
Oh that.
I heard from your father,
Have you had a graduation in recent years?
Oh no, no, it was coincidence.
If you are happy with your mother, I will talk to you.
No, you say I won’t cry.
What happened? tell me anything.
But I tell my mother, yes, it’s not possible.
But maybe I can help somehow too.
cooperation
Tell me to.
that
Yes
I am
It is the booth.
Oh is?
No because
With that virginity.
I don’t want to want an ATC.
So that
Let us calm.
If you care, you won’t be able to study.
Father
It would be hard to come.
Let us calm a little.
Let us calm.
OK is OK.
Yes is it.
Yes is
But see it.
If you were still the age of Mr. Hiro, there would be a lot of kids who have no experience at all.
No, not that way.
Everyone in the class has experienced something.
I feel like I am left alone.
I really don’t really care about studying anymore.
You will care.
Okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
So yes
No, because now
I am already concerned, I am really concerned.
Oh well, I am not.
Yes is
I’ll buy a Dakota at the store.
Be careful, come on.
Do not hold the main card.
Oh yes, be careful.
Go in and go.
Yes
Then my dad went too.
Listen to me once again.
Yes
I want to do.
Oh yeah
Oh, I want to do.
I want to do.
Yes, yes yes yes yes
Yes
I want to do, I want to do.
Or even so.
For the first time that it is.
You think it matters so much, Mom.
With someone you like.
After you first found it.
Because it is its turn.
My mother is
I want to do it with your mother.
No, I am
by Tjong
But, there is no blood.
Only my mother.
No, just do that a moment sooner.
Let me do it.
I want to try it anymore.
and then.
Please please please.
My mother is only 1 cm.
One centimetre!? to
1 cm, only 1 cm.
Oh yeah?
1 cm to.
Really just one centimetre.
Not all, not all must be.
Not all of it,
One centimetre?
So will the crap calm down?
If you put in one centimetre,
It seems like they’ve graduated, right?
Yes, yes, yes...
You put it in, right?
Oh yes, a little...
Yes, is it so?
Well, then, it is a centimeter.
Oh yeah!? to
Is your mother large?
Yes yes yes
Oh well...
No...
Oh, and then one centimetre.
If I put it in 1 cm, is it okay?
Okay okay okay, really okay.
Please please!
You should not go to your dad either.
Soon until my dad comes home.
Yes, only one centimetre.
Okay to?
So you can concentrate on studying.
If you don’t want to be with your friends, help your mother.
Yes, yes, because that is not.
I know, I know, only a centimeter.
Before you go in, get a kiss, and a lot of things.
Oh yeah?
Because there is such.
That too
Is it so?
Yes is it?
Yes to?
Otherwise, I will not be home.
by
Only one centimetre to get in.
Only 1 cm to enter.
I promise it.
I understand
Smooth but so.
If your trouble is solved.
here here?
Let me kiss.
I don’t run away, so it’s all right, so let’s kiss slowly.
Oh sorry to.
Have you had stomach bleeding?
really is?
of mother.
Sorry to
Just a little.
A little embarrassed, I am.
I’m ashamed to see you for a while.
Sorry, I am not young.
No so is.
Mom is so beautiful.
pleased
Then rest slowly.
meet for a long time, so I will be out.
The breasts are soft.
for other
Directly
More directly
Just a little.
I hate it.
Do not hide.
Just good.
Just a little.
Yes
I became a little sensitive.
Just a little.
Chicken is very hard.
No to no.
An interesting voice.
Okay now.
Oh is?
But still not
What is?
Will you see below?
Because it
You will be positioned.
Yes is
One centimeter to get in.
But
here here
I have never seen.
Yes, because I have never seen it.
I am a bit ashamed, but so.
If you can study hard, try hard.
Yes yes yes
Okay, then I understood.
Just see it.
because I predict.
What to do.
How, how, what to do
Okay, right now.
Is it said?
by
So that feeling.
Yes
Okay to.
by
The animal
Like a beast.
Yes
The animal
mother
Show me well.
Yes
No, I cannot
It is hard, I will see you for a long time.
meet for a long time.
Yes is.
Sorry, but it may not be the same as a young man.
Because I saw it for the first time.
I don’t know if you didn’t know.
I was surprised.
Can I try to sit?
Try to sit.
I was surprised, since I have not seen him for a long time.
Oh awesome.
I pull it.
Oh, just touch it.
Oh well
by
Oh is
It seems to have changed.
Oh, is awesome
No to
Try putting this in.
OK is.
by
thanks
It was warm.
Hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahah
It will be hot.
Heh he
age is
Can I keep looking?
Oh yeah
That is, I am ashamed.
Because I do these things.
Yes but
by Bubon
A little...
I am feeling a lover...
A little it...
No or...
No more...
Can I say anything? can I say anything?
No to
Grandma is
I want to lick them next time.
Do you want to lick?
Is it me?
If you don’t like EVA.
Oh Oh Oh Oh
It is getting pulled.
not slide.
Oh Oh Oh Oh
Is Lila okay?
Yes
Feel good
Oh Oh Oh
No to
Oh yeah
Oh is
No to
Oh yeah yeah yeah
I already said.
Glad to be.
I will only get one centimetre from above.
Okay so well.
See also
Oh yeah
Just one centimetre.
Yes
Oh yeah
I do it.
Just one centimetre.
Yes
Go to.
1 cm in.
Okay this?
by
This now
Not identical though.
The fish
Make a fish.
Just a centimeter inside.
Not just a minute, but a centimeter, so I can put it in.
Do not move.
A little more, a little more.
But my mother.
No longer can.
A little more.
Just a little more.
But though
The voice, something
Oh yeah
Oh oh that.
mother
Mom, I can’t stand it.
Feelings... I am...
Their...
Go to...
I said!
I am not able to sweat.
Because it wasn’t forever.
Just a little more.
OK to here.
Mom, I want to go here.
Yes is
OK is OK.
Borrow a little.
I want to go here.
again
It feels good at home.
Only one more time.
Oh well...
It feels good...
Addicted to heart.
And now more...
Ha ha ha...
Really...
Oh, I am crying...
The feeling of crying...
I am crying...
It feels good...
Feel good
It feels good.
greatly
slowly
Who is going home.
Feel good
Oh well...
A great feeling...
Oh well... well...
What to do...
well...
I want to ship something.
Because it is okay.
Come here, come full of.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh, he is very much rattling.
It has been down 500 times and is very hard.
pleased
Mom, you just got out.
Okay okay okay okay.
Not too wide, so I can go out.
Okay okay okay.
Ike is! Ike is!
meet for a long time.
Feel good
His skin hurt.
Do you know?
here here
here
yet another time.
Feels very childish.
Oh feelings.
A lot of crocodiles.
and more
outine
year
Good blindfold
Diagnostically
disappeared.
This Mr.
by Nana
What are you doing.
So much for you.
Oh well fuck.
Oh is
Give the money.
Great to get out.
I want to get this out.
I like to be released.
by  by  by  by  by  by  by  by  by  by  by  by  by  by  by  by  by  by
Painful to pain.
still can.
here
Body is big.
There is power.
It is here.
My mother’s mango.
Yes
Oh yeah
well
Let us do.
It is moving.
Oh yeah
Oh yes
Oh is
Oh, very hard
Oh, oh
Oh yeah
Oh my dear, my dear.
Oh my god, oh my god.
still cannot do.
Still not yet.
Put it all into me.
Oh oh oh!
Feel good
hurtly
Oh oh oh!
Many times
Oh, oh, oh, and put it all in.
I want you to bring me back here.
Can you?
Yes, I can still do much.
still can?
Yes
Get it all out.
Oh, it hurts
Now Grandpa, now Grandpa
Yes, I will go out.
Now, it is enough, put it in your mouth.
Now my grandfather.
Oh, it hurts
Tastefully
A lot of out.
A lot of gone out.
Sorry to
Because it wasn’t forever.
My mother did a lot of things.
It felt good.
I had no sex for a long time, too.
From now on, I will sometimes.
Yes is
Are you accustomed to the coat?
Yes, I am older than you are, but I am still older.
I live with you, yeah.
When the exam is over, we will all go on a trip.
Oh well okay.
Cotta, come here for a while, sorry.
Oh what?
I’m just talking about going on a trip with my mom.
No, but if you go, we both go.
After the exam, you will be happy, and you will be happy with all three.
Don’t worry, we’ll go with you.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah.
It’s a long trip, so don’t worry, you don’t want to go to a neighbor.
Oh yeah then
I would like to go to Hokkaido.
well is
I think something food is delicious.
Where do you want to go like that?
Oh, or me
Yes, but it is good for Kyiv and Hokkaido.
Do not worry.
Both of them taste good.
Yes, yes is
It is still cold in Hokkaido.
Well, for now, the fort case will be fine.
Yes, yes is yes
Are you studying properly?
Well, you are trying hard.
Because passing is the first goal.
Yes, you are of course.
Well, I think it’s about you, so I think it’s okay.
Yes
I need to study immediately.
Okay okay okay.
I will strive.
What happened, he was in a hurry.
It did not motivate me on the trip.
Oh yeah yeah
He will do that girl, he will be fine.
So where should we go?
not is
You will enter.
Oh yeah yeah
Sorry to
During the study.
Oh no no
What happened?
The dinner today.
I thought what is good.
The Dinner?
Yes
Dad, it is late today.
Oh yeah
Do you both eat a little better?
Oh, and so
Dad is late.
Yes
Oh well
Everything my mother makes is delicious.
Because you are already good.
No is
Then
Oh is?
Maybe meat.
I also tried to say that.
I like the hamburger.
So I’ll make a hamburger.
What are you doing now.
Now is
Yes
Oh well
Something here a little.
The change form there.
by
What happened to you, mother?
Oh yeah yeah
Sorry to
Oh is?
Because I have seen nothing.
Oh, oh
Oh sorry sorry.
Oh, this, that, that, that, that, that
Do not care.
Oh yeah, my mother
Oh, I, I, I, I have never been.
Oh, and you want to do it.
Or, mother, can you let me do it?
Oh, no, please, because I don’t think I’m going to be studying anymore, and that, I’m sure, the world will change.
No, but no, no is not.
No, no, I’m just a little bit like that, I want to get in.
I mean, Mom, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean.
Is it really just a centimeter?
Yes, one centimetre
I won’t move a centimeter, I’m sure.
I want to put in.
Well, so, it is only 1 cm.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
It really is just one centimetre.
If you put in one centimetre, it will be too much.
So I will put you in.
Take off a little.
I understand
I will take you off.
Okay is?
Yes
Just one centimetre.
Oh yeah
Do you know?
I think it is about 1 cm inside.
Yes
I know you, mother.
Do not move.
Oh yeah
Have you grown a little?
I think it is because it feels good inside your mother.
Is it enough?
A little more
A little more?
It really will be so much.
Are you really in?
It is in, it is in.
This is the first time, I don’t know much.
Is this good, Mom?
It feels good.
Even one centimetre?
Even one centimetre.
This is 1 cm.
This is?
Yes, in some way.
This is really easy to see.
1 cm in.
See well
here here?
About 1 cm.
Because you cannot move.
When you move, it feels better.
When you get here, you will feel better.
I can’t stand it until here.
It is up to here.
One centimetre is that, right?
Yes, so far
So far
One centimetre is here.
Even a centimeter will feel better.
Oh, and a little
Oh,
Or is Mr.
Isn’t it a centimeter?
Oh yeah
Oh,
This is
Oh yeah
Is this in?
You are inside, right?
Yes
Oh, oh, oh, a little
Oh,
Oh yeah yeah
Mom, what are you doing?
Feel well.
No longer out.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go
Oh yeah
No to
Sorry, I have broken up.
Is it right? back.
My dear daughter, I stole her.
Okay, if you are bothered.
What about me? was I happy?
I am glad.
I am pleased too.
Oh, so awesome, so lonely
Inks, ink, ink and ink
Stay here and look at it?
Okay really?
Yes
Try moving in the gap.
Moving like this.
Shamefully
I want to touch my breasts.
touch it.
Have you ever touched your breasts?
No, not the
Then
You can touch your breasts first.
Yes
Oh yeah
Feel good
Want to touch directly?
touch directly
Are your breasts well-known?
It feels good.
But the crap feels better.
This is
greatly
well
The first time.
Would you rather be kind?
But
I like to be strong.
Heat is
Where did you study?
I always watch it.
It gets very wet.
Try to touch.
Actually is
Since I saw your team.
I was a little excited.
Is it so?
Because he was too well.
by
Shamefully
of my mother.
Looking at my mother’s breasts.
Shut up
He stood up.
You have stood up.
Feel good
The body naturally moves.
Because the seat is moving.
Yes is
hurtly
hurt is hurt.
Yes
Swaha
Stop it.
Oh yeah
No to
Yes
Great day is good.
Okay, so is it.
well is
Very good feeling.
It is Dry.
If something had been going on all the time.
Maybe something is sleeping.
I will continue to try.
Press it up.
Yes, very good
More more
It will come.
Very cute pissed.
Great, keep up up.
A very clip clip.
Can I lick?
Yes
Oh yeah
greatly
Very good feeling.
Really pleased.
Yes
Oh, very hard
I’d better be slow.
Then came the full.
I am ashamed that you say that.
Yes
I am ashamed.
Probably out.
Will go out.
No to
mother
I want to enter.
Enter it again.
I should take off my pants now.
Take it all off.
Come to
It is here.
A little more.
Yes, there and there
Because he is young.
A day hard.
So you know?
I know.
Follow it hard.
hardly
So hardly
Yes Yes
Very good
very much too much.
He goes, he goes.
Because I am going.
Feel good
greatly
Very great great.
This will be done.
Oh, it is great, it feels good.
Oh...
Ha...
Oh there...
There is scary.
I am in a scary cousin.
Oh...
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
Can I move?
Remove the neck.
with me.
with her mother.
Something good.
Not very down.
Then I will go out.
Going out? – OK
You can do this again.
What are you doing a little.
Still hard.
I too
Oh yeah yeah yeah
I want to go out.
It might feel better from behind.
Yes is.
standing in a very good place.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
If it is harder, it will be okay.
You can do it.
I can get out.
Get out.
I want more.
Stop more.
More of
Okay is?
hardly
Let it be tough.
Oh the lie.
No longer
Put your body inside and listen to it.
Hungry and hungry.
I was hungry.
Yes
No longer
I was in a hurry to get in.
No is
Yes
Oh is
It feels good.
Yes is.
Take it from a lot of people.
I want to kiss.
It feels good.
I mean.
Once again, once more.
Something, a whore.
Feels good.
awesome this
Show me last.
Oh awesome.
again is.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Not a little.
Mrs
I do not want.
Yes
Oh yeah
Oh yeah yeah yeah
No to
As already
Same as... Same as.
Two minutes of...
Okay, my dear, it is great.
by
How was your first time in Texas?
It was so good and it felt like a dream.
by
Then
time is
Prepare the meal.
Yes is.
Yes to.
Sorry for the previous test.
No, no, it was a little coincidence.
Next, you decide if it will be okay.
Yes, it is okay.
You are studying well right now.
Where was I?
It has not yet been decided.
I have decided.
No, but it is okay.
is true?
If you say you are okay.
Yes is.
Okay, I can definitely try it.
Okay, that is okay.
Tell me something about you, do it too.
Oh what?
No, I have a test score.
But you are studying.
Yes, yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
You are well.
The test was bad.
And your dad too, too much.
Not too hard, shouldn’t you say too hard?
Okay, a little
Do you like it every time?
I think I’m working hard enough.
Well, even if you get the results out, I’ll be fine.
No, I just said it was too sweet.
That’s why I call her a mother, you.
Yes, I am calling you.
Where will you get out of it again?
1 year is.
1 year
But recently I called you.
Why would I call.
It’s been quite recently, I’ve been talking.
If you can do it together, I will help you, too.
When the exam is over, I want to go on a trip with you.
Yes, I’m sure you’re still married, and you’re not even on a wedding trip.
Yes is
Try the exam.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
All to travel together.
Good luck, good luck and study.
Yes
Where to go.
A hot spring.
Certainly
well is
Is it good to go?
Where is it.
Is it possible abroad?
from overseas?
Overseas is
Yes is.
Using the space.
You can rest for 5 days.
So can you go abroad?
If it was five days, what would it be?
Hawaii and so on.
I want to go to Hawaii.
Okay okay, I am going to do it.
Yes
But, is it still a little bit different?
Oh, but where is it?
Where do you want to go for wine?
Anywhere is good?
I want to go more home than home.
I want to go home, I want to go where I want to go.
Is it?
Not everyone in the field.
Let me study a little.
Study well.
Strengthen yourself, you
I hope you study well.
Well, you know, you know the university.
Not too sweet.
Say it a little harder.
Yes, but I’m working hard, I need to.
I know you are working hard.
Please, can I go in?
Yes to.
Sorry, I am studying here.
Oh yes, no what happened?
I wonder what is meal today.
Yes
Oh yeah
Anything is okay.
Because it
My mother’s food is delicious.
really is?
happy to
Oh yeah
well well
Okay okay.
So what is it.
Tell me something.
Oh well, what do we do?
Oh well
Sorry, what is it?
Even before.
Oh is?
Even before, it was.
I was listening.
See a little.
Oh, sorry for that, what is it?
You have been thinking about something very strange lately.
It is a moment.
I have been thinking about something very emotional.
Studying is not able to concentrate at all.
A man of class.
They are no longer virgins.
Is it so?
I am a virgin, I am the only one.
I know it, I want to try it, too.
I had a lot of Echo in my head.
I think about the Echo every day.
Oh well mother.
I want to try it, too.
But...
Mother, can you let me get rid of it?
I want to get in, and I too.
But...
Please please mother.
Please, really just put it in.
Then it will no longer be an abduction.
Yes to.
Really please.
Just 1 cm first.
Please Mom.
Then
Just one centimetre.
It really is just one centimetre.
really
Thanks to Mom.
But it is wrong to get it all in.
My mother is up.
Yes I understand.
Yes
Go to sleep.
Can I take off my pants?
My mother also sleeps.
Shame on you.
Keep an eye.
Yes
well is
Then
Look at me really.
Yes I understand.
Watch it really.
Then
I can enter.
Oh yeah
Oh, greatly
Is it in?
Is this inside?
Yes, it is inside.
Do you know?
by Nell.
Feel good
Can I look a little?
really is
greatly
Do not move.
Yes, I know
is empty.
Is it enough?
This is not, I agree.
I am scared, I do.
I will feel weird too.
Do not move a little.
Oh I am scared.
It feels great.
mother
I can no longer endure.
Oh is?
mother
Oh is
It all is in.
Feel good
Oh is
Great is
I cannot get you.
It is great grinding.
Great, very good feeling.
It feels good.
Another one
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Carlos
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, sorry
I went away.
No to
Sorry to
by now
greatly
Oh is
I let you wait.
I fear
I am doctors.
very much
See also
Try it around here.
Oh yeah
It was okay.
It is OK.
I explained this to my car.
Thanks to Mom.
Yes
Yes is
So do you get well?
Okay is?
No to
Oh is
See the breast.
Very big.
It is awesome.
You can like it.
greatly
beautifully
by Mick
Touch here too.
touch it.
Oh is
Feels good?
Feel good
No to
Look at a little.
It is awesome, I became a bettor.
Feeled...
by
Oh yeah yeah yeah
The rest of the side has moved.
Oh oh oh oh oh!
No there.
there there
Oh yeah
Did you go to my mother?
My mother.
My mother said.
The mother.
It is cool.
I want to see my ass.
Oh my ass.
See it?
Oh yeah yeah
Looks great.
Feel good
greatly
here here?
Oh there
and without
No is
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah
No to
Oh, it is awesome.
It is awesome.
What to do.
The same thing.
I will lick you.
It is great feeling.
I feel great.
Awesome feeling
by
Chouchou
Oh yeah
Then I will make you feel more comfortable.
Oh is?
by
Oh yeah
It feels good.
by
It was bigger than before.
Oh awesome.
Look great.
Put your strength in and feel good.
My mother is also good.
Feel good
Oh awesome.
Will you try it yourself again?
I put it in again.
I want to put in.
It is here.
Yes
Oh the shock.
Feel good
Just landslide.
I came back, I came back.
Feel good
greatly
Oh Oh
It feels good.
Oh oh oh
and is
Yes yes yes
by
Very good feeling.
Also from behind.
Take it from behind.
and is
is long.
Very good feeling.
What is it.
Oh, very hard
Very good feeling.
I want to ride up again.
OK is.
Looking at your ass.
by ass
Very good feeling first.
Oh oh oh oh
Very good feeling.
He fell very much.
A beautiful feeling.
repeat more.
Awesome feeling
Oh go here, go here.
Feel good
Oh here
Aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa
aaa aaa aaa
aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa
aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa
aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa
aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa
Brother, what is going on?
This is a study of the life of Ah
Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah.
And he is also.
for a second.
Aaaa no one.
Look at the silver.
One, one, one or another.
Oh my God.
Do you understand?
thanks to.
You are very welcome.
promised was made.
So come and work.
Pumped up, I am very lucky.
I brought you such a beautiful mother.
Yes, I am very lucky.
Mika, I am very lucky.
When your mother didn’t come, she
did it herself, didn’t she?
Yes is.
I did everything.
Sometimes I helped my brother.
I am very lucky to have
a real career.
Yes, I am very lucky.
Really is?
Yes is.
Are you okay?
I am good.
and beautiful.
Salute to me.
Do you sleep well?
Please please.
We need to make
more smiles.
What do we need?
We have to do the beauty
of Yukari.
No, I am not doing
beauty.
We have to be beautiful.
I do not do beauty.
He is also my brother.
Is it not?
My dear city, we have
to do beauty.
We have to be beautiful.
Really thank you.
We need to make the beauty
of the city.
Yes, my brother also has
to do beauty.
Is it not?
What is?
The city of.
What happened?
He had to fight.
No, that is very normal.
What is?
Is there nothing?
I liked it too.
had to test.
He had to just do the test.
No to.
Not a bit painful?
He was very forced.
Not anything is.
Nothing is nothing?
What did sheep do?
No to.
Yes is.
Okay is?
I am finished.
Where do you want to go?
I do not know.
Tell me where you want to go.
Yes is.
Then I have to do something.
If you want to do something, tell me.
Yes is.
It was good, right?
Meaning is...
... is it something?
He was very scared.
A joke of?
Do not worry about him.
Do not be afraid, right?
that man.
You have to fear.
What should you be afraid of?
Mama, what do you want to do?
Leave it, leave it.
was good.
Yes is.
City is coming.
by Mama.
You are also training.
There is a problem, I have to do it.
What are you learning?
not there.
Is this wrong, isn’t it?
Where to?
This is.
This is not X, but Y.
What is there for dinner today?
What is?
My daddy is going to
work today, so my
daddy is coming.
Dad always eat sweet foods
So sweet foods Aaaa Then
always eat good foods
Carabiber?
The carabiner?
Is the sweet food good
for the caribbean?
I love the carbs very much Yes, the broth is good but
the hamburger is good, and the hamburger made by my mother
is very good, the hamburger is good and the hamburger is
good and the hamburger is good and the hamburger is good
and the hamburger is good and the hamburger
is good and the hamburger is good and the hamburger is
good and the hamburger is good and the hamburger
is good and the hamburger is
good and the hamburger is good.
Well, something like a craft.
Not everyone, not everyone?
Two people with my daughter.
Only two people.
But that is good too.
He fell into the game.
Falling into the game?
Oh, oh oh oh oh oh oh
Mother and Mother.
This, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this,
this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this,
Watch your attention.
For whom?
Is not?
and...
... one...
One cm...
for a second...
Then you can absolutely
do nothing.
What is?
What do you say about the city?
I will say something.
I do not want to do anything.
I do not want to do anything else.
by Mama.
It is really a cm.
and cm.
You can absolutely do nothing.
for a second.
Please please.
City is no.
A bitter...
After we break up
with me, let’
s make a Bametice
first.
I will pay him.
I come here.
Now I will make a batch.
I make a batch.
I will make another bowl.
Will you do another bowl?
I am not at all Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely
Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely
Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely
Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely
Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely
Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely
Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absolutely Absol
Really...
It was my first time, right?
of course.
I will close zero.
I really close up.
I will shut.
I close it.
was good.
I was tired.
Definitely that is.
So much so?
This is...
Fuck it!
Ah!
Be calm, I fell again.
I fell again.
I fell a centimeter.
Strictly...
Look closely at it.
Oh, I...
I cannot do it until I.
You are so beautiful,
sorry.
and open.
But how?
I wanted to breathe for you.
KIMOS...
No to.
Kimi and Kim.
This time, move the city.
I do not move.
Wait for Kim.
It is very heavy, it is very heavy, it is very heavy, it is very heavy, it is very heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy,
it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it
is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it
is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is
so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so heavy, it is so bad, it is so bad, it
is so bad, it is so bad, it is so bad, it is so bad, it is so bad, it is so
I will teach you how to have sex.
Do you teach me to have sex?
Do it so.
Look at me.
Look at again.
and more.
Look more up.
Very big and very sweet.
Or sweet?
I am good.
See also.
very well.
I will feel my clothes.
My clothes are not dirty, right?
My clothes are painful.
It is so painful in the dark.
I will show you my clothes.
What happened?
and h?
You can eat that way.
Piro to Piro.
Yes, it is nice to do so.
very nice.
Yes is.
Yes, very nice.
He finished his finishing,
He began to pay
attention.
You say so too.
He became very nervous.
Yes, very nervously.
How is?
Very nervous.
How nervous are you, too?
Two or two are very nervous.
Both are very nervous.
He becomes more nervous.
See also.
What is this?
I can’t do anything either.
You want to say more,
right?
Yes, I want to say.
Okay stop here.
Do you eat most of your mother?
You loved it, didn’t you?
See also.
very sweet.
What is this?
What will I do?
No problem though.
and fast.
I am roots.
by Grandma.
Too much to say,
said Irk.
Say to Irk?
by?
Can you not have your whole mouth?
Accept and stop.
is so?
I want to say something better.
Do it again.
Cheated by Cheated.
Think, how
are you?
Do not stop, you probably
don’t stop.
Do not stop.
Really?
Oh well no!
But he will live again.
No, no is no.
Go but
no.
I cannot do either.
Leave it, okay?
Come on, look at it.
Come on, go on.
The moon is...
Do you read?
Ayy, stop by
To whom give the house?
What happened?
What happened again?
Tell me someone better, come
back very quickly
and very often.
Open up, come on.
Come on go.
I will never see it.
Let us go.
Look at it, late.
Very poor, very poor.
Very poorly.
The bad bag.
Their...
A, A, A, A and A
Come to my coach.
Come back to me...
I will tell you too.
I will entertain you.
here...
This is right.
Yes is.
This is very good too.
very well.
Go up another run.
Yes is.
very painful.
This, this...
This is good.
Come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come
Yes, yes, yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
Oh, very beautifully.
Oh well beautiful.
Oh yeah not?
very well.
Hahaha So people have
trouble listening to
the calculator?
Yes, there is trouble.
So, move a faster move.
and faster.
Yes, there
is trouble.
Yes, move a faster one.
Take a quick move.
I will come, I will come.
What happened?
May longolu ka fundament
saturated Serious?
Keep it unclean!
Who is it without?
We are good.
We are very good.
I went out again.
Come on Uncle.
I will complete them all.
Aaaa My daughter,
YH5 above,Viydik Aht Love A่rı
Orchestra President?
Go down the head pegar Меня, then 기대imeter
God, go in the
bread of the devil!
Let us go!
You are wearing racing!
Go in here!
Let us go!
Wear the enemy this week!
It was very painful.
I cannot do such a thing.
Come on, go on.
I need to do something first.
Do something first.
Not so bad, right?
And more yet?
My name is Mom.
That is all.
Mom went in the door.
Mom, look at me.
See you see?
It looks very nice, right?
Yes, it looks very nice.
It looks very
nice.
Very nice, very warm.
very comfortably.
It looks very nice.
Do you want to
make this work
charcoal?
I have no
way to change
this, I
am God.
God is my servant.
What will I do.
and again.
Again and again.
and open.
What will I do?
N’aber Mark?
Stop to stop.
Oh, I still forgot.
in my hand?
Let us continue the main.
in my hand.
That is all.
Go to bye.
The serpent comes again.
Oh of course.
Can you do it well with Ryo?
Yes is.
I felt the cabbage the first time,
but this time they talk
a lot.
Well well well.
He was a college student
this year.
Yes is.
A lot of things.
Then very difficult.
And night is near.
This man is also working.
How is?
is good.
Look at learning.
and me?
See also.
Can I not watch?
I will not listen for a while.
No time to talk.
Yes, of course of course.
Let’s start having
fun for a while.
Where should I go?
I want to go to Ansel.
Ryo went to school.
Yes, it is so.
A beautiful time.
Yes, I go to school.
Not in school, but in school.
E really?
I want to go to Orlando.
Ryo, good day to you.
and good days.
Did you go to school first?
Test is near.
I go to school.
and same.
This year’s meal is very difficult.
What would you like to
eat for dinner today?
and same.
Everything Yuka has
made is delicious.
and same.
This year’s meal is very difficult.
Do not fear, do not fear.
But...
It always works.
There is nothing like that.
is so?
No, there is nothing like that.
Let us tell you to learn.
I think it’s good for Yuka.
Is it not?
We were first a home teacher.
20 years ago, 10 years ago.
Can I tell the teacher first?
not be.
Yes, of course no.
Yes is.
Let us work together.
I will work a little.
Yes is.
Go to work.
work to.
Come to.
He is old too.
But he is old too.
Let us work.
Yes yes yes.
before using the example.
If you can use this example, I think it
will be remarkable.
Oh yeah, is it?
I understand.
They always ask something and
they are doing something wrong.
Yes, they are doing wrong.
My mom is really fast.
Oh, it is not so.
There
is nothing else here, right?
Oh, oh, oh, where is it?
Maybe they are making the same
mistake.
Eeee where?
Is it not so?
Yes, is it not so?
Yes, is it so?
Yes, is it not?
But this is a little mistake.
But is it not very successful?
Dad, this is very successful.
But that is very successful.
Is there a problem?
If your mother can do
anything, do I really
do something?
Yes, can I say
anything
I’ll do?
Yes at the same time...
In the heavens...
I myself...
From Oct...
I can’t do anything, I can’t do anything, I can’t do anything, I can’
t do anything, I can’t do anything.
...and...
I myself...
...and they always lie
to me...we did I also want
to do a very fast way
that, ooo...
and...
You are all very heavy.
Yes, so please at least I can’t
get the training Yes...
Yuka, please yeah
Can you drink this?
Eeee?
Yes yes...
No, no is no.
This is a little...
... nothing will happen.
But...
I wanted to ask questions.
That’s why I spoke.
But...
... has.
... yet...
Come to.
Once again...
You stop here.
Is there no heat?
Please temperature.
The temperature?
Or a little.
I want to trouble.
by SUB.
1 cm please.
1 cm?
Yuka please.
1 cm to 1 cm?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
I really is that.
All the schools fell.
I think what to do.
Please Yuka.
All the schools fell.
I don’t want to go to
my son’s school.
I want to go to good schools.
Please take 1 cm.
You can also concentrate
on learning.
1 cm?
So, you are not really
moving?
Take another 1 cm.
So, you are not really
moving?
thank you thank you.
Are you okay?
Keep up long.
Is it such a huge tool?
I thought I would go through the natural
water.
Get a little warmer.
You also have your cuts.
and same.
You really are too
old, right?
Yes is.
Then I come too.
Do not watch too much.
Okay I understood.
A little...
be careful.
Okay well.
Then...
... be careful.
Okay well.
This is a year.
Yes, it is here.
So much so?
This is also an obstacle.
This is very pleasant.
So much so?
Yes, a little more.
A little more.
The Hate?
HaKu tuha terrified name Yes
Jerusalem small so respons s
premium What should I do?
What will I do too?
I loved
it, I loved it, it was beautiful.
and beautiful.
A little more...
I will not hide.
and beautiful.
very beautiful.
Come to.
Is it beautiful?
Come to come.
Come to.
Come on, come on, come on
Oh... oh... oh...
I drink too much...
Soon...
No to...
I will tell you consensus.
The foot below.
Sit down and breast.
Okay okay?
I just promised a little.
I will teach you.
Oh really?
Want to see directly?
Oh yeah
Have you ever seen your breasts?
This is your first time.
Can I like it?
Oh awesome.
The breasts are awesome.
I was concerned about your breast.
I was a little concerned.
So I couldn’t study.
Oh awesome.
I want to see the theory.
I want to see theory.
Beautiful she has.
Reacted down below.
Can I touch?
Let us sleep.
Touched a lot.
Very soft.
Full of fools.
You are good for me too.
really is?
You feel good too.
Do you want to touch?
It is so awesome that the floor has become stronger.
You are troubled.
Oh awesome.
Yes is
Do you want to lick?
Lick it.
No to
Very delicious.
is delicious?
Drink more.
No to
This too
You can drink, it is good.
really
Did you do this massage?
Yes yes yes
It is done properly.
And then rest.
My body is hot.
You will sleep.
Stay big here.
I will make you feel good.
Same, you feel so good.
Tastefully
and...
Chennai is hot, you know?
I will make you feel good before.
So to be.
Did you think that this was something you wanted to be?
and my breasts,
Feels good.
Have it?
Did you imagine this with my breasts?
Yes, I have been thinking about this all the time.
Feels good?
Such a chench.
I want you to feel good about me, too.
Yes, of course
I want to feel good about this idiot.
What is?
Mr Mamiliah
Oh, so very good feeling.
It is hot.
Heat is
Oh yeah
A great amount or good.
Sophie, I felt good.
It felt great.
I could not endure again.
In the crap that I’ve gotten in again.
Very good feeling.
Feel badly
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Stop it.
See also
You see it coming in.
Oh well awesome.
It is right behind.
Yes, it is in this board.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
by Almighty
Oh, was
No to...
Oh well...
and zoom
A lot of touch.
No to
Feels good?
by
Oh is
Do you know the right place now?
The room here.
Stay full here.
by Rush.
I am hungry.
Not in memories.
Same, Same is good.
I feel good too.
A lot of vomiting.
Something very good feeling.
Oh, and stop now.
No more not.
I cannot endure.
Can you endure?
So find out.
Oh, but I don’t know.
I do not understand.
Oh, a little
Yes is
Go to sleep a little?
I do not sleep.
Okay is it?
You will still cry.
Is it still good?
It is already hard.
Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes
drop it
You and you!
It hurts, it hurts.
Did it hurt, you showed up?
Can you still?
Yes is
Yes, it feels good.
Please please.
Yes is
Next time, go to your mouth.
The mouth is.
Yes, I understand
by
Put it in your mouth.
Did you put it on your breast?
Sorry to
It was so bad I couldn’t endure.
Couldn’t I endure?
Next time, put it in your mouth.
So let’s do it again tomorrow.
Okay is it?
I will clean it.
Has it opened?
Yes, I have opened up.