I came to see the medical student.
adjustments are required.
What will I do?
I can't do it.
what?
I came to see you to celebrate your supplementary exam.
Come here.
Hello.
Sit down.
Here's your drink.
Thank you.
What do you want to drink?
Isn't it hot today?
I've been sweating a lot since this morning.
I've been using a sweat blanket for a long time.
But you can turn on the air conditioner.
It's cold and hot.
I'm so tired.
No one is coming.
The manager is so annoying.
I think you should be more serious.
What do you want to drink?
I'm sorry.
You're looking at my boobs all the time.
What do you want to drink?
I'll have a whiskey with water.
Okay.
Do you often come here?
It's my first time.
Is that so?
Yes.
You don't seem to have a problem with girls.
No, I don't.
You're popular, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Wait.
Do you want a strong drink?
No, I'm fine.
I'll have a whiskey with water.
It's a little mature.
Is that so?
Open it.
Okay.
I opened it.
Thank you.
Can I have a drink, too?
I want to make a toast.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'll have a whiskey with water.
What should I do?
Do you have a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
Why?
So, you haven't had a girlfriend recently.
That's right.
I see.
So, what are you going to do today?
Are you going to look for a girl?
Yes.
Are you going to walk around?
Yes, I'm going to walk around and get here.
Then, you can do a lot of sexy things today.
Sexy things?
Cheers.
What do you do for a living?
I run a business.
Business? That's great.
What do you sell?
I sell ads.
Do you sell ads?
What do you mean?
Do you sell paper?
I sell online ads.
I see.
Do you sell ads for hair removal on YouTube?
Something like that.
What do you sell?
I sell it to customers who want to make a website.
A website?
Can you sell a website?
If I have a need to make a website, I can sell it.
That's great.
What kind of website have you made recently?
For example, if a customer is looking for a talent, I can make a website to recruit that talent.
Recruiting a talent?
I see.
You work a lot.
That's right.
Do you have a hard time every day?
Yes, I have a hard time.
I see.
You get tired if you work so seriously.
Yes, I get tired.
Did you come here to relax today?
Yes.
Did you come here to play?
Yes, I came here to play.
By the way, why don't you touch me?
What?
Do you hate my boobs?
No, I don't hate them.
Then, it's okay.
What?
You don't like them?
No, I don't hate them.
What?
I don't want you to say hello to me in the store.
Just in case.
Because no one is here.
It doesn't matter.
I see.
What?
Just in case.
Just in case?
I see.
You're standing up.
What?
Just in case.
I see.
It doesn't matter.
The store manager said no.
But the store manager isn't here.
The store manager isn't here?
No.
I see.
What?
You like it, don't you?
Yes.
What?
Touch me.
Just this much.
Just this much?
Yes.
I'm going to touch you.
I see.
Yes.
Just this much.
I'm going to touch you.
You're so gentle.
I'm gentle, aren't I?
It feels good.
Can I touch you more?
Yes.
Why?
You don't have to go that far.
I want to lick you.
Is that okay?
It's okay. No one is watching.
I'll let you go.
You're standing up.
Can I lick you?
I'll lick you.
Is that really okay?
It's delicious.
I'll let you go.
You're surprised.
It's dangerous.
Is it dangerous?
I'll let you go.
It's weak here.
It's very weak.
Something salty came out.
You can't do that.
Just in case.
I want you to touch me.
I'll give you a kiss.
It feels good.
It's dangerous here.
Wait.
I'll go.
I'm sorry to let you go.
Come here.
I'll let you go.
Are you okay?
I can't do that.
Just in case.
Look at me.
You've been looking at my boobs.
You like boobs, don't you?
It's very hard.
It feels good.
It's hard.
You feel better.
It's not fair.
Let's make a six-nine.
I don't want to do that.
It's a one-sided love.
But just in case.
I see.
What? You don't like it?
No, I don't.
You're noisy.
It feels good.
Don't rub your eyes.
It's getting harder.
Wait.
I'm going to go.
It feels good.
Give me more.
I'm going.
How are you?
I can't stand it anymore.
Are you still doing that?
I'm going to put it in.
I'm going.
You were surprised, weren't you?
It feels good.
I'm going.
Can you move from below?
Yes.
I like to be rubbed there.
It feels good.
I want to rub you a little more.
Wait.
It feels good.
Don't rub my neck.
I like it.
I'm going.
Can you rub me from below again?
Yes.
It feels good.
Wait.
I'm going.
Can you move from below?
Yes.
It feels good.
Are you really okay?
You're persistent.
It feels good.
Can you rub me a little more?
There.
Hurry up.
I'm going.
It feels good.
I like it.
Can you do it?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's the best.
I want you to rub me from behind.
Can you let me take it off?
I'm going.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I'm going.
I like it.
There.
I'm going.
Can you rub me a little more?
Yes.
I'm going.
Wait.
I'll do it slowly.
I'm going.
Wait.
It feels good.
I'm going.
Can you rub me a little more?
It's amazing.
I'm going.
I want to kiss you at the end.
There.
It's amazing.
I'm going.
Can you rub me a little more?
It's amazing.
I'm going.
Can you help me?
Show me a lot of good things.
It feels good.
I'm going.
It's amazing.
I changed in 10 minutes.
Do you want to change now?
No, I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Let's do it again.
No, I can't.
I'm going.
There's no one here.
It's a normal house.
I'm going.
Welcome!
Where are you going?
Are you alone?
Are you alone today?
What are you doing?
It's a windy place.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
Please sit here.
Thank you.
What would you like to drink?
All of a sudden?
This.
Soju?
Yes.
Soju.
Can I have some?
Please.
Thank you.
A lot of ice.
What?
No one is here.
No one is here?
What are you worried about?
No one is here.
Do you want some?
I'm fine.
You put too much.
Do you want some water?
Yes, please.
Good night.
I came here after work today.
I see.
I made something cold.
Cheers.
Let's drink.
I made too much.
I see.
Too much?
Was it too much?
I'll make it again.
No problem.
It's good.
What do you do for a living?
I teach soccer to children.
Soccer?
To children?
How old are they?
They are 3 or 4 years old.
I teach elementary school students.
I used to play soccer.
I see.
I wanted to be a professional player.
I want to change my career.
I want to study sports.
I want to be a teacher.
I play soccer.
I see.
Do you play sports?
No, I don't.
I see.
I don't.
You play sports all the time.
I like it.
Do you watch soccer?
No, I don't.
I see.
I can understand it.
I don't understand it.
It doesn't matter.
It's not about soccer.
You are cheerful.
Thank you.
It's good.
What are you doing?
Your hair is big.
It's big.
You don't mind?
I don't mind.
I was wondering if something was wrong.
Don't worry.
Can I touch your boobs?
Boobs?
Do you touch my boobs?
Okay.
Don't you like it?
I don't like it.
Don't touch my boobs.
You make me surprised.
Don't you like it?
You make me embarrassed.
This is a good one.
It's a good one.
Here you go.
But this is...
I don't want to be a bad influence.
This is okay.
It's okay.
I don't want to be a bad influence.
Oh, bad influence?
I know it's not good.
Do you know?
I know.
It's almost bad.
Oh, I see.
I don't want to be a bad influence.
Why did you stop?
I'm sorry. I was surprised.
Touch it.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
I don't want to be a bad influence.
Really?
Do you want to be a bad influence?
No.
It's okay.
It's amazing.
It's like touching each other.
Is this okay?
It's okay.
You care too much.
No.
No?
I'm sorry.
You care too much.
I don't know what kind of shop it is.
I don't want to touch your boobs.
Is it okay to touch from the clothes?
It's okay to touch directly.
No way.
Really?
Really.
Is it okay to touch directly?
I can't see it.
It's okay to touch directly.
Really?
Really.
It's okay.
There is no rule.
Here you are.
I'm sorry.
Why?
No.
It's amazing.
Don't touch me.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Here you are.
I found it.
It's fun.
Is it fun?
Is it okay?
It's okay.
It's amazing.
It's amazing and cute.
It's okay.
What's wrong?
What's this?
It's okay.
If you do too much, you will be scolded.
If I do too much?
To whom?
To the shop manager.
He is not here.
It's okay.
You will be scolded.
It's on the clothes.
It's okay.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
I was touched by a child for the first time.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Don't you want to do that?
That kind of shop...
Don't you use it?
I don't use it.
You use it.
It's okay.
It's written there.
You don't have to worry about it.
Really?
Yes.
Do you like to touch it directly?
Directly?
Yes.
Can I touch it directly?
You can't.
It's okay, isn't it?
Which one?
It's okay.
Wait a minute.
No.
Which do you like better, being touched or being licked?
I like being touched.
Wait a minute.
What are those eyes?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
You touched my boobs.
How about this?
How about touching it directly?
No.
You're making fun of me.
I'm not.
Tell me what you're doing.
What are you doing?
Hey.
You're going to get angry.
I'm the one who's in trouble.
Are you okay?
No.
Wait a minute.
You're going to get angry.
What?
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
No one's here.
No one's watching.
It's okay.
Touch me.
Come here.
Where should I touch?
Here.
Where?
Here?
Here.
Yes.
Touch me.
I don't know.
Like this?
Yes.
It's not good.
No one's here.
It's okay.
Do you want me to touch you?
You're stiff.
Wait a minute.
It's embarrassing.
It's not embarrassing.
Wait a minute.
What?
What are you doing?
You're going to get angry.
I don't know.
Wait a minute.
What?
What are you doing?
It's not good.
Why?
Isn't it terrible?
It's not good.
What?
Do you want to do it or not?
I want to do it.
Wait a minute.
You can't do it.
I can't do anything.
I can't do it.
You can't do it.
Let's go to bed.
I don't want to do it.
You want to do it, don't you?
Then let's go to bed.
I can't do it.
You can't do it.
Can I do it if I can't see it?
What do you mean?
I can't see it.
You can't see it?
Is that so?
Isn't that so?
Don't you know?
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
It's not okay.
I can't do it.
Wait a minute.
It's in there, isn't it?
It's in there.
What was that?
I'm the only one who feels good.
I'm sorry.
I'll lick you.
What do you want me to do?
You can't do it.
You can't do it, can you?
You should stop here.
You can't do it.
What?
You can't do it, can you?
You can't do it.
Why do you do it?
Isn't it because you want to do it?
What?
What's wrong with you?
Does it feel good?
But...
What happens if you get drunk?
What happens if I get drunk?
I don't know.
You don't know?
You don't know.
I don't have that much money.
You don't have that much money.
It's all right.
You've been doing it all the time.
What?
He wants to do it, too.
I know it's bad, but...
You're such a good person.
I'm sorry.
You're not good at it.
You're doing everything wrong.
He wants me to lick him, too.
Where do you want me to lick you?
It's decided.
This way.
Wait a minute.
You're not going to lick me, are you?
No, of course not.
How do you feel?
Good boy.
You'll be punished.
You'll be punished if you get caught.
It's amazing.
It's so soft.
This is...
It's amazing. It's so soft.
What is this?
I'm going to do it.
You want to do it, don't you?
I want to do it, but...
Do you want to do it?
No.
No?
I'll be scolded.
You'll be scolded.
It's okay.
It's just the two of us.
But...
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Are you going to take it off?
Oh, my God.
Do you like this?
I like it.
Oh, it feels good.
What?
You're doing great.
Oh, my God.
What?
Oh, it feels good.
You're doing great.
Oh, my God.
I don't know.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, my God.
Do you want to touch it?
Touch it.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, my God.
Do you want to touch it?
What?
You have to hurry up!
Okay!
Hurry up.
I feel good!
You are moving as you like
But it's too late!
I'm sorry
I'm putting it in, so scratch it.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Hurry up.
Oh, no.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
It feels good, so scratch it.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
I feel good, too.
Oh, no.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
I can't do it.
Let's do it again.
Again.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
You didn't drink, did you?
I forgot to drink.
Do you want me to make you drink?
You drank a lot.
You spilled it.
I'm sorry.
You drank a lot.
It's my first time to drink like this.
Is it your first time?
It feels good.
What's wrong?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
Oh, no.
It's very rough.
I can't do it.
It doesn't hurt.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm sorry.
Move well.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
It's fine.
Move well.
I was waiting for you.
I'm going to cry.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'm alone.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Oh, no.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
It hurts.
It's a lot.
Did you go to the park every day?
What should I do?
You can't do it.
I can't do it.
You're kidding, right?
When will you do it next time?
Next time?
Next week.
Next week?
I'll do it next week.
A little earlier.
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
I'll do it tomorrow.
It's a secret.
Welcome.
Are you alone?
Yes, I'm alone.
What's your name?
Saki.
What's the name on the top? What's the name on the bottom?
The bottom?
The name on the bottom.
It's Yu.
Yu?
What's your name? Anything is fine, right?
Anything is fine.
Is this your first time here?
Yes, I haven't been here much.
Do you know what kind of place Sekkeba is?
Do you do anything erotic?
Do I do erotic things?
Do you touch boobs?
Yes, I do.
Why did you know about this place?
I saw it on the internet.
Internet?
Yes.
This place is not an erotic place.
It's not an erotic place?
It's Sekkeba.
Go ahead.
Thank you for the food.
You were thirsty, weren't you? Were you nervous?
Yes, I was nervous.
What do you do for a living?
I run a restaurant.
A restaurant?
Do you like cooking?
Yes, I like cooking.
Do you like serving?
Yes, I like serving.
Are you not used to talking to girls?
No, I'm not.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
All the time?
No, not all the time.
You don't have a girlfriend now, do you?
No, I don't.
Do you want to hang out?
Yes, I do.
Do you hang out with girls?
You don't, do you?
I don't.
Is this okay?
Of course.
I'm just touching your hand.
I'm not sure.
It's my first time.
Your hands are beautiful.
Thank you.
Your nails are cute.
Yes, I like them.
That's good.
They look good on you.
Did you finish your work today?
Did you have a day off?
Yes, I did.
I see.
What did you do all day?
I wandered around.
I wanted to go shopping.
Did you find anything good?
I wanted to come here.
You wanted to come here?
Yes.
I'm glad to hear that.
What's this?
The manager told me to wear this.
Did he?
Yes.
Because it's over my pants.
I see.
What's this?
Is this okay?
Yes, it is.
Why?
Because it's over my pants.
What's wrong?
Are you not used to this?
No, I'm not.
But you've done this before, haven't you?
Yes, I have.
But it's not a shop.
You don't go to a shop like that?
No, I don't.
It's getting hard.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Are you sure?
You know that, don't you?
No, I don't.
Don't you want to touch your boobs?
Is this okay?
Yes, it is.
The manager didn't tell me that.
It's soft.
Ouch!
What's wrong with your face?
Is it M size?
Is it okay?
Which one is M?
It's M.
Is it?
It's so soft.
Do you like big boobs?
I love them.
Wow.
It's getting hard.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to see them?
Is it okay?
I think it's okay to show them.
Oh.
You don't touch your boobs sometimes, do you?
I don't.
Is it okay?
Hurry up.
If you don't want to touch them, it's okay.
I want to touch them.
I've always wanted to touch them.
You've always wanted to touch them?
I thought they were big.
What's wrong?
I don't know what to do.
What if someone comes?
No one will come.
It's just two of us.
I want to see them up close.
Do you want to lick them?
No, I don't.
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid that you'll get angry.
What?
It's okay.
I've heard that it's bad.
Is it okay?
You want to lick them, don't you?
Why are you so shy?
Is this okay?
I've heard that it's bad.
No, it's not.
It's okay.
Don't you want to lick them?
I want to lick them.
It's okay.
No one will come.
Really?
Really.
It's okay.
Don't say that.
You're licking them.
You wanted to lick them, didn't you?
Yes.
I'll do it, too.
What?
Can you take off your clothes?
Clothes?
I'll take off my clothes.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
What's that face?
You feel good, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I'll lick them, too.
You can't do that.
It's okay.
I said it's okay.
But you can't do that.
I can't?
Let's not do that.
Someone will come.
No one will come.
You'll get angry.
It hurts.
It's not good.
What's not good?
It's written here.
What?
It's okay.
No one will come today.
Really?
Is it okay?
You can't do that.
I can't?
I can't.
You can't do that.
No one will come.
It's written here.
It's not good.
What's not good?
You'll get angry.
Let's not do that.
What?
Look.
Do you want to touch me?
Is this okay?
You can't do that.
I can't?
No one will come.
You want to touch me, don't you?
But...
Hurry up.
What?
Is it really okay?
It's okay.
No one will come.
Really?
Because you want me to touch you.
What kind of position do you do in private?
Normal.
Normal?
Do you want to touch me?
I want to touch you.
But...
Is it okay?
You tried to touch me.
You don't want to touch me, do you?
Is it okay?
Touch me.
Is it really okay?
Is it okay?
It feels good.
Don't you feel pain?
I feel pain.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Hurry up.
It feels good.
The customer is sexy.
Let's make a toast.
Okay.
Thank you for your hard work.
What's wrong?
I heard something from outside.
Outside?
It's okay.
There are a lot of people next door.
Did you hear that?
I did a lot of bad things.
You did a lot of bad things.
Are you okay?
I told you.
But it's okay.
No one will come today.
Really?
Really.
No one will come.
Oh, no.
You're sexy.
What's wrong with your face?
Are you embarrassed?
Yes.
Why?
You're not embarrassed anymore, are you?
I'm embarrassed.
What?
Can I touch you?
It's okay.
Do you like boobs?
Yes, I do.
Do you want me to do a boob job?
A boob job?
Don't you know what a boob job is?
I know, but...
What?
I can't do this.
It's okay.
It's okay, but it's okay.
No, it's not.
It's okay.
Take this off.
Wait a minute.
What?
No one will come today.
Wait a minute.
I'll be scolded.
It's okay.
No one will come.
No one will find out.
What?
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Stretch your legs.
What should I do?
What is this?
This?
That...
Is that okay?
What?
It's okay.
But that's bad.
That's bad.
It's not bad.
No one will come.
But this...
This...
It's okay.
Don't you want to be scolded?
Do you want to be scolded?
Then it's okay.
What?
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
Have you ever been scolded?
I've never been scolded.
It's my first time.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels great.
It's great.
What are you doing?
Hey, let go of my hand.
Does it feel good?
It feels great.
But will you be scolded?
What?
Will you be scolded?
It's okay.
What are you talking about?
It's great.
It's sticky.
Get up.
You can't do that, can you?
Of course I can't.
You can't, can you?
It's not good.
It's sticky.
It hurts.
It feels great.
I want to feel good, too.
Will you lick me?
You can't do that, can you?
Of course I can't.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Wipe it off.
It's okay.
Shall I put it in your mouth?
You can't do that.
It's okay.
She's coming.
No one's coming.
What?
I'll put it in your mouth.
Let's not do that.
What?
I'll put it in your mouth.
Stop doing that.
No, I'll stop.
I don't want to put it in.
Hm?
No...
Don't...
Does it feel good?
Don't you want to go in?
I can't do it.
This...
Are you angry?
It's okay.
No one will come.
I'll take this off, too.
It's hot.
I can't do it.
Come up a little more.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You can touch my chest.
Can I?
Can I do this?
You can do anything.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Do it harder.
Harder?
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Sit here.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
No one will come today.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
It's so warm.
I told you not to do it.
I can't do it?
Of course you can't.
Manager!
I'm sorry.
You're lying.
I'm not.
You're cute.
Manager won't come today.
I won't.
Do you want to go home?
I can't.
You can't.
She's not here.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I was surprised.
I went to the bathroom.
Are you alone?
Do you come here often?
Is this your first time?
Yes.
What are you doing here?
Are you drunk?
No, I'm not drunk.
Are you drinking?
Yes.
You're amazing.
Do you want to drink?
Can I?
What do you want to drink?
Are you off today?
Yes.
What were you doing?
I was watching a movie.
I was alone.
Are you always alone?
Basically.
I see.
Do you drink water?
Yes.
Are you weak?
I like water.
I want to drink a lot.
Do you really want to drink?
Do you just drink?
Well.
That's not true.
I know you.
Did you know me?
Of course.
I didn't think you would say that.
By the way.
Are you okay?
Why?
I think I'm in love with you.
You have a lot of guys you like.
It's fresh.
I'm glad to hear that.
I don't have a chance to talk to you.
It's done.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It's hard to drink.
Why?
What's wrong?
Are you nervous?
Maybe.
You're not used to it.
I don't know much about the store.
You're very active.
Your nails are beautiful.
Thank you.
It's cute.
I like to see this.
Are you okay?
No.
I'm nervous.
You're very nervous.
I know.
When you're nervous, you go ahead.
I'll get drunk soon.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Are you surprised?
No, I'm not.
I'm just drawing.
You two have been together for a long time.
It's rare.
I think so.
The customer can touch the girl's boobs directly.
I see.
Can I touch it directly?
Yes.
I see.
Can I touch it?
I don't know.
Don't you touch it?
I wonder if there are people who don't touch it.
Everyone touches it, right?
I think so.
Don't you touch it?
I'll let you touch it.
Drink it.
It's delicious.
It's good.
It's big.
Do you like big boobs?
Of course.
You can touch it.
I'm embarrassed because I can touch it.
Are you embarrassed?
What are those eyes?
You can touch it.
It's amazing.
You can touch it directly.
Directly?
Why are you grinning?
I'm sorry.
It's a little disgusting.
It's not disgusting.
It's amazing.
You can touch it directly.
I see.
Are you okay?
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Look at this.
I want to check it.
What is it?
How far can I touch it?
You can touch it up to here.
My boobs?
Yes.
You can't touch it more than this.
It's against the rules.
Wait a minute.
What's this?
The manager said no.
He said no?
Yes.
He said no.
I can't say it.
But no one is here.
Wait a minute.
Isn't it amazing?
You're holding it so tight.
Is it bad?
No, it's not bad.
Don't you want to do this?
I can't do it.
Touch it.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
I got drunk a little early.
Do you want to drink more?
Are you okay?
I want to drink more.
I can't touch it.
You can't touch it?
Wait a minute.
Let me drink it, too.
It's delicious.
It's pretty bad from here.
It's pretty bad.
It's pretty bad if you find it.
It's pretty bad, isn't it?
Wait a minute.
Where?
Here.
What about this?
It's pretty bad.
What?
Is it pretty bad?
It's pretty bad.
It's pretty bad, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
Touch it properly.
Properly?
Like this?
Yes.
Do you know it's slimy?
What?
This?
It's slimy, isn't it?
It's pretty bad, isn't it?
It's pretty bad.
Is it my fault?
Yes.
Why are you so swollen?
I'm sorry.
I thought it was pretty bad.
I see.
It's pretty bad, isn't it?
What should I do?
I can't imagine.
Really?
I think it's pretty bad.
It's okay.
How is it?
It's pretty bad, isn't it?
It's fun, isn't it?
It's fun, but it's a little painful.
What are you doing?
I'm going to lick your nipples.
Really?
It's pretty bad.
Is it bad?
Your nails are amazing.
With my nails?
That's how you feel.
You're good at licking.
You're good.
Really?
It's pretty bad.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
It's pretty bad, isn't it?
Show me.
It's okay.
It's not okay at all.
Show me.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
I'm embarrassed.
Touch my nipples.
Give me your hand.
Wait a minute.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
What about this?
It's not okay.
It's okay.
Does it feel good?
I'm embarrassed.
I'm standing up.
Are you embarrassed?
Touch my nipples.
Like this?
Yes.
It's okay.
It's a secret.
I'm not going to tell anyone.
It's okay.
You can lick my nipples.
Are you okay?
You're bold.
It's okay.
It's a secret.
Do you feel good?
Like this?
It's okay.
I'm sure I can't do this.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Is it easy to feel?
Yes.
I love it.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Did you feel good?
Really?
Don't do it after this.
As I expected.
It's dangerous to break the rules.
I've come this far.
You've broken it too much.
That's right.
I like to be forced.
Even if I say no.
Will you come?
It doesn't matter.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's dangerous.
It feels good.
I'm scared.
Is it too big?
Are you okay?
Can you hear my voice?
Will you come?
I like to be forced.
Do you like it?
I love it.
I'm scared.
It's too big.
It feels good.
I'm scared.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I want to hug you.
Hug?
Take this.
Are you okay?
It's hard to do.
I want to hug you.
It's amazing.
Excuse me.
I'm scared.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
I'm scared.
It's amazing.
Are you okay?
Do you like it?
I like it very much.
Your tongue is sticking out.
It's amazing.
Do you like it?
I like it very much.
You're good.
Really?
It's amazing.
Are you okay?
Don't tell anyone.
It's amazing.
I'm sweating a lot.
I told you it wasn't good.
It was the best.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sorry.
It's embarrassing.
I'm curious.
Where are the other girls?
They're in the room over there.
In that room?
You can hear them, right?
I think they know.
It's embarrassing.
I see.