I'm tired.
The test was difficult.
It's not good.
I don't have a red dot.
I don't like it.
Shinji, did you come back?
Yes, I'm back.
Welcome back.
Are you okay now?
I'm fine.
You said you were going to the gym with a pool from tomorrow, right?
Yes, I said that.
So I bought a swimming suit.
Would you like to see it?
I'm fine.
Really?
Yes.
This is it.
What do you think?
Is it strange?
I don't think so.
I used to be in the swimming club when I was a student.
I haven't been in a swimming club for a long time.
I'm a little tired.
Do you have a stomachache?
I think so.
I want to train more.
I want to tighten my thighs.
I have a big butt.
I want to tighten it more.
I don't think it's okay.
I don't think so.
I want to train my arms.
I want to train my muscles.
I don't think so.
I want to train my muscles a little more.
I think it looks good on you.
Really?
Yes.
I used to be able to wear a smaller size of this swimsuit.
Is that so?
Yes.
I don't like this part.
Touch this part.
What?
This part.
I don't want to touch it.
Touch this part.
No.
Isn't it strange?
This part?
I don't think so.
Don't be shy.
We are brothers.
Look at this part.
This part is very soft.
I agree.
I want to tighten this part.
Tighten?
Yes.
I want to tighten this part more.
Do you want to tighten this part?
Yes.
I see.
I'm worried about your lower body.
I think this part is too soft.
What do you think?
Isn't it too soft?
I don't think so.
I want to tighten this part more.
I think this part is good.
I don't think so.
Touch this part.
What?
This part.
I don't want to touch it.
You will know if you touch it.
Excuse me.
This is dangerous.
I agree.
I have to do my best.
This is amazing.
This is dangerous.
I haven't exercised recently because I ate a lot.
This is amazing.
I have to do my best.
Please tell me what you think.
Okay.
This is not strange, is it?
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Thank you.
She was amazing.
I'm lucky to have her as my sister.
The test was dangerous.
I took the test in a hurry.
It's hot.
I'm tired.
SHINJI.
Yes.
Can I talk to you now?
I bought a new swimsuit.
Did you buy it again?
I want you to look at it.
I'm fine.
Thank you.
This is it.
This is...
What do you think?
Can you swim with this?
Yes.
Is it strange?
The color is different from the other day.
I don't know if it's strange.
What do you think?
The back is like this.
Did I do too much?
Is it strange?
It's amazing.
It's not strange.
Why did you buy it again?
I went to the gym.
Everyone other than me is wearing a flashy swimsuit.
Some people are foreigners.
Some people are weird.
Some people are wearing this kind of design.
That swimsuit was the most plain.
I bought it because I thought it would be better to wear this kind of swimsuit.
It's amazing.
I don't know.
It's my first time to wear such a flashy swimsuit.
Is it strange?
I think it looks good on you.
Really?
Yes.
I'm glad.
It's better to wear a flashy swimsuit.
I heard that if you train consciously, you will lose weight.
I was worried about this.
Is that so?
Yes.
I can't see the back at all.
What does it look like?
Did I eat too much?
Foreigners all look like this.
It's amazing.
Is it strange?
I'm conscious when people look at me like this.
It's amazing.
Foreigners in Ghibli movies were amazing.
I want to be like them.
It's amazing.
I have to work hard because I have to pay.
Shinji, what's wrong?
Shinji.
Shinji, don't.
Don't do that.
Shinji, what's wrong?
Shinji.
Shinji, don't do that.
Don't do that.
Shinji, what's wrong?
Shinji, don't do that.
I don't feel good.
Shinji.
Don't do that.
I don't feel good.
I'm sorry.
I can't help it if you look at my butt so closely.
Don't do that.
Koning, wake up.
Konami, wake up.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, I don't know
Ah yeah
Hmm
Oh, it's disgusting
Sweat
I'm in pain.
Ouch!
Sorry.
I'm in pain.
I can't breathe.
Ouch!
I'm in pain.
I can't breathe.
You're out of breath.
What did you do?
Let me in.
Wait a minute.
You attacked me.
Get well soon.
I'm in pain.
I feel good.
Are you okay?
Let's continue.
Let me in.
I'm in pain.
Help me.
I want you to move more.
I'm in pain.
I feel good.
I want to have a happier time.
I'm still fine, so I can do it.
I feel good.
I'm in pain.
One more time.
I feel good.
I like it.
I'm in pain again.
I'm sorry.
My swimsuit is dirty.
I think my old swimsuit is better.
I feel good.
I should run like this.
I have to run.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Masato-kun.
Come here.
Sit here.
Here?
Yes.
Look at this.
I bought this.
Is it a book about running?
Yes.
I bought this.
You bought this, didn't you?
Yes.
It looks good.
I have to run.
Did you read a lot?
Yes, I read a lot.
You said you wanted to run, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
I haven't exercised recently.
You don't have to run, do you?
I have to run because I'm hungry.
I don't think so.
I have to exercise.
Are you going to run?
Yes.
I'm going to run.
I think you are more normal than before.
I have a muscle in my arm.
Is that so?
I want to lose it.
As far as I can see, you don't have it.
I can see it if I touch it.
Is it easy for you to see it?
Yes.
Touch it.
I'm not a woman.
Touch it properly.
Properly?
I think it's just right.
You have a lot of muscles, don't you?
Like thighs.
Yes.
You have muscles, don't you?
But I don't know if it's okay.
You have a lot of muscles.
You are doing your best, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
I don't have enough exercise.
By the way, I bought a pair of running shoes.
Running shoes?
Yes.
That's good.
The weather is good now.
I'm going to run.
That's good for running.
Let's run together.
No, I'm fine.
Why?
I'm not good at running.
It's too thin.
That's right. It's too thin.
I can't run at all.
If it's too thin, it's cold in winter.
That's right.
I can't run any more.
I'm going to change my clothes and run.
Okay.
I'm going to change my clothes.
I'm going back to my room.
Okay.
How long should I run today?
It's been a while since I exercised.
I'm going to buy some snacks.
I'm tired.
Are you okay?
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
Are you okay?
It's hot.
How long did you run?
I ran 2 km.
2 km?
2 km.
It's been a while since you ran, so you must be tired.
I ran too much.
It's hot.
I'm tired.
Are you okay?
It's hot.
My legs are swollen.
Are you okay?
I'm tired.
Did you run while stretching?
I didn't.
You'll get hurt.
I'm tired.
I can't walk anymore.
Are you okay?
I'm tired.
Give me your shoulder.
My shoulder?
Is that all?
I can't walk.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm going.
It's hot.
I'm alive.
You ran too much.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm tired.
I got a cramp in my leg.
Give me a massage.
Massage?
Massage.
Okay.
Hurry up.
Are you okay?
I'm sweating a lot.
It's hot.
I'm tired.
Do you want me to stretch your legs?
Yes.
It feels good.
Not just the back of your legs.
A little higher.
Higher?
Around there.
The calf.
It feels good.
You're good at massaging.
Really?
Do it a little higher.
Higher?
A little higher.
Around the thigh.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
Doesn't it hurt?
No.
It feels good.
Maybe I made a mistake in pace 5.
I thought I could do more.
I didn't exercise enough.
Are you listening to me?
Yes.
Really?
It feels good.
I'm done. Thank you.
It felt good.
It feels good.
Look around your chest.
You're sweating a lot.
You've been drooling recently.
Look at me.
You're sweating a lot.
It hurts a lot.
Running makes you sweat.
You're fine.
You're sweating a lot.
I want to keep running.
It seems to have a good effect.
I sweat a lot.
Look at me.
If you exercise too much, you'll be like today.
You're right.
Please be careful.
I have to be careful.
I suddenly started to sweat.
As Masato said, I have to exercise properly.
I'm sweating a lot.
Let's run together next time.
Okay.
Wait.
Masato.
What's wrong?
Wait.
Masato.
What are you doing?
Wait.
Masato.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Masato, do it too.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You're
Not good
Entirely
More.
Ah! Ugh!
Ah, ah, ah...
Ah, ah ...
Ah..
Ah, ah..
Ah...
Ah, ah, ah...
Ah aaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Ahhhhhhhhh
Ahah, ah, ah, ah...
I've had enough...
Ah, ah, ah my ears, my ears
G…
t…
I…
h…
knew…
he's…
not…
such…
a…
a boss…
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17,18,19,20,21,22,23,24,25,26,27,28,29,30,31,32,33,34,35,36,37,38,39,40,40,41,42,42,43,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44
44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44,44
Ouch!
It feels good.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Oh!港
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! matter
Oh no, oh no.
You don't have to.
You don't.
A slith…
AHHHHH
AH
OHHHH
Pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant,
pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant,
Why....
Takashi-kun, can you hold this for me?
Ah, yes.
Takashi-kun,
why don't you do some exercise?
Ah, yes.
Takashi-kun, why don't you do some exercise?
That's right.
If you have muscles, you'll be popular with girls.
Ah, yes.
You did a lot today, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
How much did you do? About 20 times?
Yes, more than usual.
How is it?
I think you have muscles now.
Touch here.
Around here.
Ah, yes.
How is it?
That's right.
Around here.
Can you touch here a little more?
Ah, yes.
It's better than before, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Compared to the first time.
That's right.
It's effective, isn't it?
It's getting harder.
That's right. Around here.
Ah, yes.
How is it?
It's very hard.
That's right.
I want to do more around here.
Touch here.
You still have muscles here, don't you?
Where?
Around here.
Ah, yes.
You don't have muscles yet, do you?
It's still difficult to train muscles here.
That's right.
I see.
Do you want to go to a gym or a yoga class?
Ah, you are thinking about it so much.
You have Takashi with you now, so you can help each other at home.
It's good to do it together, but I think you can't do it at home.
That's right.
It's good to be brothers.
Isn't it better to have a cool sister?
Ah, that's right.
That's right.
I think it's better to learn something.
Then, why don't you go with Takashi?
What?
Together?
Yes, let's go to learn together.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Are you?
I think it's fun.
Isn't it easier to go together?
But I've been alone all the time, so I'm a little embarrassed.
I think it's okay to stay like this.
I see.
I think it's good to go together.
I think I'll change more if I go with Takashi.
But you have a soft waist now.
Ah, yes.
I think you have a soft waist.
I think you are flexible.
Yes.
It's very good.
It's important to have a good butt to show your style.
Ah, yes.
I want to train your overall body.
Yes.
Actually, I've done a lot of research.
I'm looking for a gym I want to go to.
Ah, I see.
I have time tomorrow.
I'm thinking of going sightseeing.
Ah.
If you feel good, I'll tell you my impression tomorrow.
Ah, yes.
I see.
I went sightseeing.
Ah, yes.
I thought everyone was amazing.
A female trainer talked to me.
She asked me if I wanted to join her.
Ah, yes.
I couldn't do push-ups.
But she taught me how to do it.
I could do it somehow.
Ah, yes.
She was very cool.
She had great muscles.
So, I wanted to join her.
Ah, I see.
If I learn from her, I'll have better muscles.
She was very cool.
She was good at teaching.
It was easy to understand.
Ah, yes.
I think it's good.
I think so, too.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
By the way, I found a recommended gym wear.
It looked good, so I bought it.
Would you like to see it?
Ah, yes.
The trainer who said you were cool was wearing the same gym wear.
Yes.
It looked good on you.
So, I thought it was good.
What?
The trainer looked good on you.
So, I decided to buy it.
Ah, yes.
It's great.
It's a foreign brand.
Ah, yes.
So, foreign celebrities and trainers are wearing it.
Isn't it cool?
Ah, yes.
So, I bought it.
Isn't it good?
I think it's good.
It's good.
I can see your body line well.
And your legs are amazing.
I can see your body line very well.
Isn't it great?
It's great.
And if you wear it like this, it will be fixed well.
I'm glad I bought it.
Isn't it good?
It's cool, isn't it?
Ah, yes.
It's great, isn't it?
When I went to the gym, I thought it was different from doing it at home.
So, I thought I should go there.
It's good to be taught.
It's easy to understand.
It's interesting that I can do what I can't do.
If you don't do it in a proper way, you can't get muscles.
So, I thought it was worth paying a monthly fee just to be taught.
That's right.
It's good.
You don't have a boyfriend now.
You've been training.
You've got muscles.
You look cool.
You've met someone at the gym.
I thought it was great.
That's right.
I think it's going to be fun.
I'm going to meet a lot of people.
I'm looking forward to it.
That's right.
To be honest, I was going to change my school.
I'm not sure if I'm going to change my school.
I think it's going to be fun.
What are you doing?
Takahashi, what are you doing?
That's great.
Mino.
I'm sorry.
Yonatan.
I found something wrong on the back.
Ouch!
Ah!
Oh!
Ouch!
Too much pain!
Oh!
Ah!
Ouch!
Why?
And dust darkens the Seoul sky.
Still, the baby is tightly swallowed and doesn't move.
He can'tOOO
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can't stand it anymore.
Do you want to go?
It's hot.
Do it again.
Do it harder.
It's hot.
Don't stop.
Do it again.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Do it again.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
I went to the gym and came back.
If you do something bad with Takashi, you'll sweat so much that you'll be the ultimate body.
Let's do this secretly from now on.
Yes.
Let's do it more.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's really fun to watch celebrity gossip.
What kind of gossip will come next?
I'm looking forward to it.
Masakado?
Welcome back.
Can I come in?
Yes.
It was heavy.
What is that bag?
What do you think?
It looks good on you.
Actually,
I registered for a delivery part-time job.
A part-time job?
Yes.
So, I'm going to start from today.
That's good.
I bought cycling clothes.
But, I think it's too formal.
I went to buy it a while ago.
I thought I didn't have to do it formally because it's a delivery part-time job.
But, it's better to start from the shape.
Besides, you'll be on a diet.
That's right.
You said you wanted to exercise.
Yes.
So, I thought I'd start from the shape.
I bought a formal one.
What do you think?
Does it look good on me?
I think it looks good on you.
Really?
It's hard to go to the gym.
It's good to exercise at work.
Don't you think so?
I think so, too.
So, I'm going to start from the shape.
Good luck.
Anyway,
I'm worried about your muscles around here.
You look better when you have muscles around here, don't you?
I think it's good enough.
No, it's not true.
You look chubby.
By the way,
I'm going to make you slimmer.
Touch me.
It'll make you slimmer later.
Masakazu and I
finally became brothers.
You don't have to worry about it.
You look better when you have muscles around here, don't you?
Touch me.
Where?
You have muscles around here.
It's going to be like this.
I see.
You look better when you have muscles around here, don't you?
What I'm worried about the most is here.
It's hard to lose muscles around here.
I think so, too.
I think it's hard to lose muscles around here.
I think it's hard to lose muscles around here, too.
You have a lot of muscles around here.
I'm going to make you slimmer.
I see.
You look better when you have muscles around here, don't you?
You can introduce your muscles to your friends.
I think so, too.
You want to show off your beautiful muscles, don't you?
I see.
I'm going to go now.
I'm going to cheer up.
Masakazu, please cheer up for me.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
I'm going to go.
Don't forget your size.
I touched your arms and legs.
You were very soft.
This idol...
This idol was having a party with a strange politician.
I was shocked.
I was cheering for this idol with my fans.
I'm home.
Are you okay?
I'm tired.
I can't move my legs.
I can't work overtime.
I heard it's good for exercise.
That's not exercise.
It's better to go to the gym.
Is it that hard?
You should try it.
You know how I feel.
Your legs got thicker.
Was it that hard?
Kazuko.
Can you massage my legs?
I can't.
My thighs are painful.
Where is painful?
It hurts.
Can I massage it harder?
Is it that hard?
It's so hard.
It hurts.
It's okay.
Can you massage my thighs?
It hurts.
You're good at massaging.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
Thank you, Kazuko.
My legs feel better.
It's hot.
Look at my sweat.
It's like sauna.
I get sunburned if I sweat like this every time.
Isn't it amazing?
I'm sweating a lot.
I can't stop sweating.
Can I sleep here?
I can't move.
I can't stand up.
Masakazu.
Can I lie down here?
Yes.
I'm tired.
I'll get injured if I walk.
I don't have to go tomorrow.
I don't have to go every day.
But, my mom says I have to go.
I'm tired of going to restaurants.
What should I do next?
I'll look for a job again.
I'm not good at job interviews.
I was going to work on the job interview.
I started to deliver a new one.
What should I do next?
Masakazu?
Hey, what are you doing?
Wait, wait, wait.
Hey, hey.
Hey, wait a minute.
Stop it.
Hey, wait.
Hey, are you kidding me?
Hey, what are you doing?
Wait, wait, wait.
Hey, you're kidding me.
Hey, hey.
You can't do that.
Stay away from me.
Hey, you can't do that.
You can't do that.
Hey, hey.
Nozomi, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I forgot what to do.
I'm sorry.
Hey, hey.
Hey, what's wrong?
It's your fault.
What's wrong?
Give me your hand.
It's okay.
It's not a big deal.
You did it first.
Stop it.
It's ticklish, isn't it?
Yes.
Please lick my hand.
It's ticklish.
Are you okay?
It's because of me, isn't it?
It's ticklish.
I can't stop.
It feels good.
It's ticklish.
It tickles.
I'm feeling sick.
You went to the bathroom, didn't you?
It's ticklish.
Can you still do it?
It tickles.
Excuse me.
Why are you rubbing?
Do you still want to go?
May I?
It tickles.
May I rub?
HEAVY BREATHING
EXHAUSTED
I said I could call me
I told you to run away.
I'm the one who told you to run away.
It's amazing.
I slept a lot.
I'm sweating a lot.
What's going on?
Does your leg hurt?
Your back was swollen.
Don't play pranks on me.
Do you want me to play pranks on you every day?
That's what you want, right?
Is that so?
I feel like I'm a little late when I play pranks on you.
Don't you think I'm a little late?
That's right.
I feel like I'm a little late.
I see.
From now on, let's play pranks on me every day.
Is it okay to play pranks on you every day?
Of course.
It was easy.