What are you doing?
Of course, I'm studying.
Why are you studying?
Well, the test is coming up soon, so...
I'm studying.
Are you studying for the test?
Well, of course.
You don't have to, do you?
No, it's pretty important.
My life is on the line.
Isn't that a bit too much?
Yeah, it is.
I don't know what kind of test you're going to take.
I don't know either.
Yeah.
I don't know what kind of test you're going to take.
It's not like I'm studying.
I'm sure you'll get good grades if you study.
What do you mean, your life is on the line?
Are you going to college?
Well, and then I'll get a job.
Are you going that far?
Well, just in case.
You don't have to go to college.
It won't change.
Is that so?
I think it will change.
I'm just going to hang out.
Well, it depends on the person.
I see.
What do you think?
Well, let's hang out.
It's okay to hang out.
What do you mean, it's okay?
I'm busy right now.
You're busy right now?
Aren't you studying?
Let's hang out.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Let's hang out.
It won't melt.
It will melt.
It's like this.
It won't melt.
It's okay.
Like this.
Wait.
I have to open it first.
You're nervous.
It's okay.
Don't you often see my boobs?
No, I don't.
What are you looking at?
I can see that you're a girl.
Isn't it because of my hair?
I don't think so.
I look at your boobs a lot.
You said the same thing at the beginning.
I made a mistake.
You couldn't concentrate.
No, I didn't.
You're not free. Study.
I'm studying.
You're looking at my boobs, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Can you see my boobs?
No, I can't.
I saw it.
You said you'd see it.
I'll see it once.
You can see my fingers.
Fingers?
No.
It's okay.
Is it okay?
You can see it.
It's okay.
What's that reaction?
It's not good.
You don't have a girlfriend, do you?
I'll leave it to your imagination.
I think so.
What about your experience?
Don't worry about it.
I'm doing something important.
What are you talking about?
It's really important.
Can I come in?
Yes.
I'm coming in.
You're studying, aren't you?
Yes.
You're not bothering her, are you?
No, I'm not.
Really?
I was watching you.
I've never seen you study.
Are you okay?
You're not bothering her, are you?
To be honest...
What are you talking about?
You're not bothering her, are you?
You're saying you're bothering her, aren't you?
You're not, are you?
No, I'm not.
Get away from her.
I'm sorry I'm bothering you.
I'm studying seriously.
Eri, apologize to her.
I'm sorry.
You're making fun of me.
Look.
Did you see that?
What?
Mamoru's eyes.
Did you see my panties?
No, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
I'm sure you did.
No, I didn't.
You did.
No one's looking at your panties.
What are you talking about?
I'm sure you did.
No, I didn't.
You did.
You're making fun of me.
Are you studying seriously?
Yes, I am.
Thank you.
I'm on your side.
Eri, don't bother me.
I'm sure you're not looking at my panties.
No, I'm not.
Did you eat a lot?
No, I just stretched my neck.
Did you stretch your neck?
Yes.
Does your neck hurt?
Don't make fun of me.
Mamoru doesn't play with me at all.
Mamoru, you're an exam student.
There's no way someone who's not taking the exam this year is making fun of you.
That's right.
Mamoru, you're a good boy.
You say hello to me.
You help me.
I say hello to you, too.
You don't say hello to me.
Mamoru, you're a good boy.
Don't do that, Eri.
I don't want to.
You're making fun of me.
I'll call you sister.
Then call me sister.
Mamoru.
Call me sister.
Wait a minute.
I'm scared.
I'm going to the bathroom.
What's that?
Mamoru, you're embarrassed.
I'm not embarrassed.
Don't make fun of me.
I'm studying hard.
You're not studying yet, are you?
I'm studying a difficult subject.
Why are you here?
I'm going to get a shoulder massage.
Why?
I have a big boob.
That's why I have a stiff shoulder.
Then you should go to a professional massage therapist.
Don't say that.
If you give me a massage, I'll massage your boob.
It's okay.
You want to massage my boob, don't you?
That's not true.
It's okay.
Give me a massage.
If you give me a massage, I'll go out.
Please.
Just a little?
Just a little.
Like this?
Yes, like that.
You're good.
Am I good?
Yes, you are.
Like this.
You don't pay attention to me.
I'm studying.
You're boring.
You're studying math.
I'm not boring.
You're not good at math.
Math is important for science.
I see.
You should study physics rather than math.
There are few competitors.
I see.
But I want to study math.
I'll teach you next time.
Math is difficult.
You think I'm stupid, don't you?
No, I don't think so.
When I took the entrance exam, my parents got divorced.
So I couldn't study at all.
I won't tell you, but I can't study at all.
What?
Is that true?
I told you the other day.
I told you that you were wrong.
I see.
I told you.
I feel good.
I've improved a lot since before the exam.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Shall we study?
Study?
Massage?
If you give me a massage, I'll give you a massage.
No, it's okay.
It's a waste.
I don't have a chance.
What are you doing?
What?
I don't have a chance.
Is it your first time?
No, it's my first time.
Is that so?
Is it your first time?
No, it's my first time.
I'm a little scared because you're too serious.
You're excited, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Really?
What are you doing?
Isn't it big?
What is it?
Is it this big?
It's as big as my fingers.
It's amazing.
Show me.
I can't.
Why?
Show me.
Wait a minute.
It's amazing.
It's this big.
What are you doing?
Why do you think it's this big?
I'm touching your boobs.
Is that all it takes to get this big?
What if I just touched your boobs and it got this big?
Can I change this?
I can't.
It's dangerous.
Where are you going in that outfit?
Put on your underwear.
Mamoru, what are you doing?
It's the third day you haven't slept.
What?
You don't look well. What's wrong?
I don't look well.
Do you have a fever?
I don't have a fever.
Then what is it?
Do you have a problem?
No.
Then why don't you go to school?
Then let's go somewhere.
Let's go play.
The weather is nice.
I don't mind.
You don't mind?
It's better to play when you're depressed.
No.
Do you want to go to karaoke?
I'll buy you a drink.
How about bowling?
That's not a treat.
Then let's go play.
No.
You don't feel well?
Why?
You have a problem, don't you?
It's not a problem.
It's something like that.
Something like that?
Something like a problem?
It's a problem.
I don't think I can do anything if I talk to you.
You'll never know if you don't talk to me.
It's okay.
I'll listen to you.
Tell me.
Don't tell anyone.
Okay.
I'll listen to you.
You'll laugh at me.
It's okay.
I won't laugh at you.
You have a problem, don't you?
A little.
A little?
You can't go to school for three days?
Go to school.
You won't laugh at me?
I won't laugh at you.
Are you sure?
Then I'll tell you.
A boy at school laughed at me because I was the only virgin.
So I took a break.
Wait.
Were you worried about that?
You're laughing.
Leave it alone.
Don't leave it alone.
You're the only virgin.
Were you a virgin?
Well...
You should have told me from the beginning.
I'm embarrassed.
Why are you embarrassed?
You laughed a little.
Leave it alone.
You're the only virgin.
Get out.
I have a solution.
A solution?
It's funny, so I'll make you do it.
What?
So I'll make you do it.
Isn't that the solution?
But...
Graduation...
I don't mind.
Then you won't be bullied.
Isn't it good?
I can graduate.
It's funny, so I don't mind.
Can I do it?
It's the first time for you, isn't it?
I'll teach you everything.
I don't want to do it.
You should graduate.
I touched you the other day.
You wanted to do this, didn't you?
Is it really okay?
It's okay.
I'm worried about you.
Thank you.
What do you want to do?
I want to do what's not on my clothes.
Like this?
Or this?
Here you are.
Is it amazing?
I'll try it.
Can I touch you?
You're graduating today, aren't you?
Really?
I'll teach you everything.
Thank you.
I touch here, too.
How should I touch you?
Touch me like this.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll pinch you a little more.
It doesn't hurt, does it?
It doesn't hurt.
Because it feels good.
It's not just touching.
It feels good to lick you.
Can I lick you?
I'll touch you a little more.
Like this?
It feels good.
I'll touch you.
I'll touch you on the other side, too.
It doesn't hurt, does it?
It doesn't hurt.
It feels good.
You're shaking a lot.
I'm shaking.
What else?
Are you going down?
That's fast.
Is there anything else?
Can I touch you?
It's not there.
It's around here.
It feels good.
Like this?
It feels good to touch you in the basement.
In the basement?
Can I touch you?
You can.
It's easy to understand, isn't it?
That's right.
It feels good.
Can I touch you a little more?
It feels good here, too.
It feels better here.
You're getting used to it.
That's right.
Is there anything else?
Here?
That's right.
It's in the right direction.
Like this?
It feels good.
That's right.
Is there any more information you know?
Information I know?
Do you want me to lick you?
That's right.
Wait a minute.
Like this?
That's right.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You can do it.
That's good.
It feels good when you put your fingers together.
Fingers?
That's right.
Put your fingers in.
Like this.
And lick.
That's right.
It feels good.
More.
Do it more.
It feels good.
It hurts.
You're good at licking a girl.
You're good at it.
I'm glad.
Are you glad?
What do you want to do next?
Next?
What should I do?
Do you want me to look at your butt?
That's great.
It's soft.
Do you have a lot of things you want to say?
That's great.
It's wet.
Can I take this off?
That's great.
Can I put my fingers in this state?
That's good.
I'm glad.
That's great.
I'll do it for you next.
Do you want to take off your panties?
Don't do that.
I'll do it for you.
That's great.
Does it feel good?
It's the first time you've been licked, isn't it?
That's right.
Don't do that.
That's great.
It feels good here, doesn't it?
Can I lie down?
That's great.
You've never been licked here, have you?
I haven't.
Does it feel good?
That's great.
Do you like it here?
That's right.
Doesn't your finger hurt?
That's fine.
That's great.
I'll take it off for you.
You're getting bigger.
That's great.
You can see it well, can't you?
Raise your legs.
Like this?
That's right.
Does it feel good here?
That's great.
It makes a nasty sound, doesn't it?
That's right.
You're getting bigger.
Is that so?
That's great.
I'll do my best.
Does it feel good?
That's great.
Do you want to try it?
Is that okay?
Come here.
It's hot.
You can put your finger in.
Is that okay?
I don't know where to put my finger.
Put your finger in there.
Can I put my finger in here?
Can I do it?
You can do it.
It's your first time.
You don't know if you don't put your finger in.
Put your finger in.
Where?
Put your finger in here.
Excuse me.
You're big.
I put my finger in here.
How do you feel?
Does it feel good?
That's great.
I put my finger in here.
Move your hand.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
It's already out.
Let me see.
I feel like it's flowing.
It's out.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Is this okay?
I'll do it again.
I'll do my best.
Does it feel good?
Can you still move?
I'll do my best.
Does it feel good?
That's right.
Can you still move?
It hurts.
You did too much.
It feels good.
What is this?
That's amazing.
I'm sorry.
I'm sweating again.
What's next?
Can you do it?
I'll try it.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
What is this?
If I make a loud voice, someone might find out.
Please refrain.
I'm sorry.
You should change your posture.
What?
I'll move up for you.
Like this?
You're sweating.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't say it so easily.
It's not over yet.
I'll do my best.
Please tell me if you feel pain.
What do you say?
I'm sorry.
It's not over yet.
Did you bear with it?
I did.
You can bear with it.
I want to move up for you.
I'll do my best.
I have to do this.
You're sweating a lot.
It feels good.
I can still go on.
It hurts.
I want to go on.
It feels good.
I'll go on.
Please bear with it.
I'm sorry.
I'll go on.
I'm tired.
I'm scared.
I'm sweating.
I'm tired.
Please put your hair on.
My hair?
I'll do my best.
Please put your hair on.
I'm tired.
It's dangerous.
I'm sorry.
It's not difficult.
Next, put your hair on your face.
Do you understand?
I'll do my best.
I'm tired.
Did you feel good?
You'll be cool tomorrow.
How are you doing with your mother?
We get along well.
She's good at cooking.
She's kind.
She's nice to me.
How are you doing with KENTA?
We get along well.
I'm not avoiding you.
I can teach you how to study.
I can't teach you how to study.
But you're my senior.
What should I teach you?
I don't know.
Are you okay?
That's not my business.
It's important, but it's hard to be careful if you have money.
You'd better play while you're young.
In other words, it's equivalent to having experience.
You cheated on your father and got married to his wife.
Dad is playing with you.
Anyway, your father has a girlfriend and KENTA is an examinee.
I don't want you to get in my way.
I'm just being cute.
It's fine.
Don't get in my way.
You're cute.
Kenta-kun.
Come here for a second.
Come here.
I...
It's fine.
I just came to get something to drink.
Come here.
We're family.
We had a good conversation just now.
Is that so?
Yes.
Don't get in my way.
I'm just being cute.
You're cute.
You're my cute little brother.
You're close.
I was studying.
I'm thirsty.
I came to get something to drink.
Yes.
See?
I told you so.
It's fine.
You're in trouble, aren't you?
I'm not in trouble.
It's a skinship.
We're family.
It's natural to be cute.
You're cute.
You're in trouble, aren't you?
I'm not in trouble.
Besides, you'd be happy if your sister did this to you, wouldn't you?
Of course I'd be happy.
You're in trouble.
I don't hate it.
You're studying hard.
You're going to lose your mind.
I'm not.
I'm just embarrassed because you're cute.
I'm embarrassed.
Kenta-kun, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You're my daughter.
We've been living together for half a year.
How can I say this?
What?
You're getting better, aren't you?
I'm getting better.
You're surprised.
I'm not surprised.
I'm always like this.
Why are you nervous?
You're nervous because I'm in front of you.
Don't be nervous.
I'm telling you to be a man.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm sorry, Kenta-kun.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to sleep, too.
What?
Kenta-kun.
You were looking at my underwear, weren't you?
What are you talking about?
What's that?
What's wrong with your underwear?
Why did you make it so big?
Look at my underwear.
What's wrong with it?
It's dirty.
Is it okay for an examinee to do that?
It's okay.
Is it okay?
Hey.
Is it okay for an examinee to do that?
What are you doing?
What do you want to study?
Do you want to study this?
I'll ask my father.
It's okay.
It's a physical contact.
Right?
What's wrong with this?
What's this?
I want to see this.
Let me see this.
It's okay.
What's wrong with this?
It's not okay.
You said you wanted to study this.
What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
Did you have a physical contact again?
No, I didn't.
Really?
I forgot about it.
Anyway, don't be so clingy.
Why?
You said you were an examinee.
I'm just being cute.
Let me concentrate.
You're cute.
Kenta.
Come here.
My legs are tired.
Can you give me a massage?
Massage?
Massage.
I don't know how to do it.
It's okay.
I can do it.
I came here to look for a mechanical pencil.
Just do it.
I don't know how to do it.
It's okay.
You can do it.
Hurry up.
You have to do what I say.
Okay.
Here.
What are you doing?
Haven't you done this before?
It's my first time.
What?
It's my first time to give a massage.
What are you talking about?
Do your best.
You can do it.
It feels good.
Yes, it feels good.
Keep doing it.
It feels good.
Is it done?
Keep doing it.
Why did you stop?
I heard a strange voice.
It's okay.
It feels good.
Did it hurt?
Keep doing it.
Why did you react like that?
Because...
Are you a virgin?
What?
Why did you react like that?
Are you serious?
Are you a virgin?
It's disgusting.
Don't laugh.
You've never used it.
Stop it.
I don't use it.
It's disgusting.
I don't want you to use it.
I'll make you a good man.
It's okay.
No.
I'll make you a good man.
You want me to make you a good man, don't you?
You can't be a good man.
I'm a student.
I don't have to be a good man.
I don't have to study.
How long do you want to be a virgin?
It's up to me.
Do you think you can be a good man?
Your life will end if you don't be a good man.
You should have listened to me.
It's okay.
I'll make you a good man.
You're a virgin, aren't you?
It's okay.
I have a girlfriend.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Yes.
I had a girlfriend last month.
You're a virgin, aren't you?
I may be a virgin now.
You can't be a good man.
I'll graduate from here.
When?
I don't know when.
I'll graduate from here.
You can't be a good man.
It's okay.
I'll teach you how to be a good man.
I can do it myself.
You don't have to teach me.
You don't have to teach me?
I can do it.
You should wait for me.
You should do it.
You can do it, can't you?
I'll do it if I can.
I'll teach you how to be a good man.
It's okay.
What if you fail?
Your girlfriend will hate you.
I'll teach you how to be a good man.
You can do it if you do it with your girlfriend.
It's okay.
Did you kiss her?
What?
I'll do it from now on.
You didn't kiss her?
I haven't done it yet.
You haven't done it?
Hmm.
You closed your eyes.
You thought I would do it, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
What are you expecting?
I didn't expect you to do it.
Did you expect me to kiss you?
No, I didn't.
That's enough.
He's so lame.
Hey, Kenta.
Don't you go to school?
Why are you looking at me like that?
You haven't gone to school for three days.
I'm fine.
Are you sick?
No, I'm not.
I'm fine.
What?
You're an examiner, aren't you?
Are you okay?
I'll be fine.
You'll be fine?
What are you doing at home instead of going to school?
Are you skipping school?
No, I'm not.
Do you want to go somewhere with me?
No, I'm not in the mood.
You're not in the mood?
What happened?
Tell me.
What?
It's not a big deal.
What is it? Tell me.
What?
Are you depressed?
I have a girlfriend.
You have a girlfriend?
What happened?
What?
How should I put it?
I got it.
You were dumped.
You weren't dumped.
I wasn't dumped.
Then, what happened?
You were dumped, weren't you?
I wasn't dumped.
What?
Well...
It's annoying.
You know what I'm like, don't you?
Well...
I didn't do well.
What?
You didn't do well?
Well...
You're mean.
What?
I told you.
I'm not laughing.
See?
You're mean.
Hey.
It's nothing.
I told you.
I told you I wouldn't be able to do it.
I told you I'd give you a training fee.
You should have listened to me.
Well...
So, it's okay.
So, that's why you didn't go to school?
Because you couldn't graduate as a virgin?
You were depressed?
Well...
Hey.
Wait, wait.
That's why you didn't go to school?
Well...
If that's the case, you should have told me earlier.
I'll do something about it.
What?
I'll let you graduate as a virgin.
What do you mean?
If you graduate as a virgin, you can go to school, right?
Well...
Then, you should graduate as a virgin.
Graduate as a virgin?
Yes.
You said you couldn't do it because of your girlfriend.
So, I should teach you how to do it, right?
Teach me how to do it?
Yes.
Well...
Really?
Yes.
Then, you'll go to school?
You're teasing me again, aren't you?
No.
I'm serious this time.
I...
What?
You teased me last time.
Did you believe me?
So, I'll let you graduate as a virgin.
Thank you.
I've never dated a virgin before.
So, I think it'll be interesting.
Interesting?
Yes.
I'm serious.
I'm serious, too.
But, I don't know what it's like to be a virgin.
So, I think it'll be interesting.
That's why I said yes.
Well...
Yes.
Why are you kissing me?
Because it's the first time.
Because it's the first time?
Well...
We're brothers.
Right?
I know everything about you.
Give me a kiss.
Okay.
Have you ever kissed me like this?
How do you feel now?
My body is getting warm.
Is your body getting warm?
Your body is getting warm, isn't it?
Your body is getting warm just by kissing me, right?
Right?
See?
You're getting warm just by kissing me.
Because it's the first time.
But, you still don't know much about your body.
So, I'll teach you.
Okay.
How about here?
Is it weak, Kenta?
My heart is beating fast.
Is your heart beating fast?
Yes.
So, you feel good here, don't you?
Right?
I feel good.
Do you like here?
Yes.
Have you ever touched here?
No.
No?
What about you?
Don't you touch here?
I don't touch here.
Your nipple.
Can I take off the towel in the middle?
Bye-bye.
Here you are.
Lie down here.
Good boy.
It's weak here, isn't it?
Kenta.
Right?
It's good.
You got used to it, didn't you?
My heart is beating fast.
I can feel it here.
My body...
What?
My body reacts to it.
Does your body react to it?
How can I make your body react to it?
What do you like?
Hey.
Let's lick together.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
It's good to be licked, isn't it?
Bye-bye.
I've been licking you for a while.
Chinchin.
You got used to it.
It feels good.
You have an honest body.
You're standing on the desk.
Yes.
It's a waste to go here.
I'm worried about you.
Do you want to touch me?
Yes.
How do you feel?
It's very soft.
Do you want to touch me directly?
Is it okay?
You don't know if I don't touch you directly, do you?
You've never seen my chest, have you?
Yes.
It's good to be licked.
It's good.
How do you feel?
Your boobs.
It feels good.
It's good.
Don't you want to be buried by my boobs?
Can't you breathe?
One more time.
You like it.
Do you like boobs?
Yes.
You like boobs.
Do you want to lick me?
Yes.
How do you feel about my nipples?
Is it getting harder?
It's getting harder.
Do you want to lick me?
Yes.
Roll your tongue.
Don't kiss me.
Can you do it?
You're already into it.
Do you like my boobs?
Yes.
It's good.
You like my boobs, don't you?
More.
You've been licking my boobs.
Here.
What's this?
I like it.
It's broken.
What's this?
You can't stand it.
Where does this hit?
Here.
You know about my boobs.
Look.
Your nipples and my boobs.
You've been licking them.
Why?
Because you've been licking them.
I know.
I can't stand it.
You can't stand it?
I'll take it off for you.
What's this?
I don't like it.
What are you wearing?
What's this?
You're pathetic.
Let's go shopping with me.
I'll buy you cool pants.
I can't do it alone.
I'll buy them for you.
Thank you.
You should wear cool pants.
I'm going to graduate today.
I'm going to graduate.
I don't need these pants.
Take them off.
Why are you so serious?
I can't stand it.
How do you always do it?
Show me.
I do it like this.
Is it that slow?
Are you scolding me?
It's a little faster.
Show me.
How do you do it?
I see.
Show me.
I want to see it.
That's right.
Keep doing it.
What?
It's a side dish, isn't it?
I'm taking it off for you.
You're excited to see your sister's body, aren't you?
Stand up.
I'm going to do it differently today.
You always do it like this, don't you?
How do you do it?
First of all, you have to get used to it.
If you don't, you can't put it in the closet.
You have to get used to all kinds of stimuli.
Show me.
What?
How about this?
Wait a minute.
Didn't you say you were going to graduate?
I want to graduate.
That's right.
You have to get used to these new stimuli.
It's amazing.
Hang in there.
Wait a minute.
What?
Hang in there.
No, no, no.
Did you push me up?
What are you doing?
I want to be wrapped in your breasts.
Wait a minute.
You can't do this.
Can't you hold it in?
You have a nice face.
You have a cute face.
Are you holding it in?
You have a nice face.
You have a cute face.
I understand.
This is a new stimulus, isn't it?
You're very energetic.
I didn't know it was this strong.
Are you underestimating me?
I'm not underestimating you.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
I've been waiting for you.
You haven't touched me yet, have you?
Don't you want to touch me?
I want to touch you.
All right.
Touch me.
You're a monkey.
It's my first time touching you.
What's going on?
Are you nervous?
Yes.
I got excited when you bullied me.
Really?
Your reaction was cute.
I'm so wet.
I'm hot.
Can you lick me?
Yes.
That's all I can do.
It's my first time.
Why are you so strong?
Can I lick you?
Like this?
That's right.
Lick me.
Can you do it well?
I can't do it well at first, but I can't help it.
Come on, come on, come on.
I'm going to shake you.
If you're so strong.
Don't you put your finger in it?
Put your finger in it.
If you do that, you'll put your finger in it.
Oh, my God.
Wow, you're tightening your fingers.
It's all the way in there.
It's all in here.
Do you understand?
Oh, my God.
You're all wet, aren't you?
Oh, no.
I'm going to get wet.
I'm wet.
So?
You're going to put it in here, aren't you?
Do you want to put it in yourself?
Or do you want me to put it in?
What are you going to do?
Don't you know how to put it in?
How should I do it?
I don't know.
Teach me.
I'll guide you.
All right.
I'll put it in.
Look at me.
Look, it's coming in.
Oh, no.
It's in.
Look.
Can you move it?
That's great.
It's like this.
You can move it.
Let's see.
Move your hips more.
That's right.
Move your hips to a comfortable place.
That's great.
You can do it.
Thank you.
Oh, no.
Why did you stop it?
What's wrong?
Is it too tight?
It's okay.
Can you do it?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Can you do it?
Can you move your hips?
Does it feel good?
It came out.
I'm sorry.
Did it come out?
It came out.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
I can't help it because it's my first time.
Is it okay?
You can move it as much as you want.
It's okay.
You're my brother, so it's okay.
Can you do it?
It's not enough yet.
I want to feel better, too.
You can do it, right?
No.
Move your hips.
Make me feel better.
Can you do it?
Do your best.
Does it feel good?
I can't help it.
Move your hips.
Can I move now?
I can't help it.
This is good, too.
Isn't it good to be able to move on your own?
It's totally different.
Can I do it quickly?
Quickly?
I can't help it.
You can't?
Do you want to do it slowly?
How about this?
I can't help it.
I can't be a good man.
Is it intense?
I'll do it slowly.
It feels good.
I can't help it.
What?
Does it feel good?
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
Did you let it out?
It's true.
Did you let it out again?
You're a lazy baby.
You can still do it, right?
I'm still not good enough.
I want you to do more.
I want to see you do it.
Is it intense?
I can't help it.
What?
I haven't done it yet.
I can't help it.
I'll do it this time.
You want to do a lot of things, right?
I'm doing it.
You're slow.
I'll do it this time.
You can do whatever you want.
That's good.
I'm starting to feel better.
That's amazing.
You can do it.
You did it.
Are you confident?
But it's not enough yet, is it?
Don't stop me.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
But...
Why don't you practice meeting us outdoors?
Go outside.
You're still sleeping, aren't you?
Can you do it?
You like this part, don't you?
You can touch it.
If you touch this part,
your teeth will be hard again.
What?
It's getting hard, isn't it?
Come on, touch it harder.
Give me a lot of your gums.
Oh, it feels good.
Give me your mouth.
All right.
I want your mouth.
Oh, my God.
Give me your mouth.
Give me a lot of your gums.
I'm sorry.
You have a lot of gums.
Oh, my God.
Did you feel good?
Yeah.
It felt really good.
You're glad you graduated, aren't you?
Yeah, I'm glad I graduated.
You should be grateful.
Can you go to school from tomorrow?
Yeah, I can go to school.
Then go to school from tomorrow.
Thank you so much.
You're such a cute brother.
All right, all right.
Yuko.
How's your job hunting going?
Job hunting?
I'm already doing it.
Are you doing it?
You don't look like you're doing it.
I'm already doing it.
Don't look forward to it.
It's okay.
I'm going to school.
I want you to get a job.
I'm sure you'll get a job somewhere.
Somewhere?
You don't have to worry about that.
I'm worried about you, too.
I don't mind.
You're so kind.
You don't have to be so sweet.
Don't worry too much.
I'm worried about you.
But it's too early.
It's been two years since I got into college.
It's too early.
You should have gone to a four-year college.
You could have played more.
I wanted you to go to a four-year college.
You couldn't, to be honest.
Why?
You're the worst.
My mom hates me for saying that.
Don't say that.
I see.
It's been three months since I got married to your mom.
How's it going with Tatsuya?
We're very close.
I'm glad to hear that.
But you have an exam this year.
I know.
Don't disturb me.
Tatsuya.
I was talking to you.
What?
How's your study going?
I'm studying well.
I'm not disturbing you.
We're good friends.
I see.
Are you concentrating on studying?
What?
I'm studying well.
I see.
Are you not disturbing me?
I'm not disturbing you.
I'm not.
I'm worried about you.
I want you to go to a good university.
I think so, too.
Right?
Yes, you're right.
I'm trying to go to a good university, unlike you.
You always say that.
No, no, no.
I don't want to talk about it.
You're noisy.
Tatsuya doesn't like it.
I don't like it.
I'm sorry.
You're noisy.
You're always noisy.
You're really noisy.
You're noisy.
You're a nuisance.
I'm sorry.
Tatsuya.
You're looking at my panties too much.
No, I'm not.
I don't think so.
You're always looking at my breasts and panties.
Are you a virgin?
No, I'm not.
You're a virgin.
I don't think so.
You're looking at my panties.
No, I'm not.
You're always looking at my panties.
You're really looking at my panties.
Come on.
We're still studying.
Excuse me.
Don't tease me.
It's funny how you react to it.
I'm a senior student.
I'm so nervous.
I don't think so.
You're always looking at my panties.
Hey, Tatsuya, you're a virgin, aren't you?
Your reaction was like a virgin.
You idiot.
Why?
You're definitely a virgin.
That's not what I'm saying.
Don't touch me if you feel like it.
Why?
It's funny.
Tatsuya.
Yes?
I'm coming in.
You're already in.
What are you doing?
I'm studying.
Math?
Yes.
Is there anything you don't know?
Something I don't know?
I'm not good at this area.
I remember this.
I know this.
Is that so?
I don't know.
I forgot.
I know.
You're doing something difficult.
Have you ever done this before?
I think so.
That's amazing.
Is the exam coming up soon?
Yes.
I have to study hard.
I see.
Tatsuya.
Yes?
You're looking at me.
What?
I'm not looking at you.
You are.
Right?
I'm not looking at you.
Are you really a virgin?
What are you doing?
You're cute.
I'm not a virgin.
You're a virgin, right?
You're right.
You're cute.
Stop it.
Do you like me?
I like you.
You like me.
Stop it.
You just said it.
By the way, do you have a boyfriend?
Boyfriend?
Of course I have one.
I have a girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
Do you have a girlfriend?
Yes.
Tatsuya, have you ever had a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
Because you're a virgin?
No, I'm not a virgin.
You're a virgin.
I just touched your nipples.
Your nipples are hard.
Look.
I can see your nipples.
What are you doing?
Why are you so excited?
No, I'm not.
Are you happy?
Your nipples are hard.
I'm sorry.
Why?
I need to go to the bathroom.
You're a virgin.
Tatsuya, I'm coming in.
What is it?
What happened?
I'm not feeling well.
Are you sick?
I have a stomachache.
Do you have a fever?
I'll go to school tomorrow.
Is there a reason you don't want to go to school?
Are you being bullied?
I'm not being bullied.
You don't have a fever.
Do you want to go somewhere with me?
I'm not in the mood.
You're not in the mood.
Are you bullying me?
Do you want me to beat you up?
Please don't do that.
I'm suspicious of you.
I'm not feeling well.
Are you being bullied?
Are you being bullied as a virgin?
What's that reaction?
No.
You can't be bullied as a virgin.
No one is a virgin at that age.
That's true.
Is it just me?
That's right.
Why are you depressed?
You're a virgin.
I'll do it for you.
What?
I haven't done it with a virgin for a long time.
Do you want to graduate as a virgin?
But...
You want to graduate, don't you?
I want to graduate.
If you graduate, you won't be bullied, will you?
That's right.
You don't hate it, do you?
I don't hate it at all.
That's good.
Let's do it.
Is this your first kiss?
Give me your tongue.
Tatsuya, give me your tongue.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
You kissed me.
Does your tongue feel good?
Give me your tongue.
I'm standing on my nipples.
Did you kiss me?
Do you like my nipples?
I'll touch your nipples.
I want you to touch my nipples directly.
It's amazing.
I didn't expect it to be like this.
I was surprised.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I'm out of my breath.
Are you out of your breath because it feels so good?
You're a pervert.
Do you like my nipples?
Does it feel good?
Do you want me to touch you more?
I'm standing on my nipples.
Do you want me to lick your nipples?
It's the first time you've licked my nipples.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
I'm very nervous.
Do you want me to lick your nipples?
I'll lick your nipples.
Does it feel good?
What do you want me to do next?
I'm standing on my nipples.
Do you want me to touch your nipples?
You wanted to touch my nipples, didn't you?
You've been looking at my nipples all this time.
Is it real?
It's very soft.
Is it soft?
Does it feel good?
You're very soft.
Do you want me to touch your nipples?
Look at my nipples.
It's the first time you've licked my nipples.
You can do whatever you want.
It's real.
How is it?
It's very soft.
I can't stand it anymore.
It feels good.
That's what you wanted to do.
Lick my nipples, too.
It feels good.
Do you want to look at my panties?
You saw my panties.
I'm sorry.
You can touch my nipples.
It's very warm.
It feels good.
I'm excited.
I can't stand it anymore.
Look at my nipples.
It's embarrassing to look at my nipples.
It's pink.
It's very beautiful.
How is it?
It's very sexy.
It feels good.
Lick my nipples more.
Do you like my nipples?
It feels good.
You are good at licking my nipples.
Your nipples are getting bigger.
I'm excited.
Are you excited?
Do you want to kiss me?
Do you want to sleep?
Do you want me to look at you?
It's embarrassing.
Is it embarrassing?
Does it feel good?
It's very different.
Do you want me to touch you directly?
Don't touch me.
I didn't know you had such a big nipple.
Your nipple is stained.
I haven't washed my clothes yet.
Why do you have such a big nipple?
How is it?
Do you want me to lick your nipple directly?
How about you?
You have a big nipple.
What's wrong with you?
Do you want me to lick your nipple?
It's amazing.
You have a big nipple.
Does it feel good?
How is it?
Your nipple is getting bigger.
Does it feel good?
Do you want me to lick your nipple?
Your nipple is moving.
Your nipple is getting bigger.
Does it feel good?
Do you want me to pinch your nipple?
I'll do it for you.
Come here.
Your nipple is getting bigger.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
Your nipple is getting bigger.
Do you like it?
I like it.
Does it feel good?
You like it.
I'll do it for you.
You like it, don't you?
How is it?
You can't do that.
Do you like rubbing your nipple like this?
How is it?
Does it feel good?
It's rubbing a lot.
You can't do that.
Do you want me to do it?
I'll do it for you.
Do you know where it is?
It's getting bigger.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
Is it warm?
It feels good.
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
Did I make you hungry?
You're eating something hot.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Did it feel good?
Let's do it again.
You can still do it.
It feels so good.
What's wrong?
I might be able to go again.
You're going to vomit?
It's okay.
I'm not going to vomit.
Lie down.
Hey, Toshi-chan.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Hey, I'm sad, so I'll go in.
Ah, it feels good.
Hey, Toshi-chan, does it feel good?
It feels good.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, I love you so much.
Ah, this is bad.
Hey, Toshi-chan, how do you feel?
I'm shaking.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, I love you.
This is bad.
Hey, Toshi-chan, are you alive?
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, this is bad.
Ah, this is amazing.
Hey, Toshi-chan, do you want to push my back?
Push my back.
Ah, it feels good.
Do you want to push my back like this?
Hey, how do you feel?
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, this is bad.
Ah, stop it.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, I love you.
Ah, this is bad.
Ah, stop it.
Ah, it feels good.
Do you want to do more?
Do you want to push my back?
Do you want to run away?
Here, here.
There is a lot of semen here.
Put it here.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, stop it.
Ah, this is bad.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, stop it.
Ahh pass over here
Ahh
It feels so good
I want to stand up
Hey don't stand here like that
It tickles
Ahh it tickles
Ah my neck feels so good
I'm feeling sick.
I'm sick.
I'm sorry.
I'm sick again.
I'll do it more.
Do you want me to do it more?
What?
Do you like this?
I like it.
Do you want me to do it more?
I'll do it more.
I'm sick.
I can't do it anymore.
I feel sick.
I'm sick.
Tsutsu!
Don't lick my face.
I was surprised.
You still have a lot of hair.
I didn't say you were cute.
Tetsu!
You can go to school with this.
You graduated from the same school as me.
How many times did you go to school?
You went to school a lot.
I'm getting used to it.
How was it?
It was the best.
I'm glad you graduated from the same school as me.
I felt good, too.
What did you do at school today?
I skipped school.
Is that okay?
School is boring.
You don't have to pay for school.
I'm working part-time, so I'll be fine.
It's okay.
I'm worried about you.
Why?
Why are you dressed up like that?
I'm cute.
You don't come home at night.
I enjoy playing.
I know.
It depends on the society.
Why don't you play when you're young?
I'm a student until I get a job.
You may not get a job.
Why?
Don't you come out of the house?
I'm working part-time.
I'll be fine.
I'll be fine if I get married.
Don't say that.
I'll be fine.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't have a boyfriend.
I have a boyfriend who plays.
That's why you're playing.
You made a mistake once.
It's a big mistake.
It's true.
It's not my fault.
You can't say that to other people.
I can't say that to other people.
I have a younger brother.
Do you behave like an older sister?
I'm a very older sister.
You can't be a good example.
Did you buy a birthday present for your mother?
No.
I'm going to buy it from now on.
What are you going to buy?
Why do you ask me that?
You don't have a good sense.
What are you talking about?
I'm your father.
What are you going to buy?
Don't say that.
I'm going to buy a flower.
Flower?
I don't need it.
Why?
I don't need it because it will wither.
It's okay because it will wither.
I'm watering it.
I think your mother will do it.
I don't do it.
You can water it once a day.
I don't need it.
I'm angry because I don't have a good sense.
Is it a hassle to water it?
I don't need it.
I don't have a good sense.
You don't have to water it.
I don't need such a simple present.
I want to give you a better present.
For example?
I want to give you an accessory.
I want to give you a necklace.
Brand?
You don't have a good sense.
I don't need it.
I'm going to water it again.
This is not good.
I don't need it?
You have a better present.
I don't need it.
I don't like the design.
Jun, sit down.
What is it?
You are choosing a present for Jun's mother.
That's right.
What do you like?
I like flowers.
I don't need flowers.
I'm telling you the same thing.
I don't need it.
You are always playing.
You don't have a good sense.
Do you want to give flowers to men?
I don't know.
You have more, don't you?
I don't have it.
You should keep it.
It will wither soon.
It's more like a memory than a thing.
Dad.
Do something about the ring that doesn't fit.
What?
You should buy her a ring.
A matching ring.
A ring.
What is it?
There are many things.
Isn't it too fat?
I should lose weight.
A ring.
What kind of ring do you want?
A simple one.
Isn't it bad?
This is different.
Only young people can wear it.
Old people can't wear it.
Why?
You are young.
I'm not young.
I'm an old man and an old woman.
I see.
Isn't it ugly to wear it?
It's too small.
You like it.
Is it weird?
It's weird.
What?
It's a present for you.
A present?
Yes.
It's a flower.
Look it up.
It's faster to look it up.
I see.
It's a present for your wife.
It's blooming.
What?
Wait a minute.
It's a present for my wife.
Hey.
You've been looking at it for a while.
What?
Look at it.
Who is it?
I don't know.
What is it?
What?
Look at it.
Hey.
What is it?
It's a flower of it.
It would be better than a flower.
This...
It would be like this.
Well...
it would be better than a flower.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
So...
I was doing my subscription
what
You've been watching it for a long time
You were looking at it, weren't you?
No, I wasn't.
Oh, you didn't notice.
What are you doing?
Let me see.
What do you mean?
It's so big.
What are you doing?
Let me see.
No, no, no.
Please stop.
Please don't do anything weird.
What?
Please.
I'm serious.
I didn't know it was this big.
What?
I'm serious.
What's with that reaction?
I didn't mean it.
I'm serious.
What is it?
We're siblings.
What are you talking about?
I'm serious.
You were looking at it, weren't you?
What?
If it's a necklace, should it be a diamond?
That's obvious.
It's a big diamond.
Diamonds are expensive.
It's okay.
You have to make a lot of money on your birthday.
That's right.
Diamonds are expensive.
Let's open the diamonds.
There are various kinds of diamonds.
It's a big diamond.
How many carats is it?
10 carats.
How much do you think it is?
How much?
How much is it?
It's cheap.
29,700 yen.
No way.
What?
It's fake, isn't it?
I see.
12,000 yen.
Look at this.
900,000 yen.
It's not 29,000 yen.
It's fake.
It's cheap.
11,000,000 yen.
15,000,000 yen.
It's obvious.
No.
I'm in trouble.
You have to work hard.
I don't know what to do.
What's that?
I've never seen a diamond.
I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
It's time to get married.
I have to get ready.
Let's go.
I heard we're going to get married soon.
I'm studying hard.
I'm investigating.
I'm thinking about a diamond.
Diamond?
What is good?
I like diamonds.
I like glittering things.
I think you like glittering things.
I see.
I don't get it at all. It's so difficult.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm studying.
Studying?
Yes.
Do you want me to teach you?
I don't think you understand.
What?
Because I'm a college student.
I'm not a college student.
I know this much.
Really?
Do you want me to teach you?
No, I'll think about it myself.
Why?
I'll teach you.
Don't get too close to me.
Why?
I'm getting in the way of your study.
What?
Don't study so boringly.
Don't study with me.
What are you talking about?
Don't study with you.
I know what you mean.
I want to study hard and go to a good college.
Don't say that.
What?
Stop it.
You really want to study, don't you?
What?
I want to study.
You're so naughty.
You really want to study, don't you?
You've been hitting my back.
Why are you talking like that?
I'm not.
You're an actress.
I'm not an actress.
Stop it.
You're not getting any better.
That's because you're in my way.
Really?
I'm serious.
What's wrong?
I'm not.
I want to teach you how to study.
Okay?
I'll teach you.
Get out of here.
I'll study alone.
Are you okay?
You can't get out of here.
You're so naughty.
Stop it.
We're siblings.
It's true.
You can't get out of here.
Show me.
I can't.
Why are you hitting me?
You're so naughty.
What are you talking about?
You're bigger than Ryuji.
Who's Ryuji?
You're the best.
I'm not the best.
Don't play with me.
You have such a good thing.
You have to play with me.
What do you mean?
It's amazing.
I've never seen such a big one.
I'm scared.
It's amazing.
Stop it.
Wait.
It's amazing.
You can't get out of here.
We're siblings.
You're so naughty.
What are you talking about?
In front of dad.
You forced me to do it.
I forced you to do it?
I told you to stop it.
You forced me to do it.
Please stop it.
I don't want to.
What is that?
Please stop it.
It's fun to bully you.
I don't enjoy it.
You forced me to do it.
You're big now.
I don't enjoy it.
I don't want to.
Please stop it.
It's twitching.
I don't like it.
What are you doing?
It's funny.
You're a devil.
Please stop it.
I don't like it.
Do you want me to do it more?
I don't want you to do it.
You're lying.
Do you want me to do it more?
Please stop it.
I don't like it.
What is that?
Do you want me to do it more?
Don't do that.
Why?
I don't like it.
It's twitching.
What are you doing?
It's still hard.
Don't do that.
Do you want me to do it more?
Do it more.
Why?
Wait a minute.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Don't go.
Why?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Don't go.
Jun.
Why?
Why are you skipping school?
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
Do you want to go somewhere?
I don't want to go.
Do you want to go to love boat?
Are you sick?
I don't have a girlfriend.
Don't you have a girlfriend?
I'm sorry.
You don't have to be angry.
Why are you so depressed?
What's wrong?
It's none of your business.
What are you talking about?
Talk to me.
Hey.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to tell you.
Hey.
Don't hit me.
I was the only virgin in my class.
What?
Are you a virgin?
What's that?
Is that true?
That's not true.
You should have done it with me the other day.
What are you talking about?
Why?
You are my sister.
It's none of your business.
What?
We are not related.
I don't understand.
You don't want to be a virgin, do you?
That's right.
It's okay.
If I were a virgin, I would welcome it.
It's okay?
Yes.
You were a good virgin.
You want to be a virgin, don't you?
I want to be a virgin.
What?
You are persistent.
It's okay.
I said it's okay.
Right?
Show me your tongue.
My tongue?
Show me more.
I don't know because it's my first time.
Show me.
I don't know.
You are terrible.
Touch me.
Help me.
Show me more.
Does it hurt?
No.
It's okay.
It's okay?
Yes.
Touch me.
Like this?
You are a virgin.
Touch me from here.
Like this.
Is it your first time?
Of course.
You are terrible.
I'm glad that you can graduate now.
You are going to die as a virgin.
No.
Show me more.
It's difficult.
What's difficult?
I don't know because it's my first time.
I'm going to take it off.
It's going to be tangled.
Take it off.
Do you want to see my boobs?
I don't know how to take it off.
It's here.
I'm going to take it off.
I've never taken it off.
Like this?
It's difficult.
Did I take it off?
Ta-da!
It's my boobs.
Thank me.
Thank you.
How is it? Is it soft?
It's soft.
It's warm.
Of course it's warm.
It's so soft.
Touch it.
It's weird.
It's weird?
Yes.
Lick it.
I don't know how to lick it.
Lick my boobs.
Come on.
Here.
Put your tongue out.
More.
Come on.
It's hot.
Lick my boobs.
Here, too.
It's hot.
Lick my boobs, too.
Here.
Do you know how to do it?
Come on.
Lick my boobs.
You've never licked my boobs, have you?
No.
It's my first time.
Come on. Lick my boobs.
Here.
Here?
A little higher.
There.
Put your tongue out more.
It's hot.
Try putting your finger in it.
My finger?
Yes.
Here?
Yes, there.
Wow.
Your finger's in there.
It's warm.
It's so warm.
Wow.
Can I put my finger in it?
Yes.
It's hot.
There.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Did you get it?
Come on. Lick my boobs.
I'll lick them, too.
They're really big, aren't they?
What's with these boobs?
What are you talking about?
You're wasting your virginity.
What?
It's hot.
They're really big.
It feels good.
Of course it does. I'm the one licking them.
Wow.
They're too big to fit in my mouth.
What?
They're too big.
It's getting really hard.
You can't say that.
What?
I said you can't say that.
I know.
You want to graduate, don't you?
They're really big.
It's really hot.
It really feels good to be licked.
You want to put them in, don't you?
I do.
Why?
Why do you want to graduate?
You want to graduate, don't you?
Then I'll put them in for you.
In my boobs.
They're real boobs.
Real boobs?
Of course it does.
It feels good.
Wow.
This place is the best.
How is it?
It feels good.
Your boobs feel good, don't they?
Your boobs feel good.
It feels good.
They're so good, I can't get enough.
Let's stay for a while.
No.
Wait a minute.
Oh, no, I'm going to burp.
You can't.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey, what's wrong?
She said, stop, stop.
What? Is this your first time?
Isn't this a little crazy?
Hey.
Oh, my God.
I put it inside.
I'm sorry.
You're good.
What?
It's not moving.
You're good.
It's your first time.
It's amazing.
And you're still standing.
That's crazy.
Oh, my God.
It's still really big.
How many times can you do it?
Seven times.
Oh, my God.
It's amazing.
This chamber feels so good.
What should I do?
It's messed up.
It's wet.
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Oh, my God.
Hey.
You should try it, too.
What should I do?
From behind.
Can you do it?
I'll try.
Oh, my God.
Here.
Put it in there.
Oh, my God.
It's been standing for a long time.
Does it feel good?
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, my God.
It's the best.
It's too good to move on my own.
I can't move that much.
Shake your hips a lot.
A lot?
Oh, my God.
Oh, it feels good.
It's pretty good.
Oh, my God.
Shake your hips a lot.
A lot?
Oh, my God.
Shake your hips a lot.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
What's wrong with you?
Oh, my God.
You're exhausted.
You're still standing.
How long are you going to stand?
I don't know.
You've done everything you've ever done, haven't you?
Hey.
Put it in again.
Not yet.
I want to do more.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, my God.
What is it?
I want to put it on your face.
What?
You can't do that.
Why?
Your make-up will be ruined.
I want to do it.
I've been doing it for a long time.
You're still doing it?
Yes.
I don't want to die!
Hey!
I didn't tell you to show your face!
What are you doing?
My mic is going to break!
This is the worst.
I can't help it.
Hey!
It's 100 years early for a cancer.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
You have to practice 7 days a week from tomorrow.
Practice?
You have to practice having sex.
7 days a week?
It was not good enough.
I see.
Do you understand?
Yes!
Thank you for watching!