Please let me know if it hurts.
Okay.
Does it hurt?
No, it feels good.
Really?
Yes.
Your body is pretty stiff.
It's because I'm not used to it.
I've been walking a lot while I'm not used to it.
I see.
Do you get scolded a lot in Kanazawa?
No, this is my first time.
I see.
Please enjoy your meal.
I really enjoyed the food at the inn.
Thank you.
The food here is really good.
When I was able to go home, I was told that the food was delicious.
I'm glad to hear that.
Is it famous for crabs?
Yes.
There are a lot of seafood in Kanazawa.
It's near the sea.
In this season, the sea urchin is also delicious.
Please eat it for tomorrow's lunch.
Yes.
I'm a little tired.
You can eat it at all.
It's a high-end restaurant.
It's a little expensive, but it's cheap to eat here.
Is that so?
Are you from Tokyo?
Yes.
It's expensive in Tokyo.
It's expensive.
When I went on a trip to Tokyo, I was surprised.
All crabs are expensive.
I think so.
It's about half the price.
Is it so cheap?
It's cheap.
I want to go to Kanazawa.
By all means.
I think there are a lot of people walking around the city.
Is that so?
Recently, many people are going out.
I've seen a lot of young people.
Young people are still young.
That's not true.
How old do you think you are?
It's about the same age as me.
I'm 25 years old now.
You're happy to hear that.
Are you younger than me?
What do you think?
I think you're a little older than me.
How many years ago were you a student?
You'll be found out.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to say that.
I'm old enough to worry about my age.
Are you married?
Yes.
How did you meet your husband?
My husband was a senior at the company I worked for at the time.
I got along with him while he was teaching me various things.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend now.
You're working, aren't you?
I spend time with my girlfriend on my days off from work.
You'll be found out soon if you're in your 20s.
It's hard to find an old lady like me.
I'm not an old lady.
You're an old lady.
I'm not an old lady at all.
I'm in my late 30s.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it at all.
I'm used to being called an old lady.
No, it's not like that at all.
Old ladies who drink and get drunk here.
Bring me the old lady beer.
I'm a masseuse.
You're an old lady.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm not an old lady at all.
You're a beautiful old lady.
It's rough here, too.
I have to do my desk work every day.
People who sit down are very stiff around their butts.
Is that so?
How long have you been married?
Married?
I was 26 years old.
It's been 10 years.
It's been 10 years?
It's been a while.
I forgot.
Do you celebrate your wedding anniversary every year?
I did it for the first five years.
I forget when I'm busy.
Do you have children?
I have children.
Two children.
How did you know that?
I just figured it out.
Are they boys?
They're so cute.
They're cute.
I play baseball.
I see.
Did your husband play baseball?
I played grass baseball.
I got hooked on it, and I said,
I want to do it, too.
I have to wash two men's underwear.
I have to wash a lot.
While thinking about it.
It's hard.
I would be happy if you could tell me that you want to be a professional when you grow up.
When I become a professional, I want to buy a car or a house.
Is that all?
No, no, you can't get out of this country.
Is that so?
This tool is really good for massaging.
Is that so? Thank you.
Can I use a little more force?
Can you still do it?
Not at all.
Leave it to me.
Don't underestimate my strength.
I might have underestimated the strength of a beautiful woman.
Then I'll push it.
Oh, it feels so good.
How long have you been doing this job?
Well, I've been doing this job for about 7 or 8 years since I quit my previous job.
How have you been doing this job?
I've been doing my best.
Do you do anything for your husband?
No, I don't.
Why not?
If you ask me that, I'll make him pay.
I don't want him to tell me that I'm tired.
Do you love him?
I don't want him to love me.
I want him to do something for me when I'm tired.
Doesn't your husband do anything for you?
No, he doesn't.
He buys me food, beer, and a bath.
Even though he loves me so much.
It's like the Showa era.
Men in the countryside are like that.
Does it hurt?
Not at all.
I think it's better to give you a massage while looking at your sister's face.
What are you talking about?
You're a young man in Tokyo.
No, I'm not.
You're popular, aren't you?
No, no, no.
If I'm popular, I should have a girlfriend.
Maybe you're too popular to get a girlfriend.
I wish I could marry someone like you.
You shouldn't tease me like that.
I'm not teasing you.
I like older women.
But you're only 5 years old.
No, no, no.
I'm older than my mother.
How old is your mother?
She's about 50 years old.
It's hard for a 25-year-old man and a 50-year-old woman to get along.
My mother is about the same age as my sister.
You shouldn't do that.
Don't you have a massage machine?
Don't you come to my room and get a massage?
Yes, yes, yes.
Don't you get a massage?
There aren't many young men who stay at my inn.
I'm an old woman, too.
No, no, no.
Some drunk men come to my inn.
I don't treat them like that.
Have you ever been tempted by them?
No, I haven't.
I've never been tempted by a drunk man.
Is that so?
Let me touch you.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid of young men.
I want you to touch me.
It's nothing.
I think I heard you.
Did you hear me?
No, I didn't hear what you were saying.
Really?
I'm glad I could hear you.
What are you talking about?
If you say something weird, I'll press your acupuncture point.
Let's do it.
Ouch!
What acupuncture point is that?
This is stomach.
Stomach?
It hurts a little.
I think young men drink too much.
I think so, too.
It's amazing.
They eat too much and drink too much.
In their mid-twenties, they eat convenience store bento.
They eat a lot.
It's not good for your health.
You can't do acupuncture, can you?
I can.
It's amazing.
Do you have any acupuncture points that work on the lower body?
Yes, I do.
It's like lifting the blood.
It's like blood circulation.
I've been feeling a little swollen lately.
I'll press it.
Is it around there?
I think so.
It hurts a little.
I'll press it.
It's definitely swollen.
Really?
There are a lot of scars.
I walked a lot today.
When you move, your body gets swollen.
Please take a bath.
Can I do it on the front?
Yes, you can.
Let's do a stretch on the front.
Stretch?
You can do it.
If your lower body is tired, you can do it.
My lower body is tired.
I'll press it.
I'm sorry.
It hurts a lot.
Your hip joints are hard.
It hurts.
I'm a man.
There are a lot of men who have hard hips.
Do you know women?
Women have soft hips.
Is this a uniform?
That's right.
It's not good.
I think it's wonderful.
I was made to wear red.
I wanted to wear clothes like an esthetician.
I'll press it.
It feels good.
It feels good here.
I like to talk.
Do you like this?
I'll do it.
Please tell me.
I can't let you do that.
No problem.
I'm doing it, too.
It's our job to loosen it.
I'll do it.
No problem.
Have you ever had a client do it?
Not here.
There is a massage therapist.
If you like, please come to my house.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I've been seeing it for a while.
I thought this was the default.
I'm sorry.
Did it hurt?
No.
I didn't want you to hide it.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
Please take it seriously.
I've been massaging for a while.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
My body is warm.
Really?
Yes.
I'm glad.
I'm stretching my lower body.
Do you feel it?
My pelvis and legs are warm.
I'm glad.
I'm sorry.
What is this?
Can you do it again?
That?
Are you okay?
Isn't your room hot?
It's a little hot.
I'm getting hot, too.
Not at all.
What should I do?
Should I lower my hair?
Can't you take it off?
I'm wearing a shirt, so I can't take it off.
Take it off.
Isn't it easier to take it off?
Your sleeves are a little long.
I sometimes get caught.
Can I take it off?
Not at all.
I'm sorry.
That's better.
Is it better?
Does everyone wear a T-shirt under their uniform?
I think so.
Basically, everyone wears a T-shirt.
Everyone wears a T-shirt.
I'm sorry.
My boobs are full.
Not at all.
I didn't care about it at all, so it's okay.
I'm sorry.
Not at all.
Some people get better blood flow when they get a massage.
Are there people like that?
There are people like that.
It's very effective, isn't it?
It's very effective.
Some people get better when they get a massage in this area.
You don't have to worry about it at all.
It's a common thing.
I'm sure you'll be praised a lot.
There's nothing to be praised about.
Really?
There's no way.
No one even looks at my body.
Why?
Even if you ask me why, I haven't done that for a while.
That's a shame.
Thank you for saying that.
I don't have a girlfriend or a wife.
I'm a mother.
You don't look at me as a woman?
That's right.
I'm a mother.
I want to tell you that I'm not your mother.
Hey.
Yes.
What's the matter?
Well.
Yes.
I've had enough.
Oh, yes.
I want you to help me.
There's no massage like that.
What do you mean?
It's a normal shop.
It's like a back...
Back...
What are you talking about?
In Tokyo, there's a massage like that.
Back massage?
Yes.
I've never heard of it.
Really?
Yes.
With that kind of hand?
No, I can't.
Please.
Oh, really?
Then I'll just use my hand.
I'll just use my hand.
I'll just use my left hand.
No, I can't.
Please.
I'm working.
But you saw me earlier.
I saw you, but I can't.
I just touched you.
You touched me, didn't you?
I already touched you.
No, you didn't.
I said no.
You touched me, too.
No, I didn't.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Please.
Just a little bit.
You made me touch you, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
I didn't make you touch me.
No, you didn't.
Really, just a little bit.
You're not going to let go of me, are you?
Then I'll let go of you.
No, you don't have to.
Just a little bit.
How much do you mean by a little bit?
I breathe pretty fast.
Oh, okay.
Oh, really?
Yes.
No, you can't do that.
Just a little bit.
No, you can't.
I won't let you touch me anymore.
Just a little bit.
You're good at massaging.
No, I'm not.
I'm sorry.
Just a little bit.
No, you can't.
Can I touch you?
Just a little bit.
No, you can't.
Really.
Just a little bit.
It feels good.
It's really soft.
No, you can't do that.
I have a husband.
We talked about this a lot, didn't we?
Your husband doesn't see you as a woman.
That's true, but...
I see you as a woman, so...
But I'm a married woman.
You can't do that?
I can't.
Why?
Because I'm married.
You can't because you're married?
No, I can't.
I don't think so.
But I'm a woman.
No, you're not a woman.
No, no, no matter how I think about it, I'm...
You're a beautiful woman.
We're more than 10 years apart.
You're a beautiful woman, so...
You touch me like this.
You said a lot of things.
You react very naturally.
You touched and said a lot of things to me.
Yes.
I'm not a body that can be seen in such a bright room, so I don't understand it at all.
It's a very beautiful body, isn't it?
Really?
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
I'm very surprised.
I'm going to make a very erotic voice.
My stomach hurts.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
My stomach hurts.
How is my massage?
This feels good.
It's very rough.
Do you understand?
I'm going to make a very erotic voice.
It's very rough.
Do you feel better?
It's a little embarrassing.
I can't do it.
It's been a long time since I've had a massage like this.
Let's do it slowly.
It's very rough.
It feels very good.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
I'm going to throw up.
I haven't washed my body.
I've been working all day.
It's embarrassing.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
One more time.
I can't do it.
My mouth is wet.
It was delicious, so I ate a lot.
It feels very good.
Let me lick you.
I'm sorry.
It's been a long time.
It's amazing.
I didn't know a 20-year-old girl was so hard.
It's too good.
It feels good.
It's very good.
How is it?
It's amazing.
It's very good.
What do you mean?
What's that?
Don't you do this with your husband?
It's not just Tokyo.
It's very good.
Avocado
Full of moisture
Even when I was a kid, I liked avocado
A close break
Okay.
Are you done?
What?
I haven't asked you yet.
Why? I'm done.
You can't say that.
What?
You can't pretend you don't know.
You're a bad person.
What?
You can't pretend you don't know.
You made a cute sound.
You made a loud sound.
Please sit down and hold it for a moment.
It's hot.
It's small, so it's hard.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Please sit down and hold it for a moment.
It feels good.
It's hot.
You can't do that.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Can you move?
I'll move.
It's been a long time since I've been on top like this.
It feels good.
I'm sorry if I'm not good at it.
It's okay.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'm not good at this.
It's getting tight.
It's tight.
You can't do that.
It feels good.
You're not bad at this at all.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
If I move you, you'll go there.
I want you to go a lot.
I'm not the only one who's going.
I told you I'd go if you moved me.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I told you I can't do that.
The other side.
The other side?
What do you mean by the other side?
What?
It feels good.
Are you going to do it in this position?
I'll do it from this side.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's hard.
I'm so happy.
It feels good.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
It feels good.
I'm glad it feels good.
It's hot.
You're doing a great job.
I can't do it because I don't have stamina.
You're still so energetic.
Isn't that obvious?
That's amazing.
It feels good.
How do you feel?
It's the best.
Don't call me auntie.
I'm your sister.
No, you're auntie.
It's so relaxing.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's embarrassing.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's so hard.
I'm holding back my feelings.
I've never felt this way before.
It's so tight.
It feels good, so it's tight.
If you don't tighten it that much, it'll come out.
If you move it, it'll close.
You have a bad face.
It feels good.
I'll do it.
I can't say no.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'll do it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's been five minutes, so it came out.
It felt good.
I've never felt this way before.
It was fun.
Don't tease me.
I'm not teasing you.
Again.
Thank you.
Can I have a kiss?
What?
Thank you.
Is that so?
Please do your best at work.
Please do your best.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you. My name is Yamada.
Nice to meet you.
How long are you going to massage today?
Is an hour okay?
60 minutes?
Yes.
You are very beautiful.
Is that so?
Thank you.
I'm going to start massaging.
Okay.
Are you going to work today?
Yes.
I came here today.
Is that so?
I'm tired.
Where are you most tired?
My shoulders.
My back.
Do you have a lot of back pain?
I went out today.
I went out to do business.
Did you go out for a walk?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm going to start massaging.
Okay.
Is it better to leave it as it is?
That's right.
Please look at me.
Thank you.
I'm going to massage your shoulders.
Okay.
Please lie down.
I'm going to put a towel on your back.
Okay.
Isn't it cold?
It's okay.
I'm going to put a towel on your feet.
Okay.
I'm going to start massaging.
Please look at me.
Okay.
It feels good.
Is that so?
That's good.
You are very good.
Thank you.
Are you a masseuse of this hotel?
That's right.
I do what I'm asked to do.
You are very beautiful.
Do you have a lover?
No, I don't.
You are popular.
Are you married?
That's right.
Yes.
How long have you been married?
I've been married for about 8 years.
That's a long time.
I have a child.
Do you have a mother?
That's right.
I have a mother.
You look like a mother because you look young.
How old are you now?
I'm 35 years old.
I can't see you at all.
I can't resist my age.
You are good at praising me.
I'm just saying the truth.
How have you been for the past 8 years?
Have you had a bad relationship?
Have you had a fight with your husband?
That's right.
Sometimes.
I haven't had a fight with my husband recently.
When I first got married, we had a lot of fights.
You don't seem to be angry with me because I'm kind.
Don't you think I'm angry?
I'm not angry.
Are you angry?
I may be angry.
Are you angry with your child?
That's right.
Do you have a strict mother?
I want my child to be polite.
I'm strict with my child.
I think a mother like you is the best.
Did you come to Miyazaki for the first time today?
That's right.
This is a good place.
This is a very good place.
The food is delicious.
Have you eaten anything?
I ate.
I ate chicken.
It was very delicious.
Was it delicious?
That's good.
There are many beautiful women.
Were there many beautiful women?
There were many beautiful women.
I met you.
Can I touch your arm?
No.
You are beautiful.
It's embarrassing.
Look at my face.
I touch your arm.
When you massage, you two are beautiful.
That's right.
Can you touch my arm?
No.
Is that true?
That's true.
Can I touch your arm again?
That's not true.
I want to touch your arm.
Who will touch my arm?
No one.
I'm a little nervous.
Are you nervous?
Is that true?
That's true.
How do you feel?
What's wrong?
Do you want me to massage your arm?
Don't touch my arm.
Are you tired?
That's not good.
I like to massage my arm.
I'm the one who massages my arm.
I see.
If you want me to massage your arm, I'll do it.
I'm the one who massages my arm.
If you massage my arm, you'll be tired.
I'm a little tired.
You don't get tired easily.
Thank you.
But I'm fine.
Are you sure?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
How do you feel?
I'm relaxed.
Do you usually exercise?
I don't exercise.
I get muscle pain easily.
Is that so?
I exercise a little.
You're young, so you get muscle pain easily.
I'm getting old.
I get muscle pain after three days.
Do you get muscle pain after three days?
Yes, I do.
When I was young, I got muscle pain after a few hours.
I get muscle pain when I'm old.
Are you sure?
You're still young.
I'm 35 years old.
I'm old.
I don't think so.
Are you sure?
Do you still go on a date with your husband?
I go on a date sometimes.
I don't usually go on a date.
Do you usually go on a date with your husband?
Yes, I do.
I see.
Don't you go on a date with your husband?
No, I don't.
Don't you?
Aren't you lonely if you don't go on a date with your husband?
I'm not lonely.
We're a family.
So, I feel secure.
How long have you been single?
How long?
What do you mean?
I mean, how long have you been in a relationship?
Don't say it so clearly.
I'm curious.
Are you curious?
Yes, I am.
Don't say it.
How long have you been single?
I don't know.
I haven't been single recently.
I think I've been single for a while.
Don't say it.
So, you haven't been single for a long time.
I haven't been single for a long time.
Have you ever wanted to have a boyfriend?
Do you ask me such a question?
No, I don't.
Men want to have a boyfriend.
But sometimes women want to have a boyfriend.
What would you do if you didn't have a boyfriend?
I wouldn't do anything.
You wouldn't do anything, right?
It's a lie to not do anything.
No, I wouldn't.
Do you mean that?
Would you be lonely with him?
My legs are still full.
What do you do on your day off?
Sometimes?
Once a week?
No, not once a week.
Really?
It depends on the timing.
Really.
Why?
Are you touching your butt?
No, I just said it's okay.
You said it, but...
I said it.
You're teasing me, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Because you're an old lady?
No, no.
I'm serious.
Really?
You're telling everyone, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
It's not good.
It's not good?
Where is this?
There.
Right there.
Don't.
Don't?
What are you touching?
Here.
Your skin is hard.
It's about this thick.
Isn't it hot?
It's a little hot.
A little hot?
Do you want to take it off?
Is it okay?
I want to take it off.
Do you want to take it off?
It's a little hot.
Is it getting hot?
Yes.
It's getting better, isn't it?
Let me know if it's cold again.
It's cold.
What's wrong?
Why are you touching your butt?
No.
What's wrong?
It's about this thick.
Where?
Here.
Why?
I don't know.
Is this okay?
Yes.
This is...
I'm the type of person who gets angry easily.
I get angry easily.
I can't see it.
I don't want you to see it.
You can't see it?
I don't mind if you see it.
No.
It's embarrassing to get used to seeing it, isn't it?
Yes.
It's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing, but I get up.
It's a physiological phenomenon.
You're touching your feet.
Yes.
It's good to touch my feet.
Is it okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you a massage.
What?
I'll give you a massage here.
Here?
Yes.
I'll give you a foot massage.
A foot massage?
Yes.
I can't do it.
I'll give you a foot massage.
Did you get up because of me?
Yes.
I couldn't do it.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I'll keep it a secret.
Really?
Yes.
I'll give you a foot massage.
It's getting harder and harder.
I'm sorry.
Can I look at you?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It's getting bigger.
Please sit down.
Sit down.
It's been a long time since I touched you.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I can't stand it anymore.
What?
It's cute.
I can't stand it anymore.
Don't look at me.
It's difficult.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's amazing.
It's hard.
I can't stand it anymore.
What's wrong?
It's amazing.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't do that.
It's been a long time since I touched you.
It's cute.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's amazing.
I'm so tired.
Don't do that.
I can't stand it anymore.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Wait a minute.
Let me kiss you.
I'm embarrassed.
It's been a long time since I touched you.
I felt a lot of things.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
I've never seen you like this.
I'm sorry.
It's hard.
Let me lick you a little more.
Please rub my chest.
Don't do that.
Can you do that?
It's hot.
It's getting hot.
It's so hot.
It's hot.
It's getting hot.
It's getting better.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
It's been a while.
It's hot.
I feel so good.
I want more.
I know.
It's hot.
I feel so good.
Why are you making that face?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
I want to kiss you.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
I might be able to do it again.
You're fine.
Let's do it again.
Is it heavy?
Are you okay?
It just hurt.
I'm nervous.
Are you okay?
There's a pimple in my stomach.
Is this okay?
Are you really okay?
I want you to help me.
Are you okay?
You have a lot of pimples.
Do you have a lot of pimples?
I have a lot of pimples.
Can I grow up a little more?
Okay.
Where are you from?
I'm from Hokkaido.
Hokkaido?
That's a long way.
I'm traveling around Japan by bicycle.
I see.
That's why you have a lot of pimples.
That's why I have a lot of pimples.
I'm traveling around Japan.
How long does it take to get here?
It takes 30 days to get here.
Is it fast?
Is it slow?
It's amazing.
Are you going back to Hokkaido?
I'm going back to Hokkaido.
I think this is the best place.
I feel good when I massage here.
I didn't expect you to do this.
Don't tease me.
You are beautiful.
I thought you were a grandmother.
I'm a grandmother.
You are still young.
I'm in my twenties.
I'm in my thirties.
What are you talking about?
I'm in my forties.
Are you?
I can't see you at all.
Really?
I didn't know that.
I was surprised.
You don't look like a grandmother at all.
You are the only one who says that.
I'm sorry to say this.
Do you get married?
I do.
I didn't know that.
Do you have children?
I have two children.
Do you have two children?
Are they still young?
They are elementary school students.
They are 8 and 5 years old.
Are they that old?
I didn't know that.
I'm glad that you say that to such a young person.
Massage is also pleasant.
I don't normally say that.
You are popular.
That's not true.
I don't think there are many people who travel from Hokkaido.
I don't think there are many people who are doing this kind of massage.
Yes, that's right.
I've never seen such a good massage before.
Oh, wow.
The sound is beautiful.
But I don't think there are two children.
A 8-year-old and a 5-year-old girl.
This is a toy.
Is that so?
It's not beautiful.
Don't do that.
Don't make fun of me.
I hit my hand.
I'm sorry.
It's around the hip joint.
Around the hip joint?
I heard the sound of a bicycle.
I'm tired.
I want you to focus on this massage.
I'll raise my legs a little.
I'll lower my legs a little.
I'll stretch my legs.
It's very effective.
I know.
There are many men who are stiff.
That's right.
It's hard to stretch.
I'll do the other side.
I'm sorry.
It's different when you stretch your legs.
It feels good.
I'll give you a massage.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
What are you doing?
I couldn't stand it.
Don't worry about it.
You told me not to worry about it.
You'll get used to it.
If you give me a massage.
It's a phenomenon of justice.
I can't do it.
If you give me a massage, I'll get bigger.
There are people like that.
Can I ask you to give me a massage?
We don't do that.
There are people who ask you to do it.
Can I do it?
I'm in trouble.
I can't do it.
I'll do it for you.
You have a hard mouth.
That's not the problem.
You have a great body.
You have a beautiful face.
Don't make fun of me.
I'm serious.
I have a husband.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry if I offended you.
It's okay.
I drank too much.
There are people like that.
I'll give you a massage.
It feels good.
Did you do something?
I didn't do anything.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You're getting bigger.
I'm sorry.
I'm in trouble.
I can't control it.
I'll give you a massage.
It's amazing.
You're getting bigger.
I'm not a woman.
I'm beautiful.
I'm sorry.
I don't care about other people.
I only care about you.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Young people are hard.
How old are you?
I'm 25 years old.
25 years old?
It's amazing.
It's been a long time since I saw you.
Is that so?
How have you been?
It's been a long time since I saw you.
I'm sorry.
I'm happy to be petted by such a beautiful person.
You're very patient.
Did you get a massage from your mother?
I'm not a mother.
I'm glad.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I'm glad.
It's amazing.
It's beautiful.
It's embarrassing.
I don't think there are two people.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
It tickles.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I want you to play with me.
It tickles.
I can't stand it anymore.
Can I go to bed?
It tickles.
Can you stand it?
If you touch me,
If you touch me, I'll be sick.
I'll be fine.
I don't move much.
It tickles.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
There was a lot.
Please call me when you get out of here.
Of course.
It's delicious.
It's good to eat.
I don't like this.
I like the feeling of stretching my wings.
Tomorrow.
I'm going to eat chicken.
I don't have anything.
I'm going to pee.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
I'd like a massage.
Yes.
Can I go right now?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
My back hurts.
What kind of massage is this?
Please come in.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Are you Mr. Tanaka?
Yes, I'm Mr. Tanaka.
I'm Yamada.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'll start with a massage.
I'll put a towel on you.
Strength or weakness?
Do you have a preference?
Strength?
I think strength is fine.
I'll start.
Excuse me.
Where are you from?
I'm from Tokyo.
From Tokyo?
Are you on a business trip?
That's right.
That's amazing.
No, it's not amazing at all.
No, no, no, no.
But I want to go to Japan.
I want to go to Tokyo.
That's right.
This is the first time I've been to Aomori.
It's boring if you come to the countryside.
On the contrary, it's fresh and nice.
It feels like I'm surrounded by nature.
Really?
I'm glad to hear that.
If you come from the city, you'll be able to see the countryside.
Excuse me.
Mr. Tanaka, you're good.
I'm a salesman.
I see.
I walk around here.
There are no buses around here.
I walk a lot.
I've been around a little bit.
There are no buses at all.
That's right.
There's only one train every hour.
It's not convenient.
That's right.
How long have you been doing this job?
It's been about 10 years.
You've been doing this job for 10 years.
It's been a long time.
That's right.
Excuse me.
It's the first time I've been here.
Here.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Tanaka, it's hard for you to do this job.
That's right.
But it's healing.
It's been a long time.
To be honest, I was wondering if there were older people who massaged the inn.
I didn't expect such a young and beautiful person to come here.
I was surprised.
You're older than me.
I'm not older than you at all.
You're so talkative.
There aren't many beautiful and cute women in the city.
I'm tired of it.
I'm old.
I'm not young at all.
By the way, how old are you?
I'm 35 years old.
I can't see you at all.
I thought you were in your mid-20s.
That's too much.
You're so beautiful that you're going to be popular.
I'm not popular.
I've been married for eight years, and I have a husband.
Is that so?
I'm not popular.
I envy you.
If I had a beautiful wife like you, I'd fly home every day.
You're so talkative.
I'm serious.
I'm grateful to you.
You have a good style.
I'm grateful to you for taking care of me so much.
If you come to Tokyo, you can be a model.
I can't.
I see.
In the city, there are people who deceive women with such sweet words.
That's not true.
There aren't many people like that in Tokyo.
I don't know.
Where did you meet your husband?
He was my classmate when I was in college.
That's great.
Your husband, who you dated when you were in college, got married.
No.
It's not like that.
I can't get along with him.
I broke up with him once.
He had a lot of women.
Other than Japanese women.
I see.
He was dumped by all of them.
The only one left was a Japanese woman.
So we got married.
I see.
You must have had a lot of women when you were a student.
How many women did you date?
No.
It's not fun to talk about Japanese women.
I want you to tell me about your husband.
Please look at me.
Excuse me.
Please tell me if you feel pain around here.
Here.
You've been dating for 8 years.
How do you feel when you get married?
Do you feel like you're a night owl?
I don't enjoy talking about Japanese women.
I'll talk about Japanese women today.
No.
Do you have sex with your husband recently?
I don't have sex with my husband.
I wouldn't have sex with my husband if I had been married for 8 years.
I feel sorry for you.
You have a nice body.
Thank you.
Look at your nose.
I'm not drunk.
You're not drunk.
I love your boobs.
What kind of cup is this?
I won't tell you.
No, Mr. Tanaka.
You can't do that.
This is not a place like that.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I want to have sex with you.
Please put your arm here.
You're a good woman.
Thank you.
I love your sexiness.
I have a bad feeling about this.
What do you mean?
I'm telling you the truth.
You are very beautiful.
No.
I haven't met you at all while I was working.
I see.
I talked to a woman like you.
Did I say something strange?
Don't tease me.
You are not a woman at all.
You are very beautiful.
Thank you.
I'm fine.
Go to bed.
I don't tease you.
Young people these days.
Don't tease me.
Don't do that.
I'll continue.
Thank you.
You are very beautiful.
It's very hot here.
It's true.
You are very beautiful.
But.
I can't touch you.
Let's keep this a secret between us.
I won't tell anyone.
Then.
But.
I like you.
And I like you.
I can't help it.
I don't hate you at all.
I won't let you go.
It's very hot here.
But.
Tanaka.
Kanako.
It's so beautiful, isn't it?
No, it's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
It's a little embarrassing to see such an old lady's body.
It's okay.
It's a little embarrassing.
It's a little embarrassing to see such an old lady.
It's embarrassing.
It's hot.
But...
It's so hot.
I'm not used to this body temperature.
It's okay.
It's so hot.
I can't stand it.
Wait a minute.
It's so hot.
I can't stand it.
Your body is so shiny.
I'm so shy.
I can't stand it.
You have a fever.
I have a fever.
I can't stand it.
It's so hot.
I don't even enjoy your massage.
I don't enjoy your massage.
It's so hot.
I can't do it.
Wait a minute.
Wow.
I can get up easily.
I can't do it.
Wow.
I've never been a man for a long time.
Are you all right?
Yes, I am.
Oh
Um
You don't have to
Which is
Um
Oh
Ah
Sky
I'm so happy
Wow
Can you do this for me?
Yamada-san, come here
Sit down
Come here
Ah
I can't believe you're doing this for me
I'm so happy
Yamada-san, I have to give you a massage
Massage?
Ah
It feels good
Is that so?
I'm so happy
Um
Ah
Wow
Um
Wait
It tickles
Um
Ah
This side
Um
Ah
Wow
Um
This side
It feels good
Um
Wow
Ah
It's getting better
Wow
Ah
This side
Wow
Um
Ah
It feels good
Really?
It's getting better
What should I put in my might?...
Like this?
Yes.
But...
It's been a while.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
But...
Slowly.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
I want to...
I want to go into here.
This is...
I want to...
I'm dying.
Now,
A full realization of the beauty that was born from cesarean section.
It's okay.
You're not going to make a sound.
It's painful.
How many days have passed?
It's been 3 years.
It feels good.
It's painful.
More.
It's cold.
It's painful.
It feels good.
More.
It's painful.
Give me more.
More.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's painful.
It feels good.
More.
It's painful.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's painful.
It felt so good.
Me, too.
Mr. Tanaka.
If you come here again, please call me.
Of course.
Bye-bye.