Isn't Fantasy World so fun...?
There's a huge shop.
I thought it was more expensive than he wanted, but I'm going to buy it first.
I wanted to go with you.
I'm going to take a look at what's in the box.
Are there any other seats available?
It's closed, so please be quiet.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to take a look at what's in the box.
What's in the box?
I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry. That's my book.
Oh, I made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I think it's a good idea.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I think it's a good idea or not.
I think it's a good idea or not.
Oh no...
Maybe it's a good idea or not...
I'm going to eat it with the sauce I made earlier.
Even if I eat salty foods,
A grilled eel on a dish
I've never tried eating grilled eels.
I've never tried eating grilled eels either.
It's so salty I don't want to eat it.
I'm not sure if I'll be able to do it, but I'll do my best.
I'm going to do my best.
Do you want to have sex with me?
Yes, I do.
With whom?
Me?
Of course.
Do you want to have sex with me?
Yes, I do.
Oh, my god.
Oh, my God.
car
Corresponding
char
nn
Oh no...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I can't take it anymore
I'm going to get out
You can't let it out
It's me
Wait a minute
I'm going
Yes
You can still get out
Show me where you can get out
Yes
I told you not to let it out
I'm sorry
It's me
That's it for today's video!
Thank you so much for watching until the end.
I'll come back with a better video next time.
Bye 💛
I'm going to take a walk in the park.
In front of me is Mr. Sato and a member.
A few hours later, this was another.
It's a little hard to see, but there's a lot of hair on the back of the head.
It's a little weird that the background is pink.
We are now on the E376 to Exeter. Final call for the remaining passengers to go immediately to gate 146.
We are now on the E376 to Exeter.
Make me feel good.
See you later.
This is the bathroom. You'd better go out soon.
Half an hour later
But the cliff is no longer there ....
It's sad because normally, I can not argue with that..
That mountain was the base of the wooden prow.
I'm sorry.
Passengers want to go.
I'll put it here.
Goodbye!
Welcome back!
Kintetsu train
This is the last station of the E208 series.
The last station of the E208 series.
So, in the last stage W, you may encounter E188 which does not finish up.
Let's look at the last stage together.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I think it's a good idea.
I want to watch a adult film rather than a movie.
What do you mean?
Show me your whole body.
Is it really hard?
Wait a minute.
No.
Brother.
Show me your whole body.
Wait a minute.
Please.
Show me your whole body.
Hey.
Let's do it together.
No.
I can't.
Come on.
Give me a kiss.
No.
Why?
I can't.
Let's do it together.
Wait a minute.
No.
Let's do it together.
I can't.
Be quiet.
Let's do it together.
I can't.
No.
Let's do it together.
I can't.
Let's do the same thing to the other one.
Why did you hide it?
I'm sorry.
It's difficult.
Show me.
Here.
It's hot.
You're reacting.
Show me.
It's hot.
Don't say that.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
You're touching mine.
I'm getting excited.
You're doing great.
You're so beautiful.
Wait, wait, wait.
What?
My baby.
I can't do it.
You can feel my neck, right?
What?
I'm wearing a diaper.
I don't want to do it.
I can't do it.
You're blushing, too.
Why? Don't you hate it?
No, I don't.
You don't hate it.
What?
Did you say something?
Let me kiss you more.
It's getting hot.
Sit down.
You're good.
You're blushing.
It's hot.
It's hard.
Something came out of your mouth.
No, it didn't.
It came out.
Touch it.
No, I don't.
I don't want to.
It tickles.
Does it feel good?
It tickles, right?
It tickles.
It's so warm.
What?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
You're pulling a string.
It tickles.
What?
Should I take this off?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Open your eyes.
Look.
I'm holding you in my arms.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Do you want to kiss me?
What?
I don't want to.
Kiss me.
It tickles.
Here?
I don't want to.
Wait a minute.
Look.
Look at me.
I'm holding you in my arms.
It tickles.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'm holding you in my arms.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Look.
It tickles.
I don't want to.
What?
It tickles.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It tickles.
What's wrong?
I don't want to.
You don't want to?
What?
It tickles.
Little by little.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Please wear in earphones.
Sweet dreams...
Great...
That's very kind of you.
Does that feel good?
Yes, go ahead.
No!
What is it?
Oh, dear…
I want to sleep.
What is it?
I feel like I'm going to die.
Ouch!
Hey, what should I do?
Where are you going?
I want to continue.
Ouch!
What? Does it feel good?
Do it more.
Yes, more.
To the back.
More.
I feel like I'm going to die.
Ouch!
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Yes.
Lie down.
Like this?
Yes, like that.
I want to continue.
What? Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
What? Does it feel good?
Ouch!
I feel like I'm going to die.
I want to continue.
Does it feel good?
Ouch!
It feels good.
I feel like I'm going to die.
What?
I like the feeling of dying.
I don't feel good.
What?
I feel sick.
I'm getting feverish.
What? What's wrong?
I feel like I'm going to vomit.
What?
You feel like you're going to vomit?
Yes.
Are you sick?
I feel like I'm going to vomit.
All right. Come here.
Wow, there's a lot coming out.
I'm sorry.
It's coming out.
I want to see where it's coming out.
Where is it coming out?
What do you mean?
Come up.
Up?
Here?
You can't see it from here, can you?
From behind.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
I can't do it.
Come closer.
I feel like I'm going to vomit.
Wow.
Wow, there's a lot coming out.
I feel like I'm going to vomit.
I feel sick.
I can't do it.
Today is the last day.
I'm lucky.
I can't do it.
Let's look at it together.
What is it?
Let's look at it.
Let's do it together.
Together?
Does it feel good?
Let's do it together.
Look at me.
Does it feel good?
Let's do it together.
Look at me.
Does it feel good?
Let's do it together.
Look at me.
You're so excited to be licked by a stranger, aren't you?
Really?
Let's do it together.
You can stick your tongue out when you want to.
You're so noisy.
Let's do it together.
What do you want to do?
More and more.
You're so noisy.
Stick your tongue out.
Let's do it together.
I want to have sex with you.
Is that okay?
Do you want to do it?
Let's do it together.
How do you feel?
I love you.
It feels good.
It looks painful.
I love you.
I want more.
I can't do anything about it.
I'm cold.
I really am.
I must wash herrobe.
She's crying.
Mother.
She's crying!
Mother!
She's crying.
Mother's crying!
They told me to keep quiet.
Ishinomaki Ward
Hey, Shinji.
What's up?
I've got a fever.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I can't do anything.
Please touch me.
Touch me.
I want you to touch me.
More.
Touch me.
Is this okay?
More.
It hurts.
This is amazing.
Oh, my goodness!
I don't know why.
This is not good.
I'm going to cry.
I can't do it.
Wow!
It tickles me.
It feels good.
Wow!
It's great.
I don't have a good feeling.
I don't feel good.
I don't want to vomit.
I feel sick.
It's good.
Huh?
It's so refreshing.
I've got more, I've got more.
What do we do, Satoko?
It's so sweet.
I'll hold you.
It's the best.
It's amazing.
I'll hold you.
See you.