3 Hours Later
Hey. Are you alright?
Hey? Are you fine?
Who?
It's not who.
You drank too much.
I brought you some tea.
Thank you.
Do you want some?
Yes.
You can't drink at all.
I'll open it for you.
Can you drink it?
Yes.
I'm scared.
You can do it.
Can I?
I'll spill it.
Are you okay?
It's not good.
It's sake.
It's not sake.
It's dangerous.
I'll hold it.
It's hot.
Stop it.
You were all drunk.
Yes.
You drank a lot at the club.
It's hot.
You were drinking alone.
Did I?
Yes, you did.
It's hot.
It's not hot.
You don't have to take it off.
It's hot.
I'll cool it down.
Okay.
It's hot.
I can't cool it down.
Did you fall asleep?
It's impossible.
I can't sleep.
I've never been here.
There's nothing here.
It's a mess.
I can't see my underwear.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
Hey.
It's a mess.
Get up.
What if I don't do it for you?
I don't feel like getting up.
What should I do?
I don't have a power outage.
I drank a lot at the club.
I have to go to bed.
It's a mess.
I can't help it.
What should I do?
If I sleep a little, I'll go home.
It's a strange feeling.
I'll do it.
It's a mess.
My head hurts.
I drank too much at the club yesterday.
I drank too much.
What should I do?
I have to pee.
It's a mess.
Why are you in front of me?
I'm not wearing underwear.
I'm in a mess.
I don't have underwear.
What's going on?
I'm in a mess.
You're not dry yet.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You drank a lot yesterday.
Did I drink that much?
That's right.
I was surprised.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
Please don't tell anyone.
I don't want to tell anyone.
I see.
I want you to keep it a secret.
I'm sorry.
I was also surprised.
Did you see me?
I saw you.
No, I mean, I was watching it.
What?
Stop it.
I mean, you know...
What?
Why do you make me say everything?
It's embarrassing.
Embarrassing?
Why is it embarrassing?
Because...
What do you mean? It's embarrassing for me.
Because it's the first time I've been out this much.
I didn't think I'd be out this much.
I'm tired.
I didn't think Umemiya was this good.
What?
Your butt.
Your blue panty butt.
What?
It's beautiful.
I'm tired.
It's smooth.
It's soft.
What are you doing?
I don't like this.
Wait a moment. What are you doing?
Wait a moment. I don't understand.
Wait. What are you doing?
Wait.
What are you doing?
I don't like this.
Wait.
How many times did I do this?
You don't remember, do you?
You did so many things.
Is that so?
It doesn't matter.
You were a little drunk.
I thought you didn't mind.
I see. Did I do something with my fingers?
Yeah.
I see. And then I slept a lot.
You don't have to worry about it.
I'm sorry. So this is not me.
Oh.
Yeah.
And here.
You don't have to do that.
I don't do that. I'm surprised.
I'm sorry. I made your bed dirty.
It's not me. I don't care.
I'm glad. I was in a hurry.
I'm glad.
So you don't have to worry about it.
Yeah. I'm sorry that I did something with my fingers.
Yeah.
What?
I'm sorry. I did too much.
You don't have to worry about it.
I'm going to change my sheets.
Are you going to change it?
Can you take it easy?
Take it easy?
Yeah. You don't have to be in a hurry.
I'm sorry.
Let's do it again.
Again?
Yeah. You're going to wash it, right?
Yeah.
You don't have to be in a hurry.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
Touch me.
You're standing up, aren't you?
Because...
I'm not drunk. I'm fine.
Yeah. I'm not drunk.
Are you sure?
I don't care if I'm drunk or not.
It's getting warm.
It feels good.
Do it more.
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
Touch me.
Like yesterday.
It feels good.
Oh, my God.
I fell asleep again.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
You're good at it.
I'm sorry.
I always fall asleep.
Don't worry about it.
Do you want me to pat you?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hard, isn't it?
You're good at it.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's hard.
It came out.
I'm sorry, I couldn't help it.
It's okay.
I put out a lot yesterday, but it's really amazing.
I'm sorry, I couldn't help it.
It's still standing.
It's amazing.
Actually, it's good to drink alcohol.
It's good to go out.
It's amazing.
Put your hand in.
I'm sorry, I don't have a rubber band.
But you didn't have a rubber band yesterday.
So put your hand in.
Please.
Really?
It's okay, put your hand in.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
It's really hard.
It's hard.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
My eyes hurt.
It feels good.
I'll wipe it off.
It's amazing.
It's in there.
It feels good.
It feels good for me too.
It's really hard.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's really hard.
I'm going to go.
It feels good.
It's hard.
What should I do?
I'm going to go.
It's okay.
Let me go.
That's...
It's okay.
You let me go yesterday.
Let me go.
Please.
I'm going to go.
I'm going.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's warm.
Wait.
It feels good.
Let me move more.
I like that.
I like your ears.
Stop it.
Let me go.
I'm going.
I'm in trouble.
I don't know why I'm doing this.
It feels so good.
Me too.
Stop it.
I'm in trouble.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'm in trouble.
Wait.
Stop it.
I'm going.
It's too fast.
I'm in trouble.
It's amazing.
I can't open my eyes.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Stop it.
I'm in trouble.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I love you.
We've been doing this since yesterday.
My mouth.
I'm in trouble.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'm in trouble.
I can't move.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'm in trouble.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I can't move.
I'm in trouble.
My face is swollen.
Please hold my hand.
It's a big deal.
I'm in trouble.
I can't stop. What should I do?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry. I did it too much.
What should I do?
It's okay. You can wash it again.
Really?
I'm sorry. I've never done this before.
It's okay. I'm glad.
I'm glad, too.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
Let's keep it a secret.
Okay.
But I'll keep it a secret.
I won't do it again.
But...
I feel like I'm going to get stuck.
Hayashi.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You're not okay at all.
Get a hold of yourself.
Are you okay?
It was hard to bring Hayashi here.
I can't do it anymore.
Why am I drinking more than a newbie?
I don't understand.
Get a hold of yourself.
Are you okay?
I don't know why I'm not okay.
Stop it.
You're going to get fat.
I'm not okay.
Get a hold of yourself.
You're going to get fat.
I don't want to be like this.
I can't sleep.
I can't go home.
I'm sleepy.
I'm drunk.
I'm tired.
What should I do?
I'm sleepy.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm tired.
I have to remove my makeup.
What is this?
I think I bit my foot.
I'm really drunk.
I'm a little dirty.
What?
Natsume?
Why is Natsume naked?
What does this mean?
I'm naked.
Natsume is naked.
I'm wet.
What is this?
What happened yesterday?
Natsume.
What is this?
It's nothing.
I'm dirty.
I'm wet.
It's okay.
Did I drink so much yesterday?
You drank a lot.
It was hard to bring you home.
I see.
I don't remember at all.
It's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
If you hit me so hard, I'll come out.
What does this mean?
What?
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
Why did you do that?
You did it first yesterday.
What?
Did I do it first?
I didn't think I'd come out that much.
It's the first time I've come out that much.
What?
What did I do yesterday?
Why did I come out?
I'm sorry.
What?
Stop it.
Wait a minute.
What?
Wait.
Stop it.
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
What?
Hey.
Stop it.
Natsume.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I was drunk.
I don't know why.
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
I'm not dry.
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to do the laundry.
Wait a minute.
Let's do it again.
Actually...
I was worried about you.
Really?
Natsume.
Hayashi forced me to do it yesterday.
Sit down.
Are you okay?
It feels good.
Do it as hard as you do now.
Do it on this side, too.
It feels good.
I'm used to it.
Do it as hard as you did yesterday.
It feels good.
Do it on this side, too.
What's the matter with you?
It's hot.
No, no, no.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Put your butt up.
My butt?
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's embarrassing.
It's big, isn't it?
You're right.
It's really big.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
Let's do it.
I've been doing it.
It's hard.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's embarrassing.
I haven't been doing it for five minutes.
Are you okay?
You were like this.
It's okay.
It feels good.
It's embarrassing.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's embarrassing.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it again.
It feels good.
It's embarrassing.
I want to do it more.
It feels good.
It's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I want to do it more.
I like this.
It feels good.
It's embarrassing.
I want to do it more.
It feels good.
I'm a little nervous.
It's embarrassing.
I want to sleep.
It feels good.
Oh, it feels good!
Rin-chan!
I made you so wet.
I'm going to take a deep breath.
Oh, it feels good!
You made me so wet.
Rin-chan!
Oh, it feels good!
I love you!
No, no, no, no!
Rin-chan!
You made me so wet.
What's wrong?
Oh, it feels good!
You made me so wet.
What's wrong?
Oh, it feels good!
You made me so wet.
More!
Oh, it feels good!
I might say it again.
Monika, what should we do?
I'm going to cry!
Oh, it feels good!
One more time.
I'm going to cry.
Ah, I'm going to puke.
I'm going to puke.
A lot.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm going to puke.
It felt so good.
I'm going to wash this.
I'm going to take a bath.
It felt so good.
I slept a lot.
Hey, hey.
Hey.
Camera.
You're sleeping too much.
Wake up.
You're too drunk.
Are you awake?
You're not awake.
I brought you home.
I'm proud of you.
I'm drunk, too.
I'm going to puke.
I'm tired.
I'm not drunk anymore.
Can I stay here?
Can I?
I'm going to stay here.
I want to sleep, too.
Get out.
Get out of the bed.
You're a man.
Get out.
You're heavy.
I want to sleep in the bed.
Get out.
I'm going to sleep.
I feel good in the bed.
I feel good.
You're sleeping on the floor.
You're so cute.
I'm going to sleep until morning.
I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
I'm cold.
No way.
I'm sorry.
I drank too much last night.
I've never been so drunk.
What's this?
Good morning.
What?
What are you doing?
I had a lot of things to do yesterday.
You had a lot of things to do?
I came home with you.
I see.
I had a lot of things to do.
You had a lot of things to do?
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
What did you do last night?
I drank too much.
Did you drink too much?
I drank too much last night.
I drank too much.
But you drank more than that.
Did I?
You drank too much.
You're going to spill it.
You two look good together.
Do we look good together?
You were amazing yesterday.
What?
You two look good together.
Do we look good together?
You were amazing yesterday.
Was I amazing?
You were intense.
Was I intense?
I'm sorry.
It's my butt.
What are you doing?
Let me go!
Ouch!
This...
You...
You said you were sorry.
No, no.
It wasn't me.
You're not drunk.
No, I'm not.
You have a lot of hair.
You're going to be bald.
I'm sorry. What should I do?
What should I do?
This is bad.
Why do you have so much hair?
No, no.
You have a lot of hair.
I have a lot of hair.
You're not sloppy.
I'm not sloppy.
I'm curious.
I was most curious about you at college.
I see.
I think you were curious about me.
You're a drunk person.
I'm glad.
I have to wash this.
Wait.
You can do it.
Don't do it.
Wait.
If you do it again, you'll get wet again.
No.
Let's do it again.
I'm glad.
You did a lot yesterday.
I did a lot yesterday.
You'll get wet again.
I feel good.
We get along well.
You're a bad person.
You'll get wet again.
I don't want to get wet.
Wait.
...
She's asleep.
Hey.
Mommy will get mad.
Mommy will block the rain.
I can't stop crying.
You're beautiful.
I was like this yesterday.
I can't stop crying.
I'm sorry.
How cold are you?
I'm not cold anymore.
You're sweating.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to the ice rink.
I feel weird.
I can't stop crying.
I'm going to the ice rink.
I'm sorry.
It's delicious.
It's hard.
I'm going to the ice rink.
I can't stop crying.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to the ice rink.
I can't stop crying.
It's hard.
I'm going to put out a lot of video.
I don't want the camera to feel bad.
I'm going to the ice rink.
What are you doing?
You're already dirty.
You put a lot of makeup on your face.
You look like you did yesterday.
I don't care about that.
You're wearing makeup.
I'm not wearing makeup.
You didn't put on makeup yesterday.
What?
I put it in.
Oh.
Hurry up.
Oh, oh, oh.
Then, really...
But...
It's okay. Hurry up.
Oh, yes, yes.
Daddy, it feels good.
Oh.
Oh, it feels good.
There, there, there.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh.
Oh, it feels good.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
I can't do it.
Isn't it more intense than yesterday?
No, it's okay.
I'm glad.
It's okay.
It feels good.
I'm glad.
I can't do it.
It's okay.
I couldn't do it yesterday.
I can't do it.
I was just touched.
I can't stop it.
It's painful.
I've been sleeping too much.
I'm getting scared.
Do you want me to do more?
I'm getting excited.
It feels good.
It's hard all the time.
It's because we get along well.
It feels good.
It's hard.
Wait a minute.
I'm sweating too much.
It feels good.
It's hard.
Wait a minute.
It feels good.
It's hard.
Wait a minute.
It's messed up inside.
I can't stop.
Let's do it again.
There's still a lot of energy left.
No, no, no.
I'll sleep here tonight.
Hey, Tanaka-kun.
Tanaka-kun.
Wake up.
Tanaka-kun, wake up.
I don't want to.
What? You're sleeping.
Wake up.
You drank too much at the university event.
Are you okay?
Wake up.
You don't wake up.
You're always like this.
Why do I always have to take care of you?
Wake up.
Shut up. Wake up.
Your eyes are blue.
Do you like tigers, Tanaka-kun?
I've never heard of it.
What do you do?
You don't do anything at all.
Don't you have a sense of life?
Are you able to live?
Hey.
You're heavy.
You stepped on my skirt.
Tanaka-kun, don't you have to take a bath?
I'm going home soon.
Are you okay?
Hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
I'm a little sleepy, too.
I'm going to lie down and go home.
Are you okay?
I'm going over there.
I'm really sleepy.
I'm going to lie down and go home.
It's cold.
What's this?
I did it.
Event.
I drank too much.
It's the worst.
What should I do?
I'm sweating.
I'm so lazy.
What's this?
I'm naked.
Good morning.
Good morning?
What are you doing?
You're naked.
That's...
Put this on.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
I'm the one who did it, right?
I'm sure Tanaka did it.
I'm sorry.
I drank too much at the event yesterday.
That's right.
It was a big deal.
That's why I did it.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Why are you sorry?
It's a big deal.
I saw it, but I couldn't stop it.
Did you see it?
Stop it.
I can't stop it.
Why?
What?
How long are you going to be naked?
That's...
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed to be seen.
It's the worst.
I'm sorry.
It's dirty.
It's okay.
It's not good.
It's really dirty.
Let's get away from each other.
I don't want to.
I'm sorry.
I was surprised because it happened all of a sudden yesterday.
All of a sudden?
Yes.
Yesterday?
It felt good.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
What are you doing?
Hey, what are you doing?
You're awake, right?
What are you doing?
Hey
I don't want to go to bed
Isn't this me?
I went out because there were a lot of Tanaka
We both had that kind of feeling
Let's do it again
What are you talking about?
I don't know what's going on
Are you cheating on me again?
I'm not cheating on you
Well
Are you serious?
I'm serious
I'm so happy
Are you sleeping?
It's hot
I'm sorry
My mouth is swollen
I'm full
What's wrong?
I feel so good
Do you wash the sheets?
Are you okay?
I feel so good
Your sheets is soaking
I want you to change your clothes
But you were wearing new clothes yesterday
What are you doing?
Are you serious?
No...
Kimchi!
Cool.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
It hurts!
I'm sorry
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
I was so scared yesterday.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
It's really okay.
I'm sweating a lot.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
Help me.
I can't do it.
Give me a hug.
Really?
I'm happy.
I can't do it.