Mayu-san, wait a minute.
What is it?
What should I do?
What's wrong?
I told you to drink it.
Drink more.
I'm fine.
Is it good?
Why are you ignoring me?
What is it?
You're drinking it, aren't you?
You like to drink it, don't you?
You should drink it, don't you?
Why have you been acting up?
I didn't think it would be like this.
I told you to drink it like this.
Why are you acting up?
What is it?
It's nothing.
I'm sorry.
I'm bleeding.
You're bleeding.
I'm sorry.
You're drinking it, aren't you?
It's nothing.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
What are you looking at?
You want me to touch you, don't you?
It's hot.
How was it?
Did it hurt?
It's soft.
Is it soft?
It's hot.
You haven't been drinking at all for a while.
You haven't been drinking.
Why haven't you been drinking?
You like to drink, don't you?
You haven't been drinking at all.
Hurry up and drink.
It's hot.
This is delicious.
Thank you very much.
You saved me.
Isn't it hot?
It's not hot.
Isn't this house beautiful?
Is that so?
How much is the rent?
The rent is normal.
Please tell me.
It's not a big deal.
Do I have to change my company's computer?
I don't know.
You're stingy.
Am I stingy?
I saved you because you stayed at my house.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
I had a lot of work.
I missed the last train because of that.
I had to do it today.
You're far away from home.
I want to move out soon.
It's annoying.
This is a very nice bed.
Don't touch it.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
Don't you drink?
I don't drink.
Can't you drink at work?
I can't drink.
There aren't many people.
I have a drink.
You should drink.
Don't hesitate.
I bought a lot.
I don't need it.
Please drink.
I don't drink.
Thank you for staying at my house today.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's good.
This is delicious.
It suppresses the effect of fat and sugar.
It's a combination of digestive and dextrose.
It's like this.
It's easy to drink.
What do you think of this?
It's easier to drink than I thought.
This is my recommendation.
I have a sense of taste like this.
I chose a drink that suits your taste.
Thank you.
Please drink.
If I drink too much, my head will be hot.
This is amazing.
I can't drink.
I don't know if I can drink.
I don't care.
If you drink too much, you can't feel the taste of alcohol.
Please drink more.
I can't stop drinking.
I see.
Please drink more.
I can drink.
What do you think of this?
It's delicious, isn't it?
You can drink.
I can't drink.
Let's drink a lot today.
I can't drink a lot.
This is delicious.
You are serious at work, aren't you?
You don't say anything silly.
You should drink a lot and have fun at work.
I can drink.
Please drink more and have fun at work.
I will make a project.
Can I invite you to make a group?
It's beautiful here.
Do you drink at my company?
Yes.
It's close to my company.
You can see your cousin.
I agree.
Your company is close to my company.
It's hard for me to talk to you.
You should quit your job.
I don't want to quit my job.
It tastes like alcohol.
Wait.
More.
It's good, isn't it?
Drink more.
It's good.
I want to lie down and sleep.
What?
Do you have a problem with me?
No, I don't.
Is it hot?
Look at this.
It's a punishment for skipping the last train.
It's a punishment.
Which one do you want?
It's hot.
Is it hard for you?
You look tired.
Do you want to lie down?
It's hot.
It's dangerous.
Get away from me.
I feel sick.
Look at my buttocks.
Do you want to take a break?
I feel sick.
Did you see me?
Did you lick my feet?
Did you see my feet?
I'll wipe your nose.
I see.
Here I go.
You want more?
Ah, feels good!
No!
I don't feel good.
Why did you stop?
I don't want to.
What?
Hurry up.
I want you to lick my hands.
Lick my hands.
I don't feel good.
Let's go.
Let's go to a bar.
I don't want to go to a bar.
I still have alcohol.
I bought a lot.
Let's go to a bar.
I'm fine.
What is this?
It's expensive.
It's not expensive.
What is this?
It's different.
What is different?
I'm tired.
Wait a minute.
What?
I need water.
You don't feel good.
I don't feel good.
Wait a minute.
I'm tired.
Do you want to pee?
You have a lot of pee.
What?
Do you want to poop?
What is this?
What?
You don't like it?
You will poop again.
What?
I'm tired.
I have a sore throat.
You have a sore throat?
No.
I have a sore throat.
You have a sore throat.
Do you want to pee?
I'm tired.
What?
I didn't do anything.
You didn't do anything?
Why?
Do you want to drink water?
Are you okay?
Is it delicious?
It's delicious.
I'm tired.
Let's go.
Oh, no.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Talk to me? About what?
I can't breathe.
You can't breathe?
Why?
Go.
I'm sorry.
No!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
He's gone.
I'm sorry.
It's still coming out.
It's all out.
Oh, no.
What? What is it?
I can't stand it.
What? You can't stand it?
You can't go without permission.
Right?
It's all right. It's all right.
I'm still standing, so I can do it.
I can still do it.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
It's hard.
Really?
What?
No.
More.
I'm sorry.
I'm going.
All right.
Oh, no.
No.
It feels good.
I'm going.
What?
Shin-chan, do you feel better?
You, too?
What?
I'm going.
It feels good.
Next, do it from behind.
From behind?
I don't know.
Do you want to do it again?
I'm sweating.
It feels good.
I'm going.
Oh, no.
More.
I'm going.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
I'm going.
Why are you taking a break?
What?
Why?
I don't know why.
It feels good.
I'm going.
Are you tired?
Yes.
Why?
I see.
Say it while looking at me.
Okay.
I'm going.
It feels good.
Are you tired?
I'm tired.
I'm going.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I'm going.
It feels good.
Why? Are you mad?
Why?
Come on, come on.
Here.
Oh, it's nice.
It feels good.
Oh, it feels good.
I want to play with you.
I can't take it anymore!
It feels so good!
Why?
I can't take it anymore!
What's wrong? Are you tired?
It's my first time doing this.
Why?
Hey, drink some water.
I can't.
Why?
You can't?
Three times.
Four times.
I thought you were going to do it on your own.
Hey, look.
Look in front of you.
Hey, drink some water.
I can't.
Why?
Hey, drink some water.
I can't.
Miyazawa-san, wake up.
We're in the elevator.
I can't.
We're almost there.
Miyazawa-san, wake up.
I can't.
You're always so serious.
Where did you go?
I can't.
You don't have to drink anymore.
You're weak.
You drink too much.
We're almost there.
Don't move too much.
I'm not moving.
You're shaking.
I'm shaking.
I can't.
Are you okay, Miyazawa-san?
We're home.
I'll put your luggage here.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Can you get up?
I'm okay.
Are you going to sleep here?
Miyazawa-san.
You're always so serious.
Where did you go?
I'm serious.
I don't want to see you sleep in a fight.
I'm not sleeping.
You're okay, right?
I'm okay.
We're almost home, so I'm going home.
Good night.
Wait.
What is it?
I'm going home.
I can't.
What do you mean?
What are you doing?
I'm giving you an order. Don't go home.
I'm scared.
I just sent you home because it's close.
This is your home. It's okay.
I can't because it's my home.
Let go of me.
I don't want to.
You have work tomorrow.
I know.
Don't pull me.
I don't want to.
I'm serious.
Let go of me.
I can't get up.
You can't get up?
It's okay if you can't get up.
I can't get up.
What are you doing?
Don't go out in a place like this.
I can't get up.
What are you doing?
Why are you taking off your clothes in a place like this?
I can't get up.
Don't make a mess.
I don't want to.
I don't want to take off my clothes.
It's dangerous.
I can't get up.
What are you doing?
Let go of me.
I can't get up.
Don't laugh.
I don't want to.
Don't pull me.
I can't get up.
Thank you very much.
What are you doing?
I can't get up.
Let me go.
I'm going to lick your boobs.
I can't get up.
Oh, it feels so good.
More, more.
I can't do it.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, it's amazing.
Tatsumi, it's amazing.
What is?
I can't do it.
Give me a kiss.
I don't know what you mean.
Why don't you give me a kiss?
Why do you keep doing that?
You drank too much.
You have a bad breath.
Do you understand?
Why do you keep doing that?
More, more.
I can't do it.
You have a bad breath.
You don't, do you?
Seriously.
Why do you keep doing that?
It's totally different.
You'll get angry if I do this.
I have a bad breath.
You drank too much.
It's painful.
You don't have to take it off.
I don't want to.
Why?
It's warm.
It's painful.
Is it painful?
It feels good.
It's painful.
Why do you keep doing that?
Touch my butt.
It's okay.
It's painful.
It's close.
I touched it.
Did you touch it?
No.
I don't know.
It feels good.
I'm going to rub it.
Rub it.
Rub my butt.
Like this?
It feels good.
It's round.
Rub it.
It feels good.
Are you done?
I rubbed it.
What's next?
My fingers.
Put your fingers in.
What?
Where?
I can't.
Give me your fingers.
Is it always like this?
It feels good.
Let me move it.
Otherwise, it doesn't feel good.
It feels good.
Is it here?
Rub it harder.
It feels good.
What should I do?
Rub it harder.
It feels good.
It's strange, isn't it?
Rub it harder.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I'm pulling it.
Rub my butt.
I don't understand.
My butt.
I've never done that.
You can rub my butt.
I can't.
Hurry up.
I'm waiting.
Are you going to rub my butt?
Yes, I am.
Rub it.
It's an order.
Are you really going to rub my butt?
Yes, I am.
I see.
Rub my butt.
It feels good.
It's strange, isn't it?
Rub my butt.
I've never done that.
It feels good.
Rub my butt.
Do you always do that?
No, I don't.
Rub my butt.
Are you all right?
It feels good.
More.
What?
What do you mean?
Rub my butt more.
Rub my butt.
Put your finger in here.
It feels good.
What's this?
Rub my butt.
Rub my butt more.
I'm taking a picture of you.
It's really low.
It's really bad.
It's bad, isn't it?
Don't tell anyone.
I'm taking a picture of you.
It's really bad.
What are you doing?
Let's really stop.
It's really hard.
It's really bad.
It smells good.
What are you doing?
I'm taking a picture of you.
It's really bad.
What's wrong with you?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm going to throw up.
I'm going to drink this at home.
Stop drinking.
It's delicious.
It's really delicious.
It's really bad.
I'm going to drink this at home.
What are you talking about?
What?
Are you drunk?
You're cute.
It's really bad.
What?
What are you doing?
It's disgusting.
I'm going to throw up.
It's really bad.
What's this?
It's disgusting.
What are you doing?
It's hard.
It's disgusting.
I want to throw up.
I'm going to throw up.
What are you doing?
Are you serious?
It's really bad.
It's disgusting.
I want to throw up more.
I'm going to throw up more.
It's disgusting.
Ah! Ah!
I'm sorry.
Ah, I'm sorry.
Ah! Ah!
Ah.
Ah, ah, ah.
I'm sorry.
She's going to yawn again.
Where are you going?
Get me a drink.
Stop it.
I don't want to.
Get me a drink.
Wait.
It feels good.
I found your ankle.
Stop it.
Can you hear me?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to sleep.
Get me a drink.
It's so good.
It's so good that I can't stop.
Stop it.
I can't stop.
It's so good.
It's so good that I can't stop.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm scared.
It feels good.
What?
Does it feel good?
I'm going to touch your nipple.
Is your nipple weak?
It feels good.
I'm scared.
It's so hot!
It's so good.
I want to eat it all.
It feels good.
It's so good.
What?
It feels good.
I can't move.
It's so warm.
It's so good.
I can't eat it yet.
Something came out.
What?
What is it?
You can do it, right?
It's an order.
What?
It feels good.
I can do it many times.
I don't know what to do.
It's so good.
I'm going to eat it again.
I'm going to eat it more.
I'm going to stand up.
It's so good.
It feels good.
Is it good?
It's so good.
It feels good.
I'm going to eat it again.
It's so good.
I'm going to stand up.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
It's so good.
Are you all right?
Are you going to sleep?
It's so good.
I hope I don't remember tomorrow.
Excuse me.
It's so good.
Why do I have to go back and forth between work and training?
I want to go home.
It's so good.
Are you hungry?
Nozomi.
What are you doing?
I'm doing overtime.
What are you drinking?
I'm sorry.
That's not good.
Throw it away.
Look for it.
I don't want to throw it away.
Can I have a drink?
No, you can't.
I'm sorry.
Can you do it all day?
I'll do my best all day.
I asked you to do it.
Do it.
I'm sorry.
It's almost the end.
It doesn't matter.
I'll do it all day.
I understand.
If you don't do it, I can't go home.
Do it properly.
I'm sorry.
You can't pay the overtime.
It can't be helped.
It doesn't matter if you can do it.
Why?
Can't you do it?
I'll do it.
How far are you going?
This is it.
This is it?
I have collected a lot.
We haven't reached the halfway yet.
It seems to be enough until now.
Why didn't I memorize all of this before?
If you have this folder, you can get the information.
Is this enough?
I don't think it's enough.
This is the end of my work.
No, you can't. Do it properly.
Really.
Atsumi, if you're going to do it, let's drink.
No, I won't.
I said let's drink.
No, I won't. Can't you just get to work?
Don't you usually drink?
No, I don't.
You're really serious.
I'm not.
I don't have enough material.
I'll collect it.
Do it properly.
Okay.
Please.
What else do you need?
There's a lot more.
Stuff like this.
Is this okay?
Yeah, that's fine.
Okay.
Atsumi.
Yeah?
Can I have a drink?
I said I don't want to.
But I'm working overtime. It's important to relax.
No, no, no.
I said I don't want to.
There's a lot of alcohol.
Please.
What are you doing?
It's a waste.
No, it's fine.
Let's drink together.
It's dangerous.
Let's drink.
Excuse me.
If you drink this, I'll drink too.
Someone might come.
It's not like it's the end of the year.
I don't know.
Let's drink.
No, no, no.
Are you drunk?
No, I'm not.
It's so dangerous.
Let's drink together.
Okay.
Are you done?
Did you drink?
I drank.
Really?
Are you sure?
I didn't drink.
I respect you.
Let's drink.
I didn't think you were so strong.
I'm sorry. I didn't see it.
You're so annoying.
Did you drink?
I drank.
Let's drink.
You're not good at drinking.
I'm not good at drinking.
You said you'd give me another one.
It's delicious.
Do you want to eat something?
No, I don't want to eat.
Let's eat together.
I don't want to eat.
What are you doing?
Where do you think you are?
I don't need it.
You're drinking.
I really don't need it.
You said you'd give me another one.
I said I'd give you another one.
Let's do our job properly.
I'll do it.
Please.
It's hard to work.
Let's drink and do our job properly.
I can't do it without you.
Okay.
Please give me another one.
Let's do our job properly.
Okay.
Natsumi.
Natsumi, let's do our job properly.
She drank a lot.
It's really hard.
Natsumi.
I can see you.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Can't you drink alcohol?
It's hot.
I can't drink it.
You're a coward.
Look at me.
It's hot, isn't it?
I can't look at you.
Look at me.
Why can't I look at you?
Why?
Look at me.
Let's stop this.
This is an H cup.
Look at me.
I can't look at you.
You're too strong.
Why?
I'm not weak.
Look at me.
I can't look at you.
Why can't I look at you?
I'm not weak.
I can't look at you.
You're drunk.
Let go of my hand.
I can't look at you.
I can't drink alcohol.
Why don't you kiss me?
I can't kiss you.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to take a shower.
Please forgive me.
I don't care.
Let's finish this.
I don't want to.
I don't care.
I'm going to take a shower.
And I'm going to kiss you.
You are standing up.
That's amazing.
Let's finish this.
I'm going to change my clothes.
I don't care.
I'm going to take a shower.
What's going on?
I'm going to touch your butt.
Are you done?
No.
Can you be more gentle?
I'm not gentle.
I'm going to kiss you.
It's not painful, is it?
I'm not gentle.
I'm going to kiss you.
Why?
It's okay.
You are strong.
Don't move.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
Don't move.
It's okay.
Lick my anus.
I have an anus.
You usually lick my anus.
Why?
Wait a minute.
Don't lick my anus.
Why don't you lick my anus?
I've never heard of it.
Why are you licking my anus?
Lick my anus.
Hurry up.
Why don't you lick my anus?
I've never licked your anus.
I want to talk to you here.
Stop it.
Are you serious?
Of course I'm serious.
Stop it.
Don't you like it?
I don't like it.
Stop it.
Hurry up.
Okay.
You're too loud.
It's okay.
Can you continue?
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
Do you want more?
Stop it.
I don't feel good.
You're crying.
What's wrong?
What is it?
You look painful, so I gave you some medicine.
That's right.
I think you're getting big.
I'm fine.
Don't be serious.
Why are you so serious when you're drinking?
I'm not serious.
What?
It's amazing. It's hard.
Let's close this.
Why?
It's amazing.
Look, it's in such a good place.
Are you still drinking?
It's amazing.
Does the alcohol hurt?
No, it's fine.
I'm sorry.
Why?
It's fine.
Is it this way?
No, it's not.
It's Mr. Hoshigari.
Mr. Hoshigari, it's amazing.
I wanted you to do this.
No, it's not.
It's amazing.
You're so serious.
No, it's fine.
Let's stop.
You look like you're in a good mood.
I'm in a good mood.
Isn't it good?
No, it's not.
It's amazing.
It's hard.
Do you like being pinched?
No, I like it.
But I'm in a bad mood.
Why?
It's amazing.
What do you want to do?
Do you want to be in a good mood?
No?
I want to be in a good mood.
Let's do it.
Really?
No.
Let's do it.
I'll do it.
No.
Let's do it.
Really?
It's amazing.
You're big.
No.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Please take it off.
No.
Don't disturb me.
Why?
It's amazing.
It's hot.
You scared me.
It's good.
You're getting bigger.
It's good, isn't it?
It feels good.
It's good.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's hot.
One more time.
It's good, isn't it?
Please sit here.
What?
Don't lie to me.
I'm going to sleep.
It's hot.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
No.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can't do it anymore.
It's hot.
Please sit here.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's good.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm going to sleep.
What are you doing?
It's hot.
I'm sleepy.
Let's do it again.
Again?
It's hot.
I'm sleepy.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Let's go.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'm scared of your room.
I'm sorry.
I only have alcohol.
That's alcohol, isn't it?
That's right.
I don't drink alcohol.
It's my fault that I'm late today.
That's right.
You don't drink alcohol, do you?
Is that so?
I only have alcohol in the refrigerator.
Do you live such a healthy life?
That's right.
Which do you like better?
I only have alcohol.
That's right.
Which do you like better?
I think this is easier to drink.
That's right.
Then I'll choose this.
Let's have a toast.
Cheers.
It smells like alcohol.
That's right.
Do you drink such strong alcohol?
Cheers.
How is it?
It's a little bitter.
That's right.
I only drink such strong alcohol.
I don't know why I don't drink alcohol.
I'm sorry.
I haven't cleaned up my desk at all.
You haven't cleaned up your desk at all.
I thought I should clean up my desk more.
I'm sorry.
I've been busy with work lately.
I haven't been able to clean up my desk.
It's not good to not be able to clean up your desk.
I'm sorry.
Let's clean up your desk.
I think you should work more efficiently.
That's right.
I'm sorry for bothering you.
You know what you're doing.
It's important to report it.
You don't have to report it.
I helped you today.
I'm sorry.
I want you to report it.
I said the same thing before.
I see.
I didn't come this late.
I told you repeatedly that this hadn't happened many times.
Yes.
Every time, you apologize, but this happens.
Can't you be a little more careful when you apologize?
That's right.
I'm careful.
You shouldn't attention to it.
Yes.
Yeah.
Really.
What should I do?
I want you to do it properly.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I don't know if it's because it's a time like this, but I feel a little delicious.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
That's good.
If you don't mind.
Yeah.
I don't know if it's just sake.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Really.
Yeah.
If you don't mind, I have some garlic.
Oh, it's okay.
I don't want to drink that much, so it's okay.
Is it good?
Oh, that's good.
Yeah.
Nanami, you said you don't usually drink.
What do you do when you drink?
I drink oolong tea.
Oh, oolong tea.
I don't know why I have to drink sake at a drinking party now.
Oh, that's right.
It's a long time ago.
I don't need oolong tea at all.
I mean, what's so fun about the club?
I think I have to go to such a drinking party.
Yeah.
I don't drink sake, so I have to ask you a lot of questions.
You say something meaningless.
If you drink sake all the time, you'll be a bad adult.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
Don't be like that.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
I'll be careful.
You should refresh the contents of the refrigerator.
Oh, yes.
I'm going to check the contents of the refrigerator.
Oh, really?
Maybe there's water in there.
Oh.
This is all I need for sake.
Oh, I see.
I'm going to check it.
Yeah.
What's this?
But it's a small amount, so I can drink it.
Yeah.
It's not strong, is it?
It's pretty good.
Oh, excuse me.
I found a snack.
Would you like to eat it?
What?
Mr. Nanami.
You really can't drink sake.
What?
Hey, Mr. Nanami.
Your underwear is also round.
No.
Oh.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Do you have sake?
I'll put it down there.
Oh.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Look at this.
Oh, yes.
It's hot in this room.
Oh, is that so?
I'm sorry.
I didn't notice.
It's hot.
Can I take off my shirt?
What?
I'll open it.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, Mr. Nanami.
What?
Are you all right?
I'm all right.
I'm wearing beautiful underwear today.
No, I didn't mean that.
Yeah.
You drank too much.
I'm all right.
Oh.
It's hot.
You drank too much.
I'm all right.
By the way...
Yes?
You know...
Hang in there.
Oh, yes.
Hey.
Hang in there.
Oh, yes.
Do you know how hard it is?
I'm sorry.
Yes.
It's a penalty game.
What?
Penalty game?
Penalty game.
Yes.
What?
What are you doing?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Hey.
What's wrong?
What?
You shouldn't spill it.
But...
I didn't mean to spill it.
It's a penalty game.
Why did you spill it?
I didn't mean to spill it.
You mean you can't drink the alcohol I gave you?
No, I didn't mean that.
You didn't mean that?
You're so mean.
What's wrong?
What?
It's...
It's not good.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Do you want me to take it off?
What?
It's hot.
No.
What?
It's hot.
What do you want me to do?
I can't do anything.
Why are you wearing a jacket all the time?
What?
Well...
That's enough.
Ta-da!
This is a game I got from my boss.
A game?
A game.
I think alcohol is a game.
Let's play a game.
What do you want me to do?
Let's play a game with your nipples.
A game with my nipples?
Yes.
What's that?
You can touch my nipples.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Let's play a game.
Come on.
You want me to touch your nipples?
Yes.
Can't I touch your nipples?
That's not what I meant.
Don't you get it?
You know what I mean, right?
Is it really okay?
Come on.
Hurry up.
Okay.
How about here?
Do it again.
Do it again?
How about here?
That's not what I meant.
Do it again.
Is it here?
That's right.
How about here?
Do both at the same time.
Both?
Yes.
Do it at once.
At once?
Yes.
Is it here?
That's right.
It's my turn next.
Do I have to do it too?
It's my turn.
Yes.
Right?
It's going to be fun.
Where is it?
Right?
Is it hard?
Here?
No.
You can't do it?
No, I can't.
What?
You can't do it?
No, I can't.
You can't do it, right?
Really?
You can't do it.
Why not?
I can do it.
I want to see it.
What are you doing? Why are you wearing it?
Why are you wearing it?
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
What do you mean?
I'm embarrassed.
I can't look at you.
Let's go.
I found it.
It's your nipple.
I thought you didn't have it.
Why are you licking me?
I'm just touching you.
I don't care.
I'm sweating.
What?
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
You don't want me to do it?
I don't want you to do it.
Do you know how hard I tried to give birth to you?
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to do it?
I want you to do it.
You did it.
I didn't expect you to do it.
You're funny.
Do you want to see my nipple?
I want to see it.
Don't you want to see it?
I don't want to see it.
No.
Then, look at it.
You're my senior.
What are you doing?
Then, look at it.
Are you sure it's okay?
It's okay.
I'm just touching you.
Touch me.
Don't you want me to touch you?
I don't mean that.
Let me touch you.
Here?
Yes.
I have a nipple.
I see.
I think you should touch me.
Is that so?
Yes.
You're so cute.
Thank you.
Hey, Murata.
Yes.
I don't have alcohol.
Alcohol?
Yes.
Do you still want to drink?
Isn't it bad to drink more than this?
Why?
Yes.
My boss told me that you wanted alcohol.
I'm sorry.
Hurry up.
I see.
Is this okay?
Yes.
Open your mouth.
Okay.
Thank you.
It's bad to drink all at once.
It's okay.
This is strong.
What?
It's hot.
Don't you think it's hot?
I think so.
Don't you think this is hot?
That's...
This.
That?
Tear this off.
Tear this off?
Yes.
If I tear this off, I'll use it for work.
Is this okay?
But...
Are you going to tear this off?
Tear this off.
But I can't do anything else.
I told you to tear this off.
Just tear this off.
I'm sorry.
Hurry up.
Don't you know how to tear this off?
Are you sure?
Hurry up.
I'll tear this off.
It's hot.
Okay.
I'll do it.
Hurry up.
Did you make a hole?
Yes.
Is this okay?
A little more.
Not yet?
I think I have a cold.
Is this okay?
Touch here.
Where?
Here.
Are you going to touch here?
Yes.
I'm sleepy.
It's nice, isn't it?
It's nice.
Are you sleepy?
Yes.
Touch here a little more.
Here?
A little more.
Around here?
Is it that deep?
Yes.
Here?
It feels good.
Does it feel good here?
Yes.
Keep doing it.
Okay.
I'm sleepy.
A little more.
It's wide.
It's wide, isn't it?
I think so.
I'm sleepy.
Put your fingers in.
My fingers?
Yes.
Here.
Put your fingers in.
Okay.
Here?
I'm going to put my fingers in.
Are you going to do it?
I'm sleepy.
It feels good.
It's different.
What's different?
I'm sorry.
I want you to do this more.
Is it that good?
Yes.
I'm sleepy.
Hey.
Do you have alcohol?
Yes, I do.
Look at me.
My hands are down.
I'm sorry.
It's different.
What's different?
Look at me.
Look at me?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
What's wrong?
Are you naked?
No, I'm not.
Hey.
Yes.
I'm naked, too.
Take it off.
It's embarrassing.
No.
Take it off.
Hurry up.
I'm sorry.
Take it off.
Okay.
You're always late for work.
What's wrong with this?
It's a little...
I wanted to play because I kissed you.
Did you kiss me?
Is this what happens when you kiss me?
Yes.
Don't you need underwear anymore?
Do you have underwear?
Let's take it off.
Take it off.
I'm sorry.
Why are you so grumpy?
Wait a minute.
Because...
I don't know why.
Your feet...
My feet?
Your feet are touching.
My feet are touching?
It's because my feet don't touch.
No.
Well...
What?
What's wrong?
It's a little...
What's wrong with you?
What?
Your finger?
It's not my finger.
It's not your finger?
Don't you like to be touched with your finger?
No.
What's wrong?
It's a little...
What?
I'm tired.
It's hot.
What?
I don't need this.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
What?
Nothing.
Why?
It's different from usual.
Are you okay?
It's hot, isn't it?
Yes.
Don't you like it?
I'm fine.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
You can't see me, can you?
I can't do it.
You are good at it.
Hey, everyone.
Next, lick this side.
What?
This side.
Do I have to lick that side, too?
Yes, you do.
But...
Won't you lick that side?
I've never licked that side.
Then, it's your first time.
Yes, but...
Hurry up.
Okay.
I'm really going to lick it.
I said it's okay.
Okay.
Here I go.
I see.
It's okay.
It feels good.
Do it more.
I can't do it.
I'm going to lick it.
That felt good.
Do it more.
I'm going to lick it.
It's fun.
I said it's okay.
It feels good.
That's good.
That's bad.
That feels good.
I can't do it.
I'm going to lick it.
That feels good.
I didn't think you were so good at it.
No.
I don't need it.
What's wrong with you?
You've been fine.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
It's nothing?
I'm sorry.
I'll make sure it's nothing.
It's nothing.
I'm sorry.
It's nothing?
It's nothing.
It's not good.
What's not good?
It feels so good.
This is not good?
It's not good.
You're twitching.
What's wrong?
It's not good.
I can't take it anymore.
What are you talking about?
What am I talking about?
If I say I can't take it anymore, this is the only thing I can do.
Isn't that bad?
It's okay.
It feels good.
This is not good.
It feels so good that it's not good.
It's not good?
What's not good?
It's nothing.
You're doing it on your own.
I can't take it anymore.
You can't take it anymore?
It feels so good.
It feels good.
It's not good.
It hurts.
It feels good.
What's wrong?
It's not good.
I can't take it anymore.
You did it.
It's not good.
Do you like my butt?
Yes.
What?
I like your butt.
Really?
It feels good.
It's not good.
I'm going.
It feels good.
It's not good.
I'm going.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
You can do more.
Can I do more?
Can't you do more?
I can do more.
You can do more, right?
Yes.
Come on.
Lie down.
Yes.
It's not good.
It feels good.
Lie down.
It's not good.
It feels good.
I want to do more.
Lie down.
It's not good.
It feels good.
Murata.
Yes.
I want to lick you.
Do you want to lick me?
Here.
Lick here.
Here?
Here.
Come on.
It feels good.
Lick me.
Yes.
It feels good.
Don't do that.
Lick me.
Yes.
It feels good.
Do it again.
Yes.
It feels good.
Don't do that.
Murata.
It feels good.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Lick me.
It feels good.
This is not good.
I can't do that.
En-chan!
Go!
It feels good.
I can't do that.
It's coming.
Murata.
What did you do again?
It's hot.
This is not good.
What is not good?
What are you doing?
I want you to lick me.
It feels good.
Murata.
It's fun.
It's fun, isn't it?
It's not good if you drink too much.
I don't want to.
OK.
I'm counting on you.
Did you take medicine for two days?
I'm fine.
OK.
You don't have to do anything extra.
I'll do all the work.
You just drink alcohol.
I understand.
You said something strange the other day.
Be careful.
Do you understand?
Let's go.
I'm counting on you.
OK.
Let me go.
I'm fine.
Wait a minute.
We're almost home.
I'm fine.
Let me help you.
Let's go.
We're home.
Where are we?
Be careful.
Wait a minute.
This is the front door.
Kana.
Wait a minute.
Let's put this on.
Be careful.
Wipe it off.
I can't.
Wait a minute.
We're home.
This is the front door.
Come on.
Get up.
This is the front door.
Wait a minute.
You're drunk.
I'm not drunk.
I'll have to get you to drink.
I have to refuse more.
Protect me.
I understand.
I'll protect you from next time.
Please be strong.
I'm not drunk.
Don't sleep here.
Fukuda.
I didn't think I'd be this drunk.
Let's move.
I'll carry you to your bed.
You can't sleep here.
Please get up.
I'm not drunk.
Why are you taking it off?
It's hot.
I'm not always angry.
Give me a kiss.
What are you talking about?
I'm not drunk.
Can't you give me a kiss?
Thank me.
Thank you.
You have to give me a kiss.
My nose is running.
You're good.
Don't you like it?
Don't you like me?
Give me a kiss.
I'm not drunk.
I understand.
Why do you always work?
I'm tired.
I'm sorry.
Give me a kiss.
Touch me.
I'm lonely.
Give me a kiss.
I understand.
Why?
Why don't you look at me?
You're always working.
That's not true.
You don't look at me as a woman.
Woman?
I'm a boss.
I understand.
You like me, don't you?
Wait a minute.
Why?
Why don't you look at me?
Don't cry.
I understand.
Touch me.
Give me a kiss.
Don't touch me.
Touch me.
Wait a minute.
I'm not drunk.
I understand.
Give me a kiss.
You like me, don't you?
I don't like you.
I like you.
I understand.
You're an angel.
I sympathize with you.
I understand.
No.
Okay.
Wait!
Hey.
Hurry.
What?
Lick me.
Lick you?
Where?
Lick me.
Here?
Hey.
You can't lick me.
I can lick you.
What?
It's really cold.
Come on.
It feels good.
Lick me harder.
Harder?
Hey.
Yes?
Lick me.
Lick me, Amaru.
Okay.
Lick me.
Like this?
It feels good.
Lick me.
Ouch.
It feels good.
Ah!
Ah.
Ah...
I may have seen you wrong.
Yes.
Can you sleep?
I'm going to sleep.
It's so hot.
I'm so sleepy.
I know.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm thirsty.
Are you thirsty?
You'd better stop drinking.
I don't want to.
What?
Are you playing with me?
No, I'm not.
Go away.
Look at me.
You're playing with me.
Well...
Wait a minute.
Ah.
You're sneezing.
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are.
Ah.
If you put that much in your mouth, you'll spit it out.
It feels good.
What?
Ah.
It's a good snack.
What are you talking about?
Ah.
It's sweet.
It tastes like grapes.
Ah.
It tastes like sake.
Hey.
Yes?
I want you.
You want me?
Kiss me.
What?
Ah.
You'll kiss me until the end, won't you?
Yes.
Ah.
Then.
Yes.
You'll kiss me until the end, won't you?
Until the end?
Well...
What?
You won't do it?
Well...
Ah.
Yes.
I'll do it.
Ah.
You're a girl.
Be nice to me.
What?
What do you mean?
I'll kiss you.
Ah.
What?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
I'm sorry.
I think you should stop it.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
Kana-san.
You can see my butt, right?
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I told you to stop it.
Wait a minute.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
It feels good.
I told you to stop it.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I'm going out.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I'm going out.
One more time.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to fall.
One more time.
Can I do it again?
I'm sorry.
Please, I beg you.
I understand.
Ouch!
You're sweating a lot.
No, I'm not.
I'm not,
I haven't licked you for a while.
Have some water.
I'm in a hurry.
Because I need to mean.
How comfortable!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Ah ah ah ah ah no
Takamatsu
ah ah
centimeter
had
Thank you for watching!