I'm home.
Satomi is here.
I'm going to wash my hands.
Jiro?
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I was thinking about washing my hands.
I'm sorry.
Use it.
Don't worry about it.
I'll wash my hands after you get dressed.
It's okay.
I'm not in a hurry.
But you want to wash your hands, don't you?
Don't worry about it. Use it.
I don't care.
Hurry up.
But...
I don't care.
I'll do it right away.
I finished work earlier than usual today.
So I was thinking about washing my hands.
I see.
Did you finish work earlier than usual today?
Yes, I finished earlier than usual today.
I see. You didn't have a club activity today.
Yes.
You're always working hard, aren't you?
I'm just doing my best.
By the way, your mom and dad went out today.
They said they'd be late.
I see.
I didn't say anything in the morning.
Your dad is an interesting person, isn't he?
What?
Is that so?
I've been living with him since I was a kid.
I thought it was normal.
You've been talking a lot lately, haven't you?
What do you think of my mom?
What?
Well...
I think she's kind.
She said you were a good girl.
Is that true?
It's strange to be siblings, isn't it?
Oh, I see.
You're a little nervous, aren't you?
You're not used to it yet, are you?
Oh, I see.
I didn't think you were my sister.
But we're family, so don't worry too much.
Little by little.
Oh, I see.
Say anything you want.
Like a real sister.
Oh, I see.
I have to do my homework.
Good luck.
Oh, yes.
If you don't understand something, ask me.
Oh, I see.
It's still awkward.
It's hard to get straight.
Oh, I see.
F cup
But...
Right now...
Here, I feel some phlegm my body.
He looks healthy...
I feel refreshed
Chiro
What should I do?
Wait
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Jiro.
What's wrong with you?
Stop it.
You can take a shower.
What's wrong with you?
Open your legs.
You have to take a shower.
You have to open your legs.
I think you're still wet.
You have to take a shower.
Look.
Be careful.
I'm sorry.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
ah ah ah ah ah
ah...
Hush...
Huh?
I couldn't sleep tonight.
Good night...
I'll see you tomorrow.
But
Well...
Come on
I'm coming
Dear, stay strong
Ah!
He asked me to sprinkle some chookies
He said he wasn't hungry
This is good
Yeah
I feel my hands getting tired
Yeah..
I feel my muscles cramping
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
sa, sa, sa, sa, sa, sa, sa, sa,
ah, ta- ah!
Eh!
Aick-
ah..!
Go..
Go..hm..
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
What did you say?
What?
What did I say?
I'm sorry.
This part.
She brought the toilet so that I could go to the bath  interessante.
It looks okay because the water didn't fill up.
After all it is necessary to wait for the water to be filled up thoroughly.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
, son, it looks like he has a few weeks left till the final house anyway,
where should I live ?
I'm sorry.
I told you to say something, didn't I?
No, I didn't.
Say something.
I'm sorry.
I was so excited.
Can I?
I'm sorry.
I was so excited.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
my
me
ame
ぇ
Its hard
It's not that I'm busy, but I'm a bit tired.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to talk.
Oh, my God.
Whoa whoa whoa...
I'll trust you.
I'm so hungry.
I'll get you some water.
I'll wash you.
I'll wash you thoroughly.
Come here.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Do you feel good?
Get up.
Get up, everyone.
I've been watching you.
You have beautiful legs.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
You fell asleep again.
It feels good.
I'm not nervous anymore.
That's good.
I want to get along with you as much as I can.
It feels good.
Isn't this cake delicious?
What kind of cake is this?
This is the most popular shortcake in a famous shop.
It's really delicious.
I've never had such a delicious cake.
I love this cake.
This place is really popular.
There are a lot of queues.
Is this a place where people can line up?
That's right.
That's amazing.
Do you think this cake is really delicious?
Is it delicious?
It's really delicious.
I'm glad you like sweets.
I can eat as many cakes as I want.
That's right.
Did you buy this cake in a line?
Yes.
I wanted to eat this cake with you.
I bought this cake in a line in the morning.
Did you buy this cake in a line in the morning?
I'm sorry.
I'm glad you like sweets.
I'm glad I can eat this cake.
Why don't you go to that cake shop with me next time?
Do you want me to go with you?
Don't you want to go shopping with me?
I don't hate it.
I'm a little embarrassed to go out with you.
I'm not embarrassed.
I'm just wondering if it's okay.
I want to go shopping with you.
I'm fine with that.
I'm still a little nervous.
Don't you think so?
I'm not used to it yet.
You still call me REIRA.
I want you to call me sister.
I'm sorry.
I'm still a little embarrassed to call you sister.
Is it okay for me to call you like that?
That's not true.
We are brothers.
Don't you hate it?
I don't hate it at all.
I want to go somewhere with you.
Don't be nervous.
Thank you.
This is really delicious.
This has a local fresh cream.
Is that so?
Yes, it is.
Can you see it?
I can see it.
It's a little further down.
It's not there.
It's here.
Don't go there.
It's more to the right.
Is it here?
It's here.
Can you see it?
It's a little further down.
It's there.
Can you see it?
I can see it.
I can't see it at all.
Can't you see it?
Yes.
I can see it.
It's around here.
That's right.
Okay.
Thank you.
I got it.
I'm glad.
I'm sorry.
It's nothing.
It's more delicious.
Is it delicious?
Yes.
I'll eat it.
I'm glad.
Did you finish it?
Thank you for the meal.
It was delicious.
Yes.
Thank you for the meal.
Can I eat this?
I'll eat it.
No.
Thank you for the meal.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad.
Today, I went out for a while, and it seems that my parents will be back late.
Oh, you said that.
Yes, I said that.
So I'm thinking of making all the dinner.
Do you make dinner?
Yes, I do.
So I'm thinking of making dinner.
I'm very grateful.
Really? That's good.
What kind of dinner do you like?
I don't like any kind of dinner.
I'm thinking of what to eat.
What's wrong?
I thought it would be hard to wash dishes.
So I thought I should help you.
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Thank you.
You are so kind.
I think you are kinder than me.
I'm so happy.
I want to go to many places with you.
Really?
Yes.
I want to go to the amusement park.
How about the amusement park or aquarium?
Amusement park?
I want to go to a movie.
I want to go somewhere with you.
I want to do many things with you.
That sounds fun.
I'm hungry.
What's wrong?
I was thinking of wiping the ceiling.
My mom told me to clean the ceiling.
Really?
But it's not dirty.
Is that so?
If you fall on the table, you'll get hurt.
That's right.
It's better than I thought.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
I'm going to clean the bathroom.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
I was surprised.
I'm scared.
I'm always worried about Rira's chest and buttocks.
I can see her chest and buttocks.
I'm scared.
Can I bear it?
Rira, you look great.
I can see your chest better than before.
I'm scared.
I can see your chest and buttocks.
Can I bear it?
I'm scared.
I can see your chest and buttocks.
I can't bear it.
I'm scared.
It's dirty.
A little more.
What are you doing?
Don't do that.
Let me go.
What's wrong?
Don't do that.
What are you doing?
No.
No!
Don't pull me...
Yuuma-kun!
No!
No, no!
Pulling!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
, oh, oh, but
I'm sorry , I'm
in trouble because it's
close,
a little
I'm sorry.
You have to wash it.
Is there you okay okay?
Did you get angry with me?
Do not worry
I got a headache
I'm so sleepy.
Dad, please wait a minute.
He doesn't understand...
It's cold, it's cold.
What am I going to do?
I'm scared.
I'll do it again.
It feels so good.
I'll make you feel better.
I'm scared.
It feels so good.
It felt so good.
I'm scared.
I'm going to get seasick again.
What should I do?
But you're already seasick.
I just need to wash away my sleepiness, right?
Okay.
This is bad.
I'm going to throw up.
This feels good.
I threw up a lot again.
I'm going to throw up.
This feels good.
I want to do it again.
Let's go over there.
I want to do it from above next time.
I'm going to throw up again.
I'm going to throw up.
This feels good.
I want to do it again.
I'm going to throw up again.
This feels good.
Are you okay?
I'm going to throw up a lot.
I want to do it again.
Are you okay?
I'm going to throw up a lot.
This feels good.
I threw up again.
Are you really okay?
I'm fine.
I'm going to take a bath.
I'm sorry.
Doro.
Doro, wake up.
Maya.
How long have you been sleeping?
I'm sorry.
I slept late last night.
Wake up.
It's night.
Is it that late?
Maya.
I cleaned the bath.
Do you want to take a bath first?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Your father and my mother are going home late today.
So, take a bath first.
Don't you take a bath?
I'm sorry.
I cleaned the bath.
I'll take a bath later.
I'm sorry.
Why do you look that way?
You always look that way.
I don't look that way.
You don't talk to me that way.
I'm still a little...
Let's get used to each other.
It's been a month since we started living together.
We are close brothers.
Let's get along.
I'm not used to it yet.
It was a sudden thing.
It's been a month.
Slowly?
Look at me and talk to me.
I'm still a little...
No?
No.
I don't hate you.
I don't have a father or a mother.
Do you have any laundry?
I think so.
There are a lot of laundry here.
When did you buy this?
I'll wash it.
There's a lot of laundry here.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Nothing?
I'll wash it.
I'm sorry.
Can I take a bath first?
Can I have a bath first?
with Maya
I can't live on my own.
Haa...
I don't know if she really hates to be petted.
I wonder why she doesn't feel good...
I've started petting her devliously...
I really have to get used to be petting...
Yeah...how can we get along with her...?
Wow
I want to go home
Ah
But I want to swim
This is crazy.
Awesome!!
This is really awesome.
This is really awesome!!
I can't.
Wait
Wait wait, wait a minute.
just...
I can't wait!
I just can't wait!
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wait a moment, wait a moment.
Is this really happening?
Wait a minute.
Wait no no no
Ahahahaha
No no no
Aーーーーーハッハフッハー
Hey, stop it!
Stop it!
Hey, stop!
Hey, stop it!
Stop it!
Hey!
Please wait a moment.
Hey, hey!
Hey, please stop.
Hey, stop it!
Stop it
No, no, no, no.
Hey, wait a minute.
Hey, hey.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Ah, ah, ah.
Hey, hey, hey.
What are you doing?
Hey.
Ah.
Hey, where are you going?
What's up?
She is in a hurry.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
Wait, wait.
Ah.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait.
It's cold.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
A little more.
I can't stop crying.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
Ah, it feels good
Ah it feels good
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
feels so good
feeeels so good
my eyes are watering
arden gå터면 오겠다
It feels good.
She can't stop.
It's going away.
Let me flush the toilet again.
You shouldn't do it, Shi-chan!
Huh?
Shit!
You can do it, Shi-chan.
You are almost there.
I think I thought a lot about it.
Wait!
I know!
Don't!
Hey!
I'm sorry, I yelled at you, but what you did
It's cold.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Stop.
It feels good.
Stop it.
It hurts.
I can't do it anymore.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, no.
Ah, it feels so good.
I can't do it because I'm sensitive.
I can't do it. I'll go.
Ah, no. No. I'll go.
I'll go.
Exhaling
Urgh.
Ah...
Nah.
This feels great.
Aaah!
Ow.
That feels great.
Oh oh oh oh oh no no no no no no!
Oh no!
I'm going to sleep.
I feel good.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, it tickles.
But I dared to touch her.
Let's go.
Oh, it feels good.
No, no, no.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Oh, it's hot.
Kaho-san, dad and mom are not coming back home.
Let's do a little more.
No, no, no, no.
I'm tired, so let's take a break.
Let's do more.
Yes, yes, yes.
Let's go, Kaho-san.
Yes, let's go.
Oh, wait a minute.
Kaho-san, let's take a break.
I'm home.
I'm still not used to it.
Tsukasa-kun, welcome home.
Oh, I'm home.
What's wrong? Isn't it early today?
Oh, is that so?
I think it's earlier than usual.
Didn't you do anything?
Dad and mom are out now.
I'm going shopping now.
Tsukasa-kun, are you okay to stay at home alone?
Oh, I'm fine.
Are you okay? You're trembling.
No, I'm fine.
You're not sick, are you?
No, I'm not.
Well, take care of yourself.
I'm going shopping now.
Take care.
I'm going.
My shoes are old, so I have to buy new ones.
Let's buy new ones.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Is that so?
Yes.
Are you still not used to your life?
No, I'm not.
Are you still not used to me?
Are you confused because I'm older than you?
No, I'm not.
You don't like me, do you?
No, I don't.
You really don't?
I'm glad you don't hate me.
I'm going shopping now.
Make sure you lock the door.
Take care.
Bye.
I can't get used to it at all.
My hips and chest are amazing.
I'm home.
I can't get used to it at all.
Welcome home, Tsutaya.
Thanks.
What do you think of the clothes I bought yesterday?
What?
What is it?
Is it weird?
No, it's not weird.
I bought it because I thought it was cute.
Is it bad?
I think it's weird.
I'm going to my friend's wedding.
I'm going to wear it.
Is it weird?
No, it's not weird.
I'm going to wear it now.
I'd like to hear what you think of it.
What do you think?
No, I don't think it's weird.
What do you think of the length?
Do you think it's short?
What did you say?
Can't you see it?
What do you think of it from behind?
What do you think of it?
Is it short?
What do you think of the color?
There are many colors.
I chose this color because I thought it would suit me.
What do you think of it?
Is it bad?
I think it looks good on you.
Really?
Yes.
I'm glad you like it.
I'm going to wear it now.
Did you eat any snacks?
No, I haven't eaten anything yet.
You haven't eaten anything yet?
I'm hungry, so I'm wondering if there's anything to eat.
Let's look for it.
There are a lot of things in it.
Which one should I choose?
I think this is good.
Hmm...
What should I do?
There's something like this.
Hey!
Tsukasa-kun!
Stop it, Tsukasa-kun!
Hey! Stop it!
Tsukasa-kun!
Hey!
Are you listening?
Stop it!
Ouch!
Tsukasa-kun!
Stop it!
It feels so good!
Tsukasa-kun!
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Tsukasa-kun!
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Hey!
Stop it!
Tsukasa-kun!
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
Stop it.
Ouch!
Oh no, oh no...
Ah, it's hot.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Do it to me, too.
No, no, no.
Do it.
Can I?
You're good.
It feels good.
More.
It's hot.
It's okay.
It's amazing.
Tsukasa, it feels good.
Stop it.
It's hot.
It's okay.
Do it more.
More.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's okay.
It's hot.
Calm down.
Stop it.
It's hot.
I can't do it anymore.
I want to do it again.
Can I?
One more time.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Stop it.
I can do it again.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Tsukasa.
It's amazing.
Stop it.
It feels good.
I can do it.
It's hot.
Stop it.
I want to do it again.
Can I?
It's hot.
Tsukasa.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
It feels good.
I want to do it again.
I want to do it harder.
Come closer.
Tsukasa, come closer.
Tsukasa.
It feels good.
Stop it.
I can do it again.
I can do it.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I can do it.
It feels good.
Tsukasa.
Come closer.
I can do it.
It's hot.
I'm going crazy.
No, Tsukasa.
Tsukasa.
I can do it.
I want to do it more.
Tsukasa.
I can do it.
Are you okay?
It's too hot.
I'm sorry.
I'm going out.
I can do it.
I want to do it again.
Me, too.
Wait a minute.
I can do it.
I can't get used to a new house.
I'll go to the convenience store.
I'm sorry.
Ayumu.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the convenience store.
I'm going, too.
But I don't have much money.
It's okay. I'll pay for you.
I don't want you to pay for me.
I'll give you a discount.
I don't know how to say a discount.
I don't know if it's a good idea.
But I don't look good in a discount.
No, you don't.
But...
It doesn't matter.
What did you want to buy?
I wanted to buy some sweets.
That's not a big deal.
I'm older than you, so let me be older than you.
No, no, no.
I don't think that's a good idea.
It's okay.
Why?
I don't know why.
I can do it myself.
Am I a nuisance to you?
No, no, no.
I don't think you're a nuisance to me.
Am I a nuisance to you?
No, no, no.
I'm not a nuisance to you.
But I can do it myself.
I'll buy some sweets.
You can go with me.
No, no, no.
I'll buy some sweets.
I can't get used to this life.
What should I do?
Ayumu.
Yes.
What were you doing?
I was looking at the ceiling.
Were you looking at the ceiling?
Yes.
I thought you were bored.
What?
What's wrong?
Ayumu.
Don't you think I'm a nuisance to you?
No, that's not true.
What?
You haven't looked at me at all.
No, you're right.
No, you're wrong.
No, no, no.
It's normal.
No, it's not normal.
Alice, what's wrong?
You haven't looked at me at all.
No, it's normal for me.
But you're talking to my mom normally, aren't you?
Yes, but we're the same.
I think we're talking in the same way.
No, we're not.
Am I a nuisance to you?
No, it's not like that.
I'm not a nuisance to you at all.
I thought the sun was strange at all.
No, it's normal.
Isn't this room hot?
Is that so?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Why don't you do something and play?
Do something?
What is it?
Don't you want to do something?
What do I want to do?
But I don't have a hobby.
I don't have a game.
I don't read manga.
Then massage me.
Massage?
I'll do it for you first.
It's okay.
I've never had a stiff shoulder.
Is that so?
Yes.
Then massage me.
Even if you tell me to do it...
I have a stiff shoulder.
I'm sure it's stiff.
I see.
You've had a stiff shoulder for a long time, haven't you?
I think so.
Why?
I don't know.
Can you massage my shoulder from behind?
Shoulder?
Massage me.
I've never done it before.
It's okay.
Please.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
You can put more pressure on me.
Can I put more pressure on you?
Yes.
Like this?
Yes, it feels good.
How is it?
It's not stiff at all.
You can put more pressure on me.
More?
Like this?
Yes, it feels good.
How is it?
It's not stiff at all.
You can put more pressure on me.
Like this?
I want you to put more pressure on my right shoulder.
Your right shoulder?
Yes.
Around here?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Is this okay?
I think I put more pressure on you.
I'm sorry.
Is this okay?
Yes, it feels good.
Can you put more pressure on the inside?
Inside?
Yes.
Around here?
Excuse me.
Yes, it feels good.
It's hot.
I feel better.
Really?
That's good.
Can you do my waist next?
Next?
My waist?
Yes.
Is it okay?
It's not okay.
I'm sorry.
Please.
Is my waist okay?
Yes.
Is this okay?
Yes, it feels good.
That's good.
Doesn't it hurt?
No, it doesn't.
My waist hurts a lot.
Does it?
Yes.
Why?
Does it get stiff?
Yes, it tends to get stiff.
I see.
Can you do my arms?
Arms?
Yes.
Okay.
You have to put something on your arms.
I see.
Is this okay?
Yes.
I'm worried about your arms.
I want to make them thinner.
My arms are soft.
What are you mumbling?
I want to go to the gym, too.
I wish Ayumu could go to the gym with me.
Then I can push him.
What are you doing?
Ayumu.
Hey.
Hey, Ayumu.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Stop it, Ayumu.
I'm sorry.
I have to wash you.
I spilled a lot of water.
I know.
I'm going to wash you.
I have to wash you.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to wash you.
Are you going to wash me?
I'm just washing you.
Are you okay?
I have to wash you a little more.
Do you have to wash me a little more?
Do you have to wash me?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I have to wash you.
Alice, are you okay?
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
Wait a minute.
Can I touch you?
Yes.
Do you feel good?
Alice.
If you do that, you'll feel better.
I feel good.
Alice, I'm in trouble.
Did you sweat?
You're sweating a lot.
I washed you.
Can I touch you?
I'm sorry.
You can still touch me.
I'll lick you again.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to do it again?
I feel good.
Why did you do that?
That's because...
I'm worried if you'll show your body.
I'm not worried.
Since you keep yelling, my hogging is over.
Wow! It feels great.
I feel great.
I feel great too!
Oh, this is good.
Just a second!
Okay
We went out again
Right
Let me take a shower
Now?
Ya
Okay
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
I'm all right.
Let's go back to the room.
Lie down.
Are you all right?
You're still fine.
I don't like you.
I feel good.
Can I do more?
Alice, are you all right?
I'm fine.
That wasn't from me.
But you wanted to do it, didn't you?
You're smaller than before.
We can go to the convenience store together.
But I can't tell my mom and dad.