I'm so glad you decided to cry, Yuina.
Yeah, I'm happy.
But isn't it too early for you to decide to cry?
Maybe so.
Yuina, you've been a good girl since you were little.
That's not true.
Dad, you have a big nose.
I'm happy.
By the way, isn't Satoru acting weird lately?
What do you mean?
He doesn't seem to be in a good mood.
Is that so?
Yeah.
But he's always been quiet.
That's true, but...
I don't know about you, but...
Hey, Satoru.
What?
Have a seat.
What is it?
Yuina was worried about you.
I heard you're not in a good mood lately.
What?
No, I'm not.
You're still the same.
I don't think so.
Yeah.
You have an exam.
Mom told me that your test score has dropped recently.
Yeah.
I was not good at it the other day.
The other day?
Yeah.
Really?
Didn't you talk about it the other day?
No, I didn't.
It's normal.
It's not embarrassing that you're not good at studying.
Satoru, are you listening to me?
Yes, I am.
Satoru, are you really okay?
Wait.
What?
What's wrong?
Wait, Satoru.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I've got a job.
So I'm going to ask you to teach me.
Really?
I'll do my best.
What's wrong with you?
Are you really okay?
What?
So I'm going to ask you to teach me.
Promise me.
I promise.
Good boy.
I'll do my best.
You're weird today.
Don't say that.
Make a plan to study and teach me.
I'm making a plan.
I'm making a plan to study and teach you.
I'm going to the room.
I said I'm making a plan.
You're already making a plan.
How's it going?
It's a little difficult.
It's difficult here.
I'm not good at this part.
I think it's easy to solve by referring to this part.
Can you solve it?
I can solve it.
You're weird today.
Did something happen at school recently?
I'll listen to you.
I don't know.
Tell me.
I'll do anything for you.
Okay.
I'm going to the bathroom.
I don't want to go.
Satoru, I'm coming in.
Sister?
Satoru, how are you?
I'm fine.
Don't you go to school?
I don't care.
You don't have a fever.
Did something happen?
Nothing happened.
I don't want to go to school.
Did something happen that you don't want to go to school?
I don't know.
Talk to her.
Get up.
What's wrong?
I don't want to say this.
You don't want to say this?
It's hard to say.
You may be able to go to school.
Don't you laugh at what I say?
I'm fine.
You don't tell anyone, do you?
I don't tell anyone.
I'll tell you.
I...
I'm going to date a girl in my class.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I have a girlfriend.
I'm going to have an affair with her.
But it's my first time.
I can't do it well.
I failed.
So...
I'm going to have an affair with her.
Please.
You can't go to school like this.
You're going to have an affair with her.
Please.
I'm going to have an affair with her.
I can't do it until the end.
Can I use my body to practice until then?
Can't I?
You can't do it until the end.
Can I do it if it's okay?
That's right.
I got it.
Are you okay?
Let's practice.
Can I start with a kiss?
I'm going to have an affair with her.
Is this okay?
Can I take it off?
You can.
Can you take it off?
I'm going to have an affair with her.
Does your neck feel good?
Can I lick you?
I'm going to have an affair with her.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to have an affair with her?
I'm going to have an affair with her.
Does this feel good?
It feels good.
I'm going to have an affair with her.
Let me sit on your lap.
Ah !
I feel something so nice!
Ah… It's not enough.
That's fast.
It's a lie when you say Tee char!
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't stand it.
I'm so happy.
It's okay, isn't it?
I'm going to sleep.
I can't.
I want to sleep.
I'm going to rub you.
Rub me?
I'm going to sleep.
Don't move.
I'm going to move.
Okay.
I want to sleep.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
Hang in there.
Okay.
Don't move.
I'm going to move.
I'm going to rub you.
I'm not trying to move.
You're not.
I'm going to rub you.
Don't move.
I'm going to move.
I'm going to rub you.
Don't move.
I'm going to move.
It was dangerous.
I'm going to rub you.
Hang in there.
Don't move.
Wait.
I'm going to rub you.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm glad you graduated.
I want to do more.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I want to move.
It's okay.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
I made you cry again.
Are you okay?
I'm glad you graduated.
I want to do more.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
I want to do more.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I think it's better to practice going outside.
Outside?
I can do it again.
Where should I go?
Anywhere is fine.
I'm glad you graduated.
I want to put it in your mouth.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I'm going to school like this.
I'm glad I talked to you.
Thank you.
Saki.
I'm glad you got a job.
I got a job.
Saki took a break from studying because she was worried.
I didn't want to worry so much because everybody had a job at school.
But somehow I got a job.
Saki didn't have any difficult.
People gave me direction.
I think he should take a break.
Yeah, I'm going to take it easy and go on a trip with my friends.
Oh, I didn't know you had a boyfriend.
We're still close.
Oh, really?
At first, my dad didn't like it.
My mom said I looked like a high school student.
I guess it's different from what you look like.
I'm glad you think so.
All that's left is Shogo.
Yeah, it's an important time.
I wonder if he's okay with the entrance exam.
I feel like he's worried.
He's worried.
Hey, Shogo.
I was just talking about you.
Come here and sit down.
How's the entrance exam going?
Entrance exam?
Yeah.
It's normal.
Normal?
I don't know if it's normal.
I don't know if it's good or bad.
I don't know what to do.
But Shogo is doing his best.
Shogo, are you doing your best?
Hey.
I'm doing my best.
Are you listening to people?
Yeah, I'm listening.
Fortunately, you got a job at a big company.
Hey.
You got a job at a big company.
Yeah.
You know that, right?
I know.
It was a straight college.
I'm worried about you.
I feel sorry for you.
No.
Idiot.
You're so kind.
I'm me.
Shogo is Shogo.
That's right.
Shogo.
Are you studying?
Hey.
If you don't know something,
you should teach your sister.
Yeah.
I just got a job.
I'll teach her.
Okay.
Can you teach me what I didn't know?
Leave it to me.
Thank you.
You have to get used to it.
I know.
My sister said she'll teach you when you take a break.
You're so kind.
No, I'm not.
Hey, Shogo.
You should learn from your sister.
Yeah.
What?
Hey.
You should learn from your sister.
I'm going to study.
Okay.
Study hard.
See you later.
Isn't he weird?
Yeah.
He doesn't listen to me.
He didn't listen to me at all.
Is he sick?
He has a bad eye.
What's wrong with him?
He's weird.
If you don't know something,
you should tell me.
Okay.
Shogo, are you worried about something?
No, I'm fine.
You seem to have a problem when you eat.
I'm not worried.
I'm fine.
I was wondering if you were thinking about anything while you were eating or studying.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Really?
If you can do it, please tell me anything.
I'm rooting for you.
Okay.
Yeah.
Shogo, are you really okay?
You don't look like you're okay at all.
But really, if you can do it, you can say anything.
I'm really worried about you, and I'm always rooting for you.
Don't hesitate to tell me.
Okay.
I wonder if he's really okay.
Shogo, I'm coming in.
Are you okay?
I won't leave you alone.
I'm worried about you.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You didn't go to school today.
It's an important time for the entrance exam, isn't it?
I was worried that you didn't want to go to school.
No, I'm not.
Are you really not feeling well?
Yeah.
There's something going on, isn't there?
It has nothing to do with you.
There is. You're my sister.
You're worried about something, aren't you?
I think there's something only you can say.
I won't tell everyone.
If you have something to say to your mom or dad, go ahead.
I want you to have sex with me.
Sex?
Yeah.
What? What's wrong?
I don't think you should have sex.
Why do you say that?
I was going to have sex with her, but I failed.
Twice.
Twice?
I don't know how to do it, and I'm still a virgin.
And we're in the same class.
It's a little awkward.
I see. That's a shock, isn't it?
I'm worried about you.
So I want you to have sex with me.
Please.
Sex?
If you have sex, it'll be solved.
I think so.
I can't have sex.
If it's for Shogo, you can use my body as you like.
Can I?
But you can't touch me until the end.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Can I?
What should I do?
Can I touch you?
Yes, you can.
A lot?
Yes.
It's very soft.
You have a big body.
Do I?
Yes.
You can do other things.
Really? I didn't know that.
You sleep a lot.
That's why you can't concentrate.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
You can't concentrate.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Well...
I want to touch your belly.
I'll do it.
Don't touch me.
I'll touch you.
You're so naive.
Can I touch you from behind?
I wanted to touch you like this.
I wanted to touch you quietly.
Do as you like.
You're so naive.
I see.
It feels good.
I want you to touch me directly.
Do you want me to touch you?
Yes.
Do you understand?
It's difficult.
I know.
Do your best.
This is also a practice.
I did my best.
You're so naive.
Do you want me to touch you?
Yes.
You're so naive.
I want you to touch me.
Does this feel good?
Yes.
Do you want me to touch you?
It feels good.
You're so naive.
Do you want me to touch you?
Yes.
It feels good.
Do you want me to touch you?
Yes.
It feels good.
Do you want me to touch you?
Do you want me to kiss you?
I want to see you.
I'm embarrassed.
I'll show you again.
That's not true.
Where does this feel good?
Where?
Is it here?
Is it up here?
That's where it feels good.
Do you want me to touch you?
It feels good.
Tell me if I'm wrong.
Okay.
Do you want me to touch you?
I want to see you in person.
I don't want to see you in person.
It's very beautiful.
That's not true.
It's so pink.
Do you want me to touch you?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
I want to see your fingers.
Slowly.
Can I touch you?
I'm okay.
How should I move this?
Move it to the back.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I can't help it anymore.
Do you want me to lick you?
I want you to lick me.
I can't help it.
Let me see.
That's amazing.
I can't help it anymore.
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
I want you to lick me more.
Do you want me to lick you?
I'm okay.
That's amazing.
I can't help it anymore.
I want you to do me a favor.
What is it?
Don't pinch me.
I'm okay.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'm glad.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'm glad.
What is it?
Wait a minute.
Don't pinch me.
I can't help it anymore.
I want you to do me a favor.
You can't do that.
You can just rub me.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
You can't rub me.
What is it?
It feels good.
You can't move me.
You're trying to put me in.
You can't do that.
It's dangerous.
It hurts.
You can't do that.
Ouch!
I got rolls all over.
You're crying.
Shou...
You've lost a lot of hair.
We will continue to see each other in the self-introduction video for the time being!
Thank you for your nice comments!
I'd like to try it more because I felt so great.
Yes, yes.
Oh, it's painful.
Come on now.
Make a wish.
Don't act like that.
What?
Uma...
It's alright.
Ah...
I feel sick...
Me too...
Ow...
It feels weird...
Wait, wait.
It's so hot.
It feels good.
It's painful.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
It's painful.
It's okay.
Do you want to let go?
I want to let go.
Let's do it.
Do you want to do it or not?
It's painful.
That's it.
Next time, I want to practice going outside.
It's painful.
Can you go to school with this?
I'll go to school.
That's good.
Next time, if something happens, please tell me again.
Yuri, how have you been?
Have you got used to work?
I'm doing my best, but it's hard.
Have you decided on a department?
It's a general office, but it's my first year, so I'm not sure if I can get used to it.
Are your seniors kind to you?
Yes, everyone is kind.
Are you going to ask me for advice?
I'm not sure if I can give you advice yet.
Please be careful.
You've been kind to me for a long time, so I don't think I can talk to you actively.
I want to talk to my boss, but it's hard.
How long does it take to get to work?
It takes about 40 minutes to get to work.
That's a long way to go.
I'm relieved.
Masato.
What?
I was worried about you.
I heard you've had a bad record lately.
Well...
Are you okay? Can you sleep well?
You look tired.
No, I'm not.
Really?
I'm worried about you, too.
I think you should take a test.
I happened to take a test.
Really? I'm worried about you, too.
You can ask your sister for advice.
Do you want me to teach you?
Okay, I'll ask her for advice.
Masato, did something happen to you recently?
What?
Don't you think something's wrong?
What? Really?
I don't think so.
It's normal.
Normal?
I'm fine.
Is something wrong?
What's wrong?
It's okay.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Let me know if anything happens.
I wonder what's wrong with him.
He's a little weird.
I think so, too.
Did something happen?
Your hand is stuck.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Do you know where it is?
I'm just thinking.
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'm fine.
You don't know where it is.
I went to school, so I know where it is.
Really?
Masato, did something happen to you recently?
What?
I've been watching you since you were a kid, so I know.
Talk to me.
It's nothing.
Really?
I'll do anything you can do.
Talk to me.
Anything?
Yes.
It's okay.
You don't have to ask me.
I can do it myself.
Can you?
I don't think I can talk to you.
You have to tell me.
But...
I'll talk to you when I'm free.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'm fine now.
By the way, are you free today?
Yes.
Don't you have a date with your boyfriend?
Are you okay?
I was busy.
I'm fine.
I see.
By the way, do you have a girlfriend?
Well...
Have you seen her recently?
We're in the same class.
So you're close to her.
What do you think?
What?
Are you close to her?
Well...
I'm going to the bathroom.
Wait.
Did you have a date with her?
I don't want to go to school.
Masato.
I'm coming in.
What?
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
I'm fine.
I'm worried about you.
Do you have work today?
I took a day off.
Look at you.
I'm worried about you.
You can't go to work because you're worried.
Something must have happened to you.
Well...
Let me be alone.
What?
I'm asking you.
If you take a day off tomorrow, I'll take a day off, too.
I can't.
Tell me what happened.
I'll tell you.
What?
You won't laugh, will you?
I won't.
What happened?
When I had a date with her for the first time,
I didn't know how to get along with her.
I couldn't get along with her.
I tried to get along with her again, but it didn't work.
I'm a bad man.
Were you worried about that?
Yes.
I'm a bad man.
No one can get along with you from the beginning.
If I were a bad man, you'd hate me.
I don't hate you.
It can't be helped.
Cheer up.
I can't go to school because I'm embarrassed.
Why?
People think I'm a bad man.
You're delusional.
I'm sure.
Don't worry.
Let me do it.
You said you'd do anything for me.
I'll do anything.
Let me do it.
You have a girlfriend.
You can't do that.
Let me practice.
Practice?
You can practice.
But we're siblings.
I can't go to school like this.
That's not true.
Cheer up.
Let me practice.
Practice?
If you let me practice, I'll be confident.
Then I'll go to school.
Do you really want to go to school?
Yes.
Can you cheer up?
You can't go to school until the end.
But you can use my body to practice.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you.
But you can't go to school until the end.
We're siblings.
Okay.
What should I do?
Wait.
You have to touch me gently.
Gently?
The body of a girl is delicate.
How?
Touch me gently like this.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Like this?
Yes.
You have big breasts.
I want to kiss you.
I want to touch you directly.
I want to touch you.
Are you embarrassed to be looked at like that?
You have big breasts.
Bigger than hers.
Don't say that.
I'm sorry.
More.
I want to see you more.
More?
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
Touch me gently.
More?
Yes.
Wow.
It's soft.
Here, too.
Here, too?
Here.
How should I touch you?
Touch me gently.
Like this.
It feels good.
I want to kiss you.
I want to touch you.
Wow.
Teach me how to touch you.
Touch me gently like you did before.
When I was with my girlfriend, she said it hurt a lot.
Where should I touch?
Here.
There.
Here?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
Wow.
You're touching here.
Yes.
You're so gentle.
Wow.
You can be confident with this.
Yes.
I got it.
I want to exercise, too.
Yes.
Teach me.
Touch me gently when you lick me.
Yes.
That's right.
Good.
It feels good.
Yes.
Wow.
It must be painful.
It's painful.
Yes.
Really?
Did you feel good when I licked you?
Yes.
I felt good.
I'm glad.
I think I'm getting more and more confident.
Really?
Yes.
Just a little.
What?
I got it.
Wow.
It feels good.
Were you excited?
Of course.
Lie down.
Wow.
It feels good.
Yes.
Touch me directly.
Directly?
Yes.
I can't help it.
Do you want me to lick you a little?
Yes.
I don't know.
It feels good.
Yes.
Wow.
It feels good.
Lie down.
Wow.
I want to make more sounds with this one.
What?
Let's make sounds with your boobs.
With my boobs?
You've never done this before, have you?
How is it?
It feels so good.
What?
Why is your neck so stiff?
Because it feels good.
Because it feels good?
Yes.
I want to do it.
What?
Let me do it.
But you can't do it until the end.
Please, please.
We're siblings.
I want to do it.
Even if you say that...
If you don't do it, you won't be confident.
But...
Then, just rub it.
Just rub it?
Yes.
It's okay if you just rub it, right?
It's okay if you just rub it.
Because I can't do it.
Then, look.
Look.
You can't move.
Okay.
Like this?
It feels good.
I forgot.
You're not sleepy, are you?
It feels good.
It's rubbing.
Does it feel good?
It's amazing.
But it feels good.
Really?
Yes.
Okay.
One more time.
It's amazing.
It feels good when you just rub it.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's coming out.
Wait.
No, no, no.
It was about to come out.
It's okay. It didn't come out.
It didn't come out.
Let's do it a little further.
Further?
Yes, here.
It feels good here.
It didn't come out.
It was about to come out.
It's okay.
Don't try to put it in.
I'm not trying to put it in.
I'm just rubbing it here.
No, no, no.
It's okay.
It was about to come out.
No, no, no.
It's okay.
It didn't come out.
No, no, no.
It's about to come out.
It didn't come out.
No, no, no.
It's about to come out.
It's coming out.
No way.
It's about to come out.
It's okay.
Ah!
Huh?
Tetsu?
Ah!
It's in there.
Tetsu.
Ah!
Huh?
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Oh no, oh no...
She's left.
I can't take it anymore.
But it feels so good.
I feel good too, but I can't take it anymore.
My stomach hurts.
I can't take it anymore.
It's gone.
It's gone?
I'm sorry.
It's gone.
I'm sorry. It feels so good.
But I want to do more.
What?
I can't take it anymore.
It's gone.
It feels so good.
Move.
I can't take it anymore.
It feels so good.
Move your hips.
Move more.
It feels so good.
I can't take it anymore.
I want to do it more.
Let's do it more.
It feels so good.
I think I'm going to cry.
The child is having a hard time getting out of the sports car.
I'm sorry I made you cry so much.
It's okay.
I'm not ready yet.
What do you want to do?
Can I do it again?
Okay.
Do you want to practice going out?
Can I put out my boobs?
Can I do it again?
It feels good.
You did a great job.
You have to go to school from tomorrow.
Okay.
I go to school early or late.
I was just talking about you.
Sit down.
You don't look well.
I didn't notice because I couldn't go home.
You are too busy.
I'm sorry.
I want to go camping.
Let's go.
Let's grill some crabs.
Okay.
Do you want to go?
Didn't you go on a date with your girlfriend?
Do you have a girlfriend?
You have a girlfriend.
Why don't you go camping with your girlfriend?
Camping is fun.
Tell your father how to camp.
Bring her.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Okay.
It's dangerous.
There are a lot of bugs.
It's better to get rid of the bugs.
It's fun to get rid of the bugs.
It will be fun.
What's wrong?
I don't have a girlfriend.
What?
What do you mean?
We broke up.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
When?
About a week ago.
I see.
I just didn't have a chance to see her.
If it was you, I could have a new girlfriend.
But...
I thought we didn't get along.
You looked mean.
I wasn't mean.
I just didn't have a chance to see her.
Is that so?
Why did you break up?
I'm sorry.
Do you have a test?
Are you studying?
I'm studying.
Didn't you have a test?
Are you doing well?
Yes.
Do you want me to teach you?
You can do it.
Yes.
I got all 4 grades.
Isn't it great?
It's great.
But...
What?
I can't concentrate.
I see.
I'm sorry.
What?
I was about to pee.
Take your time.
I'm home.
I'm tired.
The light is on.
Dai-chan?
She's not home.
Are you sleeping?
Dai-chan, I'm coming in.
Why are you at home?
I'm home.
Why did you leave?
Why?
I didn't want to go to school, so I took a day off.
Did someone say something to you?
You went to the same school as her, right?
No.
So...
What?
I broke up with her.
Did someone say something to you?
Do you have a fever?
Let me see your forehead.
You don't have a fever.
Are you okay?
I don't have a fever.
Are you really okay?
I'm worried about you.
Why are you so depressed?
It's a little dark.
You're not the usual Dai-chan.
So...
What?
I'm talking to you.
Do you want to talk to me?
I'm counting on you.
So...
Huh?
What?
Did you do something?
I didn't do anything.
I can hear you.
Tell me.
I'll give you advice.
Well...
It's like that.
Like that?
Like having sex.
You're an adult.
So...
I'm sorry.
So?
At that time...
It was my first time.
I couldn't do it well.
I was nervous.
I cried on the way.
I couldn't do it until the end.
After that, I felt awkward.
Well...
Until the end...
I see.
It's difficult.
It's your first time.
Well...
And...
Other than me in the class...
I have a boyfriend and a girlfriend.
Even if I go to school alone...
I'm alone.
I don't want to be recognized.
I don't think I can have a girlfriend.
I don't want to be alone.
Don't worry.
You're a good boy.
You can have a girlfriend.
But I'm not a good person.
I can't have sex well.
Even if you fail...
I want you to close your eyes.
Do you think she likes me?
I see.
I don't think so.
No.
It's not a bad thing.
Maybe she thinks so.
Well...
What?
Tell me.
When will you practice with me?
What?
Sex?
You and me?
I'll do anything for you.
I broke up with you because of that.
If you get better, you can have a girlfriend.
So...
I said I'd do anything for you.
We're brothers.
I can't have a girlfriend.
Can I be alone?
Well...
I feel sorry for you.
If you feel sorry for me, practice with me.
What do you mean?
I mean sex.
Sex?
You're the only one I can rely on.
But...
Please.
I see.
Well...
I'm worried about you.
I think you should cherish the virginity.
People who love you for the first time...
So...
Don't get nervous.
You get nervous.
But it's not the reason.
Maybe.
I don't want to make you nervous.
I want you to get used to the body of a woman.
If you want me to touch you...
If you want me to touch you?
Yes, yes.
But just touch me.
I don't want to...
I don't want you to touch me.
I don't want you to do that.
It's not good for you.
Then...
What?
I know what you want me to do.
What about rubbing?
Rubbing...
Rubbing is not good.
Because I can't do that.
Rubbing...
Rubbing is a practice.
You can't do that.
I know.
That's good.
Really?
Yes, but you can't rub me.
I know.
But you have to take care of your virginity.
Really?
Yes.
You have to be with the person you like for the first time.
I know.
But if it's just rubbing...
It's just rubbing.
Rubbing...
Then...
Don't hurry.
What?
Be gentle.
I'll let you go.
Be gentle?
Yes.
Don't hurry.
I can't do that.
I know.
I'll teach you.
Be gentle.
I'll let you go.
He'll let you go.
Yes.
If my clothes get dirty...
I'll go to the bathroom.
You're so nice!
Ah...
Come here.
Yeah.
Huh?
No, Haru.
I'm not your girlfriend.
I'm your ex-girlfriend.
You can't say that.
I can't?
That's right.
Like...
When we were young,
we didn't compare ourselves to our exes.
I'm complimenting you.
Yeah.
Your boobs are big.
They're round.
Hey.
Can I look at you more?
Well...
Can I ask you a favor?
Yeah.
It's just a practice.
It's kind of embarrassing to hear you say that.
You don't have to say that.
No.
I think I'd be happier if you said that.
Wow.
Your boobs are beautiful.
Thank you.
You have a lot of clothes.
Yeah.
I thought they were shirts.
Your tongue is connected.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to.
I'm sorry.
Don't look at me like that.
You don't have to look at me.
What's wrong?
Do you feel good?
Well, then.
I'll touch you a lot.
Do that.
Wait, wait, wait.
Isn't it a little early?
Is it early?
No, it's not.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm nervous, too.
Yes.
It's the same.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Really?
Yes.
I feel good.
Is this right?
It's right.
Wait, wait.
If you touch me like that...
It's not that I don't like it.
It's just...
I'm just studying.
Yes.
It's late.
Well, then.
I'll touch you gently.
I'll touch you.
I'll hold you tight.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
My neck.
I'll hold you tight.
Does this feel good?
It feels good.
I see.
I'll do it again.
Yes.
You don't have to do it so often.
Do it more often.
Do it to your girlfriend.
What's this?
What?
It's sweet.
I'm a little...
I didn't take a shower.
Why?
Isn't it salty?
I'm sweating today.
It's not salty at all.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'll tell you how to drink it.
Yes.
It feels good now.
How do you feel?
It looks delicious.
I'll drink it.
I'll make you drunk.
And...
I'll suck your nipples.
No, no, no.
It's too strong.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know that.
It feels good.
It feels good for me.
But you have to tell your girlfriend that it doesn't hurt.
Yes.
Okay?
Ah...
I'm sorry.
My voice is coming out.
I'm so embarrassed.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
Really?
Yes.
Hey, sister.
Come here.
This side, too.
Tell me.
This side, too?
Yes.
By the way, why did you get dumped, Ai-chan?
Why did you get dumped?
You don't want to say it, do you?
No.
You don't, do you? I'm sorry.
I thought I'd like to hear it if I could.
We didn't know what to do with each other.
We couldn't lead each other.
That's why I got dumped.
I see.
Do you want to lead Ai-chan?
Yes.
What are you going to do?
Open your legs.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
Touch her gently at first.
Gently?
Yes.
At that time, while drinking and touching her nipples...
If you do that, she'll be happy.
How about here?
Ai-chan, you're drooling.
Don't say such embarrassing things.
I'm sorry.
You're drooling.
Does that mean it felt good?
I guess so.
You're good.
Does it feel better to touch her directly?
I guess so.
Do you want to touch her?
Yes.
I'll take it off.
You're drooling.
What are you going to do?
I want to touch her more and make her feel better.
But...
Don't you have to take it off for her?
I see.
You don't want her to feel pain.
That's why you're studying.
You teach me a lot.
Okay.
Yes.
Do you know where it feels good to touch?
Where does it feel good?
You're pulling a string.
It's a little embarrassing.
This is called glitteris.
It's a place where women feel good.
First...
Here...
I'll pat you.
I'll make you feel better.
I'll pat you over and over again.
I'll put my finger in your ear.
This is where I put my finger.
Here?
That's right.
What?
No, I didn't mean to hurt you.
I just wanted to make you feel better.
Really?
Try it.
That's great.
What?
I'm done.
I put my finger in your ear.
I don't know what to do with this.
What don't you know?
Are you ready to put your finger in my ear?
A little more.
A little more?
I'll put my finger in your ear a little more.
I'll move it up and down.
Is this right?
That's right.
No, no, no.
It's all right.
I'll practice a little more.
When you practice...
You can put your finger in my ear.
You can do that with your girlfriend.
But I have to practice now.
That's right.
Try moving it.
Like this?
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I brushed my teeth.
That's amazing.
You were in there.
I'm sorry.
I'll change your bed sheets.
It's a secret.
It feels good when I brush my teeth.
Is that so?
That's right.
Do you brush your teeth with salt?
You know it well.
You're amazing.
Sister.
It's been a long time.
Do you usually lick your teeth?
I do.
But I'm older than you.
But...
If you lick your mouth...
I can't put it in.
So...
I'll practice.
Sister.
Have you ever done that?
No.
If you haven't, you should do it with your girlfriend.
But you have to do it.
You said you'd practice with me.
I'll do it.
I'll practice.
Okay.
If your girlfriend asks you, tell her you've never done it.
Do you understand?
I'll practice with you.
It's big.
Really?
Sister.
I was surprised.
I'll start practicing.
Are you okay?
It hurts.
I see.
Like this.
You licked your mouth.
You licked your mouth a lot.
But it's okay because it's a practice.
You may have something to tell your girlfriend.
Tell your girlfriend how you feel.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
Tell your girlfriend how you feel.
Okay.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
How about you?
I feel good, too.
Everyone feels good.
Do you feel good?
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
I felt good.
I'll go out.
I see.
You can't.
I'll be patient.
If it's dangerous, tell me.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Did I fail?
You almost failed.
I'm patient.
Hey.
Can I practice rubbing my body?
Don't rub your body.
I know.
I just rub my body.
Okay.
Do you want to practice rubbing your body?
Do you?
I just rub my body.
Okay.
I'll rub my body.
I'm sleepy.
Do you know how to rub my body?
I just rub my body.
You can do whatever you want.
Okay.
Like this?
I'm rubbing my body.
Are you done?
I'm almost done.
Can I practice a little more?
Just a little more.
I just rub my body.
Okay.
It's hard.
I'm going to cry.
I feel good just by rubbing my body.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
It's in there.
I'm sorry.
Is it?
Don't do that.
It's in there.
I just rub my body.
You're not using your hands.
That's right.
It's in there.
Don't do that.
I'll do it for you.
Okay.
Go to sleep.
I'll show you how to do it.
I don't know how to do it.
Look at this.
It's in there.
Okay.
I'm going to cry.
Leave it to me.
Okay.
I can't put it in.
If you put it in suddenly, the girl will be surprised.
Okay.
Don't do that.
Really.
Like this.
Slowly.
Move your waist.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I just rubbed my body.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Don't do that.
I just rubbed my body.
It feels good.
I want to do it quickly.
Are you okay?
Yes.
You rubbed your body a lot.
I'm glad.
If you lean forward too much, it's good to rub your body like this.
Like this.
Okay.
It feels good.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I rubbed my body too much.
It's okay.
It's a practice.
That's right.
If you rub your body from the bottom to the top, it feels good.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I rubbed my body too much.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
I rub my body from the bottom to the top.
Okay.
It's hot.
How is it?
Turn your back.
It feels good.
I rub my body.
I was surprised.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's important to rub your body from the bottom to the top.
Yes.
Does it feel good to turn your back?
It feels good.
Can I move a little deeper?
Okay.
I don't want to put my hands in the water.
I'll turn my back.
Hey.
I'll put my hands in the water.
Is it okay?
Hey.
What?
I didn't put my hands in the water.
I rub my body from the bottom to the top.
I can't do it.
What?
Did you cry again?
Did you rub your body?
No.
It's amazing.
Did you put your hands in the water?
I didn't put my hands in the water.
I think you did.
Really?
I'll practice a little more.
Did I put my hands in the water?
No.
Are you okay?
I don't think so.
I'll be careful.
Okay.
I'll rub my body.
Ah.
Hey.
Yeah.
Ah.
Don't you feel good when you move fast and rub your body?
No.
But I feel good.
Right?
No.
I'm fine.
I won't put my hands in the water.
No.
Why?
I won't put my hands in the water.
Let me move fast.
I promise.
Ah.
Hey.
I feel good when I rub my body, right?
Ah.
Right?
Huh...
Mr.. Takacja.
Ahhh...
I'm over here, Ichiro.
Guys, please,
Because you feel so good.
You feel so good.
You feel good, don't you?
It's deep, isn't it?
It's rubbing.
I'll clean it up to here.
You feel good, don't you?
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
It feels good to lick here, too.
You feel good, don't you?
I feel good in you.
You feel good to be licked, don't you?
It feels good to be licked.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
It feels good to be licked.
You feel good, don't you?
What's wrong?
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
You feel good, don't you?
I can't help it.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
You feel good, don't you?
What?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I can't help it.
It hurts.
Did you just say that?
I'm sorry.
Didn't you say that?
I said that in my stomach.
Really?
In my stomach?
I want to sleep.
I'm so sleepy.
Do you want to do it, too?
I want to do it more.
Do it.
Let's do it.
There's a lot in my stomach.
It's in my stomach.
I want to do it.
I want to do it more.
Do it more.
I understand.
I want to do it more.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
I like it.
I'm going to die.
If you die like that, you'll be fine.
It hurts.
I can't stop my back at all.
The doctor came out again.
I can't do it anymore.
This way.
I want to do it more.
I feel good.
I can't do it anymore.
I understand.
I can see inside my stomach.
What's wrong with you?
I have to let go of your waist.
Sister!
I don't know what you're talking about.
Can I take it out?
Yeah.
I slept again.
You won't sleep anymore, will you?
Wait a minute.
I won't sleep anymore.
You won't sleep anymore.
Wait.
I can't.
You can't.
No, no.
Why can't I do it?
Hey, sis, you can't do it.
No, I can't.
I said no, but you're doing it again.
One more time.
No, I can't.
Ah!
Wow.
You did it a lot.
Again.
Sis.
Sorry, are you okay?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I feel like I can make a girlfriend soon.
Actually, I don't need a girlfriend anymore.
What are you talking about?
Are you kidding me?
I'm not kidding.
Be quiet.
Yes.
I'm not kidding.