So glad you have a job, Sasha.
I was really nervous. it was very hard.
You were hard.
Is it a construction company?
Yes, Jim and Jim.
It is hard, Jim.
But it is a good place to build, so you can get a nail.
If you don’t have hair color, you’ll have hair color.
Yes Yes Yes Yes
I have been black hair all my life, so I want to make it a little lighter.
No, it is a good company.
I really want to get a high salary and save money and live alone.
I think I miss you a little.
No, I think you should have married.
If you are a child, is it not a problem? No, it is not so.
I haven’t been on a wedding trip yet.
I didn’t go, but I’m going to live with four people.
Not about half a year.
Yes is it.
It has been a half year now.
is fast.
Do not tell me to live alone.
You can save money here.
I want to save.
It seems like two of my friends are already living together.
I think you are so good, I think you should be so good too soon.
I want you to be a little bit more sweet.
Really, I can tell you a little bit.
must be so.
Thanks very kind.
Okay, your father is.
I told him to bring him dinner for the job celebration.
Really?
Oh, I want to eat a fried meal.
It is burnt.
What is good.
Okay, I will eat a lot.
I want to eat a lot.
I can’t eat it, but I can’t.
Okay okay okay.
It will be cold in the store.
No to
But I’ll live alone, I’ll miss you.
Oh yeah yeah.
I am very hungry, so I want to.
Yes is.
You are often together and you talk.
I am glad you are kind.
Did you say something?
She says she will leave home if she gets a job.
I miss you.
If you save money, you will live alone.
It is so.
I miss you better than my family.
You are better than your family.
I think my brother can’t do it right now.
Sometimes I like your sister.
I am pleased.
Yes
I was quick.
Suddenly, they become a family.
Maybe it is a little awkward.
Oh, and what happened to you?
something
No, it’s a bit too cool.
It is cold.
is cold?
Wait a little, give me a panda.
Thanks to Mom.
Time to think about living alone.
Maybe it is the end of the year already.
Everyone around me said they started living alone.
I am not missing you a little.
Yuu, you are already working.
It looks like that.
next year.
Not since the end of this year.
You already start.
It’s too early, recently.
I won’t tell you much just now.
Take that noah.
I understand
No to no.
I want to, I can listen a little.
If my son could.
I wanted to know she was there.
Do you want her there?
There is.
That is?
I did not know.
Father
Are you there?
by
I did not know.
A little you.
Maybe his father is disappointed.
Men don’t talk about that much.
We want to see too.
No to
Or was good.
Want to see?
Yes
But maybe you’ve seen it before, right?
No to no.
Is there something?
Oh what?
Did you take a photo with them?
What? what? what? what? what? what? what?
Sorry, I am wrong.
Oh is
What is?
What happened to you? you just got a bit of a mess?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Is it still cold?
Maybe it has gotten a little better.
Nothing is anything.
What happened?
Is it okay?
I talked about dinner just before, so I was hungry.
Well, now is the time to start cooking.
What is today’s meal?
What to do.
I have to go shopping.
A supermarket before you go?
But was it not a sale somewhere?
The sale?
Yes
Just stretch your feet a little, so this is good.
If you let me get out of the car.
If so, sales.
Just now?
Is it okay?
is okay.
It looks like something.
No so is.
Yes to?
Yes
We have been shopping together once.
I want to go, I want to love you.
Sorry, I will come back soon.
Is it okay, her boy?
If you have just gone, then something.
I have to think about food.
Yes is.
Are you asking, have a request?
The request?
I want to eat.
by Tia
by Tjpa
Just got it?
So, we will finish in a moment.
Is it okay?
Yes, it is okay
Not written in a manly word?
It looks like a very yellow word.
I suspected that it was not a crazy word.
Sorry, sorry, but this would feel good.
If that was enough, it would be okay, right?
Good, I will end in a moment.
Tell me when you are done.
I could, I could.
Oh you did? Yes
Okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
Okay thank you.
Yes, I will do it, I will.
well well 😂
Come to your mother.
Just a little.
Do you want to?
I went to the store now.
What is it, mother?
Oh that?
What happened just?
Why are you sleeping?
There was a room for you.
I was tired and took a break.
Did you go somewhere? – I mean.
I just went to the store and bought rubber.
Remove the rubber?
If I told you, I would be at home.
Oh, I should have said so.
Did you go to the store?
Suffice to
I told him I would buy ice cream.
Oh yeah yeah.
Yes
Oh well, he is out.
Well, because it is a room.
You should go out sooner, right?
Oh, what is it.
Is it cold, isn’t it?
Oh, oh, that is not so.
Yes to?
Yes
It was crazy, and the room was bad.
Yes, I’ve gotten a little asleep.
I thought I would rest a little.
No to
Oh, what happened to you?
Oh yeah, nothing is.
It seems to have been a little bit of feet.
Oh, you are crying?
Mom, what is it like?
Oh, and so on.
A little bit of meal request.
I came to hear.
Anything is okay.
Meals and mother’s meal.
Because it is all delicious.
What, is it not appropriate?
No so is.
I just want to sleep in my room, so I'll sleep in my bed.
The pillow is just a good height.
Oh yeah yeah yeah?
So, buy that pillow now.
Yes, I would like to please.
Yes, I’m sure, because I’ve just been there, I’ve been living alone, right?
Yes, my mom’s friend has a little boy about a year old.
Oh, so is it.
To your friend, to your child.
Yes
Yes, I know, first of all, work at home.
He seems to be trying to save money.
Oh yeah, I’ll do that too.
Yes, I am happy to have a family of four.
Oh what what?
Talk about family and food.
Oh yeah, that is good.
Oh well, is it not?
Yes
Why did you say it well?
Well, I know, so we’ll talk about it again next time.
What do I want to be afraid of.
Oh what?
You told me something secret, right?
Oh, so I just studied with you.
Did he teach you?
Oh yes
Oh, it is great.
Oh yeah
I want to, because you are smart.
Can I teach you to study?
Yes, of course
It’s great, she’s doing a sister.
Yes
I have got a brother.
It seems my leg hurt a little.
My mother is watching.
Okay okay okay.
Can you find me by Ship?
Yes, there was a chip.
Maybe he is in the emergency school.
Really?
If you don’t, I’ll ask you to ask.
Yes, that is good.
Find it.
Yes, yes, yes yes
Even the purpose.
Yes, so whatever is.
So, I think it’s a hamburger.
The Hamburg?
It is surprisingly difficult.
I don’t like meat, do you like it?
So, I will buy meat.
I’ll go to the supermarket later.
Just one hamburger.
Salad or soup.
Yes Yes Yes
You want that too, right?
Not enough nutrition.
What is good.
and soup.
Vegetable
and bread.
Good for bread.
A little but.
It feels rich.
Yes yes
Then let us go.
I think everyone will be happy now.
Didn’t you do anything to your mother?
No so is.
really is?
I wanted to sleep a little, so go to sleep.
Yes, yes, yes is it already.
So let’s decide for a little food.
Yes
Amber and bread.
There was no bread, so I had to buy it.
And, did you have a dressing?
Dressing, oh, it was in the refrigerator, I saw it before.
Haven’t it happened?
So I can go, thank you.
Again and later.
I will call you when you talk.
Oh, a little
You are there, it will be okay.
Very much, very much, I have worn.
Maybe he will come back.
There is mother.
We were so used to each other, but we did not get together.
No so is.
Do you like this now?
Oh yeah yeah.
Next time I will put you in before your mom and dad.
No to no.
Because it will be private.
I say okay.
You will also share.
promise to
Oh yeah, I say no.
I remember yesterday’s meat was delicious.
It was delicious.
Really thank you Dad.
Let us go again.
I went again.
For the first time, you can pay for the salary.
Let me take care of it.
I am glad you decided to go safely.
Yes, you start working and you get busy.
Yes, I am am amusing.
Maybe you can’t even make a nice time like this.
Training is nervous.
Can you be a good friend?
Just had it been okay.
Until you get used to it.
Yes yes
Do you want to buy something to celebrate?
and a bag.
Go to
Oh yeah
The clock is weak.
The clock.
Not well.
can be used forever.
How many did you?
Yes
Oh my mom.
You have got a job.
That is
I thought I would buy something for a celebration.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
I want to buy something for your mother.
It is fun to give that to your dad.
Good kids too.
Do you want something?
No, I want you to have a delicious meal.
I just liked eating.
What do you want to eat?
Or a burnt meat?
The burning meat.
So let’s go here with us.
You have stayed.
Is it good to find employment?
If you go home or family,
The girl’s watch is crazy.
You can’t see a little.
What would it look like.
Not seen from within.
I have to go to the part.
Go to go.
I go home to bed.
You better go to the store.
You should go underground.
From Grandma.
This will follow.
It also has it.
You will do this too.
I will also repair.
Is it used in this way?
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Full of station.
Oh yeah yeah.
Enter the apartment.
It seems to be a shop.
Also also.
Buy the glasses.
Because I will go there.
Oh yes?
No way to hinder.
Lunch is a little red.
Maybe it is cute if it is small.
Because there is no here either.
It will be the most difficult.
Yes yes yes
Sorry to
Wait a little.
Oh is?
Even your father.
Do not say you are the former.
No, it is okay.
Just just
There is mess.
Yes is
I bought it and went home.
Will we eat a little?
I want to eat.
Oh is
Yes
It looks like 20 minutes.
So now then?
Oh what?
What are you doing right now?
I am doing a massage now.
Oh yeah, is it so?
He is studying on his shoulders.
Oh, so be kind.
Is it not too heavy to ride?
Oh, okay, it’s incredibly light, look, it’s incredibly light.
No to no.
Something is okay.
The little kids are playing.
I was reading the magazine.
greatly
You have a face, right?
Do you want to go to the hot spring?
I want to go.
It is no.
4 hot springs.
No, I don’t say hot water.
The Hot Springs
It feels like.
Yes I want to go.
Yes to yes.
So let’s go all together.
Oh you did.
Let us do something.
So much experience,
1st one.
Studying very much,
and technical charts.
2nd
The truth is the most glorious.
4 is
Good night to you.
Yes, I think it’s a tourist destination.
Anyway, I can experience something.
Sometimes it is so.
Where did you look at that?
Can you ask someone about this voice?
Do you ask when you make a reservation?
Yes yes yes
Where are you calling now?
Are you calling you?
This is Kanto.
and Kanto.
From the side of Kansas.
Yes yes
More or less stopped.
Because you will come.
Yes is
Well, if you all come in a car.
Listen to the director.
You will think about work.
Always with me.
Okay to Okay.
You probably haven’t worked yet either.
just now
New employee entrance.
Maybe I can take a break.
It is Sunday, right?
But I think I can ride well.
Oh yeah yeah.
It is a middle class two days.
Oh, greatly
Good thing, really
Bonus is good too.
You did it.
So is such a sickness.
Oh is?
next month.
just now
What is?
that is
Next month I have three vacations.
Yes
Have a rest there.
Maybe it was.
Yes
Three days vacation.
I told him about the hot springs.
Maybe make a reservation there.
I want to go.
I want to go, right?
I want to travel, right?
well is
by 4 people.
You can go.
of course.
Because we go with four.
You can go.
The house is important.
So, Mom, are you ready for today’s shopping?
And then, it is beginning to confess.
Please be prepared.
Once and once.
So, you two are going shopping.
Yes, come to me.
Go and go.
You just really excited.
Yes, but I was ashamed.
I was excited by shame.
No to
Why so
Yes
Oh yeah
Oh that
I am ashamed.
You are becoming a big biscuit.
Why are you going so down.
Shame, don’t look at me.
It is very sliding.
Please put your finger in.
I cry.
Oh awesome.
A bit embarrassed.
Oh, very hard
My tongue is hard.
No to
Oh awesome.
Feels good?
More active than usual.
seem to have eaten.
I too once.
I will go.
No to
Feel good
by
This feels good.
greatly
It is awesome.
I was gorging.
Feels good?
I will sit on the back.
I will be.
Oh awesome.
It feels good.
Oh, shit, it feels good.
Feel good
It feels good.
No to!
very painful
Stop it!
It hurts very much!
It hurts!
It is awesome!
It is hard!
Lots of out.
Was it good?
It was great feeling.
Still hard?
All your life with your mom and dad.
Okay is it?
Yes
You felt good, right?
Let us do.
Yes
5 months is.
It has not been six months yet.
Yes is
It is 5 months.
I thought it was really fast.
Since we both went to school.
You are completely familiar.
Really good.
Really?
If you come early, I’ll be happy with your dad.
Father
You said something strange.
You did not say.
Because you are Dad.
Yes is it.
She is now a college 3rd grade student.
Third year school.
Working for the first time?
Yes, the dust
Yes, it is time to start.
You have been struggling with old schoolers and teachers, right?
Yes, right
The head is good.
No, the mind is good.
His head is cute.
That is so.
Glad to be.
pleased
Mr. Dale, be honest too.
Not a good boy.
Every day is okay, right?
Try to study.
Studying is tired.
What did I talk about.
Majority
You are tired of studying.
It is lying.
Because I did not study.
I abandoned it, I abandoned it.
I did not study.
Tired of
Tired
Now let me teach you to study.
I was talking about that.
Oh my sister.
That good boy?
Oh well, I am going.
Study to.
Let me study.
Yes I teach.
This time, it is not easy, but
Next I will not forgive.
I know, I am studying.
I will not forgive you the second year.
I say you know.
I know English, my sister, I am good at English, I am not good at English, I am good at English, I am good at English, I am good at English, I am good at English, I am good at English.
I want to tell you, I am glad.
Mathematics is bad.
Mathematics is difficult.
It is difficult, right?
How can you get wrong points?
Tell me about the technique.
Technical learning, anyway.
Such a technique.
Do you want to know that there is a good learning method?
You know, you do not want to do a bad job at school because it is a waste of time.
Your mother is also smart.
And so, Mr. Dudley, really do.
I always enjoy eating my mom’s delicious food.
Mr. Aida is a good boy.
Mom, you are okay.
To whom they resemble.
The voice of my father.
Not being honest.
People in the world are better than that.
Tell it to your mother too.
My dad always says this.
I will not allow the next run.
Do you know that you are studying now?
If you are under pressure, it will become stressful.
Well, you guys, you should be pressured.
Well, right now, but not a lot of mental healing, boy.
Yes, I think it is.
Not like our generation, but now.
In front of you, really.
What do you think of the Sweat?
What is?
Effective and effective learning methods.
What is it.
Sister is
Tell me.
What happened to Sasha?
Oh, is nothing
Not even drinking?
not drinking either.
Are you sick?
All in all, he is okay.
Because you are interested.
You have to be careful.
Can you do our company?
Talk a lot.
The Tango?
He is cold and has a cold.
A week for the company.
A week too?
It is long, now.
When you speak, you will know.
I endured.
No problem, that is it.
You have to be careful.
Be careful you too.
If everyone is down in the house.
Yes Yes Yes
Studying will not be anywhere.
What happened, my daughter?
What happened.
The University report arrived.
Back to room.
Tell me.
Tell me
Oh my daughter, it is great.
I will tell you.
Oh well, really
Are you not feeling bad?
What happened to you.
But a little.
I will take care of you.
Tell me.
Because of the 3rd grade.
Okay, I did it.
Was there noise?
Yes yes, it is awesome.
There is everything.
I better teach you the SOP.
really is?
It is awesome.
I am tired today.
You worked hard.
Because you are right.
The reward.
Eat and pretend.
But to your mother.
I say okay.
It will not clear up, if you are quiet.
Because I am not studying.
See this here.
A little
I mean bad.
It is okay.
You always do.
It was like this.
Yogi’s mouth is really good.
Wait a little.
Yes is
Mother, what happened to you?
I am worried if I am studying.
It was so.
I taught my sister a great lesson.
Is it over already?
It feels like a rest.
I said community.
Teach me so much.
How is?
It pushed up too much.
Soon, even here.
It has melted.
Good, it was good.
Yeee, a little bit of it.
There is a quiet place.
I want eye.
Continue to rely on them.
Okay enough now.
that
It is reliable.
You’re going to be together for five months, right?
I am not away from you and your years.
Okay, no matter what.
I was worried if I could do it well.
It was so.
really
Sister is very kind.
confused to
Teach me to study.
It was great.
Not even your real friend.
Do it again from now on.
of course is.
Of course this one is more.
I had to hide it.
I was so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy, so happy.
I am always very kind and very helpful in homework.
Good luck, good luck, good luck with college.
Yes, parents always have to do their own.
You are a nice boy, please.
What happened?
I coughed a little.
Maybe the sunrise wind has gone.
How about you?
Heat up and go to sleep.
Yes is
I have to be careful.
Yes, I’m going to buy dinner stuff.
Fish today?
of course is.
Fish is cheap today.
Yes, I like the fish.
I say fish.
If I buy it, I will tell you.
Sorry, it was a long time.
So, I’ll go a little.
Come to go.
Do not feel good?
Whenever I say.
is there.
I will find out.
Do it really.
Definitely good.
really
OK is OK.
I do not know.
I want to be cheaper now.
Oh yes what?
and no.
Reduction and Ridge.
I will give you.
Yes to.
When the exam is over, I want to go to the hot spring with my family.
You want to go to the hot spring.
The hot spring.
Okay to.
It is awesome.
I love it, but if it doesn’t, it doesn’t.
I know, I will try hard, I will try hard.
Try slowly and work hard.
Is this good here.
I wait a little, I will definitely do it.
Can I really believe it?
Yes, it is okay.
The ordinary stone.
It is common stone.
It is in the province of Niagara.
The Nicaragua?
The Nicaragua.
Oh my little girl.
Yes to.
How about the voice, Nick?
I have never been to Nikko.
Please go.
You know for a moment, right?
Let us do.
and no.
Oh my dear,
Yes to.
What if I go to the hot spring?
I have never been to Nikko.
Yes, well well well well
I want to go.
Let me do nicotine.
It is Niko.
Something inside the hotel.
Three or four, so decide.
Yes is
well well well
Go to Niko.
That is, I have to die.
I feel like I say.
I also notice.
Oh, and then a hotel.
The rocker gets the rocker.
I love you, I’ll go in.
Really going in.
No to
The rocker enters.
Not okay.
What is said?
A little, a little, a little.
It feels good.
Oh well, so on.
Oh what?
Have you had a boyfriend now?
My boyfriend is not there now.
Is it not?
There is no.
You said I was there.
Oh is?
You are younger, my boyfriend.
The younger?
My younger boyfriend is dating.
Are you not a high school student?
Not a high school student, but.
I said that this is old life.
If I were old, I would love you.
Oh, it is true.
Men and Men.
I am there, boyfriend.
Yes to
Too much, that is.
Too much for my boyfriend.
If you were a student, you would be able to interfere with your life and study.
I love to do so.
I want to present.
Did you bring him home this time?
I cannot present.
Can not?
It is OK.
I said it was always okay.
Oh is?
What do you mean?
If you were a friend of a familiar.
Because I cannot be able to.
Why is it.
Shamefully
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Do not move.
You can choose from what you like to choose a 10 meter old anchoe.
I like the Anchorage.
Yes, I like the Anchorage.
I can go one foot.
Yes, it feels good.
Yes
Wait a little.
It looks delicious.
Yes
Oh yeah
Very up.
Then they ate two.
Yes
Tell me if I put it here.
Leave it here.
If you want more, press here.
No to
I already wanted to go.
You can go.
Can I go?
No to
No to no.
No is not.
No to
I will be hungry.
No to No.
No to
Maybe it went out.
Yes is
Not going is okay.
Is it this time?
Yes is
You thought you were going.
I love
Yes
You also go shopping.
It will feel change.
I am not.
Come and teach her to study.
Succeed to.
The hot spring journey is getting closer.
Let me wait.
I let you wait.
Maybe it was okay.
You have not found out.
We will clean it out in the room.
Do you still do?
Let us remove it.
I did though.
No to no.
is well now.
The two will not come.
Yes
That is me.
Oh yeah
Okay is.
A little though.
Bad to know.
That is good.
Not good though.
No to no.
Before the idiot.
I know I know.
No to no.
What if I find out?
You should say it was getting hot, right?
Do you know?
You don’t think we’re not together, right?
Have you not yet found out?
Not to find out.
Are you deceiving?
They are deceiving.
You just had a very hard voice.
You should have spoken more, right?
No to no.
I laughed already.
I will surprise.
No longer have to be patient.
I want more.
I want to do.
It hurts.
Go to your ass.
Yes
Feel good.
This is good.
hurtly
Feel good
by
It is growing.
greatly
This is highest.
Just here, look at it.
Just here?
Yes, here
Look at the camera.
Oh well that great.
Let’s put it on your finger.
Really the best.
really is?
The feeling?
Always bear it.
Do you like this?
I like it most.
I like your breasts.
Tagged as
by Nayem
It became big.
How many times?
It feels good.
Great
Oh, it is a lot.
You like this.
Liked it
You are messy.
It feels good.
Continued the next time.
Ji is
Oh yeah yeah yeah
No to
Is it okay?
Go to.
Oh go go
Yes agreed
Take it.
Move to
Oh yeah yeah yeah
It may be easier to go.
Fuck me, fuck me here.
Going out again.
Feel badly
Go to
Yes
Do it again tomorrow.
See also Suharto.
4 months already.
But we live together.
How about the beginning?
Are you doing friends?
We became very close friends.
Oh yes
It was good.
A little, you were worried.
Yes, because you are a good age.
At first I thought it would happen a little bit.
But he is a good boy.
At first, he is serious.
Today I am going to Iowa for a woman’s party.
So, what about dinner, what about dinner?
What is good?
Will you make me a shirt?
If it is easy, I will make it.
Yes is.
Is there no mother today?
I am on an unforgettable sea trip.
He said it was going to travel.
What do you do for food?
She said she would make it.
Will your sister really make it?
If it is simple.
How many months have you been living with your sister?
Maybe cooking for your sister and your brother.
So is it?
You have never eaten.
My mother always made it.
Maybe you can make curry.
Curry is fine.
Curry is good.
The smell of a nice spice can be a little bit smelly.
You can’t make it so genuine.
Oh yes?
Are you not working as a family teacher today?
Not today, but tomorrow?
Tomorrow is
Yes, the job
You are very good, you are doing two jobs, right?
Coffee and Family Classroom
Yes, there are more kids doing.
Because if I were a college student, I would definitely like to play more than work.
You work hard, you just play.
I am still doing good, I am still studying for the exam.
When I go to college, I want to play.
Because I have an exam.
Madonna, do you have a boyfriend?
No more boyfriend.
Maybe because he broke up a year ago.
Oh yeah yeah.
Oh yeah
So you work hard.
Yes
You are a beautiful girl, you can soon get a boyfriend.
Yes, my my my my.
It is beautiful, like the river.
No, it is not so.
I have no friends in sports.
My friend, yes, but there is.
And then, if the meeting is in.
I want to have a beautiful hair like my sister.
You can do it for the first time.
I could do it to my dad, so I could.
It’s my son, so it’s okay.
I don’t say anything bad, I’m sure the college will be fine.
If you fall, you will be as long as Ronnie.
Can I do it with IRA?
Try hard and fall.
Of course I will try hard.
If anything, if anything.
No two can.
My sister is also studying.
Is it okay?
Yes, yes yes yes
It will be hard, but please congratulate me.
Yes to.
Because I am working as a family teacher.
It is very good to teach, you know.
Okay, do it well, do it well.
Definitely already active.
Oh well okay.
I think good.
If you have to go out once, don’t you go here once?
Yes, but especially
Yes to.
You have lost.
I smoked this.
I’m gambling, I can get it back.
I like where Icon is.
Yes, yes, you are getting very low.
You cannot win, my first child.
A little please.
Studying hard.
Yes, it is natural to try.
When will you seem bored?
This guy seems good.
It seems to be.
Oh yeah
Max, is your voice bad?
A little...
You look so young, sister.
It is hot...
Is it hot?
It is hot, yes.
It is shut down in the middle.
What happened? something happened?
No, this is this.
This time.
What to do.
Buy it, you are.
The first time
Sorry sorry sorry
Do not let him sleep.
be careful.
What a sister.
This is not dirty.
Better do this.
No to
What is it, my little.
A little bit.
I am
University report
Because I have to do.
Oh yeah yeah
Yes
Sorry to
A little
The beginning
that
What
Oh well okay.
What are you doing.
I broke some candy.
Clean it properly.
You need to water this.
Your mother will be angry.
Oh, it is shit.
But more money.
Make sure it decreases.
Study well.
Maybe I will study too.
Is this different?
The lie?
But it fits up, right?
The cane is also suitable.
I did it!
It’s about 90 hours now, right?
Oh yeah, but yes
But it’s not so, so you should use it here.
No, but if this is in line with this, then it is okay.
Oh no, no, no no no no no.
Could it?
So give me a reward.
The reward?
Yes, the reward
You have to study, right?
If you would reward me.
What is your reward?
No to no.
What do you mean?
You always do it, you reward.
But Daddy, you are in that room.
So do it before your dad comes.
Even if I know.
Why do you make a thread, brother?
Do it today.
I have to do this, I don’t want to study.
If you know, you will be upset.
It is okay, I don’t know.
Oh, because only a little.
When the award is finished, you will study.
of course is.
You have to do as usual.
Hand and mouth as usual.
I understand
greatly
I want to give her a reward.
Great pan pan.
The mother?
Okay okay okay okay.
Up to the point.
Oh that is it.
The mouth of my sister.
First of all, the swallow.
I go in.
So what the beginning?
I told them to go to school and go to communicate.
by Aha
You are learning well at first.
I am struggling.
I want to borrow school.
How about.
You will borrow it from your first effort.
Today, I’m not there, I told you that I’m having a ballet practice at night.
Yes is.
What is the word for today? can you make a mixture again?
No, a little
Or do you want to take a night out, which one?
Yes, I think you can go ahead for a long time.
Oh, but what do you want to eat?
I am anything...
I can’t do anything, I’m sure it’s best.
Say you like it.
Or a rice.
Then, yes, you can also have pizza.
I like pizza, I like it first.
Yes to.
I ordered a pizza, and I ordered it at night.
So what are you studying now?
Oh, you have worked hard on this.
This signature is a signature disruption.
It is not useful at all.
I am going to study for exam, so I have to do it.
I can borrow this and do this gymnastics.
If you don’t know, tell me, Yuki.
So, it’s time to get a pizza.
Drinking is Coca Cola.
Is the Coca-Cola okay?
When I get home, I say, Today is Pizza.
Yes I understand.
I will order.
thanks to
What happened sister?
Dad has come.
Why do you do this?
I’m so excited, my sister, when you’re with your dad.
I felt something more amazing than usual.
No so is.
You lie, you’re more excited when you’re with your dad, sister.
I said more than usual.
Not so is.
Really?
Oh my mymy.
Where was your mother today?
I told him I was going out to eat with a friend.
So what will happen to today’s dinner?
Will you make it again, or will you have a hand or something?
If you want to make it simple, I will make it.
Make a Mick.
Yes, I understand
Is your mom here somewhere today?
Oh yeah
It seems your mother is coming.
A lot of things are difficult.
But it will happen when my mother comes home.
Have you tried traveling?
Yes, so I think we should go both.
Here we are, let’s.
What do you do?
What are you doing?
No, no, no more can’t be.
I say no, but I am beating myself.
You started saying that.
At first, they are also very close.
It has been six months.
First, you should massage them.
You are massage.
Good things together, good things together.
He is studying for exams.
My sister, because I love you too.
My sister walked.
Yes sister.
I told you before, I don’t know a little.
Can you tell me a little bit, sister?
Yes, I understand
Oh really?
Helps and helps.
I didn’t understand there.
Then teach me.
Yes
Shit is bad.
You can do it too.
Yes
Go to room.
You were very excited.
Even if it is not so.
is lying.
So it ends?
If you are not excited, you can say that your sister is not excited, but it is over.
It is...
What is it?
I do not want to finish.
Do you want to say it, sister?
I want to do.
Okay, it is full.
I want to be as always.
What to do.
Because it cannot.
It seems to be much more sensitive.
Woke up early.
Not warm body.
Is it warm?
You have to touch your breasts.
Try to hide yourself.
I understand
Feel good
The sad voice of my mother.
Sorry to
The highest
My sister is very good.
No so does.
You look beautiful whenever you look.
I like it very much, my breast.
My sister’s breasts are beautiful and sensitive.
My sister likes to be fighting her chest.
I like it.
Speak with a louder voice.
Do you want me?
I want to be smoked.
Spread it.
It is dirty.
This is sperm.
behind her sister’s position.
I do not know.
Oh shit, a little
It was brood and brood.
Become a scrap tube.
No is not.
In the middle.
It is very closed.
The first spirit is in.
No...
Oh oh oh oh! oh oh!
Oh shit, oh oh oh
It hurts again.
Oh to!
Oh shit...
Hike and Hike!
by HACK!
Oh to!
It feels good.
Finish it already.
What do you care about?
I returned to my sister twice.
Not yet entirely good.
The taste of the first spirit.
Tastefully
Yes
It feels good?
Feels good?
Can I do it again?
It is awesome.
It is still so hard.
Feels good?
You are still so human.
As always
Can I just do it? just now.
It feels good.
Oh well 😂
I did a lot of things before, so I got back there again.
Capped Ce
Stop and stop, pulled.
Tang is
It hurts, it hurts.
very painful
Can I do more?
Great, I can’t get back.
It is inside.
The Attic!
I too
Can I follow?
by Poco
by WIKI
Wokie
Turn backwards.
The failure is rapidly increasing.
Relaxed
So good Shirley.
Oh, you will sleep.
Okay, a little bit
I will sleep.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah yeah yeah
I too once more.
Oh yeah
It is already full.
I want more.
It is great.
Feelings are so much.
No to
Oh is
How many times, then?
Feeled...
It is hidden, feeling.
Oh... oh... oh...
The first feeding.
The Sister
Tagged as HAKKA
Oh yeah yeah
No to
Oh yeah
Oh is
Overview
Oh yeah
I am getting more and more fond of the chicken.
About you.
Liked it
Do not get along with you too.
But can I do?
Get out of it.
Get the sperm of Ashley.
The sperm of Asperger is awesome.
Become a Gucci.
Oh, and I’m a little too closed.
Still so tight.
Let me wait, Toby.
It feels good.
Skyscraper is so much.
It feels good, seriously.
Wii
by
Sorry
AsmR
I don’t know how many times I said it.
I can almost relate to it.
Oh well oh well.
and cookies.
I don’t know the previous.
This time go.
I want to put her in her face.
Oh yeah
Heaven is
appears to be.
Oh, I was wearing it.
hug him.
by
Oh well!
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, that is a great feeling.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
It felt great.
My sister, today was harder than usual.
I think it will be, W. W.
But it was so good feeling.
I did a lot.
Now, let’s go somewhere more.
from now on.
Everywhere to?
But I hope you will find out again.
Because you are not excited, you are excited.
Yes but
So, maybe that too.
by Suv
No to?
You are used to this home.
Yes, you were used to it.
Good to be.
No, it was that.
What is?
Suddenly, we had to live together.
Yes is.
How about your mother?
Yes, he is a very kind person.
Takesh, what are you?
Oh you Takeshi?
Yes, a very nice boy.
They are doing well together.
He is a good guy, his.
Yes, I think he is a very nice kid.
I too
Good was.
I was worried about it before, too.
Don’t worry, it’s okay.
No to
that
for employment activities.
I said it was done, so I put my hair on.
You can’t live that much.
I was busy a while ago, I forgot.
I was worried, yes, I was worried all the time.
Decided by that company? Yes, I said before.
I cried, oh that is.
Where I wanted to go, I decided.
So that hair.
I understand.
Maybe something happened.
No to.
I am imbecile.
by Imech.
Do not change much.
But isn’t it good?
As a father.
Would you prefer this?
is boring
No taste though.
It is taste.
This one is more cute.
It is like a hot spring hotel.
I ride a lot.
It is great, I want to go.
Just just.
I want to go.
I was talking about it with my mother.
Fuck to
Seriously
Let’s go all together.
I want to go if the company decides to go.
Oh yeah yeah yeah?
Yes is.
I want to go.
Oh, where am I, where am I?
This is so beautiful, doesn’t it look so kind?
How about a budget?
Okay, I have decided to get a job.
Yes is it.
It is my celebration, my celebration.
Oh, Mr. Bannon, sit down and sit down.
Oh what?
I was injured because I got an inside view.
Oh yeah yeah.
Well, I think we’re going to travel with four.
Oh well okay.
Yes, I think it is good to do something here.
to which?
here here.
Okay well, this is this.
Are you going to travel or go on a trip?
I have been there before, but I haven’t been there lately.
So, it is just okay.
Yes to.
No, it is fun.
Take a bath and talk to each other.
Yes is.
Yes is
You can drink it now, right?
I mean, but I drink as much.
Drink with them, and take them on your shoulders.
So why, Mr. Bates
I think I’ll decide something in two years.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Yes is
Well, I’m a bit more confident, I’ve already decided on it, and I’ve had a lot of experience.
Yes, yes is
If you have any trouble, ask the puppy.
So, please at that time.
Oh yes of course.
I am so strong, I am so strong, but there is something bad about it.
Stop for a moment.
Yes, I have never seen a stronger.
Yes
I will pump immediately.
Oh yeah, that is.
Yes yes yes yes
Maybe you are wearing a cat now.
Oh yeah yeah.
If you get used to it a little, it may change again.
No so is.
I am already a grown-up, because I am an adult.
Stop that.
Oh, you know you know.
Yes, I thought it would be good there too.
Oh, but a lot of things.
Yes, I have a lot of cousins.
Oh yeah
Long time no hot water.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
When is it, snow?
I felt like I was going when I was a little girl.
Because it is a hot spring.
There are a lot of tourist places, so there is something around.
Yes, of course
Yes, even at that time.
I went in with my mom.
I don’t want to be with Dad, I want to say.
Oh yeah
It seems you have grown up already.
Don’t listen, wait anymore.
I do not remember.
If you listen to me, I’m not a little more a laughing.
Why say that.
When you don’t listen to what you say, you do.
There was such a time, there was such a time.
Oh well, what about it.
But maybe it was like that before.
What is it, shrimp.
Oh, I want to go, a little boy.
Oh is?
Please get it.
Yes, come to me.
I am very excited, but well, goodbye.
No, we are already very close together.
really is?
Yes to.
Yes, both of you.
No to?
Next month, on March 9,
I told you about traveling with my mom.
Okay, I am empty.
Okay okay okay okay.
Is it empty?
Wait a little.
Yes, it is empty.
Good to.
Mom, you are so happy.
It is Tension Max.
Is it so?
Where to go.
Good to.
You have to decide, so you have to make a reservation.
by Early.
It is important to travel, what to do, where to go.
for the purpose.
Not for meals? not for meals?
The food.
This is good.
Which one, it looks delicious.
Oh, it looks delicious.
Looks very delicious.
Okay, that is okay.
Or local vegetables.
by S.
Oh is?
I want to eat local vegetables.
Vegetables are fine.
First, I want to decide what to eat.
You know where you are going, or where you are going, from SNS.
Yes is.
Go and you.
Meat and meat.
Meat, meat and meat.
Which one of them.
What? what?
Oh is?
Sorry, I haven’t seen it.
Meat or pork.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Oh, which one of them.
Do not think so.
Soap is delicious.
It is Soba.
Sorry for all of the SOP.
Okay, is it a shit.
What about the day?
No to?
No, it is okay.
I am so worried about Sophie.
I have not just listened.
Sorry, sorry and sorry.
I don’t know if I’m going to go, I don’t know if I’m going to go, I don’t know if I’m going to go, I don’t know if I’m going to go.
Yes is.
Where I went.
It is delicious, though.
Yes is.
Who is eating that straw.
What happened?
Not not not not.
something
I wonder what to do.
The hot spring street.
If you say hot water, you are a fool.
What else happened.
Mr to
No to?
The hot springs are all over.
Sweet and delicious.
Has the taste changed?
It is sweet.
It is a little different, isn’t it?
Probably
You want to go back to the back again, right?
I drank too much.
Did you drink too much yesterday?
Did you come home late?
From the second time.
Did you drink too much?
Be careful, I decided to cry.
Yes is.
Getting caught?
Is it okay?
A little, no too.
I want to cry.
But okay, okay is okay.
Eat curry at the hot spring.
Do you have any local softcreme?
Oh yes so.
Oh what.
Oh, it looks delicious.
Oh, that is what, that is what.
Oh well okay.
There are many nice cafes.
A lot of.
The soft cream.
It is more soft than hot water.
Yes, I would definitely prefer you.
It is older than the whole hot spring.
Yes is it.
It is soft cream.
It is used in local milk.
Oh yeah, that is it.
Definitely delicious.
I like chocolate very much.
Oh well okay.
I tried to get to Max.
No peanut cream.
What happened, what happened?
It became a toilet.
Come on quickly.
I am going.
I am unfamiliar, I cry.
Drinking too much.
It was definitely late.
This is used by this formula.
You understand?
I understand
Yes
thanks to
The challenge is over.
I helped, thank you.
recently a little.
I think you are a little too much exposed.
I will tell you a little bit about your dad.
It is OK, OK.
You are doing it well so you don’t know.
I can’t tell you, I can’t stand the voice.
I want to quit, but I want to quit.
But my sister is excited.
No, not that way.
You are more sexy than sex, right?
No, it is not so.
But the body is becoming honest.
If you say that, you will no longer have sex.
Okay is?
It is a little what?
No is
Do not like?
No to
Can you have sex?
Say you hate.
A little bit.
What is?
Why is it always so?
always is
But you are pleased.
I am glad you are crying.
Do not do it again?
No to
Do not like?
Now a little.
You are crying.
Really not?
Do not hate.
Where are you touching?
Please wait a little.
A little better.
Wait a little, really.
Well, I have no such thing to say.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
I dress up a little.
Oh yes please.
Oh sorry to.
Oh, maybe a little better.
Oh yes yes yes.
Oh is?
Did you say something?
No, I have said nothing.
I did not find snow.
Oh, I was going to a shop.
Oh, and so
Actually is
Yes is
Next month, next month, next month, next month, next month, next month, next month, next month, next month.
Oh my mother.
Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes
Something, yes
It was delicious, but I thought I would go eat it.
Oh yeah, is it okay?
See also Bamboo.
What is good.
That is that.
Anything is okay, right?
Not that it is anything.
No, but I think I’ll be happy with anything.
For example, this is
It is a plateau.
Sushi is good, but baked meat.
I love my mom’s sushi and baked meat.
No, but specifically
Anything, whether it’s meat or fish, would be good.
The burning fish?
I think, I think well.
Whether she is a sheep or a goat.
I think the goats are a bit uncomfortable.
That is what I say, listen.
But anything else is possible.
Even a bird?
No, I think it is okay.
Did you say something?
I also want to get a bit of money.
Okay, it is entirely.
No no no, it is bad.
No, no, but that is fine.
It doesn’t go, I mean, an image.
What is it, Peggy?
Well, so, you should be a steel broker or a steel broker.
The iron burn.
Yes Yes Yes Yes
If it is burned, anything is good.
by Peggy
What else, what else do you like?
No, I was a little bit sick when I swallowed it.
Oh, there is
And then the burnt meat.
Okay is.
Can I think a little more?
I understand.
Can I go in the snow?
Yes, I understand
It is fun.
is okay.
Do you hate?
It was cold, so it would have broken.
A little
Very wet is.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
My sister was also excited.
No to no.
Next is.
In front of your father and mother.
Do not have sex.
You cannot do it.
I can, okay
I will make sure you can’t walk.
Do it though.
Oh, the slumber
It is fun.
What is?
Next week’s trip.
Next week already?
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
I didn’t forget, I thought it was too early.
No, because I went by car.
really is?
Three hours
3 hours, is it okay?
It is a holiday driver’s arm.
It’s okay, but I’m a little worried.
I let him.
really is?
So, you’re going to eat curry.
Yes to yes?
What to eat?
Curry is
Curry, did you talk about it?
I was a mother, so.
If you want to say.
It was delicious on the way, curry soup.
It is so.
You like curry soup, too.
I like.
The insect of Aida.
It is fun.
What is fun?
Why is it.
It is travel.
Oh, is it traveling.
Did you talk about curry?
Talk about curry?
I drive curry on the road, rather than curry vegetables on the road.
Was it so?
I guess he did.
So, my mom got up.
I said it would be nice.
It is fun.
cannot be
Was it curry soup?
I’m also looking forward to curry, but I’m also looking forward to soft cream.
Oh yeah, did you not check?
Please check with the Sweat.
Oh yeah I understood.
Check together.
Oh what?
The Soft Cream.
The soft cream?
Oh yeah, I understand.
What is Hot Springs?
I also want to eat hot water.
Then then,
What are you doing?
Just a massage.
The massage?
Oh, you are friends.
Oh yeah yeah.
Be friends, be good.
What happened?
Come to my dad sometimes.
Father, you are okay.
by Kane
Next time.
Do not be harsh.
A little
No is?
Oh, I want you to do it.
Now here at me.
I can have inches.
Yes is.
I say Dad.
I think you should go to the store.
It just is open.
This is, here is.
I have to remember a lot.
I am worried that it is just Nash.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
You lost me here and here.
Better to be here.
Yes, yes is it.
Yes Yes Yes
My sister would prefer to be here too.
Yes, yes yes yes
such such
I think good.
It is far away.
That is it.
It is awesome.
Is it okay?
Oh I forgot.
by the Frog.
Would you like to go next?
I don’t know, but I’m next door.
well well
Looks like it is.
There are a lot of mistakes here.
Should I go next again?
What happened?
Yes, yes yes yes
Say the same, the same.
Yes or yes?
Yes it is okay.
A lot of things,
You are riding this.
Fun is okay.
Even if I just look.
Okay okay okay okay.
Is it okay?
Yes, yes, all is okay.
No to.
What is?
You have a hotel, right?
Yes, I remember I remember.
You just go to the hot spring, right?
Is it just a hot spring? – I’m sure.
Okay is.
Is it really okay?
You should go to the hospital before it grows.
Go to the hospital, go to the hospital.
So, it’s time, I think you’ll end up with a fisherman.
Go shopping and go out at the station.
I understand
Go to the station.
Yes, I cannot go.
Have you gone.
I went, I went
Then I will go.
I will go.
Come to go.
Be careful.
Birds are
No to
None is
Oh yeah yeah
Oh well
Yes
Yes is
Show me it.
Oh well
Flexible car balls.
Oh well...
well
Really well
not really
Oh well...
Oh...
by Tia
by
Oh...
Oh yeah...
Oh well
Oh oh oh
Oh is
It was
The painful hands.
I said something.
I want more.
Feel good
Fuck, it is long ago.
Okay, it is okay to be a puppy.
No to? I want to want.
What is?
I want to want.
Where do you want?
Go to the shit here.
Not well right?
Oh well
Please this.
Oh yeah
if
Oh is
Sorry to
It is
No more can.
A little
Go to
Oh yeah
by
Wake up
Why more and more.
Stop it.
Stop it, stop it.
No to No.
I am angry! I am angry!
This is a façologic.
I am sorry...
When you do it, the stomach hurts.
It is big! big!
Shit not
No to No.
is moving?
Hahahahahah
Do you feel?
Feel badly
Feels good?
Feel good
Oh, it is painful
No to no.
hungry is
Stop to?
I don’t want to, I hurt, my sister.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
Sister, turn to me.
Awesome sound
More and more.
Okay, and then go
What do you want?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Little, little, little little, little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little little
Do not drink,
Do not drink.
Feels good?
A little more...
I care about you.
See also: Widget
What do you want?
Oh, oh, oh, oh oh oh oh
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
So far...
You can have problems.
Oh yeah yeah
Do not want?
It’s too much, it won’t go, it won’t go.
It feels good.
I like it, I like it there.
Wake up, wake up, wait
It will be crazy, it will be crazy.
Feels good?
Feel good
Very good feeling.
not down
Great Gorgon
No to Gorgon.
Oh...
Yes...
Yes
Oh well
Oh...
Yes
Tomorrow...