About tidying up the room
There are a lot of people
can you please
My room is dirty
There is a special service
child 's
yes
yes housekeeper will come
please
I called you after seeing an ad
-Please take care of me - Please take care of me
bye
Sorry
off
-sorry - okay _
is a special service
Can you come in
> Come to clean your room
Please take care of me
twenty one
so many people
twenty two
God brings newcomers to training
twenty three
don't care
twenty four
It can be handed over to the housewife
thanks - please
let's clean
sorry
first sign
please come in
Sorry
We are housewives
where to start
Sorry
Is it messy?
really ?
< Is it sorted out?
Let's clean up
I am Aixiang
sorry let's start
In short , let’s clean up the trash first
I am Meiyi, please take care of me
I got it
can you
here comes
I am Huasui
is this way
Please take care of me
-yes - yes _
yes my room is messy
very good
Please take care of me
is it
Sorry for the beat
Today is a special package
I am Yuji, please take care of me
Special package please
-sorry - please _
Not a special package
ok
You can rest assured
Please
I will clean too
yes
Is that so?
sorry
Is there a trash can
stuff is here
-Is that so - I see
You take it easy and rest
put the trash here
This garbage is not classified
Sorry
How about
really big
I got it
Let's see
the trash here
Is that so?
Then classify
Is it okay to tidy up like this ?
Can I put it here?
All sorted out
Large ratio
Amazing is a special package
I got it
There is a lot of garbage here
It's okay
you go on
so sorry
all right
- please - sorry
Let me sort it out
Is it a special package?
sorry I see
Let me sort it out for you
It's hot
sorry It's fine
don't do this
I often use this set
ok
Is that so?
Wait Why did you take off your clothes ?
-is that so - yes
Wait
Wrote it on the homepage
I have seen it
I got it
I don't know =
Are you using a special package?
sorry
Have you made an appointment online?
bad wood
It's hot take off your clothes
There is a lot of rubbish here
Are you shy easily ?
Have you made an appointment online?
-Is that so- this is my ad
It's like this
-is that so - yes
Inside
You can rest assured
If we took your money
It would be nice to use a special package
how to return
It's amazing very messy
a lot of rubbish
Is there a special package?
don't care i will clean
yes
Let me take a look
look under the bed
No
Look at this
Why are you dressed like this?
Then keep cleaning
the body
ok
Why such a mess
can i have a look
thank you
Come into the room
don't
come here
This is a service
I got it
what's wrong with you
Go do the laundry
the master Can this be thrown away?
I see
It's okay
Is that good?
It 's amazing
child 's
It's amazing
a lot
ok
don't care look at us
This is how it is organized
what's wrong
do you want to touch
You can touch it for free
Let's see
Can I touch it?
Is that so?
The ass is here
come touch me
You are so cute
you can come here
you squat down
are you shaken
can you
Rub your face
It's amazing
where are you looking
I saw it
-Is that so- let 's take a closer look
You can look at it at will
if this close
It's off like this
I'm a little tired
stand together
Take it off and wash it
You like it very much
You can come and see
I'll clean it later
this off?
take it off first
okay
It 's amazing
You can see clearly
multiple flavors
11:
really
This is how to organize everything
I take it off
Not so bad
It's off like this
look at this
what's wrong with you
let's take a break
It 's a bit dirty
what to do
-what to do- is that so
It's a bit dirty here
Wait
It's still messy here
I'm a little tired
It’s fine to organize like this
Throw this away
now is bad
That 's good
sorry
take it off first
It's getting bigger
I want to relax
Sorry
don't cover
No
how is it
what's wrong with you
yes
It 's amazing
what's going on
have you hardened
Sorry clean the toilet
I 'm touching
Is it a special package?
Wait
It 's amazing
good
I go in
wasteful
go to your room
Do you want to solve it alone?
such words
don't cover It's a waste
you lie down
Let me lick it clean for you
Is it a special package?
ok
It's amazing turned red
is like this
It's amazing very hard
really
Are you comfortable?
Wait
It's amazing
don't do this
yes
can you
here too
don't do this
The cock is hard
Is the stimulus strong?
-don't- lick it for you
Is that so ?
Are you having a hard time?
It's hard
Let me lick you too
very shy
touch your tits
It's getting hard here
look at the cock is dirty
very shy
It's hard
Not so
very shy
yes
Then I want too
big
did you cum
I can't do it
Amazing cock
very shy
It's amazing made a sound
The cock is stronger than before
It's hard
don't
don't cum
keep licking
I cum
It's amazing
are you going to cum
can you still cum
Uncle
don't
It's amazing
Is it an illusion?
Come and touch me
all right
don't do this
The special package has not started yet
-wait - do you want to cum
what you say
-don't do that - reactions are cute
very nice expression
really
yes Comfortable
want to bully you
I hold it too
can't ejaculate
Are you comfortable
Very comfortable expression
don't do this
what
Then you touch me here
don't do this
what 's it like
very poor
Is your whole body shaking?
meat stick
Slowly hardened
where
Not enough
don't do this
very comfortable
It 's amazing
ok
comfortable
I can't help it
Let me touch your tits
I 'll lick it for you
Do n't be so bad
can i lick
Are you comfortable ?
Let me lick the balls
very comfortable
very wet so cute
you come and lick me
are you sensitive
Continue to lick you
Very hard glans
You see, hold it
don't be so bad
I 'll lick it for you
It's hard work
very excited
It's amazing contained
It 's amazing
Come and touch me
It's amazing Comfortable
It's amazing
Your nipples are sensitive, right?
the master
comfortable
very comfortable
3 together."
No way
touch here
very comfortable
are you touching
Is this the first time?
what's going on
are you going to cum
can't ejaculate
very comfortable
Uncle is very comfortable
It's inserted into the pussy
very comfortable
i will cum
don't do this
I'm wet down there
very comfortable
Is it touching here?
It's amazing
very wet
This is very comfortable
-how - comfortable _
Are you about to cum
comfortable
was soiled
insert into a pussy very warm
The balls are hard
It's amazing very warm
Finger inserted into pussy
move
don't do this
go on
It's amazing
don't
It 's amazing
I orgasm Comfortable
Is that so?
Pick me very intensely
I orgasm Feel sorry
Lick it clean for you
don't i cum
It 's amazing
Fingers are dirty
very comfortable
Are you comfortable ?
Clamp it for you
No
Grab your cock with your tits
It's amazing clamped
do you like it
comfortable
Are you comfortable?
The whole body is very sensitive
No way
sorry
Your nipples are sensitive, right?
yes
I can't help it
It's bad
really
It's amazing
don't cum
how come
don't do this
juice comes out
The meat stick is very red
very cute
a lot of juice comes out
It's amazing
do you want to cum
did you cum
I really want
It 's amazing
Shot a lot
don't do this
I cum
You held back for a long time, right?
It's amazing is it painful
so i will cum
I cum
can you
-I can't help it - I can't
Yes you shoot
No way
How about
don't stop
thank you
can you
It's amazing
I cum
a lot of juice
are you going to cum
-shot - no _
You see a lot of juice
-want to cum - do you want to cum
very comfortable did you shoot
I'm about to cum
sorry
You look so wet
are you okay
Yes
It's dirty here
It's amazing
I cum
don't
you come out
Did you cum on the tits?
sorry i cum
I 'm shy
It's bad
It's amazing
Let me organize it for you
cum on your tits
sorry
very cute
Shot so much
It's amazing
Your face is dirty
-that 's it - sorry
hug
It's amazing shot a lot
There is sperm here
-that 's it - sorry
There is sperm on the nipple
You have saved a lot, right?
How about
Excuse me
did you ejaculate
It's amazing The dick is hard
It's here
You now enter the pussy
-does this - want to have sex
Want to be inserted into a pussy?
But
want to insert pussy
You can still cum
No
You don't save a lot, do you?
Lick your cock clean
don't do this
If you rub like this
Want to be inserted into a pussy?
don't
-Is it comfortable ? -No
ok
Want to have sex
wasteful
you want to penetrate pussy
Not inserted into the hole yet
not pretending
This is all
just watch
you enjoy
's all for you
ok
Excellent service
let me penetrate pussy
Is that so?
I penetrated the pussy
Inside the tits
have you gone in ?
Go in ahead
very comfortable
-isn't it the same - yes
inserted into the pussy
I want to insert a pussy
-pussy penetration - want pussy penetration
-very comfortable - awesome
Insert it
comfortable
How about
sorry
It's amazing
touch here
and inside the hole different
is different
It 's all in the pussy
too can shoot
don't do this
very comfortable
How about different?
ok
knead well
I told you not to cum
very comfortable
Are you comfortable?
i will cum
It's amazing so cute
It's amazing
the master
-comfortable - touch me
very comfortable
come touch me
My pussy is very comfortable
It's inserted inside
too i cum
It's amazing
Touch carefully
very comfortable
Can't you ?
It's amazing
I am very comfortable
very comfortable
ok
I orgasm
touch here?
I have an orgasm
Put your finger in the pussy
It's amazing
after you are happy
very comfortable
the master
don't i cum
Let me be comfortable next
ok
Can't you ?
comfortable
I also went to clean
No
very intense
ok
what's going on
I continue to clean
ok
Uncle do you like ass
It's amazing
Let me show you
Tidy up
very cute keep moving
It's amazing
Pick it up here
do you go
do you want to touch
my ass
Stay calm
very comfortable
It's inserted into the pussy
do you want to cum
-It 's not working - Is it not working?
You can touch my ass
don't do this
No way
ok
don't I can't help it
- very comfortable - 100
Let me touch your tits
I cum
Wait
hold back
you hold back
I can't do it anymore
comfortable
I can't do it
You can hold back
I thank you
ok
very comfortable
comfortable
Is that so?
Insert !
touch me like this Comfortable
keep plugging me in
next you move
It's amazing comfortable
Then insert it from behind
ok
It's amazing Comfortable
very comfortable
War climax If so
It 's amazing
very comfortable
〗 \r\nVery comfortable
Can I insert you like this?
Hold it to the bottom
very comfortable
very bad
I like this very much
I'm having an orgasm
very comfortable don't want
I like to be comfortable don't want
very warm
i will cum
-comfortable- do n't do this
It 's amazing
very warm
ok
comfortable
Continue to insert the pussy
don't i cum
I am taller
don't
Continue to insert the pussy
You didn't cum did you?
I insert pussy
I orgasm went
I cut high
Hold it to the inside
very comfortable
very soft
I like this very much
like this very much
very comfortable
Yes Shoot
Boobs are soft
If you still want can continue
I like tits very much
I am very comfortable
ok
very intense
It's amazing
very comfortable
do you like it
can you
Thanks
I orgasm went
I orgasm
do you want to cum
you cum
inserted into the pussy
wait no
do you want to cum
It's amazing
cum
Cum on tits
I can't help it
do you want to cum
I'm about to cum
I orgasm
give me cock
It's amazing so much shot
yes
go clean
-go - cum _
It's amazing very soft
please come in
all right
The cock can be inserted into the pussy at will
then
But
I still want it
Uncle still hard
Can I drink it?
please
ok
There are 2 more people
too
what's wrong
ok
I scan it \r\ nRead
cum
comfortable
sorry
I want a toilet
-Cum - Cum ?
Lick it clean for you
Please please
I cum
sorry
I'm fine
So I peed
Uncle 's cock is very comfortable
then go ahead
just ejaculated still very hard
can you
Wait
It's okay
Lick it clean for you
the master
such a thing
don't touch
don't do this Owner
what's wrong
口\r\n→
don't
you touch me so lewdly
I'm going to do the laundry
don't do this
My boobs are showing
yes
is possible
don't
very soft Can I touch it?
then
I'm so excited
Wash it with water
let's start
-this - is this
Finally
give you a bath
don't do this
don't touch me
your body and mind
ok
Please
then go in
Let me lick it clean for you
You held my ass
Lick it clean for you
are you excited
- can you - ok
Sorry
comfortable
How about
very comfortable
Your cock should be washed too
ok
don't touch me
I resisted me \r\nWhat 's the matter?
Let me wash it
It's hard
- all right - yes
Let me wash it for you
Is it here?
Are you comfortable ?
very comfortable
here
-cock - cock ?
let me make you comfortable
where is
It's amazing
Let me lick you here
Is it comfortable for me to touch the nipple?
I'll wash you like this
here
It's amazing
It's hard
it is - yes
It's amazing very wet
It's amazing
Is this comfortable?
then
Let me wash you clean
Just to wash you up
It's hard
Your dick is hard
This time
It 's amazing
You are so hard
yes
It 's amazing
comfortable place
It's amazing
very comfortable
Let me wash you with my butt
It 's amazing
ok
It's amazing
It's amazing your balls are hard
very comfortable
yes
Let me wash you clean
It's hard
Uncle
Is this comfortable?
It's amazing
tell me all
sensuality
It's amazing
If you don’t touch it directly, you still know it
cumshot ...
Let me take a shower and wash you clean
comfortable
It's very wet
It's amazing
No way
Is this comfortable?
shoot
` Help you wash
comfortable
It 's amazing
No way No way
-comfortable - comfortable ?
I cum
wasteful
Still very hard
It's amazing
I cum
if you cum
It's amazing hard tits
It's amazing very excited
I cum
It's hard
ok
bad
no more
inserted into the pussy
It 's a waste
Yes
I am also very comfortable
to shoot into small ,
It's amazing Comfortable
comfortable
It 's amazing
what's going on
It's amazing
Still very hard
It 's amazing
Are you comfortable ?
's big. - Okay
inserted into the pussy
very comfortable
No way - comfortable
persistent erection No way
don't do this
I orgasm
I'm having an orgasm
Is it comfortable to insert like this ?
It's amazing
No way
don't
comfortable
very comfortable
I orgasm
It 's amazing
Oops
-comfortable - touch me
ok
It 's amazing
touch my tits
don't
I am also very comfortable
don't do this
very happy
Don't insert it in the innermost part
Wait
rub my tits
don't
very comfortable
I orgasm
It's amazing
very comfortable Owner
don't Comfortable
don't i cum
keep plugging me in
-is that so - yes
No way
I orgasm
It's amazing don't want
sorry
It's amazing Owner
It's amazing
meat stick
don't stop
Stay to the bottom
It's amazing
Continue to insert it to the bottom
in this place
don't go
The cock is hard
I am very comfortable
come make love
don't go
I have to keep cleaning
-comfortable- i cum _
I'm so good
Uncle
I'm having an orgasm
It's amazing don't want
-very comfortable - no way
It's amazing
don't cum in
don't go like this
don't comfortable
don't do this
I am also very comfortable
-Awesome - very happy
Wait Comfortable
don't do this
I have an orgasm
don't i cum
don't
I orgasm
It's amazing
very comfortable
don't
delicious
I cum
I'm about to cum
Don't become so big
You take a shower
The cock is bigger next time
ok
come to me anytime
how are you feeling
Lick it clean for you
cum in the ass
Uncle wants Is it
dirty lick you clean
here too
The sperm is all licked clean
It's amazing lick you clean
very comfortable
It's amazing
can you
-Yes _
comfortable
?
Put it in the pussy
ok
can you
It's amazing
use my pussy
ok
It's amazing
go ahead and cum in
No matter where you shoot
cum in
ok
very comfortable
Sperm in it
I am in the same row
then i went to clean
I cum
It 's amazing
anytime
I cum
No way
You are very good at
It's amazing
take it away
I went
Lick it clean for you
This is very clear
only of
don't look
It's okay
very warm
It's wet down there
watch me
don't be shy
Others over there
I 'm shy don't want
care about
# continued - don't touch
You keep cleaning
show me
No way don't have sex
Is it comfortable here ?
show me
I can't
No way
don't
show me
-what 's wrong- show me
is like this
Hold on to the table
Put your ass up
let me clean
I 'll lick it for you
Yes you clean
show me
I orgasm
I went
It's amazing Comfortable
slowly getting wetter
I'm having an orgasm
very comfortable
you come down
you are great inside
you do things like this
Can't you ?
have you gone
very comfortable
Insert to the bottom
very good
don't do this
Lick it clean for you
It's okay Comfortable
really ?
your pussy
very good
very comfortable
sorry shot in
It's okay Comfortable
very good
ok
Insert the innermost comfortable
It's very clean
ok
very erotic
very good
one more time
wait for me to finish
very comfortable
do it again
really ? very happy
C\r\ nThank you
Yes
The entrance is rubbish
Next time you can cum inside me too
yes
what's wrong look at me like this
ok
The porch has been cleaned
- thanks - it's ok
Please
can ,
You can get pussy
Your cock is hard too
don't comfortable
Is that so?
what's wrong
Yes
ت الك ازالة
The floor is already clean
It's amazing
don't do this
very comfortable
very shy
Little Moon
The floor was clean
very comfortable
You are so horny
don't do this
very comfortable
very comfortable don't want
Don't touch like this
It's amazing
I am very comfortable
very comfortable
Sorry
-touch like this - don't
It's dirty
very comfortable
-orgasm - sorry _
-very horny - comfortable
don't do this
It's comfortable here
The cock is hard
don't
Lick me clean
Is it here?
It's amazing
It's amazing dirty
Is that so ?
sorry
Let me lick it clean for you
please
Don't touch me like this
don't do this
don't very comfortable
Let’s continue cleaning behind the entrance
It's so big
Go ahead and lick me clean
It's okay
Your cock is still hard
I'm having an orgasm
don't touch
I can't help it
comfortable
It's amazing
You insert it into the pussy
Is that so?
It's amazing
I lick you
I 'm cleaning insert it
It 's amazing
It's dirty here
very comfortable
Don't insert like this
Let me insert the pussy
I penetrated the pussy
you feel free to insert into the pussy
don't do this
don't Comfortable
very comfortable
I can't clean
don't Comfortable
Wipe it clean
don't do this
very comfortable
don't i cum
It 's amazing
-are you comfortable ? -comfortable
don't do this
don't very comfortable
sorry
-how - comfortable _
comfortable
don't do this
don't fuck me like this
don't
plug me like this i cum
I can't help it
It's amazing
don't i cum
don't do this
Are you comfortable?
sorry the floor is dirty
don't
don't the floor will get dirty
sorry the floor is dirty
It's amazing don't want
Not enough
very comfortable
very intense
It's amazing No
I penetrated the pussy
Give it to me
very comfortable
It's amazing
I want it too
don't comfortable
don't do this
Enter Primary Six One
I am very comfortable
I really want
I really want it
comfortable
me too
-really ? -yes _
Good
Is it comfortable to touch here?
-Put it in the pussy - It's awesome
It's amazing
I went
very comfortable Comfortable
very comfortable
It 's amazing
Are you comfortable?
very comfortable
I orgasm
I am also very comfortable
It's amazing Comfortable
I am very comfortable
Are you comfortable
very comfortable
comfortable
This is very comfortable to lick
don't do this comfortable
Are you comfortable?
don't i cum Comfortable
- lick here - yes
No way not yet
go on
very comfortable
look
don't do this
very comfortable
The pussy is very wet
keep making me happy
don't do this comfortable
don't i cum
yes lots of water
very comfortable
It's very wet inside
Insert to the bottom keep plugging me
How about
It's very comfortable for me to plug in like this
Very hard cock
don't Comfortable
plug me like this very comfortable
Sorry
yes No
My pussy is very wet
keep plugging me in
very good
you put it all in the pussy
It's all in the hole
did you see
very comfortable don't want
yes very comfortable
don't do this comfortable
Sorry
don't do this
I went
Sorry
don't do this
Let me wipe it
Are you comfortable ?
don't the floor is dirty
don't i cum
I orgasm
don't do this
keep plugging me in
sorry very comfortable
don't stop
very comfortable
I 'm not enough , continue to insert you
don't do this
don't
don't comfortable
keep plugging me in
comfortable
can shoot
It's amazing Comfortable
It's amazing
Put it all in the pussy
very comfortable
It's amazing
Don't insert like this
It 's amazing
It's amazing
The cock is going to get bigger
keep plugging me in
It's amazing don't want
I like this very much
don't i cum
plug me like this very comfortable
very comfortable
don't i cum
comfortable
No way etc.
don't go
don't i cum
don't plug me in
No way
don't do this
Yes
can i cum in
I orgasm
sorry
Do not insert into the innermost comfortable
Wait
I'm having an orgasm
sorry dirty
I 'll keep plugging you in
I can't help it
Cum it all in
I'm wet down there
-cum - ok _
I cum inside
please
don't
Don't move away
It's amazing
No way
I 'll lick you clean
Otherwise it will be troublesome
I cum inside
give me a lick
stop licking
Shot a lot
I 'll come all
Let me lick it clean for you
No way There's still sperm left.
sorry the floor is dirty
I'm about to cum
comfortable
Next please clean up
It's amazing Shoot
The floor is dirty
I will clean the floor
please
thank you
Leave it to me
- please - lick you clean
Can I kiss
I orgasm
the master
Garbage is ready
can you
sorry
come make love
do you want to
don't
me too
It's over now
you sit here
Can I use this
use this
use this dildo
ok please
Then such words
Put it in the pussy and see
It's amazing
you said yes
Let's do porn
did you orgasm
It's amazing this
There is a lot of water in it
please
You contain
ok
have you used this
I can't do it anymore
I orgasm
It's very wet
It's amazing
It's the first time
very comfortable
a lot of water below
very good
It's amazing
Is it that comfortable?
is so far not
Yes
very comfortable
Are you okay?
It's amazing Comfortable
It can be inserted into the pussy ...
Your cock is very comfortable
you lick me
I like it very much
Are you comfortable?
you come over here and insert a pussy
if possible cock stick in pussy
very comfortable
Yes
I really want it
ok
I'm about to cum
comfortable
Continue to insert you
It's amazing
Yes
touch my tits
very comfortable
Are you comfortable?
Inside彳...... ah
I orgasm
comfortable
Do you like me touching your tits?
Yes
It's amazing Comfortable
very good
It's amazing very wet
Bo
رال
I penetrated the pussy
very comfortable
It 's amazing
Insert to the bottom
I thank you for entering
don't
I orgasm
Come and insert a pussy from behind
I cum inside
ok
Lick it clean for you
hurry up
I cum
now ?
then
want to
cum inside me
It's amazing inserted in the bottom
very comfortable
I cum
Come again next time if you want
let's get started
do you want to cum
I cum
Is it over ?
Can it be inserted into a small hole?
I cum
thank you
Are you satisfied?
Do you want to continue?
Cum it all in
all shot i am satisfied
very comfortable
then i move
Is it over ?
very comfortable
Wait
then i move
It's amazing
cum
Shot a lot
Tired ?
plug me like this i cum
Uncle
Can it be inserted into a small hole?
cum in
don't do this
Do you want to continue?
I cum
you rest
Lick it clean for you
you are up
ask first go
good morning
thank you
- lick clean - ok
Uncle
Thank you for cooperating with me
got it out for you
I am very happy
Call me next time
very clean
don't do this
so sorry
if you call me
waiting
Call me and I will come
ok
About tidying up the room
-thanks - thanks _
me too