It's been a long time since I've been to the beach, so I'm going to take a break.
I'm bored.
What?
There's a sofa.
I haven't been there in a long time.
All right.
I haven't been here in a long time.
I'm going to take a break.
It looks interesting.
There's this, too.
What's this?
I got a boyfriend at this library.
Matching in five seconds.
What's this?
What do you mean, five seconds?
What?
I'm sorry.
You mean, over here?
What?
Thank you for making eye contact with me.
Oh, yes.
Is this your first time here?
It's my first time here.
I see.
I thought it was a lie at first.
I thought it was a matching library.
What?
Matching library?
There really is.
I was surprised, too.
It's my third time here.
I see.
It's better to see your face in person than in a matching library, isn't it?
I'm lucky.
Then, would you like to exchange contact information?
Would you like to exchange contact information?
What are you talking about?
This is a library where people who have a crush on each other gather.
I can't stand it anymore.
I see.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm not okay.
It's okay.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
I'm not okay.
Some people don't know this, so they do this.
Let's be quiet.
Okay.
It's okay.
Breathe deeply.
I don't know what to do.
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah alto
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
ah
Animal
uh
ban
but
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
What's going on?
I'm going to put it in your ears
are you ready?
please put it in
I'm going to put it in your ears
I'm going to take it off.
Can I take your hat off?
I want to take it off.
Can I take it off?
It's
⑧ Protection
You did a good job!
It would be nice if you could bear with it, wouldn't it?
Oh, this is the matching library
I wonder if I can do that every time
I looked it up on the net and it was quite a rumor
Could this be
I wonder if I can do that every time
It felt so good
Was it good?
It was the best
Yes
Thank you
I opened it for a while because I would be suspicious if I came every day
I shouldn't be impatient
Student?
I don't think students know about this library
But students are good
No way
Really
I don't think students know about this library
Do you know about this place?
Yes
Is this your first time here?
I've been here a lot
Yes
Do you want me to teach you a lot?
Are you okay?
Yes
Let's read this
I'll teach you
Yes
Do you like it?
Be careful
I'm sorry
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
rar
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
ooh
I don't know why I'm laughing
I'm sorry
I've been studying a lot
So
While I was studying, I looked up the library here, and that's how I came here today.
So when I matched it, I was very nervous.
How should I put it? It's difficult.
Can I try it too?
It's good.
I'm sorry. It's stuck.
It's getting bigger.
Can I look at it?
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
It's warm.
It's good.
The scent of the wind.
It's amazing.
It's warm.
Should I put it here?
Here?
It smells amazing.
It's good.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
There's a lot.
It feels good, right?
It's good.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
What is it?
It's good.
It's amazing.
I'm nervous.
It's good.
It's amazing.
There's a lot.
It's good.
It's amazing.
Oh no...
You're still feeling dizzy
Hang in there
Please hang in there
Not a single crack
Hang in there
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Are you okay?
I want to do it more.
I'll show you.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
It's over here.
It's okay.
I'm going to put it in my mouth.
Wow, that's amazing.
You're a gentleman.
Did it feel good?
It felt good.
Thank you.
Me too.
Thanks to you, I can study hard.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
It's not the same as before.
I want to be alone for a day or two.
No, no, no.
Excuse me.
Please take this.
Please return it in a week.
Yes.
Thank you.
I'll return it.
Yes.
Please return it in a week.
Everyone is leaving.
Thank you.
Is it over today?
Please return it in a week.
Thank you.
Should I go home today?
No one is here anymore.
I have to go home soon.
I feel awkward.
I haven't been found out yet, have I?
What?
Are you kidding me?
It's not the same as before.
The staff is different.
I have to go home soon.
Thank you.
What is it?
You often come to my house, don't you?
No, I don't think so.
Sometimes.
Did you do something with the student you saw earlier?
The student?
No, I didn't.
What is it?
I'm going home.
Thank you.
What is it?
You look like me.
What?
I saw you five seconds ago.
I see.
What?
People who come here these days...
They're all doing something sexy.
I envy them.
Did you see it?
I've seen a lot of things.
But you're a staff member, aren't you?
But you saw me five seconds ago.
We look good together, don't we?
That's right.
What is it?
Someone might come.
It's okay.
I'm the only one here.
Did everyone go home?
Yes.
I see.
What do you think?
I don't like it.
I thought it was unfair that everyone was matching at this library.
I see.
So...
I want you to touch me.
Yes.
Here, too.
Wow.
Your nipples are so plump.
Here, too.
Wow.
You were so excited.
Here, too.
I've always wanted to drink your nipples at this library.
I see.
Here, too.
Wow.
There are so many of them.
What's wrong?
I'm going to clean your nipples.
Here, too.
Wow.
Your nipples are getting bigger.
I'm going to clean your nipples.
Here, too.
Wow.
Your nipples are getting bigger.
Here, too.
Wow.
Your nipples are getting bigger.
Here, too.
Wow.
Let me go.
I'm sorry.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Uh! Ah!
Ah!
Eh?
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Uh! Uh!
Eh!
Ah!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Ah, oh, oh, oh, ah, ah, ah.
humanity
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Um, hi.
How do you feel?
I felt good.
You have been well done.
It felt good.
Yes.
Please don't write anything else down.
I understand.
By the way, did you find out about our library on the internet?
No, I was in the neighborhood, so I happened to come by.
There was a memo in the book I picked up.
Did you write in the memo that you had a boyfriend?
Yes, I did.
That's me.
Is that so?
At first, we exchanged contact information and went on a date.
But it escalated like this, and now it's an erotic library.
I see.
At first, I didn't mean to do this at all.
It seems like you're looking at my embarrassing past.
I'm so embarrassed that you know everything.
I'm still shaking.
Can we do it again?
We've already done it a lot, haven't we?
But it felt really good, and I think we're a great match.
We've been seeing each other for more than five seconds, and we've matched again.
Thank you for watching!