I'm home!
Oh, Shun-kun! You're home!
Look!
This is the place for our next family trip.
Isn't it amazing?
It's 38,000 yen per person.
I wonder if Papa will be okay.
What if he dies?
Maybe I should give him some money.
What do you think?
Are they all in the same room?
Oh, they're in the same room.
I'm embarrassed.
Let's go in together.
I heard that Papa and Mama will be home late today.
I'm going to make dinner.
Is there anything you want to eat?
I don't need anything.
What's wrong?
Do you have any worries?
If you have any worries, talk to me.
It's been a year since we became a family.
You can tell me anything.
It's not like that.
It's okay.
What do you want to eat?
I can make anything.
Do you want to eat gyoza?
Let's go eat.
Are you a virgin?
That's right.
I'm a virgin.
I don't think it's a hurry.
I'm the only one in the class.
But you're cool.
It's okay.
I'm the only one in the class.
I'm the only virgin.
That's right.
I don't think I can do it forever.
I don't think so.
I can have a girlfriend someday.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Please allow me to graduate with a virgin.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, Shen.
Shen, what are you saying?
Let's go eat.
You're my brother.
Please.
But I have to die with someone I love.
No.
I want you.
Please.
Let's go eat.
No.
I told you to consult with me.
That's why I told you.
But I can't.
Please.
I'm not kidding.
No.
Let's go eat.
Please.
Let's talk about what we talked about.
We're siblings, so it's obvious we shouldn't.
Don't talk about it anymore.
Yeah.
It's okay.
I see.
Be careful on your way home.
Okay.
Bye.
Please.
That's enough.
You're the only one I can ask.
That's right. Please.
I said no.
I can't ask you to do it.
Okay.
Just pretend.
Pretend?
No.
Please.
Just pretend.
Okay?
Well...
Then...
A kiss.
A kiss?
Just pretend.
Just pretend. Of course.
Look at me.
I won't do it.
Can I touch your chest?
Just pretend.
I can't touch you.
Okay.
I'll do it on your clothes.
What?
Can I touch you a little?
Just pretend.
I won't touch you directly.
I'll do it on your clothes.
Okay.
I'll do it.
Like this?
Yes.
Is it okay?
It's heavy.
Okay.
What?
Can I touch your chest?
I won't touch you directly.
I won't touch you.
But...
Just a little.
From the top.
Okay.
Hurry up.
I'll do it.
Okay.
Just a little.
I'll do it.
Chest.
I'll do it on your skirt.
I'll do it on your stocking.
From the top.
Please.
I'll do it.
What?
Please.
I'll do it.
Like this?
Okay.
Sweat.
It's very hot.
Does it feel good?
Here.
I'll do it.
Are you okay?
From the top.
I'll do it.
Panties.
You're wearing panties.
What are you talking about?
Two panties.
I can see it.
You can't know if you don't see it.
I don't know.
You're wearing stockings.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it.
Does it hurt?
From the top.
I'll do it.
What's going on?
It hurts.
You can still do it.
It feels good.
It hurts.
You can still do it.
I'll do it for you.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It hurts.
It feels good.
You can do it.
It's hard.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's okay.
You can do it.
It hurts.
Hank!
Help me!
Are you there?
OAOAOAOAOAOAOAOAOA
It hurts!
Oh, my God!
I'm not in your hands anymore.
Oh, yeah.
It hurts again, doesn't it?
What?
Good morning.
Dad.
Have a seat.
I'm home.
Jun, are you home?
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Mom and Dad's wedding anniversary is next month, isn't it?
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
Hey, Dad.
Have you forgotten?
Hey.
Hey, hey.
What are you going to do?
What?
Should I give you a present like a trip?
A present?
What?
What will Mom be happy about?
Hey, hey.
Hey.
Are you listening?
Hey, by the way.
Mom and Dad will be home late today.
Hey, is there anything you want to eat?
Hey, hey.
Do you want to make anything?
What do you want to eat?
Fried chicken?
Do you want curry?
Or what else?
Do you want to go out and eat?
Like ramen.
Gyoza or Chinese food.
I don't need it.
You don't need it?
Hey.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Are you sleepy?
Yes.
I'll make anything for you.
We've been a family for a year.
Hey, tell me something.
I'll make anything for you.
What's wrong?
Hey.
Tell me something.
What's wrong?
I'll make anything for you.
Hey.
Anything.
Anything?
I'll make anything for you.
Tell me something.
Hey.
What's wrong?
I'm talking to you.
Yes.
What's wrong?
I'm a virgin.
What?
Jun?
So?
What's wrong?
I'm the only virgin in the class.
What?
Don't worry.
Yes.
I'm a virgin.
I'm the only one.
Don't worry.
I have a girlfriend.
I'm a virgin.
Let me graduate from the virginity.
Stop it.
You said you'd do anything for me.
I did.
But I said no.
I said no.
Please.
You should date someone you like.
I'm a virgin.
Please.
You said no.
I'm a virgin.
What?
Spend relaxing time eating and enjoying good breakfast
When you're so beat, think about what you've done today
This is the first time I've eaten it, so it's surprisingly soft.
The high quality of the pork itself seems to have been added, but there is no problem with the flavor of fish.
I think the butter has been added
It is the aspect that cracks is work
Dismantle the sink
It's hot.
Okay.
I'll see you at 3 o'clock.
Thank you.
So...
I said no, didn't I?
Please.
I can only ask you to do this.
So...
As I said before,
I'll do what I like.
Then...
Just pretend.
Pretend?
I won't touch you.
I mean...
I want you to teach me that.
I won't touch you.
Just pretend.
Please.
I won't touch you.
Just pretend.
It's hot.
Then...
I'll kiss you.
Just pretend.
I won't touch you.
I'll kiss you.
I'll kiss you like this.
Just like that.
Ouch
Just like this
Can you move the face?
Don't move you're face
I mean, I can feel it from the top of my clothes.
I mean, I don't feel anything at all.
I won't move it.
From the top of your clothes?
Yeah, from the top of my clothes. I won't move it.
I mean, I can feel it.
I won't move it.
Don't move it.
I mean, I can feel it from the top of your clothes.
I mean, I can feel it.
From the top of your clothes.
From the top of my clothes.
I won't move it.
From the top of your clothes.
What?
No, it's just...
It's just...
It's just on top of my clothes.
I'm wearing stockings.
Um...
It's definitely...
It's definitely on top of my clothes.
Just a little...
The flow...
Just the movement.
It's definitely on top of my clothes.
Please teach me.
It's on top of my clothes.
Definitely on the dress
I wonder if it's okay for you to be like this.
I don't know.
I'm going to sleep.
Can I lick your clothes?
I'm going to take off my pants.
I'm going to take off this sock.
I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough and put a piece of dough in it to make a hole in the center of the dough.
I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough, and I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough, and I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough, and I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough, and I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough, and I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough, and I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough, and I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough, and I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough, and I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough, and I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough, and I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough, and I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough, and I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough, and I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough
there is a hole in the center of the dough
you don't have to look
Yes, I'm sure
I want you to go
If you just rub here, it's okay, right?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Is there a voice here?
I feel good.
I'm getting sleepy.
Do you want to practice more?
I'm sorry.
Hold on.
Ah,
I can breathe now.
I can't get enough of this eating sound
I can't stop laughing
So hot
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it
is over.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's okay.
So go to sleep.
No, wait!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
hey
Ah ah ah
,
What's wrong?
It's okay.
Here.
More.
It's okay.
It's all right, it's all right.
Let me go!
I'm so tired.
I want to play with you tomorrow.
No.
What?
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
What?
I don't want to get caught.
Good morning.
Jun.
I got cream puffs from the store manager.
Do you want to eat it?
What's wrong?
Oh, by the way.
My mom said she'd be late today.
My sister is making dinner.
Is there anything you want to eat?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Do you have a problem?
It's been a year since we became a family.
Talk to your sister about anything.
What?
Can I ask you a question?
I want to graduate from Dotei.
I'm the only one from Dotei.
It's about that age.
I want to graduate from Dotei with my sister.
Please.
Of course I can't.
I told you to talk to your sister.
I know, but...
You can have someone you like.
You can have a girlfriend.
You can take the next step.
Please.
I want my sister.
Of course I can't.
Please.
Have you eaten?
Yeah.
Thank you for the food.
Episode 10
Onee-chan, please...
I can only ask you for help.
Just queit up!
But I can't...
No, you can't.
Please.
Just pretend.
Just pretend, please.
I'm really going to do it.
Really?
Just pretend.
I'm just going to pretend.
Look at me.
But...
Can I touch you?
I don't want to touch you.
Isn't it too close?
I'm just going to pretend.
I told you I was going to pretend.
You should pretend to kiss me, too.
Look at me.
How do I look?
Give me a kiss.
No, you can't.
You have to pretend to kiss me.
You can't.
Do whatever you want.
Please.
Just pretend to kiss me.
No, I can't.
Then can I kiss you?
Just pretend to kiss me.
Do whatever you want.
It's too close.
Like this?
I'm just going to pretend.
What should I do?
Did you touch me?
I know you didn't touch me.
I'm just going to pretend.
I don't know.
What?
Please.
Just a little.
Okay.
Please.
Here.
What?
It doesn't feel good.
That's right.
It's okay.
It's from the top.
It's close.
You touched me.
Here.
It's okay.
I told you it's from the top.
Let me touch you.
It's just from the top.
It's okay.
I'm busy.
Just a little.
What?
I have this.
Which one?
What do you mean?
It's a stocking.
It's from the top.
Which one?
I told you it's okay.
Let me touch you.
It's okay.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, right?
I can't stand being licked.
It hurts.
It's just a stocking.
It hurts so much.
I can't stand being licked.
I can't.
It hurts so bad.
I'm going to put my stockings on.
I wonder if Moa would play fetch...
I'm making a couble-play
If you give him a treat, he'll probably come back
Likely to be poorly received
It's nice, isn't it?
Wait a minute.
It's like this.
Wow.
It's like I'm touching a stocking.
Does it feel good?
It doesn't feel good.
What is this?
Wow.
Why is this wet?
I don't know.
Wow.
I don't feel good.
Run away.
Wow.
Does it feel good?
It doesn't feel good.
Wow.
I have to put on stockings.
Does it feel good?
It's like...
It's like I'm having sex.
It feels good.
How do you feel, Fure-chan?
Is this part okay?
No?
No.
But it feels good.
Here.
Is this okay?
It feels good.
It's hot.
It doesn't seem to fit.
Will it fit if I press it like this?
No?
It won't fit if I press it like this.
It feels good just by rubbing it.
It feels good.
What are you doing?
It's hot.
What?
What's wrong?
It's a secret.
A secret?
Are you sure?
Here?
It's hot.
It feels good.
It feels really good.
Can I do it again?
It's hot.
You can't just do it.
Touch this side, too.
This side, too?
It's hot.
It feels better than before.
I want to sleep.
My stomach is moving.
It feels good.
I want to sleep.
My stomach is moving.
It feels good.
I want to sleep.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm going to sleep.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I fell asleep.
I'm sorry.
I fell asleep because I was sick.
I'm sorry I kept looking at you.
I'm sorry.
You can still do it, right?
What? Still?
You can't do it more than once.
I can't do it more than once?
What?
I'm sorry.
Ouch!
Ouch!...
It's okay.
It feels good.
Touch it properly.
Like this.
It feels good.
Does it?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You can still do it.
What?
You can still do it, right?
Put it in from behind.
Can you do it?
I can do it.
I'll try it.
Wait a minute.
It feels good.
I can do it.
What should I do?
It's okay.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
What am I going to do tomorrow?
Yes.
I'm back.
Keita, I'm back.
Keita-kun, I'm home.
Huh?
Hey, listen.
The people at work said they were getting married today.
Apparently, their honeymoon is in Bali.
Where do you think Bali is?
They say it's in Indonesia.
Hey, Keita-kun.
Are you feeling unwell?
Do you have any worries?
I'm fine.
You're fine?
It looks like Mom will be home late today, so I'll make dinner.
Hey, what do you want to eat?
What do you want to eat?
Hey, are you listening?
Hey, if you have any worries, talk to me.
It's been about a year since we became brothers.
We can talk about anything, right?
Hey, if you have any worries, talk to me.
Is there anything you want to eat?
Curry, stew, or udon?
What do you mean?
Huh?
Say it again.
What do you mean?
I see.
I'm the only one in the class.
You don't have to worry about that.
I see.
I'm the only one in the class.
It's not that embarrassing.
You're still young.
It's embarrassing.
It's not embarrassing.
You worry too much.
I'll make you something to cheer you up.
You don't have to worry about that.
Please.
I don't want you to throw it away.
Keita, what are you doing?
Please raise your head.
Please.
I'm the only one in the class.
You can't do that.
Please.
Please raise your head.
I can't do that.
Please get up.
Please.
I can't go to school because I'm embarrassed.
Don't do that.
Please raise your head.
Please.
I told you to talk to me.
You're not my sister.
I'm the only one in the class.
You can't do that.
Stop it.
Keita.
Let's eat.
Please.
Keita.
You can't do that.
I can do that.
You said it.
I'm the only one in the class.
You should do what you like.
I'll do it.
I'll pretend to be a girl.
Pretend?
Just pretend.
What do you mean?
I won't touch you.
Just pretend.
Pretend?
Please.
Just pretend to have sex.
Just pretend.
Just pretend?
Can I?
Just pretend.
Thank you.
I won't touch you.
Can I?
Just pretend.
Thank you.
Look at me.
Look at me?
No.
Don't touch my lips.
Okay.
Don't you do this?
You should do it, too.
Just pretend.
More.
More?
Just pretend.
Isn't it close?
I won't touch you.
Can I?
Can I do it on your clothes?
No.
On your clothes.
Not directly.
No.
Just put my hand on your clothes.
I won't move.
Can I?
Just put my hand on your clothes.
No.
On your chest.
Can I do it again?
Again?
That's enough.
How about this?
It's embarrassing.
It's okay.
I'll do it on your clothes, too.
I won't move.
It's embarrassing.
Why?
You're wearing panties.
I'm wearing panties.
Can I?
Yes.
What should I do?
It's warm.
Can I do it on your clothes?
Can I?
What?
Just a little.
My hands are moving.
I won't move.
What?
Just a little.
It's embarrassing.
Hey.
You can't do it in your clothes.
I can't.
Then...
You can lick it from above.
You can.
You...
You can do it in your clothes.
You can lick it. It's on top of your clothes.
It's hot.
I can't stand it anymore.
What are you doing?
You can lick it on top of your clothes.
I've already done it.
It's hot.
Here.
You can lick it on top of your clothes.
It's okay, right?
Yes.
It's hot.
It's okay, right?
Yes.
I feel like I'm going to puke.
What is it?
Take off your pants.
What are you talking about?
What?
I want you to take off your pants.
What about my stockings?
What?
Put them back on.
You can lick it on top of your clothes.
These are clothes.
Take off your pants and put them back on.
What are you talking about?
These are clothes.
You can lick them on top of your clothes.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Look behind you.
It's embarrassing to take them off.
Okay.
Hurry up.
Can you do it?
I'm wearing stockings.
Okay.
You can put them back on.
Can you do it?
I'm almost done.
Okay.
Are you done?
I'm almost done.
I'm done.
Can I take them off?
Okay.
Why are you hiding them?
It's embarrassing.
You can put them back on.
It's okay, right?
It's transparent.
Wait a minute.
It's embarrassing.
What?
You can put them back on, right?
Wait a minute.
What?
It's amazing.
Look at this.
What?
It's amazing.
It's wet.
It's not true.
Your clothes are wet.
What?
It's wet.
No.
Your clothes are wet.
What?
Are you excited?
It's amazing.
Look at this.
It's wet.
It's amazing.
Look at this.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
What?
What's going on?
Wait a minute.
Get in there.
It's in there.
It's amazing.
It's okay because it's free.
Free?
Free.
It's free.
It feels good.
Wait a minute.
It's going to come out.
It feels good.
You don't have to cry.
It's going to come out.
I'm sorry.
I told you it was free.
But...
Wait a minute.
It's free.
Let me see your hand.
Yes.
I'll pretend to touch your boob.
How do you feel?
I'll pretend to be nice to you.
Is it free?
Yes, it's free.
It's free, but it feels good.
Really?
Hmm...
Slurping
Ah
Hmm...
Slurping
Ah
Hmm...
Slurping
Ah
Hmm
Slurping
Ah
Hmm
Yeah.
Hey.
Do you want me to play with your boobs?
What?
Well...
How do you feel?
But...
It's okay.
This is also a brush.
How do you feel?
My boobs feel good.
Feel good?
I feel good.
You feel good?
Yeah.
Come here.
Let's do it again.
What?
Ouch.
Hey.
What?
This time...
I'll do it for you.
What?
What do you mean?
Wait a minute.
But...
Wait.
I'll do it.
What?
Ouch.
Hey.
My boobs are...
are...
Are...
in?
No.
I said...
they are in.
Ouch.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, sis.
Go, go, go.
Wait.
Oh, no.
Wait, sis.
It's coming out.
Let me go.
Go.
Go, go, go.
Oh, no.
It's coming out again.
No, sis.
It's bigger than before.
Wait.
It's just coming out.
Oh, no.
It's coming out again.
It feels good.
Touch me.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
Go.
Oh, no.
From behind.
From behind?
Come here.
From behind.
Yes.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
Touch me more.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
Touch me.
Oh, no.
Go.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Do you want me to hug you?
Not yet.
You can do it.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
I like here.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Do you want me to hug you?
It feels good.
You have a lot of hair.
You can do it.
Do it again.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
I told you it was a bad idea.
You did it.
When will you do it again?
Thank you for watching.