Hey, Yasu-kun.
Yes?
What do you want to eat today?
What do I want to eat?
Yes.
I'm not sure what to eat.
Well...
Mapo tofu.
Mapo tofu?
Yes.
You'll get full.
No way.
You should eat more.
What do you want to eat?
Karaage.
Karaage and...
Mapo tofu.
Is it bad?
It's not bad, but...
How about fried chicken?
Chinese style.
That's good.
Right?
Can you make it?
I can.
Really?
According to the recipe.
You're late today.
Oh, I see.
I thought you were late.
I had a long meeting today.
I see.
So, I thought I'd make something you want to eat.
Really?
Yes.
Then...
Wakame tempura.
Wakame tempura?
What?
I can't make it, but...
Is that okay?
It's good.
Really?
I've never made it.
Please make it.
Do you know how to make it?
Just deep-fry wakame.
How about seasoning?
Season with mayonnaise and shichimi.
Then, eat it.
You're a little strange.
You can season it with salt.
I see.
Then, wakame.
Wakame.
I didn't know that.
I'll make miso soup with wakame.
Really?
I hope you eat a lot.
Eat a lot?
Yes.
I hope you eat a lot and grow up a lot.
I'm already growing up.
You're still growing.
Still?
I hope you grow up more and more.
I don't grow up that much.
You'll grow up. You're a boy.
A boy?
Yes, a boy.
What did you think?
What?
Nothing.
I'd be happy if you made a lot.
Really?
Yes.
I'd be happy if you said that.
Rice is delicious.
Are you happy?
Yes.
I'm glad.
You're good at cooking.
Really?
Then, I'll make more.
I'm glad that you said that.
At first, you didn't care about rice.
That's right.
I was embarrassed.
Were you?
At first, I was...
I was the one who disturbed you.
I think I was like that at that time.
I'm not like that now.
Really?
No.
I'm glad.
Let's get along with each other.
Get along?
Yes.
I'd like to go on a trip with you three.
A trip?
Yes.
Three of us?
That's good.
If you're too busy to go on a trip, let's go together.
Two of us?
Yes.
How about a hot spring?
Two of us?
A hot spring?
Yes.
That's not good.
Not good?
I'm sorry. I'm kidding.
I'm kidding.
I'm sorry.
Let's go together.
Well...
One day...
Yes.
One day?
Won't you go with me?
I'll go.
Really?
Yes.
It's a promise.
I did it.
Where should we go?
Oh, no.
The supermarket is about to start.
Let's go.
Wakame seaweed.
Yes.
That's all.
Change your clothes.
Take care.
Yes.
I'm home.
What's up?
I'm cold.
What's wrong with you?
I was about to fall down on the way home.
I was worried about you.
I'm wet.
I'll bring you a towel.
Thank you.
I'm home.
You're wet.
It was amazing.
It was like a waterfall.
I'm cold.
I have to wash my face.
I have to put on my socks.
I wonder if the food is wet.
It's wet.
What should I do?
Yasu-kun?
I have to wipe my face.
I'm sorry.
I'll wipe my hair.
It's wet.
Yes.
My feet are wet.
Can you wipe my feet?
I see.
My feet are wet.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm cold.
Your clothes are wet.
I'm wet inside.
Inside?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm cold.
Do you want me to hold you?
Yes.
Hey.
I want you to wipe my feet.
How is it?
Is it wet?
Yes.
Can you wipe my feet?
I'm cold.
I'm sorry.
It's wet.
How is it?
Is it wet?
Yes.
I have to wipe my feet.
Can you wipe my feet?
I'll wipe my feet.
I'm sorry.
I'll put your luggage here.
Thank you.
Can I hold you?
Yes.
How wet is it?
Is it wet?
It's wet.
Yasuko, how wet is it?
Is it wet?
Yes.
How wet is it?
It's wet.
How is it?
I'm wiping my feet now.
I'll wipe my feet a little more.
A little more?
It's still wet.
Can you wipe my feet?
Yes.
How is it?
It's still wet.
Yes.
How is it?
It's very soft.
It's still wet.
Really?
Yasuko, there is a wet part.
How is it?
Here.
It's wet and cold.
Can you wipe it?
Yes.
I'll wipe it.
How is it?
Is it wet?
Yes.
If you don't wipe it well, you may catch a cold.
Is it wet?
Yes.
It's very cold, isn't it?
It's cold.
Can you warm it with your hands?
It's cold, isn't it?
It's warm.
Your hands are warm.
It's cold.
I think I should take a bath.
I think it's cold.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I'll prepare a shower.
I'll warm it up.
It's cold.
I'll prepare a shower.
I'll warm it up.
I'll prepare a towel.
Can you wear it?
I'll catch a cold.
Do you have a towel?
Yes, I do.
What should I do?
It's not wet yet.
I'll catch a cold.
It's cold.
If you catch a cold, you can't eat Mapo Tofu.
Mapo Tofu with seaweed.
Mapo Tofu is important to me.
Are you sure?
I'll bring a towel.
You're cute.
I'll tease you a little more.
I'm ready.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Can you wipe my back?
I can't reach it.
My shoulders are still wet.
I'll do it.
I'll do your hair.
My hair?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Is the food okay?
Yes, it's good.
I was worried if the seaweed was back.
I see.
I didn't know it was raining.
Yosuke.
Yes?
I think this part is still wet.
It's still wet.
Can you wipe it for me?
My clothes?
It's cold.
Can you wipe it for me?
No, I can't.
It's cold.
Isn't there a lot of water?
Yes, there is.
Is there a lot of water?
Isn't there a lot of water?
I think it's wet.
What should I do?
I'll wipe it for you.
Won't you wipe it for me?
Can you wipe my feet?
It's wet.
Wipe my feet.
If you don't wipe my feet, I'll get a cold.
I'll wipe your thighs.
It's wet, isn't it?
Which one is wet?
That's right.
Wipe my feet more.
That's right, Yosuke.
Thank you, Yosuke.
I feel like the inside of my feet is wet.
Is it inside?
I feel like it's wet.
How is it?
Is it wet?
It's a little wet.
I can't.
Thank you.
I think it's getting loose.
What should I do?
I'll fix it.
Are you going to fix it?
Do it.
The towel is going to fall.
It's going to fall.
Yosuke.
I can't do this.
I made you wet so much.
I can't stand it anymore.
It was fun to tease you.
I can't help it.
I made you wet so much.
Are you so excited to see me wet?
You can't help it, Yosuke.
All right.
It's out.
I'll warm it up with my mouth.
Can you warm it up?
It's getting cold.
Is it warm?
It's warmer than a bath.
It's hot.
It's getting cold.
It's delicious.
I'll warm it up with my mouth.
Will you warm it up?
I'm glad.
It's warm.
It's warm in Yosuke's mouth.
It's warm here, too.
It's warm.
It's warm in your mouth.
I'll warm it up with my mouth.
It's cold here, too.
That's right.
It's the coldest place.
Is it getting warmer?
It's getting warmer.
Can you make it warmer?
It's warm in Yosuke's hands.
It's getting warmer when I put my fingers in it.
It's warm.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'll do it.
Ahh..
Gosh..
It got wet again
Wait a minute
The end of her butt got wet too
Wait
Your face turns red.
I'm recording.
olive oil
I'm crying again.
oh
Yes
Yeah
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
!
a
tch
Let me lick the warm part of your face.
It's warm.
Oh, no.
It's really warm.
Let me see.
Oh, no.
You're strong.
It's warm.
It's really warm.
It's really warm here.
It's warm.
Do you want me to warm you up?
It's really warm.
It's warm.
Your forehead is getting warm.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I want you to look at me.
It feels good.
Do you want me to warm you up?
Do you want me to stand there?
I'll warm you up.
No.
It's warm.
It's warm here.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
What?
Did you want to see my face?
It's warm.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
My stomach is getting warm.
It's warm.
My body is getting warm.
Why?
It smells good.
I'm getting tired.
Oh, no.
What?
I finally saw you.
Oh, no.
It's warm.
You were warm.
Ah!
My body is so warm...
Ah...
Ah!
Hey!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
ha ha
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
yeah tenho
hade
Ah!
Can you see anything?
There's a lot inside
It's really hot, isn't it?
Ah!
It's really hot
My body is always warm
Ah!
So cool!
Let's play in dad's arms
We are surely going to lie down
But...
Why don't we do it in the room?
How is it?
I want to do it more.
Can't you stand it?
I can.
That's right.
Come here.
It feels good.
I want...
It feels good!
Eh, Eh, Eh, Eh, Eh, Eh, Eh, Eh!
Ai!
Ah...
Ah?!
Kuhh!!
Ah...
Ahh, uhhh...
Come on, let me move too...
No...
What am I doing!
Ah...
I'm sorry.
Eh?
It's hot.
Is it hot?
It's so hot.
It's hot.
It's hot for me, too.
I'm getting cold.
It's so hot.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
Stop it?
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
It hurts.
Can you see it?
It's amazing.
It hurts.
Please let me go.
Give me a warm life.
It hurts.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
Do you want to do this again next week?
What?
Tomo is late next week.
Is my brother late?
He's late for a meeting.
What?
You're getting stronger.
Do you want to go in with me?
Let's go.
Tomo.
Atsushi is late.
I want to have dinner with you.
Do you want to eat something?
Anything is fine.
Really?
Yesterday,
I ate fish.
How about hamburger steak?
Okay.
Really?
Yes.
Well...
Do you want to eat anything else?
That's enough to make you hungry.
How about soup?
Okay.
Is that enough?
Yes.
Why are you so nervous?
I'm not nervous.
We've been like this for a long time.
We're family.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Do you need water?
No, I'm not thirsty.
Your face looks hot.
No, I'm fine.
Did you feel pain?
How about hamburger steak and soup?
Okay.
Really?
By the way,
I heard something from you.
What is it?
You don't talk to girls at school, do you?
Well...
You're so cute.
You should talk to girls.
Do you have a favorite type of girl?
A type of girl?
Yes.
Do you have a favorite type of girl?
Do you like a girl who is good at studying?
Do you like a kind girl?
Well...
I like a girl who is older than me.
I like an adult girl.
I see.
I'm surprised.
Do you think so?
Do you like a girl who is the same age as you?
No.
I feel calm.
I see.
How about me?
What?
I'm kidding.
I'm too old for you.
No.
I don't think so.
You're beautiful.
Thank you.
I don't think so.
I see.
Thank you.
Do you enjoy your school life?
Yes, I do.
It's fun.
But...
There are female teachers, right?
Yes.
What kind of teachers are there?
Ryoko is more beautiful than female teachers.
She is beautiful.
Really?
Yes, she is.
You're good at flattery.
No, I'm not.
It's been a long time since you said that to me.
You don't say that to me.
I see.
It's time to go.
See you later.
Okay.
I was nervous.
But...
I'm glad that I could talk with you.
See you later.
It's raining heavily.
Ryoko didn't bring an umbrella.
Is she okay?
I'm back.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
My clothes got wet.
I'll bring you a towel.
I'm sorry.
I was surprised.
I should have brought an umbrella.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
It's raining heavily.
I know.
I didn't expect it to rain suddenly.
I didn't read the weather forecast.
What should I do?
I'm crying.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
You're soaked.
No.
I'm sorry.
Me, too.
I slept in the rain.
I'm really sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes.
What's wrong?
I thought I shouldn't look at you.
Did you get wet?
No.
You're wet.
I'm really sorry.
Yohei.
Yes?
Can you wipe my sweat?
What?
Can you...
wipe my body?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Wait a minute.
This part is the most wet, isn't it?
No.
Right?
I'm sorry.
What?
Can you wipe my body?
Yes.
I see.
You're good.
I'm sorry.
Can you wipe more?
Yes.
Your hands are warm.
It's warm, isn't it?
Is it?
Yes.
My body is getting cold.
I'm sorry.
I feel sorry for you.
It's warm.
Can you warm me up more?
More?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Yohei.
You're wet.
No.
I...
touched...
your...
chest.
What?
I...
touched...
your...
chest.
You're so cute.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for teasing you.
I'll change my clothes.
Thank you.
Why don't you change your clothes?
You're always with me.
But today, you're alone.
So, I changed my clothes.
No.
Why?
Well...
What's wrong?
You're so cute.
Don't tease me.
To be an adult,
you have to get used to it.
No.
But...
It's not good.
You're married.
I can't hear you.
So...
Come closer.
Are you hungry?
Well...
What's wrong?
You're right.
I can't show you...
this side of me.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Are you married?
No.
It's okay.
I was surprised.
But...
Do you want to touch me?
No.
But...
Look.
Look at me.
You can touch me a lot.
Really?
I teased you.
I really...
want to tease you.
Ah.
Hey.
Continue.
Ah.
Um...
Your...
eyes are so...
soft.
It feels good.
So...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's been a long time.
It's not just your boobs.
Look.
Do you want to touch me?
Ah.
It's okay.
If you want...
to do it,
you can do it.
It's okay.
Ah.
It's so...
You touched me a lot.
I'm so wet.
Can I really touch you?
Touch me.
Ah.
Um...
You're really...
amazing.
You're so wet.
Ah.
You're so...
wet.
Ah.
Um.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Can I...
touch you?
Ah.
You're so good.
Um.
Ah.
Your...
fingers...
feel good.
Really?
Ah.
Um.
Look.
I'm...
touching you.
Um.
Ah.
Where did you learn this?
Um.
Ah.
It's all messed up.
Um.
Ah.
It's all messed up.
Um.
Ah.
It's all messed up.
Um.
I feel good.
Ah.
Wow.
You've grown up.
Yes.
Um.
Why did you
grow up so much?
Um.
Your body is
so beautiful.
Ah.
Wow.
It's your
first time
doing
something like this,
isn't it?
Ah.
Yes.
Is it really okay
to do it for the first time?
Yes.
I'm glad
you like it.
Um.
I'm glad.
Ah.
Um.
Wow.
It's all in your mouth.
You're getting bigger and bigger.
Ah.
Yes.
It feels good.
Um.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
Um.
Ah.
It's amazing.
Isn't it hard to sit there?
What?
Come here.
It's amazing.
You're full.
You're patient.
It's amazing.
You can't stand it.
Yes.
I can't stand it either.
What?
I'll put it in your mouth.
Yes.
It's amazing.
I'll put it in your mouth.
It's big.
I'll give it to you.
It's amazing.
It's big.
I'll move it a lot.
If you move that much...
It's amazing.
What?
Do you want me to pat you?
Yes.
Lie down.
I'll put it in your mouth.
From here.
Can you see it?
Yes.
I saw it earlier.
It's amazing.
It feels better than I thought.
I'll touch you a lot.
It's amazing.
It's in here.
I can feel it.
It feels so good.
It's amazing.
Yoko, don't do that.
It's going to come out.
Don't eat it.
I just...
It's amazing.
There's a lot.
It's still a corpse.
What?
Can you still do it?
Wait.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
It's in the back.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Do it more.
More.
It's amazing.
Wait.
It's big.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
There's a lot.
It's overflowing.
Yoko.
Can you still do it?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
More.
It's amazing.
I love you.
I want more.
It's hot.
Come here.
It's amazing.
It's overflowing.
It feels good.
Yes.
When you're not here, can you do this for me?
Of course.
It's amazing.
It stopped raining.
That's right.
I have to make dinner.
I'm sorry.
Can I help you?
Yes.
Let's make something delicious.
You're here, Tsuyoshi.
Yoko.
Are you off today?
Yes, I'm off from college today.
I was lazy.
Were you lazy?
Your parents aren't here today, are they?
That's right.
So, I came to ask you if you're going to have dinner at home.
I see.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm not sure.
I think I'm going home.
Are you going home?
Yes.
I'll make you something you like.
Can I?
Yes.
What should I make?
Anything is fine.
I'm not sure.
I always cook according to my parents' tastes.
I see.
Fried food?
What should I make?
It's hot, so it's hard to make fried food.
I see.
I'll make something easy.
Are you sure?
Yes.
It's old-fashioned.
I'll make it for you.
What?
I'll make cold Chinese food.
Cold Chinese food sounds good.
I'll make sesame sauce and soy sauce.
I'll make cold Chinese food.
Thank you.
Why are you acting like a stranger?
Are you nervous?
No, I'm not.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'm not used to having a woman at home.
But you've been married for a year.
Why do you say that?
No, I'm not.
I'm not saying you're bad.
I'm just nervous.
Are you nervous?
You're at home every day.
Yes, I am.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little lonely.
What?
I'm lonely.
I've been married for a year.
I'm not used to being at home.
I'm nervous.
You've got a sister.
What?
A sister?
Yes.
That's right.
But I don't feel like a sister.
You don't feel like a sister?
Do you think I'm unreliable?
No, I don't think so.
You're my brother's wife.
You're my sister.
Don't you have a girlfriend at university?
A girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
You don't have a girlfriend.
Don't you have a girlfriend?
I have a girlfriend at university.
I don't have a girlfriend.
But I can't get along with her.
You can't get along with her.
I'm not used to talking to a girl.
What are you looking at?
What?
You're cute.
I'm not looking at you.
I didn't see anything weird.
Sorry, I was teasing you.
I'm going to go shopping.
See you later.
See you.
I'm going to go shopping.
I'm nervous.
It's raining heavily.
Did she say it's going to rain today?
I'm home.
Hi, Yoko.
I'm so tired.
It's raining.
It's terrible.
It's wet.
I'm sorry.
Please wait a moment.
Thank you.
It's wet.
It's terrible.
Thank you.
I'm fine.
It was sunny when I left the supermarket.
It's terrible.
It suddenly started to rain.
It was about to rain.
It started to rain when I woke up.
It was thundering.
Is she okay?
It's terrible.
Look at this.
It's wet.
My shoes are wet.
It's terrible.
You didn't leave the laundry, did you?
I didn't leave the laundry.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
You must be hungry.
No, I'm not.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I'll put this in the drawer.
Can you help me put this on?
I have to tighten my skirt.
I want you to put this on.
But...
It's okay.
Is this okay?
Put it on harder.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm just wiping it off.
You can't cook if you catch a cold.
That's right.
It's warm, isn't it?
Yes.
Wipe it off properly.
My body is getting cold.
It's warm, isn't it?
It's warm.
My body is getting cold.
Warm it up.
It's warm.
Thank you.
It's cold, isn't it?
It's cold.
I'm sorry.
Your hands are warm.
I'll take a step with your hands.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Did I tease you too much?
I'm in trouble.
What am I thinking?
I almost attacked you.
I'm sorry.
I was mean to you.
I'm sorry, too.
I'm sorry.
You're cute.
I wanted to tease you.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to take a bath.
Don't do that.
Did you want to touch me?
I know.
I made you so big.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm not supposed to do that.
You're not supposed to do that?
Do you want me to do that?
I'm sorry.
You're making a lot of noise.
You're so big.
I like this breast.
You always look at my boobs.
I noticed.
I'm sorry....
I'm always so stressed...
uwu
drink?
ok
actually,I've expose my neck
it's embarrassing
it's awful
what?
How do you feel?
Do you feel better?
Ah...
Darling...!
I'm sorry. I'll never be able to rub you like that again.
I feel my back becoming harder and harder....
It's not that I can't do it, but...
I'll catch a cold if I stay in bed.
Why are you bullying Chikubi?
Do you hate Chikubi?
Don't do that!
Why are you still in bed?
I'm sorry.
I want to touch you like this.
It's very sensitive.
I feel like I'm going to collapse.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I feel like I'm getting hotter and hotter.
It feels good.
I feel like I'm going to collapse.
I feel like I'm getting hotter and hotter.
It's amazing.
You're quite a pervert, aren't you?
What?
If you say such a thing, you'll get sick.
I'll get tired and dirty.
You'll get dirty?
How can you get dirty?
You're mean.
It's amazing.
Why do you think of such a thing?
How is it?
It's amazing.
I can't take it anymore.
If I touch you?
If I touch you.
I can't take it anymore.
It's amazing.
I'll go if you kiss me.
You're quite a pervert, aren't you?
It's amazing.
You're wet.
You're quite a pervert, aren't you?
It's amazing.
It's embarrassing.
It's very hot.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I didn't know you were this big.
I'm sorry.
The rabbit is weak.
He's twitching.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to pet you?
Is it okay?
It's okay.
Do you want me to pet you?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I'm sleepy.
It feels good.
I can't stop.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I have to go soon.
I have to go.
Ah!
It hurts...
Yoko-san, can I go with you?
No, I don't want to.
Let's go.
Yoko-san, can I go with you?
Is something wrong?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
You have a cute face, but you do it when you have to.
I'm sorry.
If you have a baby, take responsibility.
Responsibility?
I'm kidding.
I'll do it.
Are you sure?
It's a secret.
Hey, Makoto.
My mom and dad are not here.
And Shinichiro is late.
So I'll make you something you like.
What should I make?
Anything is fine.
Anything?
What do you want to eat?
Anything you like.
Don't be shy.
I'm not.
You like a lot of things.
That's true.
You don't eat what you like, do you?
No, I don't.
You can eat what you like.
I like everything.
Anything is fine.
Shall I make a hot pot?
That's a good idea.
What else do you want to eat?
Fried food is fine.
How about a kimchi hot pot?
That's a good idea.
What do you want to eat last?
Udon?
Ramen?
How about udon?
That's a good idea.
I'm looking forward to it.
I have to change the ingredients.
I'm glad you've been able to talk to me lately.
You couldn't talk to your baby before.
You were happy, weren't you?
I think so.
I'm glad we're getting closer.
That's good.
Is there anything you want to ask me?
What do you want to ask me?
We haven't talked much.
That's true.
Let's talk when we eat.
Let's talk a lot.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going out.
I'm going to change my clothes.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Are you embarrassed?
I'm nervous because such a beautiful woman suddenly comes to my house.
You're good at it.
Are you nervous?
I'm good at it.
I'm glad to hear that.
Why are you so embarrassed?
What's wrong?
Stop it.
You don't have to run away.
I'm sorry I teased you too much.
Your reaction is cute.
I'm going out.
Wait for me.
Is she okay?
Makoto.
I'm back.
Can you bring me a towel?
A towel?
It's raining a lot.
Thank you.
I'm soaked.
You saved me.
It's raining a lot.
It's raining suddenly.
I thought I could go home, so I ran home.
I'm soaked.
Are you okay?
My hair is wet.
The floor is wet.
What's wrong, Makoto?
What's wrong?
Your face is red.
It's nothing.
I'm soaked.
My feet are wet.
My pants are wet.
It's been a long time since it rained.
I'm soaked.
Maybe I should take a shower.
Makoto, look.
What?
I'm soaked.
Is it transparent?
It's a little transparent.
It's terrible that it's raining suddenly.
That's right.
When I came back, I was seen by an old man.
Is that so?
It's terrible, isn't it?
It's terrible.
Why are you holding my hand?
It's nothing.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What?
Can you wipe my face?
That's right.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Wipe my face properly.
Here?
That's right.
It's getting cold.
Can you warm me up?
Your hands are warm.
My body is getting cold.
It's getting cold.
The sun is shining.
You're so cute, Makoto.
Don't you have a girl you like?
No, I don't.
You're so cute.
Don't touch me.
I'm sorry.
Did I overdo it?
I have to take a shower.
Hiroko.
It's hot.
What's wrong, Makoto?
Hiroko.
Makoto.
What's wrong?
I can't stand it.
Did I overdo it?
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
Did I overdo it?
I have to take a shower.
Makoto.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
Did I overdo it?
Don't do that.
I have to take a shower.
It's hot.
It's okay, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
Did I overdo it?
Don't do that.
It's hot.
I have to change my clothes.
Don't do that.
Makoto, you'll get wet.
It's hot.
Makoto.
I can't stand it.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry, Hiroko.
Makoto.
Let's continue what we were doing.
You can touch me again.
I touched you so much that my nipples stood up.
Don't tell Shinjiro.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Makoto, you're cute.
You can touch my butt.
Do you like my butt?
I'm looking at you.
It's getting cold, isn't it?
Warm it with your hands.
It's warm.
It feels good.
I feel like I'm going to puke.
Touch me more.
Touch me directly.
It feels good.
Makoto, you're amazing.
You're amazing.
Touch me more.
It feels good.
I feel like I'm going to puke.
Where did you learn that?
My panties are wet.
Touch me from the front.
It feels good.
I touched you a lot.
My nipples are like this.
Look at me.
My clothes are wet, so my nipples are like this.
Are you excited?
What's going on with your nipples?
I'll make you feel good.
It's pink and cute.
Does it feel good?
Your nipples are so hard.
Are you excited?
I'll take them off.
That's great.
Your nipples are big.
Does it feel good?
That's great.
I'll take your underwear off.
It's warm.
Did you get up because I licked your nipples?
Makoto's nipples are warm.
What do you want me to do?
I'll lick your nipples.
Your nipples are big and can't go deep.
Lie down next time.
Lie down.
I'll touch your nipples.
How do you feel when I touch both of your nipples?
You're surprised.
I'll lick your nipples.
Oh, Makoto.
I want to lick your nipples.
Can I?
I'm going to get on top of you.
It's so hard.
I'm going to put you in.
You went in right away.
You went all the way in.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's making a sound.
Does it feel good?
It's getting hot.
It's hot.
I'm about to go.
This is amazing.
There's a bear in there.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'm about to go.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
This is amazing.
I'm about to go.
I want you to put it in from the back.
Put it in here.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'm about to go.
It's hot.
Let's do it from the front.
It feels good.
It's hot.
There's a bear in there.
I'm about to go.
It feels good.
There's a bear in there.
It's fun.
It's hot.
Wait!
Did you go too?
You couldn't stand it?
Did you get angry?
It can't be helped.
There's a lot of them.
It's a secret about today.
It's hot.
I have to get ready for dinner.
I'll go get ready for the hot pot.
Wait for me after I get changed.
It's hot.