What happened sister?
Oh, you have been hit.
was not?
Oh, I mean something.
Oh well
Did you fight two more battles?
I found out.
I know, mostly
Because it is.
I said I’m busy working lately.
Not all contact.
I told you I was on a trip to the Aquarium, remember?
They both said they had to cancel their work, so they said they cancelled it.
I was looking forward to it.
Yes, I was looking forward to it.
The hotel was also fun.
I decided to go with you.
I am not busy, I know.
Why not? he is not talking about it.
by Fuck?
I do not know, but.
I’m back, it’s been late recently.
Probably too late.
No, but what about Annie? Would you vomit so quickly?
Not that type?
I don’t think you’re a type, but what?
Yes, it feels like the beginning.
But I have a beautiful wife, she can’t get rid of her.
is beautiful?
So it is okay.
Why are you kind?
I got a little better.
Good to be.
Is the worker not there?
I am not there.
Definitely a lie.
Really no longer understand.
Really to?
No more than one.
You are so kind, you listen to me.
Because they live together.
Oh well, yes is it.
Well, but please be reassured.
Why Why?
It is OK.
really is?
If you feel like your brother’s brother, you’ll sound like a brother.
No, Professor, it is okay.
I hear anything.
really is?
Thank you for not having anybody to talk about this.
Teacher, you are okay.
Really kind.
Okay okay, that is it.
I have rubbish on my shoulders.
Just now
Welcome to.
Did you both eat?
I ate
Congratulations to
Get to be sooner.
Soon to soon.
Good night.
My job was late today.
Become a new project leader.
be late for a while.
I am going to the bathroom, but can I go in?
If you are hungry, I will make something.
So I take a bath first.
I understand
No beer?
I am cold and crying.
So, can you water?
Sorry to
So, I’ll take a bath.
No to
I said a new project was beginning.
Can not get involved?
Yes is.
Once again it is a little tough.
Even the previous trip to the county of Kashgar was not possible.
Next month, on the wedding anniversary, we’re going on a trip.
really is?
In the hot spring, we go.
I did it!
No, I think it’s time for you to have a child.
I want to do it, but I’m a little busy now, so wait a little longer.
I will be opening my house for two days from tomorrow.
I have not heard of travel.
Sorry, I decided suddenly.
Sorry, but please please.
Knowledge of just now.
Well, what about the university?
Okay, it is okay.
I think I can graduate this year.
Yes, it is okay
You have to decide on a job.
I will be okay, okay.
Get a job, just like me.
You have to have a beautiful girl and be happy.
You will be a loser in life.
Ellie is
Have a coffee or something?
Oh, there is
Not making now.
Not too fast?
Good night.
First put the cover.
I dropped it.
Be careful, come and go.
Please stay at home for 2 days.
And you have to take care of them, take care of them.
Yes I understand.
So go go come.
Be careful.
Go to
We were both alone, waiting.
I was always worried about the last.
I wanted to take off my face.
It is nice.
Let us go.
Heat is
So feel good on my shoulders.
Oh yeah yeah
primarily
Drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk, drunk.
Those such
Sorry to
Oh yeah
by
Oh is
Oh yeah
by Barca
became beautiful.
They will return the counterattack.
I said that he was a heroin, so it was okay.
Go back to.
That is?
Oh yeah yeah?
This, what happened to it?
Sorry, it just happened.
Yes is.
Working faster than scheduled.
Oh yeah yeah.
Something was too early.
I finished work earlier than planned.
Oh yeah yeah
I am hungry, I think I can do a little.
Oh, so I’ll make food.
Oh yeah, do you love it?
Oh, oh, maybe it was a job, I said yesterday night.
At this time?
I don’t think he came home at night.
So I take a shower and I will get dressed.
Okay, I’ll prepare dinner here.
You have a little baggage.
I got home quickly and was a little nervous.
must make.
What happened, it was dark.
What happened? what happened?
Because it...
I think it’s time I want a child.
New one is traveling.
You cannot confront me.
Oh, I think you seem to be busy.
by
Do you talk to your brother?
Sometimes it’s like that, but I’m tired and I think it’s not going to be okay.
So I haven’t done it lately.
I am sure you miss it, right?
Yes, I am missing you.
I miss you.
Let me say it somehow.
Well, but it is a bit.
Is it a little annoying?
Not a hassle, but I know something.
Yes to.
Because we are a couple.
Yes
I can wait until the pancakes calm down for a while.
I am married, but it has been a year.
Do you miss it?
I miss you, I miss you, I miss you, I miss you, I miss you, I miss you, I miss you, I miss you, I miss you, I miss you.
One year is not so long.
New marriage or new marriage?
It’s a new marriage, but isn’t that?
How about it.
Is it so?
I hope you try a little more.
I hope you have a good time, a little.
What is it.
But he is working hard.
A little next time.
They are not very close together, right?
are good together.
So that is that.
Same is different.
Maybe it is wrong.
Probably is it.
Is there no one with her?
Probably not now.
We broke up a month ago.
Yes is.
I want to do so much now, I am very busy with my work.
Well, yes, I think the timing will be over, or maybe.
Oh yeah
Yes is.
Good morning.
Tired of you.
It is a trip again.
What is it.
You are not traveling and you are not working.
This company really.
Sorry, I’m at work, because I haven’t been anywhere lately.
I like to go to the hot spring or you.
I like the hot springs.
It was a hot spring, and it was delicious.
Use it slowly.
Oh, I want to go.
No, it’s going to be tomorrow, again.
Oh yeah, it is so.
Yes, it is enough now.
Really tired, now
very difficult
Sorry, I’m bothering you something.
No is okay.
Sorry to
No yes
Oh yeah yeah.
Sinai is you.
Not just work.
Do you not seek a saint?
Oh yeah yeah
Because I am thinking.
If you are a man, you no longer have to work as a saint.
There are limits to barbecue.
Barber is a time pay.
As a brother, I want you to work hard.
Is there anything you want to do?
The Me?
Especially not.
It’s a little different from me there.
You have to have a goal.
Just find something you want to do.
Life is fun, right?
It was a work.
I mean, there is no motivation.
Oh yeah yes!
by
This trip is about two days.
Open a little house.
is busy.
Can I take care of your home?
I understand
Maybe at night, maybe it’s the middle of the house.
Please go to the center.
If you sweat a little, Florence will come in.
Good luck to you.
I still have a brother and he is still in good shape.
Yes to.
Stop the cousin.
Two days later.
Go on hard.
Then I will go.
thanks to
Please do not go too.
Be careful.
And then the child.
Welcome to.
Please be successful.
I am going to go.
Okay, I tried hard.
Congratulations to
very good
Very disturbing.
More of
Go to room?
Thanks for the viewing.
Hold a little.
by
Feel good
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Will go out again.
I am
Oh yeah
well is
I am
by us
How many times have we done it?
I do not know.
Very good.
No to
Oh yeah
by Miley »
Beware of Arthur.
and then
and complete
Oh is
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah yeah
Yes, it is damaging.
by 時
Oh oh oh oh oh oh
Time for a thing.
Oh Oh Oh
by 24h
2nd
Oh yeah
No to
Yl is
Oh is
was
is
No to
Oh is
Oh yeah
by
Oh is
No to
I’m going to be the mayor of Fukuoka tomorrow, I’ve been there for a long time.
What happened to.
No, but not anything.
Cook it and do it later.
Yes, if there is something.
Do not just use the carrier case.
Oh I understand.
You leave the pool.
Oh sorry you.
Yes yes yes
and so,
The trip may take about two days.
I go for two days.
So is.
Yes, we will be together.
Something sweet.
Then wait.
Do not forget the gift.
We have been married for two years.
Yes is.
So is
It is time.
child
Do not want?
well
It is time for that time.
No, I want it too.
Even your mom and dad.
Too much told.
Oh yeah that.
I want to show you your face.
Oh yeah.
Well, you are yes.
But I am a little busy now.
Oh yeah.
If people lose their jobs.
When is?
Yes, it is a bit difficult to say that.
Let us think well.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah.
Yes I think.
I’m going to sleep, tomorrow is early.
When is?
Tomorrow is 7 in the morning.
Yes to.
Well, let’s talk about it after we get home.
Okay, then go to bed first.
Good night.
It is a pity to leave you both.
Because they will be gone for two days.
Do you know?
I know.
Must be tight.
Yes is.
Getting it.
Oh is?
Please please
About the river.
of course
If anything happens, help me.
Yes
Now it is time to go.
Come to go.
Be careful.
According to Football
and link
Oh yeah
You have full.
It is secret.
of course
This is this?
Then
This position
Whose fault?
Because of this?
It became my bread.
What do you do?
I will want to come.
The shower.
to go once?
Rethink it once.
He was sweating.
Yes, it is shit.
What? what? what? what? what?
What are you doing?
Something is hit.
What is?
Okay now sir.
Why Why?
What is?
Just done it.
I want to always.
What do you do?
Wait a little.
I can do nothing.
What is?
My feet are exciting.
Go to bed.
Give me a bed?
You and you are with me.
Oh yeah
thanks to
Is it okay?
What is?
Do something clean.
You put out a lot.
Did you have sperm?
Just a little.
You did it again.
Yes, I did it.
Yes what?
He was very out.
meet for a long time.
His face has come?
Do you do it again?
Yes
Good night.
Do not say.
I want to cry.
Very well.
Feel good
Can I be good?
Sorry to
Oh well ðŸ™‚
Oh yeah
Imagination is
Which of the pros?
Both of
Do it
Feel good
Feels good?
The hunger grew.
This silver will soon stand up.
I want to put it in again.
Can I enter?
Yes
Would you talk?
Enter it.
Feel good
I like it.
by Slip
by Cuc
Oh is
This can
Feel good
Oh is
Oh oh oh!by
and adjective
Oh oh oh oh oh
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Technically
Wait a little.
Go to.
be to be.
Stay this
Inside it
Was it good?
Yes
Was it okay inside?
It is OK.
It is okay.
Yes
Stand up a little.
Can’t stand up?
No, because
My sister will come home.
It is OK.
Is it okay?
still is
I want to do.
Okay is it?
Again a cowboy.
Can several times.
How many times can I give you?
Is it okay yet?
still can go.
Still not yet?
I still want.
Great is
I entered.
You put a lot of it inside until the end.
A great feeling.
When will you come home, brother?
Maybe it is time.
Shower this.
Take a shower.
Showering in the shower?
feed them.
My sister has not come home today.
It seems to be late today.
Yes is.
Always so
Yes
Are you tired, okay?
Oh what do you mean.
Not being tired.
It feels like something is being thought out.
Oh what do you mean.
He told me that he wanted to see the witch's face.
It is about a year soon to get married.
Yes, but I don’t think that’s that.
No, the truth is not bad, and I don’t hate it.
Because I am busy with work.
Yes, there are times, too.
What to do.
Sorry to tell this to you.
If you are concerned, ask anything.
thanks to.
I am so excited to see this woman’s face.
I am also in trouble.
Do you want to have children because you do that with your brother?
You hear that, new tree.
Hearing something strange.
That will interest you.
No, it’s a bit crazy to talk about this.
I mean, I mean nothing, but
You are busy with your work and you are late to come back, right?
I watched it, too, too much, too tired.
No, I have to say something like this, sorry.
If you want to have children, I think it will be cut off.
Yes it is.
It is quite difficult,
Does she like to talk about Pearl than about me?
I have not been with that guy for a while either.
Maybe you’re interested in the type of pearl.
Is it your favorite type?
I want to hear.
Well, at the age of.
You like the repair.
So cute and short, in terms of appearance.
Do you like short cut?
Yes is it.
A lot more?
But you are a type like your sister.
Oh no, maybe you’re laughing here, stop.
I was surprised, I don’t realize it at all.
It is not funny to laugh at me.
No, I can’t laugh from here.
Really? no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
I really like her, like her sister.
Is it so?
Very kind and beautiful.
Oh what do I do?
Do you hate younger?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, I don’t like that, but I don’t like that.
How about the two?
Oh is?
Why is it.
No is
I do not hate.
My sister
I like it.
Yes is
I am
I really like it.
Yes is
For your sister.
Do anything.
No, I am not going to consult.
Just now
Oh, what did you do today?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I don’t wear clothes, I can’t work for you.
Because I have eaten.
Oh yeah yeah yeah?
I understood.
Come to me.
So now now.
Oh well okay.
I have a job in the local area, I have a word.
Oh yeah yeah?
I have to travel next time.
How long is?
Not so long, than before.
Oh yeah yeah.
Today, my parents told me that I wanted to see a magic face.
Again to?
Yes it is.
To be honest, that is.
But it is time to be okay.
Tell me if you can, it will be okay.
Oh... yes...
Yes, but I will tell you great.
That’s also about deceiving, right?
It is my wife’s job, right?
Yes...
No is
Oh well Sinai.
Oh is?
What will you do in the future?
Oh no, that...
I hope you find a job right now.
So I told you to introduce me, so go there.
No, it is far away there.
What are you holding.
What do you want to do.
This is OK.
I am so happy, I have a brother now.
But I cannot endure.
But I say there.
She is beautiful because she likes her sister.
I know, a little, a little, a little.
I know. – A little bit.
Yes, yes to you.
Well, this time we are going on a trip.
Where are you going?
That is the northern.
Did you go to you? – I mean.
Oh yeah yes.
Oh yeah yeah.
Well, from Rosie, don’t bother me.
Oh yeah, I understand.
Do it yourself, right.
Oh yeah yeah
I have something to do, so I can do it.
I might go to the bath too.
Come to me.
It was in Shenzhen.
Oh no no
I don’t like it.
sister, what did you do?
I did nothing, though.
Yes, otherwise
My sister cannot stand it either.
I don’t know what you are talking about.
Because I cannot endure.
Let us continue.
What is next?
Oh well
Oh yeah
Yes is
No towels.
I think it has all the baggage.
again is
I think I will contact my parents.
Appropriately is.
Because it is new land.
Not to be wrong.
Brother, go now.
What do you do today?
Today is a work holiday.
Time to get pulled, I’ll get pulled.
Yes is
I will go.
You will go.
I am going.
Okay, it is okay.
Must dissolve
Make it clean.
It is so cool, still calm, it is hard.
Then the next there.
Let us go.
Yes
Oh yeah
No to
What is it?
and sweat.
sweat too much.
Just lick it a little.
Oh yeah
No to
Good there, good there.
There there there there there there there there.
That feeling there.
It is already feeling.
I no longer know.
No to?
Oh yeah
by Tess
No to?
Let us go.
Oh yeah
A little
A little before that.
I will clean it.
Oh yeah
No to?
Yes
Let us go.
I did it.
Something a bit strange.
Yes is.
The monster?
Roads do not come back yet
You can more.
Zen of Things
I will die now.
Congratulations to you, Mr.
cannot go.
by Adieu
You are always well, you are always well.
well well.
greatly
It has become new.
It feels good there.
I was hungry.
Go to
What is?
I wanted to do it again.
What did I do.
No other way anymore.
He stood up again.
I was tired.
Still put in?
Even a little more.
No is no.
Give me out.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Oh oh oh oh oh, my friend.
Of course the
tier is
by Ruth
Oh there
in a piece.
Shake it.
by BED
there
and more.
Oh, that is hard.
Go to long.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh hey hey...