You've brought a lot of furniture, haven't you?
Yes, I have.
Do you have any furniture you want?
No, I don't.
I want something like this.
Did you look it up?
You read a lot, don't you?
What do you read?
No, I didn't.
I've never heard of such a person.
I want you to do something about it.
I don't know what to do.
I've become good at everything since I went to college.
I'm relieved to have a good sister.
That's not true.
You don't study, do you?
No, I don't.
I want to study at home.
I want to study English.
You don't have to go to the United States.
You can go to a good university.
That's right.
You can speak English.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
How was school?
It was as usual.
You're boring.
Don't you have anything funny to say?
I don't have anything funny to say.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little grumpy.
That's not true.
Do you have homework?
I have homework.
Do your homework before you play games.
I know.
Can I teach you again?
No.
I'm glad you have a good sister.
I'm glad you taught me last time.
Can you say that?
You want to go to a good university, don't you?
You don't have a chance like this.
If there's anything I don't understand, I'll tell you.
That's what you're saying.
You should be grateful to your parents.
You should get used to it.
You look nervous.
You should straighten your back.
You're slouching.
You should eat properly.
You're always slouching.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Can I teach you?
Be a man.
I'm counting on you.
Do you have homework?
I have homework.
I have a new homework today.
What is it?
It's math.
I see.
Where is it?
It's here.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
You shouldn't do that in front of your parents.
I'm doing my best.
I'm behind you.
Hurry up.
I don't think it's a problem.
You're slouching.
Do you have homework?
I don't have homework.
You should get used to it.
I'll teach you.
I'm fine.
You're slouching.
I think you can do it.
I'm doing my best.
What are you doing?
I'm behind you.
I'm doing my best.
You're slouching.
I have homework.
What are you doing?
Don't go there, Kyon.
But Max will fall for me.
And these things. Well, why is he okay with it?
Does he know we need Film it?
Wait...
Just a second.
So little does he need these things.
Not enough yet.
Come here.
What's wrong?
Did you get hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Sakazu, are you doing your homework?
Yes, I am.
Teach me.
I'm doing my homework, so I'm fine.
Sakazu is very honest and easy to teach.
Really?
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You can't teach, can you?
I don't want to.
I'm sorry.
What did you do?
I went to a university, but I didn't go to college.
That's your expectation.
That's my expectation.
I don't think so.
That's not good.
I want to go to a university.
I don't think so.
I think you're a good student.
I can't see it.
I've been studying hard, so I'm going to a university.
I see.
I'm free all the time.
I was just kicked out.
I had a doctor's appointment today.
Are you okay?
I can't work.
I was supposed to host a beauty salon with you, but I was kicked out.
What are you doing?
I'm studying alone with Asakazu-kun.
I thought I'd take a break.
That's right.
It's tiring to teach him.
No, it's not like that.
I'm glad I have a sister like you.
I'm not like that.
You're calm.
No, I'm not.
Right, Asakazu?
Yes.
What's right?
I'm glad I have a sister like you.
I'm sorry I didn't rely on you.
It's okay.
Please take care of Asakazu.
I'm fine.
Tell me if you don't.
Okay.
Tomita-kun.
I miss my family.
I know you miss them.
It's almost time to go back to work.
We have to go back to the company.
Is it bad?
I see.
I can't bring you with me.
It's still a long way to go.
Let's go outside.
I'm going to take a shower.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Do your best.
I'm going out.
Good luck.
It's thrilling.
I'm glad my mom and dad are not here.
Why?
I don't want to talk to you.
I'm glad my mom and dad are not here.
My parents are not here.
I'm going to take a shower.
You have a hard stomach.
You didn't want to go outside, did you?
What's wrong?
You're excited, aren't you?
If you do this to me, I'll be excited.
You wanted to do this.
What do you want me to do?
As usual?
I want you to do it as usual.
You have a hard stomach.
I can't stand it.
You wanted to do this.
I'm glad my mom and dad are not here.
You didn't want to do this.
It feels so good.
Oh, my God.
You got up early today.
I'm glad my mom and dad are not here.
Look at this.
You have less hair than before.
Did you do it yourself?
No, I didn't.
You can't stand it?
You don't have to say that.
I thought it was bad.
You said you didn't have to stand it.
I'm going to touch your hair.
Do you like my hair?
Yes, I do.
You said you didn't have to stand it.
It feels good when you laugh like that again.
I want to do it again.
I'm glad my mom and dad are not here.
That's not enough, is it?
You want to touch my hair, don't you?
I want to touch your hair.
I'm glad my mom and dad are not here.
Are you looking after her?
Yes.
Let's do it tomorrow.
No, I can't do that.
You can't.
I can't.
It's not over yet.
Isn't it bad to go to the balcony?
It's okay.
It won't come out so soon.
No.
Let's do it now.
It's still like a hostel.
It's still like a hostel, isn't it?
Yes.
It's still like a hostel.
It's hard.
I can't hear you.
A rat's feeling.
What are they doing?
Oh no.
Did you sleep?
Yes.
I'm glad.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
What?
Do you want me to do it again?
No.
Let me out of your neck.
What is it?
I feel sick.
What are you doing?
I'm taking a break.
Why are you sitting there?
I thought you were studying.
I thought I was tired.
I thought you were tired.
Why are you sitting there?
I thought you were studying.
That's all.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Study hard.
Yes.
Mom left.
I don't think she'll come back.
I'll kiss you.
Can you hear me?
Yes.
I'll kiss you from behind.
From behind?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
Move more.
You can move, right?
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
I don't want to go.
I'm sorry.
I want to go inside.
I can't do it anymore.
I feel sick.
I'm sleepy.
Are you sleepy?
I feel sick.
I'm sleepy.
Thank you.
Look at this.
It's dirty.
I'm sorry.
Look at this.
Let's get along well from now on.
I don't want you to find out.
Have you gotten used to this place?
Yes, I have.
I was a little worried.
I know, right?
I'm sorry I kept you waiting.
But it's fun every day.
I know.
It's nice to have a big brother.
That's true.
I'm a little confused, too.
But I think we'll get along well.
I think so, too.
What do boys like?
I'm sure you'll like this.
Really?
There's no boy who doesn't like Nikujaga.
I wonder if Tsukasa will eat it.
It's okay.
I'll let him eat Nikujaga.
Tsukasa is back.
Welcome back.
I'll be right back.
Is it good?
I'll have to simmer it a little longer.
I see.
It's good.
The flavor will come in from here, so it's okay.
It looks good.
It's good.
Really?
I'm sure it's good.
Shizuku is making Nikujaga today.
Is that so?
You're good at it, so it's okay.
I'm not confident.
Do you like Nikujaga?
Well...
It's good.
You're right.
I'll simmer it a little longer.
I think so, too.
What else should I make?
What should we make?
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry, too.
I can't wait to eat it.
Is the potato a little crumbled?
Potatoes don't crumble.
Really?
I think it's better to eat it when it's crumbled.
I think so, too.
Mom, you like it when it's crumbled, don't you?
I know.
I like it, too.
Is it good?
Yes.
It's good.
It smells good.
I want to eat it quickly.
What should I do?
What are you going to do?
Mom, I want to add a little more onion.
It's good.
I'll eat it.
We're in Japan now.
It's good even if it's crumbled.
That's right.
It's a little hard.
Really?
I see.
The fire is worse than potatoes.
I like soft carrots.
I see.
Is it soft?
It's not soft.
It's still hard.
I see.
Do you like it harder?
I like it softer.
Do you like it softer?
Yes.
But, I don't like it when it's crumbled.
It doesn't look good.
I see.
But, I like it better when it's crumbled.
What?
Are you still standing?
No.
Are you looking forward to the meat dish?
Well...
Tsukasa, don't you have to go to school today?
I have to go.
I'll teach you.
Then, I'll watch you cooking here.
Really?
Yes.
Let's do it together.
Okay.
You don't have to go back yet.
You don't usually cook, but you stopped cooking.
I want you to be refreshed.
I'll be refreshed.
What?
I want you to be refreshed.
Wait a minute.
Be quiet.
Be comfortable.
I don't like it here.
Why?
I know you don't like it here.
I don't like it here.
You'll be fine if you stay quiet.
Okay?
Be comfortable.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
Do it directly.
Let's do it as usual.
Let's do it here.
That's fine.
I'm sorry.
She doesn't notice at all.
It's okay.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
I was under a lot of stress.
Really?
I was waiting for you to come.
Do you feel good?
Don't you notice because I'm washing your hair?
I'm sorry.
What?
What? I went to Tsukasa's room, but it was dirty.
What? But he's a boy, so it's probably dirty.
Yeah, so I thought I'd study here.
Oh, really? That's good. You can't do it yet.
It's okay. I'm here.
You're here, right?
Yeah.
I'm going to study here.
What? You're going to study here?
But you two are getting along pretty well, so I'm happy.
She's happy.
Tsukasa, if Shizuku does something annoying, tell me.
What's annoying?
I want to clean up the room.
That's not true, is it?
Oh, okay.
Are you going to study here?
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Wait a minute.
You've grown up.
You've grown up so much.
Cute.
What?
It's not falling, is it?
It's okay.
You've grown up so much, but you say that?
It's getting really hot.
You've only touched it a little.
It's okay, right?
It's hot.
Be quiet.
Oh, my God.
Shizuku, what are you doing?
I'm going to take Tsukasa's button off his pants.
Oh, I see.
I thought I'd put it on him.
Can you do that?
I can do it.
I've never heard you can do it.
I can do it, so it's okay.
Are you okay?
Don't worry.
You've grown up.
You've grown up so much, but you say that?
It's hot.
Be quiet.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I want you to feel better than I do.
It's hot.
I'm going to take Tsukasa's button off his pants.
It feels good.
Do it again.
That's right.
It feels good.
It's hot.
You're so good at this.
Shizuku.
What is it?
I think you're okay now.
Is that so?
I'll put out the fire.
Thank you.
Then I'll fry it.
Are you still studying?
I am.
I see.
I'm going to clean up the bath.
It's still going to take a while, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It's difficult.
I see.
I'll do it.
Do you have a towel?
Yes.
You're good.
Be quiet.
What?
Are you still studying?
Of course.
Be quiet.
You're good.
Give me your hand.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
You're cool.
I'm cleaning up the bath.
No, you're not.
My mom won't notice.
I want you to be cool.
I'm cool.
Do you like it?
Yes.
It's hot.
Be quiet.
I want you to touch my belly.
This way.
I'm getting hot.
Is it hot?
More.
Put your finger in my belly.
I want you to touch my belly.
It's hot.
I like it.
Let me sleep.
I want to sleep.
Good night.
I did my best.
I want to sleep.
Let's sleep in the room.
I want to sleep now.
I don't want to waste time.
I want to sleep.
You have a lot of hair.
You can still do it, right?
I can still do it.
How about your head?
Do you take a long time to clean the bath?
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I want to sleep.
It hurts.
It's hot, isn't it?
I don't like it.
Are you okay?
What?
It's hot, isn't it?
Can't you take a bath?
I can take a bath.
I can't take a bath.
It's exposed.
Do you want to take a bath?
You can still do it, can't you?
I can still do it.
Are you young?
It hurts.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
It feels good.
My voice is hoarse.
It's hoarse.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You're wearing a bra.
I'm wearing a bra.
It's hot.
What are you doing?
I'm taking a break on the deck.
What's that?
It's not a bed.
It's a small sofa.
Sit down.
I'm giving it to you.
Are you giving it to me?
This is good.
I'm looking forward to eating it.
I'm hungry.
Eat this.
It feels good.
What?
I think it's very good.
I'm glad.
I made it for the first time.
You can make it with confidence.
That's right.
It's hot.
What?
It's good.
You can take it out.
It's hot.
Did you take it out again?
Shizuku, look at this.
Did you make it?
You can taste it.
Thank you.
It looks good.
You're right.
It looks delicious.
It's not delicious.
It's delicious.
I'm glad.
It's good to learn from your mother.
That's right.
I'm looking forward to eating it.
I made a lot of bread.
That's a lot of bread.
I put it in the refrigerator.
That's right.
You must be full.
I'm full.
I'm looking forward to eating it.
I'm hungry.
Toru will be back soon.
That's right.
I think he'll be back soon.
You guys get along well.
Your mother is helpful.
He's a cute brother.
I have to be like my sister.
I'm glad that Toru came to my house.
I'm glad.
Are you glad?
I'm home.
Toru, welcome back.
Sit down.
Have a snack.
Thank you.
It looks delicious.
How was school today?
It was as usual.
I lined up in front of the station.
Did you?
Yes.
Do you have to line up to go home?
I lined up for about 15 minutes.
It looks like a famous rice cracker.
Eat it.
Thank you for the food.
It looks delicious.
Toru came to my house.
I feel better.
Do you feel better?
I think so.
What's wrong with you, Toru?
Why do you look around?
Do you get along well with Toru?
Of course, we get along well.
Toru is good at math.
No, I'm not.
I'm impressed.
I want you to teach me how to read and write.
No, I don't want to.
I'm not good at it.
I don't want to teach you.
You're smarter than me.
Maybe you're right.
I don't want to teach you.
You go to a good university.
I can learn from you.
But I'm not good at it.
I want you to teach me how to read and write.
I'm sorry.
You're always like this.
You're a little sloppy.
What's wrong with you?
Toru.
Do you feel sick?
No, I'm fine.
Are you sure?
I'm glad.
Be nice to Toru.
Thank you.
You're right.
You're excellent.
Stop it.
Do you want me to teach you how to read and write?
No, I don't.
I like to study.
I see.
It's good to like to study.
You have a different gene.
Do you mean my dad?
Yes.
He's a new dad.
He's a very happy person.
That's right.
He has a good DNA.
He's a member of an entertainment company.
That's right.
Mom.
Yes?
You haven't done the laundry yet.
I have to do it.
I'll do it.
What?
Don't be surprised.
What's wrong?
I sometimes do it in the morning.
That's rare.
Really?
I sometimes do it when my mom does it.
Is that so?
No way.
Do you do it when your mom does it?
I do it sometimes.
Really?
I think you'll do it tomorrow.
What's this?
Is it snow?
No.
It's really rare.
I'll try it.
I knew it.
Try it.
Okay.
You haven't eaten it yet.
I'll eat it.
What's wrong?
Why do you look like that?
I thought it was delicious.
It looks delicious, doesn't it?
Yes.
I was surprised.
What's wrong?
Did you buy it?
No.
I bought it in front of the station.
That's right.
I finally bought it.
It was really delicious.
You said you wanted to eat it all the time.
Right?
That's right.
I finally bought it.
You can eat it every day.
I can eat it every day.
It's dinner time.
I'm going to eat it.
If you eat too much, you won't be able to eat dinner.
That's right.
I gained weight recently.
Did you eat this senbei?
I ate it.
What were you doing there?
I was washing my bangs.
Did you listen to your mom's song?
Can you listen to it later?
It's okay.
I'm going to wash my bangs.
Please.
Thank you.
You've become a good girl since you registered.
Is that so?
Did you register?
No, I didn't do anything.
Eat more.
Eat this, too.
What's that?
This is...
I recently opened a new store.
I've been waiting for about 30 minutes.
It looks delicious.
Is it sweet?
Is that so?
It's delicious.
This is a limited edition.
You can only buy this in Okinawa.
Is that so?
Do you want to try it?
I don't know.
Is that so?
You're smart.
You're smart, aren't you?
I think so.
I think you're tired.
This is good for your brain.
That's right.
I've eaten this before.
It's really delicious.
This is delicious.
Is that so?
It's delicious.
What are you doing?
I'm washing the dishes.
I washed all the dishes.
Did you wash the dishes?
You didn't wash the dishes.
I washed the dishes.
Is that so?
I'll help you.
It's better to do it together.
That's not true.
Why are you busy?
I'm eating sweets.
I want to talk to you.
I'll help you.
Thank you.
Let's get along well.
I'm eating sweets.
It's good.
Mari.
What?
How do I open this?
It's hot.
It's delicious.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
You should eat this.
It's delicious.
It's hot.
Mari.
What's going on?
What?
Nothing.
What's going on?
Where is Toru?
I'm here.
What are you doing?
I'm cleaning up here.
You don't have to do that.
Thank you.
You should do your best.
I'll do my best.
It's hot.
It's delicious.
Mari.
Do you want me to buy all of them?
You can.
I'll buy them.
It's going to take a long time, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
I'll buy them.
Mari.
Yes?
I can't breathe.
It's not that bad.
It's okay.
Be careful.
I'll buy a vacuum cleaner.
Really?
It's dirty.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Mari.
You promised me that you wouldn't do this again.
I did.
When I see a man like you, there's a chance for me to get angry.
I'm a serious person.
And I stop getting stressed out.
It's like playing pick-up lullabies to your mom.
I got you.
Let's have this last time.
It's the last time.
This is getting harder again
We always have to take a break
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh
Number
Ah ah ah ah
Ah ah seriously
No
Hey
Ah ah Ah,
Yeah, make it stronger
No, don't do that
You're so energetic, you shouldn't do that
It doesn't feel good
It's not that I don't want to
It's not, right? You're so energetic
Wow
Wow, you're so energetic
Is it good?
Yeah, it's good
I'm going to do it from now on
Is it good?
Yeah, it's good
No, it's not
It's not
It's okay
No, it's not
There's a lot
It's amazing
It's going to get dirty
It's okay
I didn't want to apply it
This is the color, right?
Yeah
It's okay
I'm going to do it from now on
Ouch
It's okay
It's going to get dirty
She fell asleep
Can I do more?
I'm sorry
It's okay
It's going to get dirty
It's clean
It's okay
I'm going to wash it later
Are you okay?
It's okay
Yeah
Ouch
It's okay
It's going to get dirty
I'm going to clean around the kitchen
It's okay
I'm going to do it later
Really?
Did you wash the dishes?
Yeah
I'm going to do it later
It's okay
I don't know what to do with myself.
One two three...
I'm sorry.
Are you OK?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
How are you?
Are you ready?
I'm sorry.
Be careful.
What about you?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It hurts.
Yes, she's here.
Oh, she's here?
Yes.
She's still in there.
Oh, really?
She spilled a lot.
She spilled that much?
Yes, she did.
I guess I'll go put the vacuum cleaner in the hallway.
Okay.
Mom's here.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Okay.
I'll go get the vacuum cleaner.
Mom's here.
She's still in there.
Are you okay?
but she is like...
she is like making me angry
she is really mean
but
she is letting me do something
actually
I told her
to let me do everything
whether she will go to school or not
but to her
it is like
no
please
leave
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Ame
Oh
teu
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah  nonprofit
Hmm
Oh no.
Oh my.
It's okay, it's okay.
Ouch!
I'm done cleaning the hallway.
Let's do it again.
I'm going to clean the kitchen.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm going to record it.
I'm still doing it.
Oh, really?
I'm going to clean the bathroom.
Okay.
Mom, it hurts.
You didn't notice it at all, did you?
No, but...
She'll find out someday if I do this.
It's okay.
She won't find out.
Let's do it again.
Let's do it like this.
No, no, no.
It's okay.
But...
You did a good job.
It's okay.
Are you feeling better?
It's okay, right?
Yes.
Ryuzo.
Thank you for cleaning the bathroom.
Oh, no, no.
I was bored when I came back from school.
It's really helpful.
Really?
Please tell me.
I'll do this much.
I'm really happy.
Thank you.
No, no, no.
It's okay.
I think my sister will be back soon.
Oh.
Then...
Then let's have a snack together.
Oh, snack.
Yes, I understand.
Then I'll clean the bathroom until then.
Do you have any requests?
Snacks.
Anything is fine.
Then let's have a cake.
Then I'll have a cake.
Then I'll do the laundry.
Oh, yes.
I was surprised.
She didn't find out.
If she found out, it would be a big deal.
I have to be careful not to be found out.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
She's back.
I'm home.
Welcome back, Natsuki.
My sister is back.
I'm tired.
It was a long day, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
I had a long lecture.
I see.
I had to write a paper.
I didn't know what to talk about.
I see.
I didn't have time to decide.
I was talking to my friends, so I was late.
I see.
I'm sorry I'm late.
It's okay.
But I'm looking forward to it.
I know it's hard to write a paper.
Don't say that, mom.
If you say that, I'll feel pressured.
Why don't you go to a library?
You're right.
I have to get a reference book.
There must be a lot of reference books.
I'm tired of looking for them.
University libraries are big.
That school is big.
By the way, what are you doing now?
I'm going to do the laundry.
I'll help you.
It's okay.
Aren't you tired?
You have a lot to do.
Don't worry about it.
Thank you.
I'll do it.
Yuzo, please clean the bathroom.
Okay.
I got it.
I'll prepare dinner.
Okay.
I'm going to finish cleaning the bathroom.
I have to do my homework.
I'm going back to my room.
Excuse me.
What?
I'm going back to my room.
Excuse me.
Natsuki.
I have to do my homework.
Is it okay?
It's not okay.
What?
What do you mean?
I mean...
You know that, don't you?
But...
You have a girlfriend.
I can't do that.
My mother is there.
It's not okay.
I don't care if you say so.
It's okay, isn't it?
What?
I can't do that today.
Why?
My mother is there.
I can't do that.
What are you talking about?
Please forgive me.
I can't do that.
If you say so, I'll scold you.
You look normal to me.
If you come here...
It's not okay.
I can't do that.
You want me to do that, don't you?
Please stop.
I can't do that.
I want you to stop.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it again.
I can't do that.
You want me to do that, don't you?
Please don't say that.
My mother might see us.
Oh, you're going to make curry.
That's a good idea.
But I made curry the day before yesterday.
I feel like I'm going to be told that I ate curry the day before yesterday.
So I'm a little tired of making curry.
I feel good.
It's noisy.
I can't do that.
Be quiet.
That's enough.
I told you to deal with my stress in the morning.
Look at me.
I can't do that.
I feel good.
Is that enough?
That's enough, isn't it?
I haven't decided yet.
That's not enough, is it?
I can't do that.
I'm used to making curry.
Touch me properly.
I can't do that.
It's wet, so take it off first.
Is that enough?
I feel good.
That's enough, isn't it?
Touch me properly.
You've been doing it for a year.
Why?
Put your finger in it like you did the other day.
That was the last time.
What are you talking about?
I don't want to do it.
I'll tell your mother.
You can't do that.
I'll do it, so don't tell her.
Put your finger in it.
Is that enough?
That's enough.
Touch me properly.
Put your finger in it like you did the other day.
I feel good.
Put your finger in it.
It's a little dirty.
What should I do?
It's still dirty.
Clean it up.
Put your finger in it.
It's a little dirty.
You have to lick it more.
I feel good.
Do it like that.
Is that enough?
Did you do it?
Put your finger in it.
I feel good.
Natsuki.
What's wrong?
I don't know what to make for dinner.
Do you want to eat something?
Anything is fine.
Sorry.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
You can eat anything today.
What should I make?
It's easy.
It's not easy to cook.
How about a spinach soup?
That's good.
I know how to cook spinach soup.
I'm not good at cooking spinach soup.
But it's good.
Our laundry is going to be over soon.
Do you wanna continue the work tonight?
Thank you.
And there is the lizard
What do you think?
What are you doing?
Let's continue
Here is the head of the cat
Oh no, this has a really bad smell...
Oh, it really does smell!
It doesn't smell at all, does it?
Gulp Gulp
Sigh
So cold
Hold on
huh?
It's okay
Gulp Gulp
Gulp
Oh!
No, no, no, no, no!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh!
Uh!
Ah, ah, ah, ah!
Oh!
Ah!
I've got a lot of them out.
My skirt got dirty.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
You got a lot on your nose.
It's hot.
You know this sound, right?
Do you want to pee?
It's convenient, isn't it?
I'm going to pee.
You have to make a loud noise.
What do you want to do?
Are you okay?
I'm going to sleep with you.
Don't make a loud noise.
Are you okay?
Oh, my.
If I rub it like this, you'll want to do it, right?
I'm going to put it in.
Oh, it feels good.
If you make a loud noise, you'll hear it.
What should I do? What if my mom finds out?
No, no, no.
I'm going to sleep with you.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, no.
I'm going to sleep with you.
Why are you moving so hard?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm going to sleep with you.
Oh, it hurts.
You're gone.
I'm scared.
You're wet again.
I'm wet.
I'm sorry.
You're all over the place.
I'm sleepy.
You're still not enough.
You're going to get bigger, aren't you?
You're going to get bigger if you do this, aren't you?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It hurts.
You're all over the place.
You're going to get bigger if you do this, aren't you?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Your slippers are dirty.
You can still do it, can't you?
What are you going to do?
Let's do it over there.
It's okay.
Be quiet.
It's annoying.
Natsuki.
Have you finished washing up?
Thank you.
What do you want for dinner?
Let's search it.
Mom, what do you think?
I'm looking into it.
I see.
Anything is fine.
It's easy.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I heard a strange voice.
Really?
Anything is fine.
It's easy.
OK.
I'll make something.
I can't.
I'll be found out.
Natsuki.
What?
I'm going to buy some ingredients.
Really?
OK.
I'm going to buy some ingredients.
Leave it to me.
She's not here.
Hurry up.
Here.
I feel good.
I can't move my hand.
Give me more.
I can't.
I'm glad you are here.
I'm getting so hot.
I'm so hot.
I feel so bad.
Let's do it again.
No, I can't.
But you're not here anymore.
I don't know when you'll come back.
I can't do that.
Why?
I can't.
I'm so hot.
What?
You didn't hear me?
I don't know.
Wait!
Wait.
I can't.
I'm so happy to hear that you like me so much.
This is the last trial.
I won't let you go.
Wait.
Thank you for the meal.
How was it, Jiran? Did you like it?
Yes, it was delicious.
I'm glad to hear that.
My mom's food is always delicious.
Really? I'm glad to hear that.
Did you work hard today?
Yes, I did.
I see.
Why don't you eat more vegetables?
Vegetables?
A little more?
I'll eat a little more.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Don't you get irritated if you don't eat a lot?
I'm fine.
Really?
Yes.
Then, don't eat too much.
Thank you.
Don't eat too much.
Look. Jiro is eating well.
You're right.
Right?
No, no.
Your food is delicious.
Thank you.
Then, I'll eat less for you from now on.
Really?
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear that.
Then, can you eat all of them?
Maybe.
It can't be helped.
You're right.
Jiro eats well every meal.
I want to eat a little more.
Really?
You're kind.
You're right.
We've been together for a long time.
So, we don't make a lot of food.
You're right.
So, it's worth making food when a boy comes.
Jiro always eats anything.
Is there anything you don't like?
Something I don't like?
Yes.
Nothing in particular.
Really?
I was raised by my father so that I don't dislike anything.
It was a good education.
You don't force yourself to eat anything because he eats everything deliciously.
That's right.
He always eats deliciously.
If the seasoning is strong or light, tell me right away.
OK.
I like strong seasoning.
Really?
You're like your father.
Yes.
I always make strong seasoning.
You're right.
You like strong seasoning, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I think it goes well with you.
It's true.
I like strong seasoning.
It's important for a family.
So, you don't have to eat anymore?
I'm fine.
Really?
Thank you.
Shall we clean up?
Thank you for the meal.
You're welcome.
Let's clean up.
I'm glad.
I can't carry everything at once, so I'll do it little by little.
Thank you.
Thank you for the meal.
You're welcome.
Can I put chopsticks on it?
Yes, you can.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Wait a minute.
I found a big one.
What are you doing?
You're welcome.
My father will come back soon.
I'll take a video of you.
OK.
You like the food today, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Really?
Well, let's eat.
It's been five minutes, so Dad will be hungry.
Yes.
There seems a little overflow today.
Reina, tomorrow is breakfast, but
I ed the strawberry jam for breakfast.
Oh, really?
Would it be okay if you put mangarene in it?
No, not at all.
Can I just have whatever, please?
Whatever.
But I forgot to buy jam.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Mom, don't say that.
Can you not say that in front of Jiro?
Why not?
I mean,
you should be a good mom.
What are you talking about?
No, I'm not.
I'm not like that.
I mean, I've been with you for a long time.
I see.
By the way, do you want to eat something for dinner tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
I want to eat hamburgers,
but I'm on a diet.
Oh, tofu hamburgers.
I see.
By the way,
it's better to make tofu hamburgers without calories.
I see.
I'll find out how to make delicious tofu hamburgers later.
You're so kind.
You're a good mom.
I want you to eat like Jiro.
I'm sorry.
I thought it was normal to leave so much food,
but it's nice to have a son who eats so much.
I think so, too.
It's nice, isn't it?
Dad eats a lot, too.
I think so, too.
The dining table will be lively.
Men eat a lot, too.
I think so, too.
I'm glad.
Dad said he'd be home at this time,
but it's just the time for the drama I want to watch.
I see.
You're into something now, aren't you?
Yes.
Well, it's a hot topic now.
Many people are watching it at work.
I think it's like a drama for lunch.
I think so, too.
Dad, I've liked that kind of drama for a long time.
I don't know why, but it doesn't feel real.
I think so, too.
It's interesting to watch that kind of drama.
I think you'll understand it when you get married.
When did I talk about that?
It's a good thing.
But when you get married,
you have to be careful not to bully your mother-in-law.
I see.
My mother-in-law is an adult.
It's her experience, isn't it?
That's right.
That's why I get excited when I watch that kind of drama.
It's a good story.
As a heroine,
there is always a good thing.
I see.
My mother thought she should have said that.
In the drama, there's a story about revenge.
You're right.
That's the reality.
I'm getting old, though.
That's why I wanted you to be careful, too.
I see.
Yeah, while watching the drama.
Because your father changes the channel right away.
That's right. My father changes the channel right away.
Yeah, even though you haven't seen it.
What's wrong with you?
I have a runny nose.
Really? You might have a cold.
What should I do? Do you want something warm?
No, I'm fine.
By the way, where did you go?
I went back to my room.
Oh, really?
You went back to your room.
Were you sleepy?
Yeah, I was.
Be careful not to catch a cold.
Make yourself warm and go to bed.
Yeah.
Your father will be back soon.
You should take a bath soon.
Oh, yeah. He'll be back soon.
Yeah, he'll be back soon.
Oh, yeah.
He'll be back soon.
Yeah, he ate dinner.
Yeah, I'm full now.
Yeah.
Reina?
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Really?
Didn't you have a runny nose?
No, I'm fine.
You don't look well.
I'm sorry.
You don't eat a lot of rice.
Especially vegetables.
Yeah, vegetables.
Vegetables are low in calories.
Yeah.
You should eat more vegetables.
I'm fine.
Yeah, you should.
We'll have tofu hamburgers tomorrow.
Yeah.
Don't use too much oil.
You're on a diet, aren't you?
Yeah, I should eat as little as possible.
Yeah, I should eat more.
Oh, yeah.
I heard an interesting story.
I heard you're on a diet because of the scent.
The scent?
Yeah, I heard grapefruit is good for you.
What's that?
I've never heard of it.
Maybe you'll hear it someday.
I really like that kind of story.
Because my neighbor will tell me.
How about the scent of grapefruit in the bath?
Does it have any effect?
Maybe it doesn't.
Or maybe it does.
What if she finds out that I'm in the living room?
It's so cold.
Can I sit here?
Sure.
I'm sorry about earlier.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done that before my mom was here.
You're my father.
And it's not just about today.
I don't know when my mom or dad will find out that I'm in the living room.
Let's stop it.
I know.
I know, but...
You know, right?
But listen to me.
I'm stressed out.
I'm on a diet.
I have to be a good boy.
I told you that before.
I know.
But I want you to help me a little bit.
Well...
Do you think it's a good idea?
I've already helped you a little bit.
It's not just a little bit.
I've been helping you a lot lately.
I think you should stop.
Don't you want to help me anymore?
I don't want to help you anymore.
I don't want to do that in front of my mom or dad.
You can't?
I don't want to help you anymore.
I don't want my mom or dad to find out.
So you don't want to help me anymore?
I don't want to help you anymore.
Do you want to help me?
Okay.
How about here?
Here?
Yes.
How about here?
But my mom is nearby.
I can't open the door.
Are you okay?
I can't hear you.
Your mom won't come.
But...
She won't come?
No.
Are you okay?
Excuse me.
She's nearby.
I can't open the door.
You're under stress.
But my mom...
Can you help me?
I...
I'm really...
I want you to do it again.
Do it again?
I'm really...
I'm really hungry.
I...
I want you to do it again.
I can't open the door.
Do you want me to do it again?
I want you to do it again.
I...
Put your finger in.
I want you to do it again.
Let's grab this arm and give it a massage.
What should I do?
No.
What do you mean?
Don't go.
No, don't go.
Do you want me to do more?
Yes.
But...
My voice is getting louder.
What should I do?
I'll be quiet.
Yes.
No.
Shiro.
Can I come in?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Excuse me.
Shiro.
Were you there?
Yes.
I just had a massage.
I see.
You two got along well, didn't you?
Yes, we did.
I feel great.
My sister said she got tired.
Really?
Shiro is good at massaging.
You didn't force her, did you?
No, I didn't.
Here.
By the way, Shiro.
Yes.
You didn't take a bath yet, did you?
No.
I boiled a bath for you before you came back, so you can take a bath now.
Oh, thank you.
But...
What should I do?
I'll take a bath a little later.
Really?
Yes.
I have to do my homework.
Or...
Did you notice that I was massaging you?
No, I didn't.
Right, Shiro?
Really?
Then, you should take a bath, too.
Okay.
I got it.
Then, take a bath when you're done.
Okay.
I got it.
It's dangerous.
There isn't, really.
Is there any danger?
No, there isn't.
Because...
Look, there is a lot of aerial gas inside her body.
It's hot in here.
No...
Just hold on a moment.
APPLAUSE
Why?
What?
Huh? A little more.
A little more.
I don't want to breathe.
Come on.
A little more.
Come here.
It feels good.
A little more.
I don't want to breathe.
It feels good.
It's enough.
Huh?
I'll do it next.
Next?
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
I don't want to breathe.
Wait a minute.
It's getting bigger.
Does it feel good?
It's good.
It's scary.
Wait a minute.
It feels good.
It's scary.
I can't stand it.
Wait a minute.
It's like a scorpion.
It's scary.
Can you see the scorpion?
Yes.
Don't eat it.
It's dangerous.
You'll drop it.
Yes.
It's scary.
It's getting bigger.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm sweating a lot.
Are you all right?
I'll wipe it off with this.
Wait a minute.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'll wipe it off.
Wait a minute.
I'll wipe it off again.
I'll wipe it off.
It feels good.
It's getting harder.
It's hot.
I'll wipe it off.
It feels good.
I'll wipe it off again.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Give me more.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Did you sleep a lot?
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Wipe it off.
I'll wipe it off with your skirt.
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sweating a lot.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Thanks to you, I feel refreshed.
Thank you.
Okay.
But...
If you keep doing this, your mother won't be able to see you.
Hey.
It's me.
Okay.