It's been a while.
I think it was since the last neighborhood meeting.
I think so.
It was fun.
What do you usually do?
I usually clean the house.
What else do I do?
I watch TV.
You clean the house.
Here you are.
Thank you.
It tastes good, doesn't it?
This is a souvenir from Thailand.
You just mentioned about your part-time job.
You said that you bought an apartment.
The room was left over.
I have some space left in my room, so I was wondering what I should do.
And I'm doing a part-time job at a men's clothing store.
I used to work part-time at a men's clothing store.
So I thought I couldn't go there.
And the content of the men's clothing store is like this.
It's about this much for an hour.
But I don't have any experience.
But it's okay if you don't have any experience at all.
Because everyone starts with experience.
You can learn it really quickly.
I can remember.
Because it's really easy.
My husband probably doesn't accept this kind of thing.
But your husband is late for work, right?
Yes.
You can do it even if you don't have a husband for an hour or two.
Is it okay?
You can earn more than 5,000 yen in an hour.
Is that so?
Yes.
So I think it's really good.
But you don't have any children now, do you?
That's right.
Then you don't have to do housework.
I think it's a way to make money.
You need money, don't you?
That's right.
I don't know when your husband will collapse.
And you have to pay for his retirement.
So if you have time, you should do housework.
You can earn money and use it for your hobby or study.
I study three times a week.
Is that so?
You can go on a trip once a month.
You're cute and have a good style.
I think you'll get a lot of customers.
I'm sure you'll make money.
Can you tell me a convenient day for you?
A convenient day?
You can work on that day.
You can do it with a light heart.
I'll teach you how to do it.
If it doesn't work, you can quit right away.
I'll try.
It's easy.
You just need to massage it with oil.
Thank you.
You look good in that outfit.
Really? Thank you.
It's perfect.
You don't have to hide it.
I heard that all the people in this store are married.
Yes.
It's nice to be single.
Really?
I like being single.
I see.
Can I sleep with you?
Sure.
Which do you prefer?
I'll sleep with you.
Thank you.
Are you Mizuhara?
Yes, I am.
It's cute.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Go ahead.
I see.
You started this recently, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Can I put more pressure on that area?
Here?
That's good.
It's my first time today.
Is it your first time today?
Yes, it is.
I see.
I want you to teach me how to do it.
You don't know how to do it yet, do you?
No.
Can you put pressure on my buttocks?
Really?
Yes.
I'll put pressure on your buttocks.
Okay.
That's good.
It's good for your health.
It's good for your body.
I see.
Thank you.
Is this okay?
That's good.
Can you continue?
Okay.
I'm going to put pressure on your back.
Your back is relaxed.
Can you put pressure on my arms?
Okay.
Can you lean on me?
Lean forward.
Can I lean on you?
Yes, you can.
Open your body.
Lean forward.
Stretch your arms.
I see.
Yes, that's right.
Move your body forward a little bit.
Are you okay?
What?
It's just right.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Move your body forward a little bit.
Can you move your body to the other side?
To the other side?
Yes.
Move your body to the other side.
That's good.
Like this.
This.
What?
My hand.
Your hand.
Massage your hand.
Are you okay?
Yes, that's right.
Massage your hand.
That's good.
It feels good.
It's better to move your body like this.
That's good.
Like this.
What?
What's wrong?
I don't like it.
You don't like it?
I'm sorry.
I see.
Can you move your body to the other side?
To the other side?
Yes.
That's good.
Can you move your body to the other side?
Yes.
That's good.
Can you move your body to the other side?
You're amazing.
What?
Your boobs.
Don't you say that?
I do.
I see.
Which cup do you have?
It's J.
J?
J.
That's right.
It's my first time to come here.
Really?
Yes.
Do you have J cup at your husband's house?
That's right.
You're amazing.
Your boobs are too big.
No.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm just massaging your boobs.
I think I was lucky today.
I see.
It's not easy to touch the body of my husband.
I asked you to do that on the phone today.
What?
No, no, no.
You don't have to do that.
I'm paying for it.
I heard that there are a lot of men's restaurants like that these days.
It's not a big deal.
I think it's okay.
No, no, no.
I heard that there are a lot of men's restaurants like that these days.
I see.
I heard that your wife knows that.
I think it's okay.
Men will be happy.
It was cheap to do as much as I wanted.
No, no, no.
It's amazing.
You are sensitive when you have big boobs.
No, no, no.
Can I touch here?
You look comfortable.
No, no, no.
It's big.
It's amazing.
It's hard to believe that you have big boobs.
You have big boobs, don't you?
Yes.
You are a genius.
I didn't know that you had such a concept.
It's too erotic.
I can feel your nipples.
It's erotic.
It's okay.
It's not erotic.
It's comfortable, isn't it?
It's beautiful.
It's hard.
You like it, don't you?
Do you like being teased?
That's why you decided to work here, isn't it?
You have big nipples.
I didn't know that you had such a body.
It's a waste to touch your body.
It might be bad, but I'll give you a bonus.
Do you mind?
No, thank you.
I'll give you a bonus.
Come here.
You did such a thing.
Your nipples are too big.
It's amazing.
I'll give you a bonus.
It's delicious.
It's getting warmer.
I'll give you a bonus.
I'll give you a kiss.
You have big nipples.
It's better than the massage I gave you earlier.
I'll give you a bonus.
Can you come here?
Please turn this way.
It's delicious.
It's the best.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I'll give you a bonus.
Can you give me a good service?
I'll give you a good service.
I can't touch you with my hands.
Please raise your hips.
Please move forward.
I think it's just the right place.
Please move forward a little.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Please keep it a secret.
Is it okay?
I often do this at your store.
Yes, it's quite normal.
I'm going to lick it.
It's good.
I'm going to put it on like that.
I'm going to give it back to you.
It's a little bit.
It's good.
I'm going to put it on like this.
I'm going to put it on like that.
You're doing it too much.
I'm sorry.
I've been touched by you directly.
It's not good because I have pants on.
It feels good that you touch me directly.
I'm sorry I touched you.
This is amazing.
Gerry is having a hard time when gottail is round and hubby is holding onto a new toy.
This mark will be disappeared tomorrow.
What?
I feel some strange blockage on a nail.
Oh, my goodness.
I don't know what to do with myself.
I don't know what to do.
I feel sick.
I'm scared.
I'm sick.
I was surprised because it was so pleasant.
It's amazing.
You have a lot of skills.
It was pleasant.
I'll keep it a secret.
Oh, did you say that?
Yes.
That's good.
Then I'll keep it a secret.
I'll keep it a secret.
Is that okay?
I'm sorry.
Even if you get a rash,
I'll do this.
Can I do that?
Yes.
It's okay, right?
What's wrong with you?
That's a little...
You've come this far.
It's weird if you don't put it in.
It's a recent trend.
It's amazing.
I'll put it in.
I'm sorry.
It's wet.
I'll put it all the way in.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You have a very nice face.
Is this around here?
This?
It's easy to understand.
I'll rub it around here.
I'll rub it a little.
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
Did it go well?
It went well, didn't it?
I'm sorry.
You look so good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You like this kind of thing.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
How do you feel?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm sorry.
You look satisfied.
You can feel good now.
Master!
I hate you.
Yun-Nyang's calling.
Yun-Nyang...
What?
Cultivate my clothes for me.
Don't you know who you are?
That's awful
What happened with your leg?
I don't know
I am really sorry
this is terrible
Oh!
It's not enough.
Can I do more?
Yes.
Let's do more.
Lean back and do more.
Oh!
Are you comfortable?
I'm sleepy.
I love you.
That's the best.
It feels good.
I love you.
We're getting the hang of it.
It's getting better.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
Let's get rid of the leg from behind.
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
This is...
How about this?
I'm sorry.
I need energy!
Ban Ban is scary!
Mother Cry
Mother is crying
Doctor is crying
It's hot.
I'm scared.
It was the best.
It was very pleasant.
I didn't think I could go this far.
Thank you very much.
Can I show you again?
It's hot.
I'll come again.
I'll ask you again.
This is what it looks like.
It's about this much in 60 minutes.
It's going up.
I think I can earn more than 5,000 yen in an hour.
You can earn 5,000 yen in an hour.
I can do it once a week for an hour.
I can decide it myself.
You can do it freely.
I can go to work freely.
Surgery is easy.
It's super easy.
I can finish it in a few hours.
I just apply oil and massage.
It's that easy?
I don't touch it.
I'm not suspicious.
I can't touch it.
Don't you do it?
You're free in the afternoon, aren't you?
I'm free.
Let's save money.
Let's expand our hobbies.
Let's do it together.
Let's go on a trip together.
It's okay.
You're cute and stylish.
Minatsuki is doing it, too.
I'm doing it, too.
I'm doing it.
I'm doing it freely.
When are you free?
I'm free.
I'm going to practice.
I'm going to practice next Monday.
Are you free on Monday at about 1 p.m.?
I'm free.
Really?
Let's do it there.
If it doesn't suit you, you can quit.
Thank you for today.
Thank you.
You're so cute.
No, I'm not.
You're really cute.
I'm sorry.
What should I do next?
You've been here recently, haven't you?
It's my first time today.
Are you my first customer?
That's right.
I'm sorry.
No, not at all.
Thank you.
I'll give you a massage first.
I'll put a towel on you.
Thank you.
I'll give you a massage.
I'm sorry.
Can you put a weight on me?
You want me to put a weight on you?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Can you put a weight on me?
Does it hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Can you put more weight on me?
Can I put more weight on you?
Yes.
Like this?
That's good.
That's really good.
You're good at it.
No, I'm not.
I'm sorry.
It's my first time today.
I'm not good at it.
I'm sorry.
You're good at it.
Do you often have a man's estee?
No, I have a man's estee once in a while.
I see.
Have you ever had such a job before?
No.
I haven't had such a job before.
I see.
There are a lot of things I don't know.
What did you want to do?
I was invited by my husband.
I see.
I thought I'd give it a try.
Can you move your legs?
My legs?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Is it around your thighs?
Yes.
You can move your hips.
I see.
Can you move your hips?
I can.
You can put on some weight.
Why did you sit on my thighs?
I'm sorry.
You thought your husband was invited to his house?
I thought it'd be a good idea to work while I had some spare time.
Everyone says that's what they do for the living.
I see.
Can you move your legs?
My legs?
Is it around here?
How about the back of your neck?
Around here.
Thank you.
You do a lot of massages.
Yes, I heard that everyone does a lot of massages.
I was told that I can do a lot of massages.
I'm still thinking about going out sometimes.
How is it?
It's very good.
That's good.
You have a beautiful belly.
No, I don't.
Can you hold my calf and massage it?
Hold it?
Yes.
Like this?
Massage it well.
Yes.
I can't move my legs.
Can you do it well?
I don't know.
I think so.
Do you often do massages in the men's room?
Yes, I do it every week.
Can you do it more?
Yes, sorry.
That's good.
Can you push me harder?
Harder?
Can you massage both legs at the same time?
Both legs at the same time?
Yes, both legs.
Yes.
Thank you.
That's good.
Can you push me harder?
Yes.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
I want you to be closer to me.
Closer?
Yes.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Can I be closer to you?
Closer?
Yes.
Okay.
Can you be closer to me?
Yes.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
It's okay because the towel is hot.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'll massage your hands.
That's good.
Thank you.
It's hard to do it by myself, so can I help you?
Yes.
Can you hold my hand?
No, thank you.
It's easier if you support me with your body.
Okay.
Can you massage my arm?
Excuse me.
I'm massaging your arm.
I'm sorry, but I don't work here.
Is there a problem?
I'm massaging your arm.
I'm sorry, but I don't work here.
Can you massage my arm?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but I don't work here.
Is there a problem?
I pay an additional fee to the shopkeeper.
What do you mean?
My daughter is a newcomer.
I'll give her an extra fee.
I'll ask the shopkeeper if it's okay.
Do you need to pay?
What?
I don't know.
You already paid, so you don't have to pay.
I thought it would be okay because it's your clothes.
You don't have to pay.
Wait a minute.
I thought it was big, but it's comfortable to touch.
Okay.
Excuse me.
I want to give you a massage.
Can't I give you a massage here?
I'll give you a massage.
I'll give you a massage here.
Can't I give you a massage here?
Everyone is doing it.
It's not like that here.
Everyone is doing this kind of massage.
It's okay.
I'll give you a massage on your clothes.
You don't have to pay.
Wait a minute.
It's big, isn't it?
Show me more.
I'll give you a massage on your hands and knees.
That's enough.
I'm not done with the massage yet.
You can give me a massage later.
Later?
I want to give you a massage.
What do you mean?
What are you doing?
You can give me a massage here.
I can't give you a massage.
That's enough.
If I don't give you a massage, you'll get angry.
I won't say anything.
I'll give you a massage here.
You're very angry.
I'm really angry.
Your hands are very hard.
How do you feel?
I can't.
You have a beautiful body.
You're cute.
Do you like it here?
I don't like it here.
Don't you like it here?
Did you do it recently?
Are you married?
Don't you think it's a waste?
No.
I'll keep it a secret.
What are you talking about?
You have a beautiful body.
I can't.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
I can't.
Are you okay?
Can I look at you?
I can't.
I'll lick you.
Get up and look at me.
I can't.
Can I borrow your boobs?
Your boobs are messed up.
Can I have your right hand?
I can't.
Turn your back on me.
Please rub my butt.
I can't.
I want to rub your butt.
I can't stand it.
Can I kiss you?
I can't.
Please.
You haven't had sex recently, have you?
I can't.
Are you touching me?
Please rub my butt.
I can't.
Look at me.
Don't you want to see me?
Please.
I can't.
Please rub me harder.
Ma'am.
I'll pay you 10,000 yen more.
I'll let you stay here.
I can't do this.
Can you do me a favor?
I can't.
The others can do it.
You're getting hot.
Can I touch you?
I can't.
Try it.
It's hot.
I can't.
Can I touch you?
It's hot.
What's wrong?
Wait.
I can't.
It feels so good.
Wait.
Can you look at me?
I can't.
I'm sorry.
I made a lot of noise.
I think I can do a little more.
Can you go out with me?
I can't.
It's great to have a men's bathroom.
Men's bathroom is a place where men apply oil and massage.
That's all.
That's all?
Really.
I don't have to do anything like that.
Where do you do it?
There are some rooms left in the apartment I bought.
I do it in that room.
Are you alone?
I'm alone.
I'm alone, but it's okay.
I don't have many customers who are really creepy.
There are a lot of young people.
I have a neighbor, Minazuki.
I have about eight people.
Really?
I have about eight people, but they're all safe.
If anything happens, you can call me on my cell phone.
Really?
It's okay.
It's my apartment.
I've never had anything that dangerous.
That's right.
I'll try it.
I can remember it right away.
When is it open?
I think it's on weekdays.
That's right.
Is it open tomorrow afternoon?
Yes, it's open tomorrow.
Really?
I'll try it at about 1 p.m. tomorrow.
If it doesn't work, you can quit.
Let's decide on the next day of work at that time.
Yes, I understand.
That's right.
I heard that there are a lot of people in this men's room.
Are you really alone?
Yes, I am.
I envy your husband.
Do you think so?
You are very young.
That's right.
How old are you now?
I'm 24 years old.
You're so cute.
You have a good figure.
No, not at all.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm sorry.
Do you often go to men's rooms?
Occasionally.
It's my first time.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Really?
Thank you for today.
Thank you.
Can you lie down?
Lie down?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'll put a towel on you.
Okay.
Please tell me if it's too hard.
It's comfortable.
Really?
Do you do this for training?
Yes, I do.
It's good.
I've been doing this for a long time.
Thank you.
It's good.
I've been doing a lot of desk work lately.
My back hurts.
Your back?
Yes, my back and back.
It's hard, isn't it?
That's right.
It's good.
You have a good sense of strength.
Really?
It's my first time.
You have a good sense of strength.
I'm relieved.
You can do it harder.
A little more?
I think it's easier for you to put more strength.
More strength?
Yes.
I want you to put more strength on my body.
Then you'll gain weight.
Is that okay?
No problem.
Okay.
You don't have to worry about it.
Excuse me.
Okay.
How is your body?
Is it like this?
That's right.
I sometimes do training.
It's a deadlift.
I've been training my lower back.
Your lower back?
That's right.
My lower back.
My lower back and shoulders.
I have a lot of muscles on my arms.
Arms?
Can you touch my arms?
I have a lot of muscles on my arms.
Do you do that?
Yes.
I have a lot of muscles on my arms.
I want you to touch my arms.
Do you want me to?
Yes.
That's right.
I have a lot of muscles around here.
Okay.
Can you touch my wrists?
Wrists?
Around my wrists.
Around here?
I have a lot of muscles on my wrists.
I want you to touch my wrists.
That's good.
Can you massage my muscles with oil?
Oil?
Yes.
I'll turn it over.
This feels good.
Does it feel good?
Does it?
Yes.
That's good.
Can you massage my lower back?
Yes.
That's good.
Do you have a lot of muscles on your legs?
That's right.
That's good.
I have a lot of muscles around here.
On your legs?
Yes.
That's good.
I want you to massage my lower back.
Around here?
That's right.
I want you to massage my lower back.
I heard that lymphatic drainage is concentrated in this area.
It feels good to be massaged here.
I want you to massage my buttocks and my crotch.
Around here?
Yes.
I want you to massage my buttocks and my crotch.
Around here?
Yes.
It feels good.
I want you to massage my forearms.
Forearms?
Yes.
I want you to massage my forearms.
Okay.
I want you to massage my whole body.
I want you to massage my scapula.
Here?
Yes.
It feels good.
I want you to massage my upper body.
Okay.
Upper body?
Where should I massage?
Around here.
Okay.
It's hard for you, isn't it?
I want you to massage my whole body.
Okay.
It feels good.
I want you to massage my upper body.
Upper body?
Yes.
It's hard for you, isn't it?
I want you to massage my upper body.
Okay.
Around here.
Is your arm stiff?
Yes.
It's hard for you, isn't it?
I want you to massage my neck.
It's okay.
It's hard for you, isn't it?
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
You're amazing.
If you keep doing this, your shoulders will get stiff.
I didn't ask you.
What did you say?
I didn't ask you not to touch me.
No.
A woman told me not to touch you at all.
What?
You're a new girl.
So, please touch me as much as you want.
What?
A woman told me not to touch you.
You're amazing.
You're big.
Please touch me as much as you want.
It's hot.
You're amazing.
You're sexy.
It's hot.
My lower body is stiff.
You're amazing.
It's hard for you, isn't it?
I'll show you.
You're beautiful.
You have a beautiful neck.
I'm in trouble.
I was told not to touch you.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Look over there.
It's hot.
You're amazing.
You have a beautiful body.
I can't stand it anymore.
You're looking at me.
It's okay, isn't it?
Just a little.
It's hot.
Put your tongue out.
Are you okay?
It's hot.
You're amazing.
Can you feel the heat?
It's a little dirty here.
It's hard to get dirty here.
It's okay, isn't it?
It's hot.
Don't look at me like that.
I won't hide it.
It's a little wet here.
Why are you so wet?
It's hot.
You're so wet.
Let me see your face.
It's hot.
Open your legs.
It's tied up.
It's hot.
It's a little rough here.
What's wrong with you?
It's hot.
Open your legs.
You're going to get a burn.
It's so wet.
It's hot.
It's a little wet here.
I know.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's the best.
Use your hands.
It's hot.
Your mouth feels so good.
You have a lot of teeth.
It's hot.
It smells good.
It feels good.
I'm going to drop my wife here.
It's the best.
I have a hard jaw.
Can I put this in your mouth?
I'll keep it a secret.
I'll pay for it.
I'm going to sleep.
I feel so good.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
ah ah ah ah ah
Pen
Hmm
me
It's over.
You...
you hurt me...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Ah ah
dancing
with
my
husband
postpone
hehe
vious
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
no
Yeah Yeah amore
yeah yeah
me
Ouch!
I was heavy
Heave-ho
Massage your butt
Oh, woah
Hey...
Mokichi...
Hey..
Eh, mum
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
jobbar
Ouch...
This is confirmed.
Doctor...
...I'd like to recover quickly.
I'm going to sleep.
I feel great.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
.
I'm worried because the
number is not collected yet , but
please look near me,
touch this a little
I haven't settled down at all yet, so it's too attractive, so I'll make it a little more comfortable.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's too attractive, isn't it?
Do you always do this?
I haven't settled down at all yet, so it's too attractive, so I'll make it a little more comfortable.
It was really good, including the massage, so can I ask you to come every week?
Every week?
Yes.
Can I?
Then I'll come every week.
I'm looking forward to it.
What do you do in the afternoon?
I don't do anything in particular.
Oh, really?
I think it's a waste of time, so I don't think it's a waste of time.
I don't know much about men's esthetics.
You say esthetics, but you massage your husband easily, right?
Occasionally.
It's like massaging your husband, and you just apply oil and massage it, so you can remember it in a short time.
Why don't you try it, too?
Can I do it?
Yes, you can.
I invited my neighbors' wives.
How many?
Is that so?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7 people.
That many?
My wives are doing it.
You're doing it that much?
Yes, everyone is making money.
My shop never has a smelly old man.
Is that so?
There are a lot of young people.
Some people just talk and it's over.
Is that so?
Yes, everyone is having fun.
It's a good story, isn't it?
I'm going to teach you how to do it.
Is that so?
It's very easy.
I see.
When are you free next week?
Next week?
How about Wednesday?
You're free, right?
You don't have kids, right?
You're going to work, right?
Yes.
You don't have to do a lot of housework.
I see.
Come to my house next Wednesday.
I'll teach you how to do it.
Then, I'll decide on your next day of work.
Are you a new employee?
Yes, I am.
It's my first day.
You're not used to it, are you?
I'm sorry.
You'll get used to it as you practice.
I see.
You don't have to use the practice table at all.
But...
It's strange that you can do it so well at first.
That's right.
It's strange, isn't it?
Yes.
Well, I hope you can do it easily.
Thank you.
I hope you can do it easily.
Okay.
Then, I'll give you a massage.
Please stand on your back.
Okay.
Excuse me.
I'll give you a massage.
Okay.
You're good at it.
Really?
Yes.
You've never done it before, have you?
No.
You're good at it.
Thank you.
It's relaxing, isn't it?
Are you okay now?
Yes.
I hope you can do it easily.
It feels good.
Does it?
Well...
Can you massage my lower back?
Your lower back?
Yes.
Okay.
Around here?
Yes.
It's good.
It feels good.
That's good.
Doesn't it hurt?
No.
If you do it like this, it doesn't hurt at all.
Okay.
Please let me know if you need anything.
Thank you.
Your lower back feels good.
Is it good?
Yes, it's relaxing.
Really?
Next.
Can you massage my thighs?
Your thighs?
I'm sorry.
It's not thighs.
It's calves.
Where are the calves?
It's around the soles of the feet.
I see.
I usually get a masseuse to do that.
Is that so?
Yes.
Here?
Please.
How is it?
It's a little different.
A little more?
Yes.
It's easy to shift, isn't it?
It's small, isn't it?
Yes.
It's like this.
It's really big.
Yes.
It's amazing.
You're beautiful, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
You're really cute.
Thank you.
Are you married?
Yes.
How old are you?
I'm 30 years old.
Are you 30 years old?
Yes.
I thought you were younger.
Is that so?
I thought you were 35 years older than me.
Are you the same age as your husband?
Yes.
Do you get along with him?
I think we get along normally.
Normally?
How old are you?
What?
Do you have a boyfriend?
No, I don't.
I see.
I'm 28 years old.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Yes, I do.
What do you mean?
I don't mean that.
Excuse me.
Can you move a little to the center?
Around here.
Like this.
This is the first time you've had a menstrual cramp.
Around here.
Menstrual cramps are about this big.
Like this?
Yes, like this.
It's hard to tell at first.
Can you use an oil?
An oil?
Apply it around your chest.
Okay.
Around here?
Yes.
Can I?
Like this?
Yes.
Now, this side.
Isn't it hard?
No.
Yes, like this.
Can you move your chest like this?
Yes.
It looks like a menstrual cramp.
A little more.
Around here?
Yes, like this.
Like this?
Yes, around here.
Okay.
It feels good.
You can touch your nipples.
Like this?
Can you touch a little more?
A little more?
Yes.
It feels good.
Your nipples are amazing.
They are big.
Just a little more.
You may be surprised at first.
Keep massaging.
Just a little more.
Your nipples are big.
You have a good style.
How big are your nipples?
I can't touch them.
I heard that you can touch your nipples as much as you want.
Is that so?
I massaged your nipples.
Your nipples are amazing.
Your nipples are soft.
What's going on with your nipples?
That's...
Your nipples are about to come off.
Please stop.
Your nipples are amazing.
Your nipples are very big.
Is that all right?
Your nipples are about to come off.
Your nipples are sensitive.
That's not what I mean.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Your nipples are amazing.
Please show me more of your nipples.
Your nipples are very big.
Your nipples are very heavy.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Your nipples are very sensitive.
Your nipples are amazing.
I'll clean your nipples.
Your nipples are very beautiful.
Can I lick your nipples?
I'm sorry to bother you.
Your nipples are very beautiful.
I'll pay extra for your nipples.
I'm sorry to bother you.
It's a waste to leave your nipples like this.
Is it true?
No.
I'm about to die.
Can I strip?
But...
I'm fine.
I'll give you an extra dose.
You have a sensitive skin.
I'm fine.
You have a very nasty smell.
Have you ever done it with your husband?
You have a very sensitive skin.
It's a waste to have such a nice boob.
I'm fine.
You have a beautiful butt.
Let me see your butt.
It's not that beautiful.
It's very smooth.
I'm sorry.
Your butt is very beautiful.
Do you have a sensitive butt?
It's like this.
It's very soft.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
You have a very beautiful butt.
Let me see your butt.
I'll give you an extra dose.
I'm fine.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
Do you have a bad smell?
It's very hot.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
You have a good style.
You have a good sense of smell.
You have a very good sense of smell.
Let me see your butt.
I'll give you an extra dose.
I'm sorry.
It's very hot.
I can't do that.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It's very hot.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Wait a minute.
I'll give you an extra dose.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
I can't do that.
It's easy to breathe.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
Let's take this off.
It's amazing.
Let me see your butt.
Don't look at me.
It's amazing.
It's shiny.
Let's take this off.
It's making a sound.
Are you upset?
No.
It's very shiny.
You're pulling a string.
Wait a minute.
It's amazing.
It's making a sound.
You like this, don't you?
No.
I'll give you an extra dose.
I can't do that.
It's amazing.
It's wet.
I'll give you an extra dose.
Does it feel good?
No.
Here.
You're pulling a string.
Does it feel good?
No.
I'll give you an extra dose.
Take your time.
Here.
I can't do that.
I'll give you an extra dose.
It's amazing.
I can't do that.
Did something come out?
I'm sorry.
It's wet.
Let's do it again.
It's amazing.
There's a lot of stuff coming out.
Come here.
It's amazing.
Your hands are soft.
It feels really good.
Please lick my hands.
Do I lick your hands?
Yes.
Just a little bit.
Okay.
It's amazing.
It feels really good.
Like this?
Just a little bit.
Can you add a little more?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It feels really good.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
You're really good at this.
It feels really good.
I can't touch your hands.
Can you put your hands on my chest?
I can't put my hands on your chest.
Please put your hands on my chest.
It's amazing.
Your breasts are soft.
It feels really good.
Can you drool a little?
Drool?
It's amazing.
It feels really good.
I can't do anything.
It's amazing.
I've never felt this way before.
I can't do this.
It's amazing.
I'm a little sleepy.
It feels really good.
I've never felt this way before.
Is that so?
Is it your first time?
It's my first time.
I can't do anything.
I can't do this.
Can I put my hands on your chest?
It's amazing.
What is this?
I can't do this.
It's amazing.
Oh, you are making a face.
Look at me.
I can't see anything but my beloved Sasaki!
Play a little more, will you?
I don't see you at all.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I will pull you up little by little.
Mhmm
Mmm
Mm
Mhmm
Okay
Mmm
Mhmm
Aaaah!
I lost quite a bit of weight.
Oh, I lost some weight.
Right.
My stomach is a little challenge.
Let's see if this stretchcan will work.
Let's do it!
Oh, oh, oh brushing
Oh I'm
good
Ah ah ah
Oh
It's working.
I can't stop moving.
Sir?
Let's get off soon.
Just a minute.
Sir?
Hold me!
Huh?
You fought from a distance.
Ahhhh
Ahhh
Ahh
Ahh, it feels good
Ah
Good
Hmm
Ah
I'm tired
Hmm
Ah
Pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant, pant,
pant, pant, pant , pant, pant, pant, the
first
time Pe Cha
Wooaa bookstore
Oh, my...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, my
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Yeah, it's in the back
Ah!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Wow
Yeah
Ah ah ah
Hmm
It felt so good.
I didn't think I'd be doing this.
I'm sorry.
Please don't tell the store.
Of course.
Can I do it again when I come back?
I won't tell the store.
Okay.
Can I?
Yes.
I'll do it again.
Okay.