Hello, I'm Ishikawa from Kajidai High School. Nice to meet you.
Oh, nice to meet you.
Did something happen?
It's my first time to ask for a service from Kajidai High School.
Oh, I see.
I thought an old lady would come.
Oh, but it's my second year.
I'm sorry if there's anything I can do.
Please tell me.
Oh, I see.
First of all, can I clean up the room?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I did my back at work.
Then, please take your time.
Is it okay? This posture is a little easier.
Please take your time.
I'm sorry.
Please fold your clothes and put them in this area.
Oh, I see.
The price is more reasonable than I expected.
Oh, really?
Oh, yes.
I thought I could do it.
I should have asked for it earlier.
Oh, I see.
Oh, but it's great.
You're good at folding clothes.
Oh, really?
Thank you very much.
When you fold T-shirts, they look beautiful.
Oh, I see.
Did you pay attention to how to fold them?
No, I didn't.
I always mess them up.
Is it okay if I look for magazines in this area?
Oh, I see.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You don't have to worry about it at all.
When I go to a girl's house, there are magazines like this.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You don't have to worry about it at all.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Is it okay to fold T-shirts like this?
Oh, I see.
Thank you very much.
Where should I throw the garbage?
Garbage?
Oh, here.
Oh, there is a garbage bag.
Is it okay to throw it away here?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
When did you clean up recently?
I was so busy that I couldn't do it at all.
And my vacuum cleaner just broke.
Oh, I see.
I thought I had to buy a new one, but it ended up like this.
Then, I'll clean this area, too.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
For example, like this.
If you think it's good, can you make a name for it?
Oh, I can.
Like this.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, there's a lot of dust.
Can you see it?
What's wrong?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I could see it very well.
I'm sorry.
If I move suddenly, my back hurts.
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, it's not like that.
It's hard for men, isn't it?
It hurts my back.
Hey.
Can I do something about that, too?
What?
What do you mean?
Because my back hurts.
No, it's not like that.
I'm sorry.
I'm really embarrassed.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
No, it's not like that.
You're a housewife, aren't you?
Yes.
But it's not like that.
I'm really embarrassed.
Hey.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that my back hurts because I'm on duty.
Yes.
Can you come here?
Oh, yes.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
Yes.
Where should I put it?
You can put it around here.
Is it okay?
Is it okay to continue?
Oh, yes.
I understand.
Is it okay to be strong?
Is it better to be stronger?
Is it better to be gentle?
No, I'm fine now.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Please tell me if there's anything like speed or strength.
Well...
Yes.
I don't mind if you tell me if you can't do it.
For example...
Can you tell me if you can't do it?
Speed?
Yes.
Oh, it's okay.
It's okay if it's a little.
Yes.
I'll try again.
Is it like this?
Yes.
Oh, what?
What?
Well...
It's big, isn't it?
No.
I'm sorry.
I really want to do it with my mouth, but I haven't finished cleaning this area yet.
The room is dirty.
No, I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
Was it stinky?
No, it felt good.
I'm sorry.
Isn't it a little dirty?
Oh, it's okay.
Don't you want it?
Oh, I'd like to say it's soft, but it's a little more than before.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
Did you feel refreshed?
Yes.
I'll clean this area, too.
I'm sorry.
No, it felt really good.
I've got a lot of work to do.
You've got a lot of work to do.
I'll clean this area, too.
Yes.
Tissue.
I'm sorry.
Then I'll continue.
Yes.
This is...
Where's the fire?
Do you have a service line to cook?
I can only cook simple dishes.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm glad to hear that.
Is your waist okay?
Oh, it hurts.
I'm lying on your side.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was wondering where the plates and seasonings were.
I'm sorry.
Doesn't it hurt?
It's easier to stand up than to lie down.
It's a little different depending on the situation.
Do you have pepper?
Well...
Actually, I'm a little embarrassed.
I haven't been able to cook at all.
Well, that's about it.
I'd like to buy it, but I can't find it anywhere.
Oh, here it is.
I found it.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Can I ask you to buy something in advance?
Yes.
You can buy it in advance.
What should I do when I ask you to buy something in advance?
Do you mean dishes?
Yes.
Well...
I'm sorry.
I can only buy what's on the plate.
Then, I'll wash them.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
Is this soup?
Yes.
Do you like tomatoes?
Yes, I do.
It looks delicious.
Is it done?
Can I taste it?
Oh, yes.
Then, I'll eat it.
Are you all right?
I'll wipe it off.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
Do you want me to wipe your hands?
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I feel like a child.
Well...
What should I do?
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to wipe your hands again?
It was delicious.
I'm glad.
You have a lot of friends.
You have a lot of friends, don't you?
Do I?
I can't meet them all.
But I feel so good.
Don't you have a girlfriend?
You look so happy.
I don't have a girlfriend now.
Do you lick me, too?
It's delicious.
I'm afraid my voice is going to come out.
Are you sure?
I'm sorry.
You have a lot of hair.
Do you feel refreshed?
I feel refreshed now.
But I still have a lot of hair.
I still have a lot of hair.
Do you want to do more?
Yes.
Don't you have a backache?
I'm fine now.
Is this okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I feel so good when I'm kissed.
Do you like this?
I like it.
I'm sorry.
Don't touch me.
I'll throw it away.
Can I touch you?
You are very gentle when I touch you.
I feel very good.
I think it's better to touch your ears.
Oh, my ears?
What?
Oh, I feel good.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
I want to kiss you one more time.
Are you ready?
I'm sorry.
I want to lick you.
Don't you feel pain in your waist?
If I lean on you too much, it hurts.
Even if I lean on you, it doesn't change.
I'm sorry.
I want to lick you.
Can I lick you?
Yes.
I want to lick you.
It hurts.
What should I do?
Can I lick you?
Can I?
Are you sure?
Yes.
I want to lick you.
I'm sorry.
Don't you feel pain in your waist?
Don't push yourself too much.
Your waist is big, so it feels good enough.
How do you feel?
It feels so good that my waist hurts.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It feels so good.
I'll do my best.
Please let me go.
It hurts.
I feel refreshed.
But I can't stop it yet.
Can I do it some more?
I let you lick my back.
I lick you.
If it's impossible...
It doesn't matter.
I'm sorry I didn't take a bath.
It's okay.
You are kind.
I'm sorry I didn't take a bath.
It feels good.
Do you want to take a bath?
My waist hurts, so I'll move.
Please.
Can I sleep?
It feels good.
Do you want to sleep here?
I'm sorry I didn't take a bath.
It feels good.
Does your waist hurt?
It doesn't hurt at all.
Can I move?
Yes.
It feels good.
It doesn't hurt at all.
I'm sorry I didn't take a bath.
Can I move?
Yes.
It feels good.
I'm sorry I didn't take a bath.
Can I move?
It's hot.
I'm sorry I didn't take a bath.
Please call me again.
I'll come to clean up anytime.
I'll call you.
Thank you.
Yes.
Hello.
I'm Ayase.
Are you a housewife?
Yes.
Didn't you ask for it?
I didn't ask for it.
Are you a mother?
Yes.
Can I come in?
I'm sorry.
Probably my mother called me.
It's not bad.
Mother said that you should do Christmas Eve sooner, so only water police should be done in your room and later.
Can I clean up?
Can you wait a moment?
Mr. Kitamura, you can take your time.
Let's get started.
Is this toilet mat washable?
Yes, it's washable.
Really?
I'm going to turn the washing machine.
I'm going to wash the slippers, too.
I'm going to borrow the washing machine.
Can I turn on the light?
Yes, you can.
I'm going to turn on the light.
You haven't washed the toilet towel for a while, have you?
Can I wash this, too?
Can I turn on the light?
Yes, you can.
You're so close to me.
What's the matter?
I don't know what to say.
Can I help you?
Don't worry.
I'll ask you if I don't know what to say.
Take your time.
Don't worry.
I'm going to take off my mask.
I'm sorry.
It's hot, so can I take off my mask?
It's hot.
It's hot today, isn't it?
Oh, no.
Mr. Kitamura.
What's the matter?
Did you want something?
Well...
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm not that young, though.
You've grown up.
I'm sorry.
I've grown up.
You've grown up.
You've been taking care of yourself.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I'm not that young, though.
I didn't expect you to react like that to me.
I'm glad to hear that.
Are you excited?
No, I'm not.
I haven't seen a woman for a long time.
If you don't mind, can I help you?
Help?
I'm going to clean your room.
If you don't mind.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Come here.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Are you sure?
Can I clean your room?
I don't mind.
I'm sorry.
Can I clean your room?
You've grown up a lot.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Please forgive me.
Please tell me your strength and speed.
Is this okay?
I feel better if I do it quickly.
I see.
Is this okay?
You're amazing.
I'm sorry.
Is this okay?
I can't help it.
You've grown up a lot.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Do you feel better if I do it quickly?
I feel better if I do it quickly.
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
You're amazing.
You've grown up a lot.
I'm sorry.
I don't mind.
You're amazing.
Do you feel better?
I'm sorry to bother you.
I don't mind.
I'll flush the toilet.
The kitchen is amazing.
Do you eat this fried chicken now?
No, I don't eat it now.
When did you buy it?
Two or three days ago.
I'll put it in the fridge.
Do you still drink this coffee?
Yes, I do.
I'll put it in the fridge.
What time do you eat this?
The expiration date of this rice will expire soon.
I'll eat it soon.
You'll eat it soon.
There are a lot of dishes.
Don't you wash the dishes?
I was going to wash them.
I see.
You do your homework at the end of the summer vacation.
I want to do it again.
I was surprised.
What's wrong with you?
Do you need help?
No, I'm fine.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You're amazing.
You said you felt better.
Did you get bigger again?
I can't let go of your hand.
I'm sorry, but I can't use my hands now.
If you don't mind, you can put your hands behind your back.
From behind.
Can I?
Yes, you can.
Really?
Can I really do this?
Yes, you can.
I have a lot of things to do, so I can't do anything.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to do.
What?
I'll put it in.
Okay.
If I do it too hard, I can't wash it.
You said you could put it in.
That's right.
Wait a minute.
I can't wash it.
I'll do it slowly.
Wait a minute.
I can't wash it.
I spilled it on the floor.
It's clean now.
I'll clean here, too.
Please.
I'm going to clean up Kitamura-san's room.
Yes, please.
I'm going to clean up this area.
I can't clean up this room.
I'm sorry.
I want to clean up this room.
Can you take this off?
I have no choice.
I want to clean up this room.
Can I wear this T-shirt in this basket?
Yes, you can.
I want to clean up this room.
It's hot.
I can't clean up this room.
It's heavy.
It's hot.
Why do you put a glass here?
I can't wear this T-shirt.
It's hot.
Wait a minute.
I can't wear this T-shirt.
It's wet.
I have to clean up this room.
I can't wear this T-shirt.
Wait a minute.
I haven't finished folding this T-shirt.
I can't wear this T-shirt.
Wait a minute.
I have to wash this later.
I have to remove this sheet.
I can't move if I put it in too much.
Wait a minute.
I can't move.
I'm sorry.
I can't clean up.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I have to clean up.
Time is running out.
I'll take off the cover of the bed.
I'll put this on the washing machine later.
Is this sleeping?
I may use it for something.
I'll use it for something.
There is a pillow in such a place.
Is this the one that I broke the washing machine?
I'll use it for something.
Is this okay?
I'm sleepy.
Yeah, yeah...
Don't wake me first.
Don't rip myNeck off.
Go!
Okay then.
Oh~~
I see.
Please wait a little.
Please make yourself soft again.
Please wait.
Don't go there.
Wait a minute.
I'll be back in a minute.
Don't go there.
Wait a minute.
I'll be back in a minute.
It's too early.
Wait a minute.
Don't go there.
I'll be back in a minute.
It's too early.
I have to wipe it again.
I've finished cleaning up.
Do you feel refreshed?
Not yet.
Not yet?
Don't you feel refreshed?
I can't help it.
I'll finish cleaning up.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good in the back or in the front?
I feel good in the back.
Do you feel good in the back?
How about speed?
I feel good.
I can't help it.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
I can't help it.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
I can't help it.
How do you feel?
A lot of white stuff came out.
I feel good.
I'm glad.
I can't help it.
I feel good.
I cleaned it up.
Hitamura-san, come here.
Look at me.
I feel good.
I can't help it.
How do you feel?
It's hard.
I feel good.
Hitamura-san, stay like that.
It's refreshing.
How do you feel?
I can't help it.
I feel good.
It's still hot.
I can't help it.
I feel good.
I have to clean it up.
I'm glad.
I have to clean up this mess.
My mom will come back tomorrow.
I got it, mom.
If you need more cleaning supplies, I'll pay you.
I brought 10,000 yen here.
If you sleep here,
there is a key in the box upstairs.
Please use it for your room.
Just go away somehow.
Shut up.
Don't be lazy.
You can do it alone.
I can't.
You don't have to do it.
I really can't do anything.
Please look forward to it.
I got it.
Please take a call.
Please say hello.
OK.
I'm telling you to say hello.
Hello.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry.
I have to go out.
I can't come back today.
I'm sorry.
If you can do it as much as you can,
I can't do anything.
No problem.
Please leave it to me.
Thank you very much.
Do it properly.
Shut up.
I can't do it.
I'm Daiko Kaji.
I'm Kitayama.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
It's young.
It's very beautiful.
I can see the valley.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'm going to start cleaning.
Yes.
Can I mess up around here?
Yes, please.
This magazine...
Yes.
Can I?
All right.
Did you wash these clothes?
Yes, I did.
I didn't wash them.
Can I?
Yes, please.
It's dirty there.
Yes.
By the way,
how old are you?
I'm 29 years old.
What?
29 years old?
I can't see you at all.
No, I'm not.
I thought you were very young.
I can't see you at all.
Thank you.
By the way, I'm 32 years old.
Oh, I see.
You're young.
Thank you.
It's just right.
Can I put this magazine on this table?
Yes, please.
Can I put the trash in the trash can?
You're very good at it.
No, I'm not.
Do you do anything?
I don't do anything now.
Oh, I see.
You're good at it.
Thank you.
My mom is very good at it.
No, I'm not.
You're very good at it.
Thank you.
Can I put the trash in the trash can?
Yes, please.
I'm 29 years old.
Thank you.
I'm sorry I got dirty.
No, it's okay.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
By the way, do you have a day off?
I don't have a day off.
I've been drinking a lot lately.
Do you like alcohol?
Yes, I do.
I like it, too.
Really?
What do you drink?
I drink beer.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Do you drink a lot?
I drink a lot.
I drink a lot, too.
I'm surprised.
What kind of food do you like?
I've been into Ikebukuro lately.
Ikebukuro?
That's a strange name.
I'll look it up.
There are many good restaurants.
Oh, my God.
What's the result of drinking?
What do you drink?
If you drink too much alcohol, you become addicted to it.
You become addicted to alcohol, right?
Do you become addicted to alcohol?
I don't drink alcohol unless I know it.
If so, I wouldn't drink it.
Then, I'm the right person for you.
Is that so?
I'm often called a gentleman.
I want to drink with you.
I don't know what to do.
Why don't you?
There are a lot of people like this.
There are a lot of old ladies.
That's right.
You are still young.
Am I young?
You are young.
By the way, do you have a boyfriend?
I don't have a boyfriend.
You must have a boyfriend.
I broke up with my boyfriend when I was doing this job.
He was a married man.
Was he married?
That's right.
That's how it was.
But I had a bad point.
So I thought I couldn't help it.
What's wrong?
I was playing a little.
I had a backache.
Did you have a backache?
That's right.
That's surprising.
I didn't think so.
Is that true?
You are popular.
That's not true.
Do you have a boyfriend now?
I don't have a boyfriend.
I see.
How long have you not had a boyfriend?
It's been about three years since I started this job.
You don't have a boyfriend for a long time.
That's right.
I don't have a boyfriend for a long time.
Aren't you lonely?
That's right.
I'm lonely, too.
I understand.
That's right.
You are alone on your day off.
Do you have a place you want to go to?
I want to go on a date at the aquarium.
I like the aquarium.
I like animals.
Is that so?
You like animals.
That's right.
Do you like fish?
I like fish.
It's a good date.
That's right.
I want to go on a date.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
Please tell me.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't look at me.
I don't know what to do.
I'm working.
Do you want me to do something?
I'm still working.
Can I do it while I'm working?
What are you doing?
I'll do something.
What's wrong with you?
Please take it off.
What are you doing?
Please tell me how strong and fast you are.
I haven't cleaned this side yet.
Can I clean this side?
How strong do you want me to be?
Is this a fire?
I see.
I was taking care of a patient.
I wanted to do something for a patient.
I see.
Excuse me.
It's a fire.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Did you feel better?
Thank you.
I'm glad you're here.
Your t-shirt.
Oh, my t-shirt.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm going to make something.
Oh, okay.
How much do you want?
Okay.
Mr. Murakami.
You can't cook, Mr. Murakami.
It's almost done.
I was surprised.
It smells good.
What's wrong?
Do you know tomato?
I thought it was curry.
I was surprised.
It smells good, doesn't it?
It looks delicious.
Does it look delicious?
It smells good, doesn't it?
It looks delicious.
It's almost done.
Again?
What's wrong?
It smells like curry.
I thought it smelled good.
It's dangerous.
It's almost done.
Can't you wait?
I can't.
I'm in trouble.
I can't let go of your hand.
Can I make it?
Okay.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's hot.
It's not enough.
It's delicious.
It's hot.
How is it?
It's the best.
It's delicious.
I'm in trouble.
It's in the curry.
Can I eat this?
It's okay.
Is it delicious?
It's good for your mouth.
Do you feel better?
Do you want more?
I can't stop eating.
But, the rice is ready.
Don't you want to eat?
I want to eat you first.
I don't know what to do.
Will you eat after that?
Yes, of course.
Can I?
As you like.
Okay.
You can do that.
Thank you.
Can I?
You have a good style.
Thank you.
It's good for your eyes and hands.
It's wonderful.
You have a good style.
It smells good.
It's delicious.
You have a good style.
Thank you.
I knew you had a good style.
I knew it.
I'm hungry.
Did you find me?
Can I?
You are beautiful.
I'll eat this.
It's delicious.
Please sit down.
You have a good style.
It's wonderful.
It smells good.
You have a good style.
Can I smell it?
Please clean my face.
I'll clean your face.
It's delicious.
You have a good style.
Can I sit down?
It's very hot.
It's hot.
Did you leave already?
You have a good style.
Can I see you?
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Look at me.
You have a good style.
How do you feel?
You have a stain on your face.
I feel good.
I have a stain on my face.
You have a good sound.
What's wrong?
You have a bad voice.
I like that.
What's wrong?
Do you like this?
I like this more.
I feel good.
Do you like this?
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
You have a stain on your face.
Do you like this?
Is that so?
That's not true.
Why do you have a stain on your face?
That's amazing.
Do you like this?
You have a good voice.
That's not true.
Do you like this?
You have a stain on your face.
Get off the chair.
Come here.
It's very hot.
You have a stain on your face.
Do you like this?
That's amazing.
You have a stain on your face.
Do you like this?
That's amazing.
You have a stain on your face.
Do you like this?
It's delicious, isn't it?
Can I eat it?
I'm sorry.
It's delicious, isn't it?
I'm going to go again.
You're really good at it.
Like this.
I'm going to drink it.
I'm going to go again.
Mr. Murakami, don't do that.
Did you go?
I went.
Are you excited again?
It's delicious, isn't it?
I'm going to go again.
I'm going to drink it.
It's delicious, isn't it?
I'm going to go again.
It's refreshing.
Do you like it?
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's hard all the time.
Ah
Ah, no, not yet
Touch here
How is it?
Not yet
Use your mouth
Ah
Ah...
Mmm...
It's so good.
I'll take it off.
Don't lick it.
Here, take this.
Take this.
Ah...
Mmm...
It's the best.
Ah...
Here.
Mmm...
Until it's gone.
Ah, that's it.
Ah...
Ah, good.
You listen to everything I say.
Mmm...
Look this way.
Ah, I want to play with you.
Ah...
Mmm...
Ah, go deeper.
Ah, that's it.
Ah...
Ah, good.
That's a wonderful smile.
Do you like it?
I love it.
OK, one more time.
Ah...
Oh, it's so good.
Oh, that's it.
One more time.
Oh, it's so good.
Let's enjoy the last bite.
Oh, I'm sweating a lot.
Oh, it's so good.
I can't stand it anymore.
Please stand up.
Oh, it's so good.
I feel great.
It feels so good!
Over there!
My nose!
My nose is running!
It feels so good.
It doesn't feel tight.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
My nose!
My nose is running!
It's so good.
Over there!
No, no, no.
No, I'm going to fall again.
I'm going to fall again.
Over there!
It feels so good.
Did you cut your toenails?
No, not yet.
Really?
Yes.
Can I do it a little more?
Let's go over here.
Can I sit here?
Can you move slowly?
It feels so good.
It's amazing.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It feels so good.
I'm going to fall again.
Let's do it together.
It's embarrassing.
It feels so good.
I'm going to fall again.
Did you feel refreshed?
I did.
Let's eat curry.
Hello.
I'm Tomi Kurata from Kaji Daikou Service.
Nice to meet you.
Is there anything wrong with your body?
I hurt my body while I was working.
I'm sorry.
You had a hard time at work, didn't you?
I had a hard time at work, didn't you?
Are you okay?
I'm getting better, but I can't move yet.
I see.
Please leave the house to me.
Thank you very much.
Please take a rest.
I'll start cleaning.
Please make yourself comfortable.
I heard that you work.
What kind of work do you have to do?
I'm in charge of the construction industry.
I see.
That's a lot of work.
I don't think a man can do such a job alone.
Don't you have any particular obsession?
I'm fine.
I don't often visit such a young man's house.
I'm not young at all.
You are young.
I'm 36 years old.
I can't see you at all.
I'm old.
You are very young.
I'm already 33 years old.
Is that so?
Yes.
I can't see you at all.
No.
You are good at it.
But...
It's a waste.
I understand that.
You seem to be very popular.
That's not true.
As I said earlier,
I often visit a young man's house.
I've been alone for a long time.
I was married.
But we broke up.
We broke up.
I see.
I haven't seen him at all since then.
You haven't seen your boyfriend, have you?
I haven't seen him at all.
I feel sorry for him.
Do you feel sorry for him?
If he was alone,
I think he would be very popular.
I think so, too.
I'm glad if he was popular.
Do you wash this?
I washed it.
I forgot to do it.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to see you again.
I can't move.
Are you all right?
I'm sorry to see you injured.
I'll continue.
I haven't seen him at all since then.
I'm sorry to say this.
It's a waste.
I wish I had more chances to go to a nice man's house.
I washed this, too.
It's better to wash it.
I've cleaned up a little.
Can I sprinkle this?
Not surprised at all.
If he's going to love me this much, he should have told me earlier.
You've often been in the situation, haven't you?
That's what the dishonest man said, wasn't it?
That's what the honest man said, isn't it?
That's what a honest man said, isn't it?
What?
No, no, no. I'm not like that at all.
Really?
I'm not like that at all.
I see.
Then, you two are lonely.
What kind of woman is your type?
What?
What kind of woman?
Well, I'm kind and...
And I have a lot of boobs.
Oh, really?
Do you have a lot of boobs, too?
Yes.
You look so popular.
I feel like I can have as many as I want.
What a waste.
I see.
It must be hard for you to do that when you're injured.
Yes, it is.
I see.
You do it yourself, don't you?
Because you're a man, of course.
I don't do it myself.
You don't do that?
Oh, I see.
Do you do it alone?
Like a solo activity?
Yes, I do.
Because I'm a man.
I have a lot of boobs.
You do, don't you?
Yes.
I found a book like that around here.
Like a DVD.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I can't clean it up.
You don't have to.
I see.
By the way, do you exercise?
I used to do swimming when I was a student.
Swimming?
Yes.
I don't know if it's because of that, but my butt got bigger.
I see.
Yes.
I think it's a good thing.
Is it okay for a woman to have big boobs?
I don't think so.
But I think it's good for women to have big boobs.
Oh, really?
I'm glad to hear that.
By the way, did you get a haircut?
Yes, I did.
That's great.
It's good to get rid of your body hair.
It's good to exercise together.
Oh, I see.
It's good, isn't it?
It's time to clean up.
Do you want to make a meal?
A meal?
Yes.
No, I don't want you to make a meal.
No, it's part of my job to make a meal.
It's okay because it's included in the bill.
Is that so?
The washing machine is running now.
Would you like to make a meal while the washing machine is running?
Yes, please.
The kitchen is over there.
Every house is the same.
Yes, the kitchen is over there.
If you don't know where the kitchen is, please let me know.
Thank you very much.
Is there anything you don't like?
No, I don't hate it at all.
I see. Please wait a moment.
Yes, please.
Your buttocks were amazing.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. I don't want you to be found out.
I feel like I'm going to stand up.
I'm going to stand up.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I'm sorry. I'll eat it myself.
No, it's because your body hurts.
Oh, I see.
Don't worry about it.
How is it? Does it suit your taste?
It's very delicious.
Oh, it's delicious. I'm glad to hear that.
I'll have another bite.
How is it?
It's the best.
Oh, I'm glad to hear that.
I'll have some tea, too.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
I put it in my mouth all of a sudden.
I'm sorry. I put it in my mouth, too.
Oh, I'm sorry. Can I use my towel?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
This is a little different.
I'm fine.
I didn't do anything terrible at first.
I feel sorry for you.
Even an old lady like me is fine.
I'm glad to hear that.
You're not an old lady at all.
You're very nice.
Do you think so?
This is a little different.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad to hear that.
As I said earlier, I often visit the houses of old people.
So, I'm glad to see such a cheerful young man.
I hope you'll always be healthy.
I think I'll be calm after a while.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it again.
I hope you'll always be healthy.
I'm sorry.
I think I'll be calm after a while.
Do you think so?
You look like you're in a tight spot.
I think you're having a hard time.
I think so.
I think I'll be calm after a while.
If you don't mind, I'll help you.
I don't mind.
I don't usually do this.
I'm nervous because I'm taking care of someone like you.
I'm responsible for you.
I think it's hard for you to be alone.
If you don't mind, I'll help you.
I don't mind.
Can I help you?
Please lie down.
Excuse me.
You look like you're having a hard time.
I'm sorry.
I'll wash these pants later.
Can I help you?
You're very energetic.
You moved a lot.
I don't know if I can help you because it's been a while.
Which do you like better, hands or mouth?
Do you like your mouth better?
Are you okay?
Do you want me to be more intense?
I'm sorry.
Is this it?
I'm starting to feel a little bloated.
I'm starting to feel bloated.
I'm sorry.
I feel much better than before.
But it's still a long way off.
I'm still warm.
I feel much better than before.
I'm starting to feel bloated.
You said you liked your breasts.
Do you like this one better?
I'll take it off if it gets dirty.
Do you like your breasts?
It looks like it.
I can't change my underwear if it gets dirty.
I'm taking off everything here, too.
I'll start with your breasts.
If it's okay, it doesn't hurt, does it?
It's amazing.
I feel a little pain in my chest.
That's good.
It's amazing.
It's so big and soft.
It's so hard.
If it's okay, I think it's hard for your hands, so can you sit down?
Is that okay?
It's amazing.
Are you okay?
It's shaking.
My back hurts.
Can you stand up?
Please tell me if it hurts.
It's easier, isn't it?
That's right.
It's hard and hard again.
How is it?
Is it better than before?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
That's right.
It's amazing.
How is it?
I'm sorry I didn't notice it.
You wanted to touch me, didn't you?
That's right.
Can you stand up?
It hurts a lot.
That's good.
It's easier, isn't it?
You said you didn't want to die, didn't you?
Can you see me?
That's right.
If you don't mind, please touch me.
Of course.
It's moving a lot.
I thought it would be hard to move my arms.
That's right.
Don't move.
It's easier, isn't it?
I'm sorry I didn't notice it.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
Is that so?
I'm sorry I didn't notice it.
I'll do it as it is.
Does it feel good?
It hurts.
I'm tired.
I didn't have enough alcohol.
Does it feel good?
It's good, right?
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
I made you dirty.
I came to wash you.
I'm sorry.
I made you wet.
Did you feel refreshed?
It feels good.
It feels so good that I'm still a little scared.
It's true that it's still hard.
I think I can do it a little more.
I'm sorry.
It's still hard.
I'll do it this time.
I'm glad.
I think I can do it a little more.
I'm sorry.
It's still hard.
it's still hard.
i'm still hard.
It's still hard.
it's still hard.
i tried so hard, but it's still hard.
I am happy.
My pacey has come out again.
I am going to use a tissue paper.
I might have used quite a bit of it.
Ah, yes.
I'm sorry.
I gave you a lot.
Are you satisfied now?
Yes, yes.
Yes.
You gave me a lot, didn't you?
Yes, yes, yes.
I feel like your body condition has gotten much better.
I don't know if it's because of the pain, but it doesn't hurt at all.
Ah, really? That's good.
Ah, yes.
That's true.
You can still do it.
You can still do it. That's amazing.
Then, can you move?
I don't think I can move at all.
Then, can you get on the bed?
Ah, yes, yes.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Ah, it feels good.
Ouch!
It really hurts.
I want to hold...
So painful!
So painful.
Together!
Ouch!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh
Dun
Ah ah ah ah
Will
Hmm
Ah ah ah eat
I'm sorry.
Did I overdo it?
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll change the sheets later.
I'm sorry.
How is it?
Is it empty?
Are you feeling better?
That's good.
Please call me anytime.
I can't do much.
I'm sorry.
I'm Honma.
I'm in charge of the housework today.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
You don't have any furniture, do you?
I'm going to move out.
The person who used to live here didn't clean up.
That's why it's so cheap.
I can't clean up by myself.
That's why I'm here.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Where should I start?
The white part of the kitchen is dirty.
I see.
I'm going to start.
It's dirty.
Normally, the owner would clean up.
That's right.
That's why it was easy to clean up.
Do you have anything?
I'm sorry.
I thought there were a lot of elderly people who worked as a housewife.
That's not true.
I'm in my 30s.
Is that so?
I can't see you at all.
I'm serious.
I'm glad to hear that.
I can't see you at all.
I'm going to clean up.
You don't have to go over there.
I have to clean up after you.
I'm going to clean up after you.
I'm a professional.
Thank you very much.
How old are you?
I'm in my 30s.
Is that so?
You look very young.
I thought you were in your 20s.
That's not true.
That's amazing.
Your hands are dirty.
That's not true.
How long have you been working here?
I've been working here for about five years.
That's right.
You look like a professional.
Isn't it hard?
That's right.
I'm a single mother and I have a child.
I have to work hard.
Do you have a child?
That's right.
I can't see you at all.
Thank you very much.
Don't you have a wife?
I don't have a girlfriend.
Is that so?
You look very young.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I have a child.
I haven't talked to him for five years since I got divorced.
You haven't been here for five years?
That's right.
I can't see you at all.
I haven't talked to him at all, so I'm lonely.
I see.
Excuse me.
Yes.
I have something to say.
I'm sorry.
I haven't had a girlfriend for a long time.
I've never had such a beautiful woman come to my house.
I'm sorry.
I'm not angry at you.
I'm afraid of you.
I'm cleaning now.
It's hard for me to do something for you, so I don't know what to do.
What should I do?
If you don't mind, can I do it while cleaning?
What?
I have to go to the bathroom after this, so I can't stop you.
I thought I could do it while cleaning.
While cleaning?
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it while cleaning.
You've grown up a lot.
I'm sorry.
It hurts if I do it like this.
What?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
It's not enough to do it while cleaning.
What?
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Can you move back a little?
It's hot.
It's very hard.
What's wrong?
It's very hot.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
That's good.
I'll continue to clean your ears.
Yes.
Do you want to get married?
I want to get married, but I don't have a girlfriend.
I see.
I don't have a girlfriend, so I'm afraid I'll get married soon.
I see. You'll get married soon.
I don't think so.
I'm sorry.
Didn't I do a good job?
I didn't mean that.
I'll continue to clean your ears.
You're sweating a lot.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
My ex-husband is a very kind person.
He was very strict with me.
I think it's good to have a cute husband like you.
Yes.
I'll clean your ears again.
I'm sorry.
I'll continue to clean your ears.
Do you cook?
I'm not good at cooking.
I see.
I cook at a restaurant.
I can cook anything.
I see.
I'll introduce you to a restaurant.
I'll cook for you.
I'm glad to hear that.
Does your husband come to your house to cook?
No, he doesn't.
He cooks at home.
I see.
Where does your husband work?
He works at a company.
I see.
Yes.
He sits in front of the computer all the time.
I see.
Does your husband have a girlfriend?
He has more than 90% of girlfriends.
He also has an older girlfriend.
I see.
He doesn't have many girlfriends.
He has many boyfriends.
It's true that he doesn't have many girlfriends.
I'm not good at using a computer.
Is that so?
Yes.
He says he's broken even though he hasn't done anything.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I see.
It's delicious.
You're amazing, Sato-san.
You just ate.
I'm full.
Did you want to eat more?
Yes.
I see.
Then, I'll do the dishes.
Is that okay?
My nipples are weak.
Are your nipples weak?
This is the last bite.
You're very surprised.
I'm full.
You're amazing.
Are you more satisfied when I touch you like this?
Yes.
Is that okay?
You're amazing.
I'm sorry.
You've been looking at me for a while.
I've been looking at you for a while.
You have a baby.
I don't have a good body.
You have a big, soft, and elastic body.
I'm sorry.
You can do whatever you want.
You're amazing.
I'm sorry.
I said I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I
'm sorry,
I'm sorry,
I'm sorry
You look beautiful
Please don't look at me
I'm sorry
It's hot.
Are you OK?
I'm sorry.
I'll put you on the bed.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Can I cry?
Yes.
It's been a while since I've done it, so I'll be gentle.
It's hot.
Stop crying.
kte...
I can not sound seaweed
I'll do my best
I can not
It feels so good.
Ah, ah, ah...
AH!
Father, wait...
Ah, ah, ah...
I won't take this off!
I'm so happy!
Ahahahahahahahahahahahahaha
Ahahahahahahahahaha
You scratched there
Oh, Seriously!
Oh, Dear!
Have no idea!
Oh Yue!
We, Why should we!
Did like this,
I,
It's hard.
Be careful.
I dropped it.
I'm sorry.
I can't control my voice.
Can I do it again?
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
My head.
I'm sorry.
Ahhg...
Ahhhg...
Ahg...
Ahhh...
I don't know what to do.
It hurts, it hurts!
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh, oh!
Please go!
Ah!
Oh, oh!
I'm so sorry.
It got I have to fix it.
I'm sorry.
If you ever come to my house again, please call me anytime.
I will come to clean up your room again.