Newcrib seems to have arrived at the room today.
Great-grandmother and great-grandmother who have known my grandmother for a long time and regarded me as family.
We got a letter about having a grandmother before.
I'm really curious.
Aren't you curious?
I'm sure you are.
Thank you.
What's your father's name?
Which one?
It's Ryunosuke-kun's father.
Oh, I see.
I've never heard of him.
That's good.
It's good, but...
I'd like to know his genes.
What?
I'd like to know his name.
I've never heard of his name.
I'm sure you have.
Well,
he's our father.
It's hard to say.
I know.
I'm sure you don't have a father.
I don't have.
No, I don't.
I don't have a father.
I'm sure you don't.
I'm sure you have.
If I have,
I'll go to him.
You don't have a father.
I don't have.
No, you don't.
I'm serious.
If you say no, I'll go to him.
No, you don't.
I'm serious.
Well,
Ayako's father
has sparkling eyes
when he's sleeping.
What?
He's staring at you?
I don't think so.
But he's conscious of you.
I think so.
He's like,
I'm watching you.
He doesn't look at you.
He's staring at me.
But he doesn't come to me.
He doesn't come to you?
He comes to you.
You're the same.
You're the same, too.
I'm curious about what he has.
It's important, isn't it?
I won't go to him.
Really?
You won't?
You can't leave him if he won't come.
You had to make him come.
That's not true.
Saku-sensei's face is pretty.
You look great.
As a young girl,
Do you know what I'm talking about?
I know what you're talking about.
It's a combination of sexual desire.
That's right.
You're doing it.
It's the same, isn't it?
It's the same.
It's similar.
It's impossible for me to do it now.
It's impossible.
That's what happens when you're in this job.
I don't like it.
I think it's a good idea to put it in a trendy app.
I've never done that.
Isn't it scary?
It's different from the picture.
I've said that before.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
I'll be right back.
Please.
The app is scary, isn't it?
I've done it before.
I've done it once.
He's so handsome.
Hello.
I'm Ito's brother.
I'm Ito's sister.
Is my sister not here now?
She's cleaning up.
Is that so?
What should I do?
Why are you here?
I was told to come.
Isn't it too early?
Isn't it over yet?
I'm sorry.
I was mistaken.
It's going to take a while.
I want you to wait.
I want you to kill time outside.
Outside?
I won't tell you to wait here.
I don't have much money.
There must be a place to kill time.
I don't know much about this area.
You should have stayed here.
I've already cleaned up here.
It's okay.
It's going to get in the way.
Let's wait together.
You're too kind.
Please.
It won't get in the way.
It's okay.
You have a lot of luggage.
I'm sorry.
Please be quiet.
I still have work to do.
Please take care of Daiki.
She's a good girl.
She's like a mother.
Excuse me.
Would you like some tea?
I'm sorry.
I'll bring it.
It's going to take a while.
You have a younger brother.
I didn't know that.
I've never heard of him.
He's my younger brother.
I see.
We haven't been together since we were little.
That's why you don't look like him.
He's cute.
Thank you.
He's like a dinosaur.
He's cute.
You have a lot of luggage.
Thank you.
I was going to stay at your house for a few days.
I see.
It looks heavy.
I'm sorry.
You have a lot of luggage.
I have a lot of luggage.
I'm worried about your luggage.
He's cute.
I envy you.
You have a cute younger brother.
I feel sorry for him.
I was surprised.
I came to your workplace for the first time.
You are all young.
You are all beautiful.
I'm glad to hear that.
You all have cute aprons.
I'm sorry.
I'll clean it myself.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
My clothes are wet.
I have to wipe it well.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I have had my clothes wiped.
Are you really okay?
You're still wet.
I'm sorry.
I'll dry your clothes.
I'm sorry to bother you.
You're so wet.
You're soaking wet.
What's wrong with me?
My hand slipped.
I see.
Your voice is trembling.
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Your pants are wet, too.
You're soaking wet.
You should take off your pants, too.
Pants get wet, too.
Are you all right?
You'll catch a cold.
You should take off your pants, too.
You're like a baby.
I'll wipe it for you.
Are you all right?
Raise your legs.
You're low.
Are you all right?
Your face is red.
It's still wet around here.
I'll wipe it for you.
Don't be afraid.
Raise your head.
Cute!
You have become bigger.
What a relief!
It looks like ovary, right?
What? Wait.
Sorry.
Carefully.
I have to wipe here too.
Let's make it clean.
We have to make it clean.
Is this really okay?
It's warm.
I can't see it at all.
Wow.
It's warm.
It's big.
It's quite big.
It's so fluffy.
It's true.
I'm embarrassed.
What about here?
I can feel it, but it's cute.
It's cute.
Do you like here too?
Yes, I do.
It's cute.
Raise your head.
Do you want to see more?
Don't you want to see more?
Yes, I do.
You want to see more, right?
Do you want to see more?
Yes, I do.
Then, I'll show you something special.
Come closer.
You're trembling.
You like it.
It's true.
It's bigger than before.
It's cute.
It's burning.
It's so cute.
I just want you to blow on it.
I don't want you to do this.
It's cute.
Don't do that.
I'm used to it.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of you.
Do you like it so much?
Your ears are red.
You're trembling.
What should I do?
Do you want me to pinch you?
I'll double it.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's like a baby.
It's cute.
It's getting bigger.
It's licking you.
It feels good.
It's getting bigger.
Do you want to see the teacher's boobs?
It's cute.
It's getting harder.
It's like a baby.
It feels good.
I'm glad you have a lot of boobs.
The teacher is here.
She's not here yet.
I'm going to throw it away.
I have to wipe it off.
Did you all wipe it off?
I'm going to throw it away.
No, no, no.
I don't want to see it.
Let's wipe it off together.
Isn't that enough?
I haven't wiped it off yet.
It's amazing.
Look at it.
I've never seen it before.
I don't know what's going on.
I'm curious about the teacher.
What is it?
The quality is a bit different.
I said no, but why are you making such a face?
That's because of the boobs.
Oh, I see.
Aiki loves boobs.
Oh, is that so? That's why everyone is watching.
I was surprised when I came back.
You love these boobs, don't you?
It's cute.
You love boobs, don't you?
Oh, you love boobs, don't you?
You were born with boobs.
Boobs.
It's twitching here.
It's not closed yet.
It's really twitching.
You love boobs, don't you?
You love boobs.
You look lonely, so I'll hug you with my boobs.
You're kind.
It's warm.
Is it warm?
It's always twitching.
Why do you have so many boobs?
Why?
You love boobs so much, don't you?
You're cute.
It's warm.
I can't stand it anymore.
Your face is getting bigger.
It's warm.
You feel good.
I've never seen you like this.
You're a good girl.
Look, she's pulling a string.
Look at me.
You have four boobs.
You're beautiful.
I'm going to be sad.
You look like you're in pain, but you look happy.
You don't have to do it.
You're so cute.
I've seen a lot of transparent stickers.
You're a good girl.
I've never seen it before.
It's not connected.
I don't think it's connected to the image of being a solo artist.
But she's been looking at the confession for a long time, hasn't she?
You haven't seen it, have you?
You want to see it, don't you?
No, I don't want you to show me that.
Yeah, I don't want to see it.
I don't want to see it.
You don't want to see it, do you?
I think it's a good picture.
She has a great face.
Daiki, come here.
Look at me.
Come here.
Oh, that was great.
I'm worried about my sister.
I didn't think it would be this good.
You don't have to be nervous.
I can't see it.
That's great.
It's amazing.
I can't see it at all.
I've never seen that face before.
It feels so good, doesn't it?
Daiki's penis is sandwiched between my sister's boobs.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's like a baby.
That's what I did.
I'm surprised.
What's going on?
It's like a baby.
It's coming out.
I haven't done it yet.
I'm going to explode.
Don't take a break.
Daiki's boobs are big.
It's big.
Do you like boobs?
I love boobs.
I'm sleepy.
That's great.
I've never seen that face before.
It's amazing.
It's like a baby.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's the best.
Daiki's penis is getting bigger.
What's going on?
It's coming out.
I can't take it anymore.
It's coming out a lot.
It's amazing.
I'm going to put it in my nipple.
It's a lot.
It's amazing.
It tastes like a penis.
That's great.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
You like butts, don't you?
What?
It's noisy, so I'll cover my mouth.
You're so energetic.
I was sad.
What are you talking about?
It feels good.
There is not enough.
It's not enough.
What?
That's true.
It's amazing.
Don't get your throat dirty.
You like it, don't you?
The string looks like it's going to break.
Maybe I should fix it.
She's so excited.
She likes it.
Thank you.
You should say thank you.
Really?
You like it, don't you?
Maybe it's the next one.
She looks like she wants it, too.
She's staring at it.
I'll show you closer.
She's crying.
Look at her nose.
Do you want more?
More?
She's crying.
She's standing on her hands.
The next one is...
It's her butt.
She's surprised.
It's amazing.
She's licking it.
I'm glad you like it.
Are you happy?
She's surprised.
What did you do?
She can't see her butt.
She's happy.
Does it feel good?
Are you happy?
She's happy.
Don't say you're happy.
I'll tell you one more time.
She looks happy.
Don't be so weak.
You're strong.
Do you want more?
I don't know what she's doing.
She's like a baby.
She's cute.
What is she doing?
Who do you like?
Where are you going?
Wait a minute.
She's naked.
I'll put her clothes on.
I can't let her take off her clothes.
Isn't this a swimsuit?
Thank you.
Raiki.
I'm sorry.
Raiki was so cute.
Raiki.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
Why are you so depressed?
I didn't know you were looking at me like that.
Were you that shocked?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
I was so embarrassed in front of everyone.
You were embarrassed.
But it's okay. It's not something to worry about.
It's okay.
I was so embarrassed in front of everyone.
It's not something to be embarrassed about.
It's not something to worry about.
Come here.
It's okay.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
What?
I bumped into you again.
Did you bump into me again?
I didn't have a chance to talk to a woman.
Let me see.
You're right.
It's good to get well soon.
Don't be embarrassed.
Let me see.
I'll pet you gently.
I'm sorry.
You're right.
It's warm here.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
You felt it a lot, didn't you?
That's right.
It feels good.
Did you feel good?
I'm glad to hear that.
It's warm here.
You have a stiff neck.
I have a stiff neck.
Do you have a stiff neck?
Do you want me to touch you directly?
I want you to touch me directly.
You felt good, didn't you?
I'll take off your T-shirt.
You're a good boy.
Your body is warm.
You're sensitive.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
You know my face.
I know your face when you feel good.
You look happy.
I'll take off your T-shirt.
No.
Don't you like it?
I can't go home now.
I have to take care of you.
I'm embarrassed.
I saw you earlier.
That's right.
You have a stiff neck.
Your panties are wet.
I wonder what will happen to your boobs.
Do you want to see it?
Do you want me to show you your favorite boobs?
You're cute.
You're fascinated by my boobs.
What do you want to do with my boobs?
I want to touch them.
Do you want to touch them?
Do you want me to lick your boobs?
I felt it when I licked your boobs.
How do you like my boobs?
I like your boobs.
They are big and soft.
You can lick them as much as you want.
Your neck is getting stiff.
Does it feel good?
You have a body that is easy to feel.
You have a stiff neck.
You're cute.
I'll lick your boobs, too.
I'll lick both of them.
Does it feel good?
You feel good when I lick your boobs.
You're honest.
You're cute.
Do you want me to touch them?
Your boobs are big.
You have a lot of boobs.
Do you want me to lick them?
You're cute.
Do you like it?
I'll give it back to you.
I was surprised.
You're stiff.
I'll lick your neck.
Can you do it well?
I'll lick your boobs.
You're honest.
Does it feel good?
You feel good when I lick your boobs.
You feel good.
You're honest.
Your boobs are getting harder.
It's hot.
Your face is red.
Does it hurt?
Your nose and mouth are covered with boobs.
It's hot.
You're good.
Can you lick them together?
You have a lot of boobs.
You feel good.
You're good.
If you lick me so much, I'll get my nipples.
You have a lot of boobs.
You're good.
You feel good.
You open your mouth again.
You're getting red.
You're getting pretty red.
Do you want your boobs to be tickled even more?
Do you want to be tickled more?
You also like your hip.
You can touch my hips.
Let's tickle while watching your hips.
Do you want to see the back of the teacher?
I want to see the back of the teacher.
You can see it up close.
Look at the back of the teacher.
The back of the teacher is very beautiful.
Gin-chan is getting hot.
I'll make you feel better.
There's a lot of gel coming out of you.
It feels so good.
I wonder if white gel will come out again.
Gin-chan is delicious.
The back of the teacher is getting hot.
The back of the teacher is getting hotter than before.
I'm looking at a lot of places where you can lick.
The back of the teacher is getting hot.
Gin-chan is full.
Are you full?
The back of the teacher is getting hot.
You have a nice voice.
Did the back of the teacher feel so good?
There's a lot of gel coming out of you.
You're full again.
It feels so good.
If you keep doing this, I wonder what will happen to your penis.
It's moving all the time.
It feels so good.
It's not difficult anymore, is it?
Show the teachers more of your erotic face.
Show me more.
Look at me.
It's moving again.
It's round.
You're honest.
I'm going to put it in your head.
It's swelling up.
Does it feel good?
Does your head feel good?
It's a lot of erotic.
You can imagine a lot of erotic while looking at me.
Think about a lot of erotic.
Make your penis harder.
You're out of breath again.
Does your penis feel good?
You can say it feels good.
You're full of energy.
You're amazing.
Make your penis harder.
You're out of breath again.
When you go to the toilet, tell the teachers that you want to go to the toilet.
Say it with a loud voice.
Can you say it with a cheerful voice?
You're a good boy.
You're out of breath.
You're out of breath again.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
You're a good boy.
The teachers will clean up your penis.
I'll clean up your dirty penis.
I'll lick your penis.
Your penis smells good.
I'm getting more excited.
It's hot and humid.
You look so happy.
Can you touch me?
Look at my penis.
Are you okay?
I'll make you wake up everytime after listening to your dad.
It's time to go to bed.
You're always lacking food though.
You're not awake yet.
Hang in there.
I wonder if I can put my finger in this.
I want you to put your finger in it.
I'll put my finger in it.
I wonder if I can move your fingers at the same time.
Good girl.
It tickles, right?
Slowly.
You are doing well.
You are doing great.
Oh, you are doing great.
More, more.
Oh, it feels good.
You are doing great.
It feels good.
You can make the students feel good.
You are doing great.
Can you do that?
Oh, you are doing great.
You are doing great.
It feels good.
Can you lick the floor like the teachers did?
There is a mat here.
You can lie down on it.
Can you see well?
Can you touch me?
You are a good boy.
It feels good.
Oh, it feels good.
Can you lick me a lot?
Oh, you are doing great.
The teacher took away your food.
He is going nuts.
He can't bear it any more.
It feels good.
The next is that
I can't stand it anymore.
But it's okay.
I can see a lot when I go in.
I'm going in.
I went in.
I'll move a lot for you.
You just have to stay there.
Yes.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
It's been a long time.
I can't stop my back.
I feel good.
Raise your head.
I can't stop my back.
It's cracking.
It's making a lot of noise.
Aiki-chan, your teacher is giving you a lot of love, isn't she?
She's giving me a lot of love.
She's shaking.
Are you going to go again?
I'm going to give you a lot of love.
Can you say you're going again with a loud voice?
You can say that, can't you?
You can give me a lot of love, can't you?
She's shaking.
Aiki-chan, let's go.
Teacher, Aiki-chan.
She's shaking.
Give me everything you have.
Did you get a lot of love?
You got a lot of love, didn't you?
She's shaking.
Aiki-chan, can you give it back to your teacher?
Can you give it back to her?
She's still shaking.
That's amazing.
I wanted to be a teacher because I saw your love.
I'm going to give you a lot of love.
It's so hard.
It feels so good.
I can't stop moving my hips.
It's been a while since I've been a teacher, so I might leave soon.
Can I go?
I don't think I'll see you again.
That's amazing.
It's amazing to see your favorite butt and teacher's boobs at the same time.
It feels so good.
Come closer from behind.
It's just the two of us.
It feels so good.
Teacher, please mix it.
You're good at touching your hips.
You make us feel good.
I can't stand it anymore.
It feels so good.
Let's feel better together.
Teacher, I'm going.
Let's go together.
You're doing it again.
You're sweating a lot.
You're still sweating.
Let's do it together.
Please put me in the water.
Take your time.
I did it.
It feels so good.
You can see the roundness of the hips well.
It's amazing.
You can see the connection of the teacher.
It feels so good.
Please put me in the water.
It's amazing.
It feels so good.
It's hard all the time.
My hands hurt.
I'll wipe it for you.
It's amazing.
It feels so good.
It's hard all the time.
You can do it.
Let's go together.
It's not enough yet.
You can do more, right?
It feels so good.
It's not enough yet.
It's hard all the time.
I'm sweating a lot.
Let's feel good with the teacher.
It's hard all the time.
It feels so good.
It hurts.
It's hard all the time.
Can I move more?
It's not enough yet.
It's the most painful.
It feels so good.
It's hard all the time.
Let's go together.
It hurts.
Can you do it?
What can you do?
It's amazing.
I can't stop.
It feels so good.
It's amazing.
It hurts a lot.
It's hard all the time.
It feels so good.
I'm getting more sensitive.
I'm sweating a lot.
Do you want to do it again?
Can you do it well?
Put a lot of white stuff in the doctor's room.
I love it there.
You're very good at shaking your hips.
I'm getting tired.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Put a lot of white stuff in the doctor's room.
In the doctor's room.
I want white stuff.
I'm getting tired.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm out of breath.
I can't do it anymore.
Your lips are soft.
I love you so much.
I'll put it in.
It feels good.
It feels so good that I'm shivering.
It feels so good.
You put a lot of it in.
Can you put it in the doctor's room?
Hang in there.
I just took a picture.
My voice is hard.
It feels good.
Hang in there.
The doctor is sleeping.
It feels good.
Thank you.
You made a lot of cute faces.
You can do a lot.
You're a good girl.
You're amazing.
What's that?
You know what I'm talking about.
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's almost over.
I'm hungry.
Nice to meet you.
I need your help.
I'm grateful.
What should I do?
You're close to her, right?
Are you staying over tonight?
You're asking a lot of questions.
Aren't you a craged man?
It's amazing.
What do you use this for?
It's her birthday.
So I buy her a decoration.
That's adorable.
She's too young to be able to play with it.
It's so loud.
It's Japan.
But it looks good.
Yes.
I want you to do it.
If you take it off,
it will be double-sided tape.
Oh, I see.
If you stick it on,
it will be a big decoration.
It's amazing.
It's cute.
It will be a big decoration.
It's fun to do this kind of thing.
Is it fun?
I'm glad.
I don't have a house.
Mothers are lazy, aren't they?
We are
lazy.
That's right.
Are you not suitable for that?
I don't know.
I don't hate it even as a child.
Do you like it?
I think I like it.
It's cute.
It's a scaffold.
A scaffold?
Is that the relationship?
It's a treatment.
It's cute.
Can you draw it?
Let's draw it together.
I don't have a drawing book.
I know.
You are good at drawing.
I'm not good at drawing.
I thought you drew a rabbit.
I thought you drew a cat.
You drew a cat.
No.
I'm not good at drawing.
Let's try it.
We still have a drawing book.
Let's draw it.
Let's draw a bear instead of a rabbit.
No.
There is a perfect bear here.
It's a live-action.
What should I do?
Let's draw a bear.
I can't draw recently.
Isn't it difficult?
There are only difficult things.
I can't understand if you request me.
I can't draw.
There is a flower here.
Maybe I should draw a bear.
There is a pattern here.
I think we have to draw a white frame.
Can you see it?
That is a panda.
I thought you drew a bear.
Did you listen to this panda too much?
What should I do?
If you put this on the side, it will look like a spinach.
I don't like it.
It's a recent problem.
Do you know what I mean?
Wait a minute.
It's Tsuburana Hitomi, right?
I'll draw Tsuburana Hitomi.
It's cute. What should I do?
It's going in that direction.
Wait a minute.
Why is it different?
It's like a thief.
Daiki.
Are you good at drawing?
What's wrong?
What?
Daiki.
What's wrong?
No.
What?
Again?
What's wrong?
Actually, this happened earlier.
What?
Is that what happened earlier?
That's right.
What do you mean by that?
I was loved.
I'm sorry.
Your butts were so nice.
It's my butt.
I'm in trouble.
What?
What happened?
While I was cleaning up earlier,
the teachers said,
Daiki, this is your lesson.
What?
Everyone...
Everyone was holding back.
What?
Why didn't you call me?
I was going to call you.
That's mean.
You didn't call me, did you?
No, I didn't.
I didn't think you would come at this time.
It can't be helped.
That's right.
I know.
You look happy.
Is that how you feel?
I thought it would be nice.
I just put it out earlier.
When did you put it out?
It was a while ago.
I think I can still do it.
You recover quickly.
It's something I can do.
It's amazing that you're young.
It's painful, isn't it?
It's amazing.
What's this?
It's okay.
I'm curious about you, too.
Let me see.
No.
Don't you like it?
It's fun.
I'll take it off for you.
It's amazing.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I can't stand it when I see something like this.
Wait a minute.
How was it when you lived together?
I don't care.
At that time, I was absorbed in other things.
I didn't expect to be my brother.
Was it your first time?
I don't like it.
I'm going to break up with you.
I'm sorry.
It's not bad.
Look at this.
It's amazing.
I didn't see it earlier.
It's really big.
Daiki, do you want to hold it?
It's hard to hold it, isn't it?
Daiki is very strong.
Can I touch it?
Yes.
How is it?
It's hard.
It's amazing.
I'll make it harder for you.
I love it.
Daiki, why did you make it so hard?
What were you looking at?
We didn't do anything.
We just drew a picture.
The butt was amazing.
Only the butt?
It's amazing.
I didn't know that either.
Which part of the girl do you like?
That's...
You like the butt, don't you?
You like the protruding part.
I like the butt and the butt.
You're honest.
You made it so big.
Is it flat?
It's not like that.
Why?
You should have told me that you made it like that.
You made it so big.
It's amazing.
I don't like it.
It's not like that.
It's amazing.
It smells good.
It's been a while.
How is it?
I haven't had a chance to touch it.
Are you happy?
She made it like this.
I'm happy and embarrassed.
It's cute.
I want to tease you.
I don't like it.
I have to make it cute.
I want to tease you in a cute way.
I'm tired.
You made it so big.
You're a good girl.
It's in the way.
You should shake it all off.
I'll do my best.
You're doing your best.
You made it so big.
What's wrong?
You're shaking.
You made it so big.
You're doing your best.
She's not in a good mood.
Let's do a lot of fun things.
You're doing your best.
I'm scared.
I only licked it a little.
You made it so big.
Let's do it again.
Good boy.
What kind of play do you like?
Tell me.
I don't know.
I'll teach you.
I'll teach you a lot of fun things.
Here you are.
It's quite scrunched here.
It's dark pink now.
In a word, she is an expert in cutting hair.
Come on.
You have to see this, sis!
I'm going to have you lick me a lot.
How is it? It feels good, doesn't it?
It's good, isn't it?
You're very energetic, aren't you?
How can you be so energetic?
You love it, don't you?
How's your teeth, Mr. Natsuki?
Mr. Natsuki's teeth are very soft.
Do you want me to touch you properly?
I have to touch you properly, don't I?
You love it, don't you?
Boys love it, don't they?
Do you love it? It's cute.
I have to brush Mr. Natsuki's teeth properly, don't I?
You know what I mean, don't you?
But even if Mr. Natsuki teases me...
I'm already ticklish.
It's ticklish, isn't it?
It feels good in your mouth, doesn't it?
It feels good, doesn't it, Mr. Natsuki?
Do you want more?
You're desperate.
You love it, don't you?
Did you taste a lot of it just now?
You're amazing.
I'll give you a lot of it.
Is it good?
It's hot.
You're amazing.
You're very strong.
I'm sorry it's not milk.
It's good.
It feels good.
You're amazing, Mr. Natsuki.
You're so desperate.
Your teeth are big, aren't they?
Let's eat.
You like to be pinched.
You don't like it, do you?
It's mine.
It's for my brother and sister.
You didn't lick it earlier, did you?
You didn't lick it?
You didn't lick it, did you?
I'll let you lick it.
You're a good boy.
It's hot.
You're so cute.
Lick it properly.
It's hot.
It's good.
You're a good boy.
It's not just this.
There's another one.
It's hot.
It's good.
You're a good boy.
You like it, don't you?
I'm pushing you.
It's hard.
You look like that.
You're so cute.
I'm not.
You're a good boy.
This is what it looks like.
It's cool.
That's how it is.
Just put on an apron.
If you don't have one,
I'll do it just in case.
Just in case.
It's hot, isn't it?
Dad, is it hot?
It's hot.
Let's put on Natsuki-sensei's boobs.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's amazing here.
It's shiny.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Natsuki-sensei's boobs are shiny.
I see.
How about putting them together with your boobs?
It doesn't look like it.
Look.
It's getting shiny.
It's amazing.
It's very shiny.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I have Natsuki-sensei's boobs.
I have two.
I have four.
Look.
It's amazing.
It's shiny.
It looks delicious.
I'll give you more.
It's shiny.
It's amazing.
You like it, don't you?
I have to put a lot of them together.
I'll give you more.
How is it?
It's delicious.
How does it feel to have two boobs?
You like it, don't you?
You like all of them, don't you?
I'll lick the bottom.
I'll lick the top.
It's hot.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Sensei might have liked it.
You're a cute little brother.
Your pants are very loose.
Satsuki-sensei, you're not fast.
I'm not fast.
Really?
You like this, don't you?
You know it well.
Do you like it?
It's amazing.
You're eating a lot of soup.
How is it?
You're excited.
Do you like it, Satsuki-sensei?
Isn't it bad to play like this?
I like it.
You're not trying to make me sleep.
It's not my fault.
You're talking, so it's okay.
You like to talk, don't you?
It's not because of the pants.
You want to wear it, don't you?
You were tired, didn't you?
It's painful.
You're making me sleep.
It's amazing.
You're very excited.
You're very fluffy.
It's amazing.
You're making me sleep.
Do you want to wear panties?
It's not your fault.
You want me to wear panties, don't you?
Let me see.
I see.
You want me to wear panties, don't you?
Taiki is a pervert.
It's not because you're a pervert.
What's wrong with you, Taiki?
You don't know if you don't wear panties, do you?
I'm sorry.
What are you going to do in that case?
Can I let it out?
You can.
You can let it out.
I asked you nicely.
I have to make you feel good.
I see.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
You're good at licking, Taiki.
Where did you learn that?
It's amazing.
You're like a pervert.
I'm telling you that you're good.
I'll take my panties off and wait for you.
Don't take your panties off in front of me.
I'm waiting for you.
I can't see you.
Raise your head.
I don't want to.
I'll take my panties off.
It's amazing.
I don't know what you're doing.
What's the matter?
Is this better?
I can see your face.
I don't like it.
You don't like it, do you?
Are you too sexy?
No, I'm not.
I don't like it.
You're sexy.
What's wrong with you?
You're not supposed to do that.
I don't like it.
You're licking your panties.
I'm happy.
You're cute.
You can lick my panties, can't you?
Lick my panties.
You're good at it.
But you keep doing that.
I'm sure your panties are tight.
Wait, I'm coming.
Oh, my God.
I'm coming.
You're good at licking your panties.
You're good at it.
No, I'm not.
It's a playroom.
It's in there.
Look at Daiki.
It's in Daiki's bag.
It's in there.
Daiki's panties are so tight.
It's amazing.
It's round.
I'll put it in there.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
I'll give you a lot later.
It's amazing.
It's so round.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's amazing.
Daiki, your lower back is moving.
Even if I don't move it, your lower back is moving.
It feels good.
Look at this.
It's moving.
It's amazing.
What should I do?
I'm sorry.
I let Daiki sleep.
But it feels good, so I can't help it.
I'm hungry.
It feels good.
Can you see me?
I'm licking my boobs, so you won't notice.
Do you want me to see it?
I'll show you.
I'm licking my boobs, so you won't notice.
It feels good.
I'm licking my boobs.
It's embarrassing.
You have to clean your boobs.
I'm cleaning your boobs.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I didn't think it would feel so good.
It's getting weird.
I have to get ready.
It feels good.
Let's go.
I don't want to do it.
I'm sorry.
I want to do it.
I've never done it before.
It's embarrassing.
Don't forget it.
It feels good.
You've been doing a good job lately.
There.
Let's go.
It feels good.
It's wet.
My legs are wet too.
I don't want to do it.
Do you understand?
There.
You're doing a good job.
I'll help you.
I don't want to do it.
Let's go.
It's getting intense.
I can't stop moving my hips.
There.
You're doing a good job.
Wait.
Let's go.
I'll help you clean up.
It's so wet.
You're a pervert.
Let me see.
It feels good.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
You're doing a good job.
No, no, no.
It hurts.
It's so wet.
What are you doing?
I'll clean it up later.
When are you going to give it to me?
It feels good.
It hurts.
You're going to get better soon.
What's wrong with you?
You're a good girl.
You're sweating a lot.
I don't want to.
The tears of Daiki have become messy.
This is too dark.
I die.
How long have you been eating?
You've been eating for a long time, haven't you?
I didn't think I'd be able to eat this much.
You've eaten a lot.
I just got out of bed.
Can you not run away?
I don't have any medicine today.
I don't feel anything.
You've lost a lot of weight.
I just got out of bed.
You're still in my body.
You've been waiting for a long time.
Look at this.
You can't see it, can you?
I'll give you a meal.
I'm sorry.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I love you.
My stomach is getting harder.
It's a little hard.
I don't want to do it.
It feels good.
Sorry.
Thank you.
It doesn't taste well...
Ah...
Ahhhh...
I'm touching you
Woah... today it becomes intense
What's going on?
Oh, I see.
It feels good.
You're amazing.
You've been opening your mouth all the time.
I want you to feel better.
Come here.
I want a lot of people to come from behind.
I'm envious.
Let's go.
It feels good.
It's getting really tight.
It's amazing.
You're amazing.
I can see your muscles.
No, no, no.
Wait a minute.
Stop.
I'll give you more.
Come here.
It's tight.
If you lick me, I'll go away.
Don't do that.
You two are trying to make me go away.
It feels good.
It's really tight.
I can't stand it.
I'm sorry.
I'll go first.
No.
I'm sorry.
Did you just say that?
It's amazing.
Who is it?
It hurts.
You just let it out.
Take it off.
You let it out so much.
My skin is dirty, too.
That's right.
You let it out so much.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Do you want me to take it off?
I don't think it's enough.
What?
She's talking to you.
Really?
Who is it?
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
You let it out so much.
I'll do it again.
You're lying, aren't you?
No.
Does it feel good?
Wait.
I'll do it.
You let it out so much.
I'm sorry.
It's dirty.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
What do you want me to do?
What?
Do you want me to do it from behind?
No.
What is this?
It feels good.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it.
It's a lie.
I don't want to do it.
I'm sorry.
I can't stop it.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
It's getting intense.
Wait.
It feels good.
Help me.
I'm scared.
I can't do it anymore.
What's wrong with you?
I want to do it again.
It feels good.
Let me play with you again.
Are you going to stay here?
I think you should work at my house.
You should work here.
Then we can do it again.
Together.
Let's do it together again.
I can't do it anymore.
Wait.
I have to work.
I have to clean up.
Bring more.
I'll bring more.
Daiki, are you awake?
I'm sorry.
I thought you were sleeping.
Were you sleeping?
I'm sorry.
Where is your sister?
I have a favor to ask you.
I want to practice how to drink milk.
Can you be my partner?
Me?
Yes.
I'll give you milk.
Drink it.
Will I be able to practice?
Yes, you will.
Be a baby.
Okay?
What should I do?
Swallow it.
Think of it as a baby.
How is it?
Did you swallow it?
Do you lick it?
It's a little embarrassing.
It's okay.
Come here.
Like this.
You're good.
Drink a lot.
You're a baby.
I've never given you milk.
I don't have the opportunity.
How is it?
Are you doing well?
I'm doing well.
Yes.
What's wrong?
It's a little...
It's okay.
You're a baby.
Drink it.
You're good.
Drink a lot.
You're a baby.
Pat it.
What's wrong?
It's a little...
What?
You're a baby.
Babies don't do that.
It's okay.
You're good.
You're a baby.
You drank a lot.
That's right.
Can I practice?
You're not good at it yet.
Go to bed.
Can I go to bed?
Yes.
Let's change your diaper.
Please open your mouth.
What's this?
What's wrong?
I'll take off your diaper.
I'll do it later.
It's okay.
It's not embarrassing.
Let's change your diaper.
What's wrong with your hand?
What's this?
This is...
Babies don't do that.
I'm sorry.
Why are you standing?
That's...
That's what?
What is it?
Is it your boobs again?
I'm sorry.
It was a practice.
I can't practice at all.
What should I do?
I'll take it off.
If you touch me like this...
What?
I can't touch you.
I've been taking it off since you didn't touch me.
That's right.
You're not good at it.
I'm sorry.
You have to do this once.
Otherwise, you'll stay big.
Let's make it smaller.
If you don't make it smaller, you won't be able to wear diapers.
I'm sorry.
You're not good at it.
If you make it this big...
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Do you want me to lick you a lot?
Yes.
You're a baby.
Even if you beg me...
I'm sorry.
You're a baby.
You're so big and hard.
What's wrong with you?
You're a baby.
You've grown up so much.
I'll let you out.
You're not good at it.
You've grown up so much.
It hurts.
I'll let you out.
I let you out.
You're not getting smaller at all.
I don't know why.
This won't make you smaller at all.
You're a baby.
It's a practice.
You're not getting smaller at all.
You're not good at it.
You're a baby.
I'll let you out.
Do you want a real thing?
Do you want it?
It can't be helped.
It's a real thing.
Think of it as your mother's breasts.
Breathe in a lot.
Is it good?
You're not getting smaller at all.
You're doing a great job.
Do you want a real thing?
Do you want it?
Breathe in a lot.
What's wrong?
Does it feel good?
I'll touch your nipples.
You've grown a lot of nipples.
Don't rest your mouth.
I'll lick you.
Does it feel good?
Let's lean on your legs.
You're good.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
You're great.
You're all curled up.
Yes, yes.
Is it difficult?
But your penis is very hard.
It's hard.
I can see all the way to your buttocks.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
Does it feel good?
Don't do that.
Is it too hard?
It's okay.
It's hard.
Does it feel good?
What are you resting on?
It's your favorite boob.
You like my nipples.
Don't do that.
Daiki licks your nipples a lot.
Your tongue is wet.
Can you lick my nipples?
No.
Let's lick your nipples.
I'm going to lick your nipples.
Does it feel good?
Daiki licks your nipples a lot.
Your nipples are sensitive.
It looks painful.
Do it again.
No.
Does it feel good?
That's great.
Not yet.
Does it feel good?
No.
What?
Do it again.
Does it feel good?
I'm going to lick your nipples.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Su...umbling nchste
Oh! Oh!
Ah  that feels good.
Thank you
It's hot.
It feels good.
Put your finger in.
Put your finger in here.
It feels good.
It's hot.
You can put your finger in.
It feels good.
It's hot.
There.
It feels good.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it feels good.
I want a bed, not a finger.
Put it in.
Put it in your bed.
Me, too.
Put it in.
I'm scared.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
It's hard.
Oh, it feels good.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
It's coming out.
It's going to be gone.
Oh, it's coming out.
It's coming out.
Ah!
Ah, amazing...
Ah, feels good...
Ah, ah...
Ah...
Ah, feels good...
Ah, more...
Ah, that's it, there...
There...
Ah...
Ah feels good...
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Ouch...
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
Ah, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
More...
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
It feels good.
Come on, do it more.
More?
Ah, it feels good.
There, there, there.
It feels good.
Ah, I can't stop.
Why can't you stop?
Ah, it feels so good.
I can't do it anymore.
Come on, do it more.
Why?
Ah, I can't stop.
Come on, do it more.
Okay, then.
What?
Come on, do it.
I can't do it anymore.
Hang in there.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, I can't do it anymore.
Slowly, slowly.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, this part is amazing.
It's amazing.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, it hurts.
What?
Does it feel good?
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, I can't stop.
Slowly, slowly.
Ah, it feels so good.
What?
I can't do it anymore.
Then, lick my lips.
You can film while licking my lips.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, it hurts.
Ah, you're still filming.
I have to make it smaller.
Ah, I can't do it anymore.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, it hurts.
You're still filming.
Why?
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it anymore.
What?
It feels so good.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels so good?
It feels so good.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, it hurts.
Can I move more?
No.
Ah, it hurts.
It feels so good.
It feels so good?
Can I move more?
Ah, it hurts.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, I can't do it anymore.
It feels so good.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, I can't do it anymore.
Ai-kun, Ai-kun, Ai-kun!
It tickles!
Give me more!
Ai-kun, Ai-kun, Ai-kun!
It tickles!
I can't stand up.
But I can still do it.
I want to do it more.
Why are you still standing up?
Are you that lonely?
I can't stand up at all.
I can't do it anymore.
I want to do it more.
Then, I'll just clean up.
I'll just clean up your mouth.
I'll do it again next time.
Just your mouth?
Then, I'll do it again next time.
Okay?
Huh?
Taiki-kun.
Are you still here?
Yes. I was waiting for you.
I'm already home.
What?
You're home?
I've been waiting for you.
I have to finish my drawing.
I think you got a call.
What?
I got a call quite a while ago.
I was already home.
I've been waiting for you.
You're terrible.
What were you doing?
I was waiting for you.
I was going to live here.
What?
Are you serious?
Let's go home together.
Okay.
You're terrible.
Let's go home.
What do you mean?
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
Why can't I contact you?
You came to see me.
You lost your sister, didn't you?
Yes.
So...
I don't know...
I feel awkward.
I don't know how to approach you.
I don't know.
Well...
You seem to like sexy things.
And...
You don't seem to like it at all.
Oh...
Is that so?
Because...
I haven't met you yet.
Oh...
So...
You don't have to worry about it.
Oh...
Hey.
I want you...
to do it with me.
What?
You're cute.
There, there.
You were surprised, weren't you?
You did that suddenly with me.
Really?
I was surprised.
I'll...
forgive you...
and make you forget everything.
Okay?
What?
Oh...
You'll be relieved when I touch your boobs, won't you?
Yes, I will.
How do you feel
compared to other doctors?
Well...
It's soft.
I feel relieved.
You're cute.
Do you like my boobs?
Yes, I do.
Okay.
Do you want to see inside?
Here.
Okay.
I'll touch your boobs
as much as you want.
Do you want to touch my boobs?
Yes.
Okay.
Do you want to do it?
Taiki is
a spoiled boy.
You can be spoiled
as much as you want.
You're cute.
You're like a baby.
Do you like my boobs?
Yes, I do.
You do, don't you?
Okay.
I'll touch your boobs
as much as you want.
You're cute.
Taiki,
do you get bigger easily?
Yes, I do.
You're a bad boy.
I need to punish you.
Punish me?
I'm scared.
Are you?
I'll be nice to you.
Taiki.
Look.
I love your boobs.
I'm not scared
no matter what you do.
You're a baby,
but I can feel your nipples.
You're a good boy.
I'm scared.
Taiki, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
I'm getting bigger.
Why?
My boobs.
What?
My boobs are delicious.
If you don't tell me,
I won't give you boobs.
I want more boobs.
Tell me more.
Taiki.
I'm so happy.
Do you want more boobs?
I'm hungry.
You're cute.
Next,
I'll make your boobs
beautiful.
What's wrong?
Taiki,
you like this the most.
I love it.
Are you okay?
Your boobs are relaxing you.
Your boobs are getting bigger.
I love it.
Do you want more boobs?
You're cute.
Your boobs are relaxing you.
I love it.
Do you feel good?
Do you feel good now?
Yes.
What?
I see.
You're cute.
Yes.
I want you to make
your boobs
beautiful.
Can you do it?
Yes.
Okay.
Come here.
Can you look at
where I am?
Can you see
from there?
Yes.
Taiki,
can you see
well?
Yes.
I can see well.
What's going on?
It's shiny.
What if it's dirty?
I'll clean it.
Okay.
You're good.
It feels good.
I know.
You're a good boy.
Yes.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're a good boy.
I'll clean the inside
with my fingers.
I see.
Can you do it?
Yes.
I see.
The inside.
It feels good.
I know.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I see.
I'll do it
while licking your ears.
Can you do it?
While licking?
Yes.
I'll do it.
You're good.
I'm so happy.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's clean now.
It's clean.
I cleaned your ears a lot.
Your mouth is sticky.
You're good.
You're a greedy baby.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Does it feel good?
I'll rub your ears.
Let's do it together.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll rub your ears.
Does it feel good?
You're a good baby.
I can't believe I'm having sex with you.
You're a bad baby.
I'm sorry for the bad baby.
I'll swallow it all.
Next, I'll hug you.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're a good baby.
I'm so happy.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm so happy.
I'll give you a massage.
You have a lot of hair.
You still have a long way to go.
Good night.
Big baby, come here.
You still have a long way to go.
Huh?
Oh no
AI, are you okay?
AI!
No!
I'm sorry, Su-yama.
I'm sorry.
I'll clean up to your breasts.
I'm sorry, Akane.
I'm sorry.
It's all right, it's all right.
It's all right.
You're a good girl.
It's all right, it's all right.
What am I going to do now...
That felt nice.
Awww, Nene-kun
Good boy
I'm happy that you feel better
I can't do it anymore.
Help me.
I can do it.
I can't do it anymore.
It hurts so much.
You did a good job.
You did your best.
I can't do it anymore.