I'm home.
Why does he refuse me?
I wanted to do it.
I gave him a sign to let me do it.
But he didn't notice it.
I want to do it.
Is there anyone here?
I'm home.
Welcome back.
What is it?
Did you just get home?
Yes.
What are you doing here late at night?
Are you getting tired?
No, I'm not tired at all.
You are a good girl.
But, you should go out only at night.
I understand.
Shuji is your brother, right?
You should be aware of him, and consider your father.
I really can understand him, and I don't want to be a careless daughter.
And next thing is,
Shuji is studying hard for his entrance exam.
You're going to college, too.
Why don't you give him a day off?
Me?
Yes.
That's right.
He has a younger brother.
I'm listening.
Oh, my.
What about you, Shuji?
I'm not at home, so I can't say that.
Shuji is going to school now.
He's studying until late at night.
Wait, wait.
That means you can do it right at home when you want to do it.
That's great.
I understand. I'll talk to him later.
Are you listening to me?
Yes, I am.
Is Shuji home yet?
I want to do it as soon as possible.
He's back.
I'm home.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
Something's wrong.
I'm just kissing you.
But we're brothers.
We're not connected.
I can't do it.
I want to do it when I want to do it.
What's wrong with you, Shuji?
You've grown up so much.
You're excited because you can't do it.
Because I don't have a car.
Is that so?
You're so cute.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
I just kissed you.
I can't do it.
Don't hide it.
I'm taking a bath now, so don't make a loud noise.
You're standing up.
Did you kill him?
I'm scared.
I should have noticed earlier.
Don't let it out.
If you let it out, you can't do it.
I can't do it.
I'm scared.
I have to do it.
What?
Of course you have to do it.
I'm scared.
If you don't talk, Dad won't know you're here.
I'm sorry, I have to go to bed.
It's okay, you don't have time for that.
I don't have time for that.
It's okay.
I'm going to sleep.
It tickles.
I can't tell if you speak out loud.
I'm going to sleep.
You can't.
It tickles.
I wanted to do it today.
I'm sorry.
What?
Why?
It tickles.
Did you want to say it?
You can't say it right away.
What did I do?
I'm not satisfied.
It tickles.
Why are you so close to me?
I'm so excited that my body is wet.
It tickles.
Does it tickle?
I'm going to sleep.
You can't.
You can't speak out loud.
I'm going to sleep.
You did it, didn't you?
Hang in there a little longer.
If you do it a little longer, I'll feel bad.
It tickles.
You can't.
You can't speak out loud.
It tickles.
You've been sleeping all the time.
I'm going to sleep.
I feel good.
You feel good.
I'm in trouble.
I feel good.
I can't believe I was hiding this.
It tickles.
What?
I'm in trouble.
Wait a minute.
I can't.
I'm going to sleep.
Then you can speak out loud.
I can't.
You slept a lot.
I'm in trouble.
Don't worry.
You can do a lot every day from now on.
Every day?
I'm looking forward to it.
I feel good.
I'm in trouble.
What's going to happen?
You're going to the bathroom, aren't you?
I'm in trouble.
You have to take off your pants.
What are you doing?
I'm in trouble.
Why are you standing up?
It's morning.
You're standing up because it's morning.
You can pee.
I can't.
Why?
If you don't, I'll do it.
What do you mean?
Wait a minute.
I can't.
If you want to go to the bathroom, do it.
I just wanted to have sex.
I can't.
It feels good here, doesn't it?
Wait a minute.
What's going on?
Do you want to touch me?
I can't.
It feels good.
Do you like my boobs?
I like them.
If you touch my boobs, they'll get hard again.
It feels good.
It feels good here.
It's the best in the morning.
I can't.
What's going on?
Are you going to go to the bathroom?
I can't.
I can't go to the bathroom yet.
It's too hard.
It's hard, isn't it?
I can't.
I can't go to the bathroom yet.
You said you couldn't go to the bathroom until I said you could.
It feels good.
I can't.
Do you want to go to the bathroom?
All right.
Can you go to the bathroom like this?
Do you want to stand up?
Come here.
You can go to the bathroom like this.
I can't go to the bathroom yet.
It smells good.
It feels good.
It's the best in the morning.
I can't.
I can't move.
It's the best.
I can't.
It feels good.
You did a great job in the morning.
Thank you.
I'm relieved.
You can go to the bathroom.
Thank you.
I'm relieved.
It's the best in the morning.
I woke up.
It was just dawn.
It's just dawn.
You're fine.
8.5 degrees...
Good boy. Were you studying?
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
Don't move.
You were studying, weren't you?
I can't study.
I'm doing it on my own.
I can't do it.
Shunji.
You're an examiner.
You have to study properly.
I have to study.
You were using this?
Yes.
This and...
Thank you.
I can't concentrate at all.
I'm doing it on my own.
You have to study properly.
I can't concentrate.
Concentrate properly.
You have to concentrate.
I can't do it.
I can't do it at all.
You have a good reaction.
I can't concentrate.
It's okay.
Studying is important.
I can't do it.
You have a good reaction.
Are you ready?
You're ready, right?
Of course.
I came here because I wanted to see you.
I can't do it.
How do you feel?
Look at me.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
You were excited when you touched my boobs.
I can't do it.
What's wrong?
I'm not satisfied yet.
It feels so good.
You can do it if you're so excited.
One more time?
Let's do it again.
Come here.
I want to touch you.
You can lick me if you want.
I can't do it.
You're wet.
You're so excited that you can't do it.
Let me touch you.
It feels so good.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
It feels so good.
I can't do it.
Are you okay?
I was trying to do it.
It feels so good.
You're licking me.
I can't do it.
It feels so good.
Are you sleepy?
Are you always sleepy?
Wake up.
It's hot.
It's amazing that you're young.
Move more.
I can't do it.
It feels so good.
Wait.
I can't do it.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
I can't do it.
Do it properly.
It feels so good.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I can't do it.
I moved my legs a lot.
It feels so good.
I can't do it.
Do you want to do it again?
Let's go together.
Wait.
I can't do it.
Move more.
You're so cute.
I'm surprised.
I can't do it.
It's hot.
Wait.
I can't do it.
Let's go!
It's amazing.
You did it three times in the morning.
You haven't done it yet.
You moved your legs a lot.
You did it three times in the morning.
You can still do it because your legs are so hard.
I can't do it.
It's okay.
You can do it at home anytime.
You should study hard.
You were studying until a while ago.
When you finish studying, let's have sex again.
You can do it anytime because you're at home.
Let's do it after studying.
I can't do it.
I can't concentrate on studying in this environment.
I'm home.
It smells good.
It's curry rice.
Give me a bite.
Is this for me?
I'm hungry.
Home is the best.
It's rare to see you at home.
Can you make curry for me?
It looks delicious.
What's your name?
I'm Naoki.
Naoki.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Who made this?
My mom.
This curry rice is the best.
What about you?
I'm going out to buy something.
It's delicious.
It's been a while since I came home.
Have some curry.
Thank you.
I'm Naoki.
Thank you for the meal.
Let's eat.
It's delicious.
How many times have we met?
Is it the third time?
That's right.
It's been a while.
How have you been?
Do you get along well?
Yes.
It's delicious.
You like curry, don't you?
I love it.
I think this curry is the best curry in the world.
My mom taught me that.
Your mom's curry is delicious.
Men say they can't take off their stomachs if they grab their stomachs.
What do you think?
That's right.
I think rice is delicious.
I'll make curry for my boyfriend.
I'll make sure he doesn't miss it.
He hasn't met me at all lately.
I see.
I made curry for him.
I want a boyfriend.
He hasn't met me at all lately.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Yes, I have.
How about you?
I don't have a girlfriend.
What do you do when you can't meet your girlfriend?
There are times when you want to meet your girlfriend.
There are times when you can't sleep.
When I can't sleep?
I don't think so.
That's good.
You're a pervert, aren't you?
You look like a pervert.
What are you talking about?
I'm not a pervert.
I'm more like a souffle.
When I want someone to be close to me, I think it's important to have someone I can meet anytime.
I see.
You can meet your girlfriend as soon as you call her.
You can make a souffle.
Try it.
Here you are.
What's your name?
My girlfriend is a passenger.
A passenger?
Yes.
It's the exam period, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
You can't meet your girlfriend at all.
Do you have a girlfriend?
We're both studying.
I have a girlfriend.
That's great.
If you can't meet your girlfriend, you must have a girlfriend.
You're a pervert, aren't you?
That's why you should make a souffle.
It's very convenient.
You can meet your girlfriend as soon as you call her.
I was honest with you a while ago.
But I want to make a souffle now.
I want to make a souffle at that time.
I see.
Wait a minute.
What's this?
I'm sorry.
Did I do this to you?
Do you look like you're going to be stabbed?
I see.
You were looking at my boobs, weren't you?
No, I didn't.
Or did you look at my butt?
Minami, wait a minute.
I can't believe you're making a souffle with me.
I'm your sister.
I just realized something important.
By the way, we're not connected to each other.
That means we can do it.
What are you talking about?
I'm so happy.
Minami, what are you doing?
I can do it.
Wait a minute.
It's painful, isn't it?
What are you talking about?
You don't have a girlfriend, do you?
I'll be your girlfriend.
You're so young.
I don't hate you.
What are you doing?
You don't hate me, do you?
You're so cute.
You're so small.
Do you like me?
You don't care about me, do you?
Are you looking forward to it?
Wait a minute.
You can't do that.
I can't do that?
That's...
Is that so?
You want me to do it, don't you?
I want you to do it.
You're so cute.
It's hard.
Was it this hard?
I'm sorry I didn't notice.
It's hot.
Hey.
Do you have a lot of hair?
I can't help it.
I'll take care of your hair.
You smell like a good boy.
My head is spinning.
You're so cute.
Do you like me?
I'm so cute.
You have a lot of hair.
I'll take care of your hair.
It's delicious.
I can't stop.
What's that?
You're so cute.
Does it feel good?
Your mouth.
Did you like it?
No.
Don't do that.
I want to touch you.
Is that okay?
We're not connected.
If you touch me, I'll put you in the blanket.
I can't do it.
Come here.
Are you going to stop?
Look at me.
I'm like this because of you.
Are you going to stop?
It feels good when I put you in the blanket.
Come here.
I'll make you feel better.
Does it feel good?
Is it dangerous?
I'm going to sleep.
Wait a minute.
I'll put you in the blanket.
There.
I haven't put you in the blanket yet.
Why did you stop?
You can't do that.
You can't do that until I tell you to stop.
I want to touch you.
It's hard.
It's hot.
I want you to touch me.
Come here.
You can't do that.
Why did you stop?
I'm going to leave soon.
Wait.
I'm going to leave.
Is it dangerous?
You can't do that.
I'm going to leave.
It feels good.
I want to move.
Don't stop me.
You're amazing.
You're drooling.
You're drooling a lot.
She won't do this to me, will she?
Come here.
You're drooling a lot.
Did you feel good?
I wanted to do it more.
I thought I could do it anytime.
I'll let you go this time.
So, you can do it anytime.
Did you feel good?
See you later.
What are you doing?
You're studying.
You're studying hard.
I'm going to leave.
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
I'll do what I want to do.
You can study.
Don't worry about it.
Study.
I'm studying.
Don't worry about it.
Study.
I'm going to leave.
You're the best.
You're drooling.
I'm going to leave.
Hey.
It's so good.
I'm going to cry.
Crunch, crunch, crunch.
The next problem is...
I'm going to cry.
It's so good.
Give it to me.
I'm not going to bother you today.
I'm going to cry.
It's hot.
It's very hard.
I'm going to cry.
Do you want me?
You have to say you want me.
I want you.
I'm going to cry.
You can do it.
It's hot.
I'm going to cry.
I love you.
A little more!
Hang in there!
She rubbed my eyes.
She rubbed my eyes!
Ah!
Once more!
It hurts!
Study hard!
It's true that it's hard to study.
Then,
I'll show you the problem here.
The problem here is...
A, B, and X?
I don't know.
It feels good.
I'll tell you.
This is the correct answer.
It feels good.
I'll answer the equation.
It's too good.
Don't be so serious.
Think about it.
Let's go! Let's go!
I can't stop it.
Show me.
I have to see the problem.
The blood pressure is dropping.
Oh, no!
The air is stuck to the ground.
It's so uncomfortable.
Oh, no!
I'm stuck.
It's coming.
It's stuck to my back.
Why are you stopping it?
You can't stop it.
Move your hips.
Move your hands.
You have to study.
Your hands are stuck.
You can't stop it.
No, you have to study.
Move your hips.
No, no, no, no.
No!
It's so uncomfortable.
Isn't it?
What?
Isn't it uncomfortable?
I haven't said it's uncomfortable yet.
It's tight.
It's very tight.
It feels good.
It's tight.
It's coming out.
Study hard.
It's coming again.
Let's go to bed.
Hurry up.
Is this also studying?
Is it okay?
Hello.
Minami.
I was waiting for you.
What's in it?
You're cheating.
I'm going out.
What do you want to do?
I want to take a bath.
You said you'd go out with me anytime.
What were you doing alone?
I'm going to take a bath.
Call me.
You're cute.
I'm going to take a bath.
Do you like being with me?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It feels good for me, too.
What?
Did you wash it properly?
I washed it properly.
Really?
I'll wash it for you.
I washed it properly.
It's okay.
I'll wash it properly.
I'll use this.
I'll wash it clean.
It feels good.
I'm just washing it.
It's thick.
Naoki.
Don't you know Minami?
I don't know her.
I see.
It looks like she's back.
Have you seen her yet?
I haven't seen her yet.
What's wrong?
I think she said she was going out.
Really?
Yes, I made a mistake.
Are you going out again?
I see.
We've been living together for about two months.
How's Minami?
She's doing well.
I see.
We've been getting along well.
Really?
That's great.
It's all thanks to you.
Minami.
I wonder if she comes home when you're around.
Yes, that's right.
Really?
Yes, we've been getting along well.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Minami.
I wonder if she comes home when you're around.
Your mother found out.
I'm glad.
I want to go to the bathroom.
This is the bathroom.
I'm so cold.
I want to go to the bathroom.
But I'm so happy.
It's delicious.
I'm so happy.
I'm so cold.
Your face is wet.
Did you see that?
Do you want me to wash your face?
Your face is wet.
Did you clean your face?
Yes.
I'm so cold.
I want you to dry your face.
Did you dry your face?
I'm so cold.
I want you to dry your face.
I have a tongue.
Ouch!
You have a lot of bumps.
I'm going to eat your bun.
Ouch!
I want you to rub my fingers.
Okay.
I'll rub your fingers.
Ouch!
What's going on?
You have a lot of bumps.
I want you to rub my fingers.
Let's eat.
Wait.
Don't.
It's so hot!
Is it getting tight?
Is it tight?
Do you want me to cover your mouth?
It's so hot...
Are you scared?
It's hot.
It's hard.
What do you want to do?
I can't wait.
I want to put it in my mouth.
Me, too.
Give it to me.
I can't wait.
It's hot.
Do you like cats?
I can't wait.
It's hot.
I want to put it into my mouth.
tilt
Tipsy
I want you to touch me
To the vinegar
Why did you stop me?
I told you not to stop me.
You know that, don't you?
I told you not to do that.
She found out.
Be quiet.
I'm hungry.
I'm so hungry.
I feel sick.
I'm sick.
I'm so sick.
Come here.
Oh, it feels so good.
I feel like I'm in heaven.
It feels so good.
I can't stop.
I feel like I'm in heaven.
It's so hard.
It feels so good.
I can't do it anymore.
It's so hard.
Wow.
Hey, it's so slimy.
There's a lot coming out.
How was it?
It's going to be fun from now on.
Because I can do it anytime.
Kiss?
Hey, Nanki?
Yes?
I think I heard Miyai's voice.
What?
Do you know?
No, I don't know.
I see. How many people are there?
Yes.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, I'm sleepy.
Hey, touch me.
I'm not taking a break.
What?
It's okay.
Touch me.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, I'm sleepy.
What?
I'm going to do it.
I told you to touch me.
No, not yet.
Oh, it feels good.
Hey, does it really hurt?
I can't believe it.
I'm sorry.
I was going to do it.
Hey, let me stand up.
I can't do it right away.
Why?
Because I just went there.
But you can stand up, right?
I can't do it today.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I told you it's too early.
I put a rubber band on my waist.
If you didn't put it on, it would have been faster.
I can't do it.
Go home.
Why?
I can't do it.
Don't throw away the rubber band.
I know.
I'll throw it away.
I'll give you a tissue.
I can't do it.
Why do I have to complain?
I'm so annoyed.
I can't use it.
I should have put it on my face.
Why did I say it's too early?
I don't know.
I put a rubber band on my waist.
If you didn't put it on, it would have been faster.
I thought it was good.
I can't do it.
I'm home.
What is it?
It's nothing.
Who was it?
There was a man.
What was his name?
Taro? No.
Shinji? No.
He was a man before.
Who was his name?
I can't remember.
There was a man.
He was a good man.
He was a student.
He was young.
He was a voice actor.
There was a good man.
I can't remember his name.
I'm home.
Ami.
What are you doing?
I have a day off.
It's not good.
Why?
Kenji is there.
Kenji?
I don't remember his name.
I'm kidding.
I remember his name.
I remember.
I told you it's not good.
I know.
Wait.
I haven't confirmed it yet.
My brother is...
My mother's son.
What are you talking about?
It's been 3 to 4 months.
He wasn't at home.
He was my brother.
Why is his blood connected?
It's not related.
Are you crazy?
Wait.
I'm sorry.
I know.
It's not related.
In a drama,
they get married.
Like marriage.
Marriage?
It's in the drama.
Drama?
Yeah.
I mean,
it's not like they're not related,
so there's no problem.
Right?
I don't think there's a problem,
but that's what I'm thinking.
No, no, no, no.
There's no way.
There's a distinction.
It's complicated, so it's in the drama.
Yeah, right.
It's not good.
No, no, no, it's not about me.
It's about a friend.
A friend?
Yeah, recently,
my parents got married again,
and they had a sibling.
Isn't it my family?
Yeah, I thought it was similar.
I told you.
Confirmation.
I told you, but I'll tell you later.
Well.
So there's no problem.
There's no problem, but there is.
That's why it's in the drama, right?
Yeah, well, well, well.
You know that, don't you?
I know.
How many times have I told you?
How long are you going to be childish?
That's enough, that's enough.
I'm always telling you to dress up.
Well, you should change.
Yes, yes.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's creaking.
Oh, no.
There's no problem.
So I can do it, right?
Well, let's do it.
Yes.
Can I come in?
Oh, yes, please.
What, are you studying?
Oh, yes.
Ero.
Hey, your brother.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Kenji?
Yes, I'm Kenji.
So what?
How many years are you in now?
About 2 or 3 years old.
Oh, I'm in my third year now.
You're in your third year, right?
I knew it.
That's right, I knew it.
I told you.
So what?
Exam this year?
That's right.
Wow, that's great.
Is there anything amazing about it?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, but a little.
Yes, I'll do my best.
That's right.
You said you were going to get into a good place, didn't you?
Well.
That's great.
You've been studying all the time.
Don't you have a club?
One study?
I've already retired from the club.
Oh, you're retired.
Oh, you said you were retired.
What club was it?
Was it something like soccer?
Oh, it was a track and field club.
Oh, a track and field club.
That's a lot of information.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, I see.
Huh.
What, do you have a girlfriend?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I don't have a girlfriend.
You don't have a girlfriend?
Oh, oh.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
Since when?
No, even if you ask me when, I'm not sure.
So what?
Have you had a girlfriend since you've been in school?
Not exactly, but we were together for 2 years.
Oh, you were together?
Wow, that's great. You're still young.
But now I really want to pass the exam.
You're so talkative.
No, no, no.
That's great.
I see.
I've always wanted a younger brother.
It's great to have a younger brother.
That's true.
I'm happy to hear that.
I think it's a good thing to have a younger brother.
You don't have many siblings, do you?
Do you have a lot of siblings?
No, but I've been single all my life.
Wow, that's great.
I'm happy to have an older sister.
Really? I'm happy to hear that.
I think it's a good thing to have a younger brother.
It's a good thing to have a younger brother.
I think so, too.
Which do you prefer, having a younger sister or having a younger brother?
What do you think?
I don't know.
I think it's a good thing to have a younger brother.
Did you know that?
What?
If you don't have a younger brother, you can do a lot of things.
A lot of things?
A lot of things.
Did you know that?
I don't want to make it a problem.
I was wondering what to do.
But when I checked it earlier, it said there was no problem.
What did you check?
There's no problem.
Even if you do this.
You can do this.
Did you know that?
I don't know.
There's no problem if you mess with this.
He said it's okay because he doesn't have a younger brother.
It's not good.
You can't do that.
I can't?
It's good.
It's good to have a younger brother.
It's the best.
What?
What's wrong?
It's okay. There's no problem.
Don't worry. I won't make a problem.
I've decided not to make a problem since I became an adult.
It's okay.
Your neck is standing up.
Is that so?
I'm sorry. I'm the only one touching you.
I'm sorry.
Tell me.
You're my brother.
You prepared a different kind of tea.
Do you want to touch me?
I'll touch you.
I'll touch you, too.
Touch me a lot.
How is it?
It's big and soft.
Can I touch you from here?
I touched you like this.
You can touch me.
I can't touch you.
Can't you touch me?
I'm in trouble.
I'll touch you from here.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It feels really good.
Let's lick your boobs.
Lick?
Go to the futon.
How do you take off your necktie?
I took it off.
Go to the futon.
Lick my boobs.
Can I?
What?
I checked that there was no problem.
Lick my boobs.
It feels good.
Is there really no problem?
I told you there was no problem.
Lick my boobs.
It feels good.
I'll lick your boobs, too.
This side?
Which side do you like?
Right or left?
I don't know.
Which side is sensitive?
Does it feel good?
Great.
This side is bigger.
How about this side?
What?
How about here?
When was the last time you licked here?
You didn't do it?
You did it yesterday.
What did you do?
What?
Nothing.
I was reading a book.
I see.
You're watching a video.
That's right.
You should have told me.
I would have given you a treat.
What?
You've had a lot of boyfriends.
What a waste.
But, you know...
You don't have to worry about a treat anymore.
Right?
What?
You're doing this.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
I'm scared.
You're embarrassed.
Show me your face.
You're amazing.
You're so energetic.
You did it yesterday, right?
That's why your ears are like this.
You're amazing.
It's good to be young.
You smell.
I don't smell.
You haven't changed since you came back from school.
You smell.
I think you smell like a gentleman.
Why?
Really?
You didn't do it yesterday.
You did it a while ago.
I feel sorry for you.
I'll make it easy for you.
It's fun.
You're the best.
Kenji.
You react well.
You're the best.
I can't stand it.
What?
That's not good.
It's okay. I told you it's okay.
It's okay.
Shut up.
Look.
It's not in yet.
It's in.
You're the best.
I'm sorry.
You're good.
I feel great.
I can't do it.
I feel like I'm going to die.
You can't do it.
You have to endure it.
Do you understand?
You can't do it until I say so.
I feel great.
I can't do it.
I feel like I'm going to die.
I feel great.
You're the best.
You can't do it.
You have to endure it.
I feel great.
Even if I feel more than I do yesterday...
It feels like five times more than yesterday.
It feels the best.
It's fun.
This is not good.
It feels good.
Hey.
Kenji.
I tried it.
Follow me.
Yes, yes.
More, more, more.
No.
Don't go.
It feels good.
No.
It's the best.
Give me more.
Kenji.
Do it again.
Yes.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
It's great.
It feels good.
Yes.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
No.
Wait. It feels good.
Let's go.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
More.
No.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
Really?
Yes.
Go.
You can go.
It feels good.
I want to go out.
It's great.
You're so energetic that you can go out.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Actually, I wanted to do more.
It's okay.
It felt so good.
I'll forgive you today.
It's hot.
Calm down.
It felt so good.
I'll get along with you.
Good luck with your study.
See you later.
Why are you sleeping?
Kenji, good morning.
Why don't you wake up?
Why?
I gave you a chance.
Why are you sleeping?
Kenji, good morning.
Why are you in my room?
He's here.
He has a button.
You were awake.
and what are you doing?
what are you doing, Milady?
did you wake up?
what are you doing?
what am I doing?
I'm trying to wake you up
you know what?
You just came back from the school reunion.
You said you have a good girl at home.
You refused to be a manager.
Why are you sleeping?
I don't want you to say that.
How long are you sleeping?
What time do you think it is?
I'm going to sleep at this time.
It's not time yet.
It's going to be dark soon.
It's early.
Why do you try to sleep right away?
Hey, lick here.
Lick here?
Lick here.
Oh, it feels good.
Hey, take off your pants and lick here.
Hey, lick here.
What?
Don't you understand what I'm saying?
You've been studying too much, so you've gone crazy, haven't you?
Hey, lick here.
Your eyes are very wet, aren't they?
I was looking forward to talking to you.
You've been wet all the way from the train.
Oh, it feels good.
Yes, lick a lot.
Hey, lick here again.
Lick a lot.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
You can lick it.
Oh, it feels good.
I'm going to put it in.
What?
Here.
You wanted to put it in early, didn't you?
Oh, that's...
Oh, it's in.
Don't do that.
Oh, it feels good.
Can't you see where it's in?
Do you want to see it better?
You're a pervert, aren't you?
It's in there.
Oh, it's in there.
Oh, it's amazing.
It's in there.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's getting harder and harder.
Oh, it's in there.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it hurts.
Oh, it's amazing.
What?
Does it feel good?
I know.
Give me more.
Oh, it's amazing.
It's in there.
Oh, it feels good.
You're a pervert, aren't you?
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it's in there.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it's hot.
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
Hey, Kenji, move.
Hey, come on, move.
Don't make yourself feel better.
Oh, more.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it's good there.
Move more there.
More.
Oh, it feels good.
No, no, no.
Oh, it's good there.
It feels good.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
Move more firmly.
Here.
Give me more.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it's good there.
Oh, it feels good there.
Oh, more.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
No, no, no.
Where are you going?
Go, go, go.
Oh, it feels good.
Move more firmly.
Oh, it's amazing.
No, you can't go yet.
You can't go until I say so.
Move more firmly.
You can't go yet.
No, you can't.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
You can put your hand here.
No, you can't go yet.
You can't go yet.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
Go, go, go.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
What should I do?
It's okay.
You can go.
Move more firmly.
Oh, it feels good.
No, you can't go yet.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it feels good.
It's okay.
You can go.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
Move more firmly.
You can put your hand here.
Oh, it feels good.
Go, go, go.
I'm sleepy.
I want to sleep like this.
I have to take this off.
It's hot.
Can I sleep here?
Let's sleep.
Don't you want to sleep?
What?
Can I sleep here?
It's the same house.
Good night.
Oh, it feels good.
Kenji.
Yes.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
What?
Kenji.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
I'm coming in.
I'm sorry to wake you up early in the morning.
It's okay.
Did Ami come home yesterday?
What?
I didn't see it.
I see.
I told her to come home.
I have to wait.
I'm sorry.
I told Ami to come home with a new family.
I see.
You have a good daughter.
What?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I told you to come home.
I see.
Do you think so?
Yes.
I want you to be strong.
Did I raise you badly?
I don't think so.
I'm bothering you a lot.
No, I don't think so.
I raised you alone.
I don't think it was good.
I don't think so.
I want you to be happy.
I want you to get married in a few years.
I don't think so.
Ami is coming out.
I'm going home.
I'm sorry.
Please tell me when Ami comes home.
What?
I'm going to be found out.
Are you going to be found out?
What are you going to do if you are found out?
I'm fine.
My father told me that I was safe.
You are not safe.
I'm safe.
What?
You are in a hurry.
What if you are found out?
I'm going to be found out.
Are you going to be found out?
Hey.
I want to see you.
Look at you.
You are patient.
What's wrong?
You have a lot of hair.
You are going to be found out.
Look at you.
You have a lot of hair.
I'm sorry.
You don't like it?
You have a lot of hair.
What?
You don't like it?
I'm going to be found out.
You can't do it yet.
Why do you want to be found out?
I want to do it.
I want to do it, too.
You said you don't like it.
I'm sorry.
You are so impatient that I'm going to be found out.
You are doing something amazing.
You have been putting up with my body for a while.
You have a lot of hair.
You don't like it?
What?
You have a lot of hair.
You are amazing.
It's getting harder and harder.
You are energetic.
You don't like it?
It feels good.
This side, too.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
Let me take off your underwear.
Let me lick you.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
Let me in.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
It feels good.
Go deeper.
Shake your hips.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
You shouldn't do that.
It feels good.
Go deeper.
No, no, no.
Oh, no.
Go deeper.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
It feels so good.
It feels good.
Don't stop.
More.
It feels good.
Give me more.
More.
It feels good.
Go deeper.
No, no, no.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
It feels so good.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Go deeper.
It feels good.
More.
Touch more.
Oh, no.
It feels so good.
Go deeper.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
Go deeper.
No, I can't stop.
More.
What?
Oh, no.
It feels good.
Give me more.
Oh, no.
It feels good here.
No, it feels good.
Oh, no.
Go here.
It feels good.
More.
Here.
It feels good here.
Oh, no.
I want more.
I can't stop.
It feels good.
Go.
Oh, no.
You're all wet.
Why did you do that?
It's not good.
More here.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Come here.
It's a mess.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
More.
Give me more.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
What?
Let's go together.
Together.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
Let's go.
No.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
What time is it?
What?
I'm going to be late for work.
You're going to be late for school, too.
That's right.
Oh, no.
I have to change.
I have to get ready.
That's right.
I have to go to school.
What?
You have to go to school.
Hey.
Let's continue when you get home.
What?
Continue?
Continue what?
That's right.
No.
I don't feel well.
What?
Don't worry.
When you go to school, you can take a break.
Let's continue when you get home.
Hey.
We're brothers.
You have to say you want to do it.
You have to say yes when you want to do it.
When you get home, you have to say yes.
Do you want to do it?
Let's do it.
Oh, no.
I have to go to the bathroom.
See you.
Kenji, you have to go to school, too.
Where did I put my clothes?
See you.
Have a good day.
Kenji, you have to get up.
See you.
When you get home.
When I want to do it, I do it.
When I'm satisfied, I do it.
You're amazing.
I can't stand it.
Ah!
No!
Not yet!
I can't do it.
Did you say it?
I can't believe it.
I said no.
It's too early.
I can't help it.
I said no.
Go home.
It's too early.
I can't believe it.
I'm so tired.
I thought I could do this and that.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
I wonder if anyone's home.
This is no good.
By the way, my brother was here.
We're not connected.
When did he get here?
I'm home.
I'm so tired.
Get out of the way.
You drank a lot.
The beer was so strong.
By the way, your brother was here.
What was his name?
Shunsuke.
It's been three months.
Is that so?
Shunsuke?
Yes, Shunsuke.
Get along with him.
Shunsuke and I are not connected.
That's right.
What are you talking about?
Shunsuke is my father's son.
You are my daughter.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Can blood-related siblings get married?
What?
I have a friend like that.
I'm worried about the other person's brother.
I'm worried about that kind of relationship.
I don't think it's a problem.
Is that so?
Don't think about weird things.
It's not me.
I thought you were home.
Do you think I would do that?
I haven't seen it yet.
I don't know.
I don't trust you.
It's a friend's story.
I don't know anything.
Is that girl okay?
I don't know.
Sit down.
Let's talk.
Okay.
Sit here.
Don't sit far away.
We haven't talked to each other for a long time.
That's right.
I'm busy.
I have a lot of work.
I'm not at home.
That's right.
Are you OO?
I'm OO.
Are you wearing OO uniform?
That's right.
How many years have you been studying?
I've been studying for three years.
I see.
Are you an entrance exam student?
That's right.
Are you studying?
I'm studying a little.
Are you in a club?
I'm not in a club.
You don't have any muscles.
That's right.
Is school fun?
It's fun.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I have a girlfriend.
I see.
How long have you been dating?
About six months.
I think it's been a long time.
I see.
It's been six months.
You've just started dating.
I think so.
It's been a long time.
You are popular, aren't you?
Don't you have a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
You're lying.
You're going to be told off.
I don't have a girlfriend.
You don't have a girlfriend.
Don't you want a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
You want a girlfriend, don't you?
I don't know how to find a girlfriend.
Do you have a dating app?
I can't do that because I'm a woman.
You're serious.
I think there are people who want to have a girlfriend.
Do you think so?
I'm close to you.
I'm close to you because you don't notice me.
What are you talking about?
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
Did you get bigger when you talked about it?
I got bigger when I touched you.
You're cute.
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
I'm close to you.
But we are siblings.
It's okay. We are not blood-related.
Your mother came home.
My mother?
I don't think so.
She went out with me because she had something to talk about.
Is that so?
I don't think she'll be back in 15 minutes.
Besides, it's thrilling.
But...
I can't do this with my girlfriend.
I see.
Are you going to do it here?
No?
You don't want to?
No, I don't want to.
You want it, don't you?
You're sweating.
I'm not sweating.
It feels good.
Do you like here?
Do you like it?
It's my first time.
Really?
You're cute.
Oh, my God.
You're sweating a lot.
A little more.
It's hot.
You're bleeding.
I'm sorry.
You're sweating a lot.
You don't want to?
No, I don't want to.
I'm sorry.
I'm sure I'm better than her.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I don't have time to do this.
I want to lick you all the time.
Lick me, too.
Yeah.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
It feels good.
I'm touching you.
I'm sweating a lot.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
I can't do this.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Oh, my God.
I can't do this.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Touch me.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I feel good, too.
I can't do this.
I'm sweating a lot.
It's hot.
I can't do this.
I can't do this yet.
I want to do this more.
Take your time.
It feels good.
I can't do this.
I'm sweating a lot.
It's hot.
I can't do this.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I'll make you clean.
You're clean.
Can you do this more?
My mom will come back.
I can't do this.
I'll make you clean.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
What were you two doing?
We were talking.
Really?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
It's okay.
We're friends.
What's that?
What happened?
We were eating sweets.
You should've told me.
I'm sorry.
I'll tell you.
Are you okay?
Do you know how to do this?
Yes.
This is a revenge, so I'm fine.
You're studying hard.
If you don't know how to do this, I'll teach you.
I'll teach you.
You haven't taught me at all.
Is that so?
I can study by myself, so don't teach me.
Don't say that.
This is useless in society.
But I have to study for the entrance exam.
You're serious.
I'll teach you.
But I'll teach you something better than studying.
That's...
I just did it.
It's okay.
We're a couple, right?
Is that okay?
Isn't it?
You have a girlfriend, but you're with me.
That's right.
I want to do it when I want to do it.
You'll answer me, right?
Is that so?
Isn't it?
You don't have a right to refuse.
I see.
Come on.
I want to do it.
What should I do?
You're younger than me, right?
I'm older than you, so I have to listen to you.
But brothers don't usually do this.
Shut up.
I want to do it, so I'll do it.
Don't bite me like that.
You're getting bigger.
I'll make you feel better.
That's great.
Mom, I'm back from shopping.
I'm making rice now, so I have plenty of time.
Okay.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
That's great.
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
Do you lick such a place?
Do you like it here?
It feels good.
You think it feels good, don't you?
You want to do it.
It feels good.
I'm going to do something she hasn't done.
You're so soft.
That's great.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
How do you feel?
You want to do it, don't you?
I want to do it.
You can't do it yet.
I can't do it.
You don't want to do it?
I want to do it.
I'm not going to do it yet.
I can't do it.
You can't do it yet.
You can't do it faster.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
You can't do it yet.
I want you to feel good about me.
Touch me.
Okay.
I got excited when you licked me.
I'm going to put my fingers in.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Touch me more.
It feels good.
Here?
That's good.
Hey, lick me.
Ah.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
Ah.
You're good at licking me.
Lick me more.
Ah.
It feels good.
Ouch.
Ah.
I can't stand it anymore.
Let's do it.
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
Ah.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Ah.
It feels good.
It's hard.
Ah.
Ouch.
If you speak too loudly, my mom might hear you.
Ah.
You're right.
I should be careful.
Ah.
But it feels good.
So I speak loudly.
Ah.
What?
The meal is ready.
Get in.
Ah.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I was just getting changed.
Oh, I see.
I came to pick you up because dinner's ready.
You're going to eat, right?
Yeah, I'm going to eat.
What are you doing?
No, no, no.
I was just getting changed.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
What?
No, I'm not embarrassed in front of a girl.
Hey, what are you doing?
What am I doing?
I was just getting changed.
What are you doing?
I came to pick you up because dinner's ready.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Well, there are a lot of things for girls.
Hey, by the way, do you know Shunsuke?
What? I don't know.
I just went to his room, but he wasn't there.
Didn't you say you'd teach him how to study?
What?
I didn't say that.
Didn't you say you'd take him for a walk?
I guess so.
He seems to like to take a walk.
Is that so?
Well, dinner's ready, so come on.
Yeah, I got it.
Hey, are you really okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You don't have a stomachache, do you?
You told me earlier.
You're out of breath, but you're not sick, are you?
I'm fine.
Really?
I'm fine. Don't come.
What are you talking about?
I'm worried about you.
I'll be right there, so get out of here.
You don't look well.
I'm fine.
I'll be right there.
Get out of here.
Call me if you need anything.
Yeah.
I'll be right there.
Hey, what are you doing?
Mom's here.
I want to do it when I want to.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
How's it going, Tomoi?
Are you used to living together?
Yeah, I guess so.
I'm getting used to it.
I'm sorry to ask you this all of a sudden.
I'm happy to have a dad and a sister.
I'm glad to hear that.
How's your study going?
I'm doing pretty well because I have an exam this year.
I see.
I might be able to teach you something you don't know.
If you want me to teach you something, let me know.
Tomoi.
Yes?
If you don't know anything, you can ask me.
You don't know anything?
You want me to teach you?
We're family.
Don't worry about that.
I see.
Naomi.
You didn't do so well in college.
But you can teach me something, right?
I see.
I'm studying for the entrance exam.
Teach me something.
I see.
I said I see.
You can teach me something, right?
I see.
Tomoi.
Yes?
Ask Naomi to teach you something.
But she seems busy.
She's not busy.
I have a lot of things to do.
I know.
I don't think she's at home.
You should get a job.
Right, Tomoi?
What?
I'm going to college.
I'm studying for the entrance exam.
You're family.
You should study hard.
I see.
I'm going to work.
See you later.
Can you clean up here?
Okay.
See you later.
Bye.
What?
Right?
Yes.
I can teach you something.
But she seems busy.
Really?
You should study hard.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What?
You should have told me earlier.
What do you mean?
You stood up when you saw me, didn't you?
No.
It's a physiological phenomenon.
I tend to stand up in the morning.
But you were looking at my chest.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were wearing sexy clothes.
So, I was worried about you.
I didn't want you to worry about me.
But I want you to study hard.
What do you mean?
You're my sister.
You should take care of me.
Take care of you?
No.
It's okay.
What?
Oh, right.
Wait a minute.
Hello?
Good morning.
You said we'd meet at the lab today.
Lab?
I'm sorry.
Cancel it.
What do you mean?
I'm scared.
Can I say it?
Yes.
Don't worry.
Can I?
Thank you.
See you.
You had a plan, didn't you?
It's okay.
It's my usual plan.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't have a boyfriend.
I have another boyfriend.
Another?
He's my boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
I'm tired of taking the train and walking.
Because I have a boyfriend here.
What?
Let's go to school after this.
I have to go to school.
You can't go to school if you don't have a boyfriend.
What?
Let's go to school.
What are you doing?
It's hot.
Is it okay?
It's huge.
Didn't you want to touch it?
That's...
Yes.
I wanted to touch it.
It's amazing.
It's soft.
It's huge.
It's beautiful.
How is it?
It's soft.
It's beautiful.
It's huge.
You're good at it.
I'm not good at it.
It's getting bigger and bigger.
I'm embarrassed.
Why?
It's okay.
You can't get your uniform dirty.
That's right.
We're going to school.
Wow.
You're good at it.
Naomi.
But...
We're siblings.
We should stop it.
Should we stop it?
No.
Even if we're siblings, our blood doesn't connect.
That's right.
We can't stop it.
How do you feel?
I don't like it.
It's not good.
How about this?
How do you feel?
It's not good.
I see.
I don't have time.
I'm happy, so I'm nervous.
You can touch me.
Really?
Yes.
Naomi.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It's wet.
Are you already wet?
Don't you want to put it in?
I want to put it in.
Do you want to put it in?
Yes.
It's hot.
I feel like I'm in a good place.
Me, too.
I feel good when Naomi laughs.
It's hot.
Are you all right?
You are all right.
It's hot.
Oh...
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
I have to do it cleanly.
Do you like it?
I have to prepare meat.
I'll do the cleaning.
I'll be back early.
So come back early.
Okay.
See you later.
Okay, I'll be back.
Your bag!
I did it.
I got Sefre at home.
I can do it whenever I want.
I was surprised. I didn't know Naomi would be like that.
It's awkward. I couldn't say anything when I went home.
What?
Oh, you're back.
You should have told me that you were back.
I was in a hurry to do my homework, so I forgot to say hello.
But you said you'd do it when you got home.
I think I said something like that in the morning.
Right?
Yes.
Then you don't have to do it.
I'm sorry.
I want to do it when I want to.
What?
But I have to study.
I have to take an exam.
Now?
I do it when I go to school in the morning.
Oh, I see.
It's too late.
Isn't it cute?
Let's go to bed.
You can do this kind of erotic thing every day.
What?
Isn't it good?
That's true.
Make it bigger.
I'm sorry.
You like it, don't you?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Why are you crying so hard?
It's big.
You're making it so hard.
I'm sorry.
What do you want to do?
I want you to eat and play with me.
Okay.
You like it, don't you?
One, two, three.
Here you are.
Take it.
You like it, don't you?
Yes.
Here you are.
You like it, don't you?
Yes.
Here you are.
No.
Take it.
You can't eat it yet.
Okay.
You like it?
I like it.
What?
What's wrong?
Are you going to eat it?
Yes.
Then.
No.
I don't want you to eat it yet.
Next time.
No.
I want you to eat it.
It'll be fine, don't worry.
Stretch out to the legs and exhale heavily.
Oh...
I want to lick you a lot.
Oh, no.
Oh...
It's so delicious that I can't stop eating it.
What is this?
I can not stop it because it seems to come out.
I'm coming out.
If that's the case, I'll come over here.
If you're going to do it, do it this way.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good that I'm sweating.
What's wrong?
I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it.
But let me stand up again soon.
Is that okay?
Then it's okay.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm out of breath.
Let's continue.
I can't do it anymore.
It hurts.
Let's continue.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels so good.
I'm out of breath.
I can't do it anymore.
What are you doing?
You should stop it.
I can't do it anymore.
I need to clean your ears.
I'm going to regret for the next three months.
You should have told me earlier.
I'm sorry.
But...
I'm going to do it every day from now on.
I didn't think it would feel so good.
You need to study.
You're a student now.
See you later.
Can I pass the audition?
What will happen to me from now on?
Can I study?
Can I pass the audition?
I don't want to have sex with Naomi.
What are you doing?
It's warm.
Wait a minute.
I have a bath.
Isn't it too small?
It's okay.
I'm not wet.
But my father will come back today.
Don't worry.
I won't be able to see him.
Really?
If I take a bath,
I'll be able to see him.
So I should take a bath, right?
I see.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
You can touch me if you want.
Okay.
If you touch me,
I'll kiss you.
I'm drunk.
If you have a girlfriend,
don't touch me.
Don't you have a girlfriend?
Even if you have a girlfriend at home,
don't touch me.
Okay.
I promise.
You have a big belly.
Your boobs are big and soft.
If you want to touch my boobs,
you can come to my room.
Instead,
if you want to touch my boobs,
let me touch your boobs.
Okay.
I'll kiss you.
Your boobs are big and soft.
It's delicious.
I want to drink your tea.
Okay.
Can I touch your boobs?
It's okay, it's okay.
It's amazing.
It's amazing how you feel over there.
Tomoshiku?
Yes, yes.
Have you seen Naomi?
Naomi?
I don't know her.
Is she in the toilet?
I don't think she's in the toilet.
I wonder if she went out.
She said she was going to cook for us, so I'm sure she's in there.
Is that so?
That's why I bought a new one.
Tomoku, let's go eat something.
What?
Are you going?
No, I'm not going.
No, I'm going.
Are you going or not?
I'm going, but I'm not going.
Let's go.
No, I'm not going.
I can't go now.
I see.
Let's order.
Yes, let's order.
You're not going, are you?
I'm not going.
I'll leave it to you.
I'm sorry.
Yes, please.
Naomi, my dad will find out.
He'll find out.
It's okay. He didn't find out.
But I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to be so harsh.
Let's continue.
Are you okay?
Hurry up.
You can't go to the bathroom.
You can go to the bathroom as many times as you want.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
You can't go to the bathroom.
It's disgusting.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
Are you okay?
Come on.
Tickles.
What is pulling me?
What are you running this time!
Mom-
That's a lobster!
Keep calm.
my baby!
Don't cry!
It's so good.
It feels so good.
Let's go to the kitchen and other places around the house.
Yes.
I have to go back soon.
My father will be suspicious.
I understand.
I'll cook the rice.
Okay.
He is definitely a prisoner.
I don't care.