I'm Eri. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
What's up?
I thought you were cuter in person.
I'm glad to hear that. Thank you.
I'm glad to hear that.
You're amazing.
Am I?
This is the first time I've been on a blind date.
Is that so?
It's my first time.
I heard you have a good friend.
So you're developing a new experience, aren't you?
I'm listening to it today for 120 minutes.
Is 120 minutes okay?
Okay.
Is it okay with Silk Long Course?
Yes.
What about the options?
Options?
If it's today, it's not oil.
Powder is free.
If you use powder, the oil is included in the price, but the powder is a separate price, so if you use powder, I think you can have an unknown experience again, but I'll put it on for free.
Oh, then this.
Yes, powder. I understand. Thank you very much.
Then, if you don't have any questions, please read this and explain today's date and the bed.
Yes, I understand.
Yes.
Yes. Thank you very much.
Oh, that's the first time.
Oh, is that so?
I have turtle pants, so please take a shower and put on turtle pants, and come back when you're done.
Oh, I understand.
Yes, I'll be waiting.
Oh, right. I forgot about the money.
Oh, that's right.
It's a 120-minute long course, so it's perfect for 20,000 yen.
20,000 yen?
Yes.
Yes. I'm sorry.
I'll keep it. Thank you very much.
Then, please put your clothes in here.
Yes.
I'll be waiting.
Oh, I understand.
Yes.
Oh, I see.
Um, I'll just change my clothes.
Oh, welcome back.
I'll take it with you.
I changed my clothes, but it's a little...
Yes.
It's pretty awkward.
I'll teach you how to do it.
Can you teach me how to do it?
Of course.
You're wearing a T-bag.
Yes, I am.
But everyone else is wearing a T-bag.
It's okay.
I see.
Yes.
Please teach me.
Okay.
First, we're going to do a Utsubu-sen.
Utsubu-sen.
Yes.
Like this?
Yes. It's okay.
Okay.
Let's start.
First, we're going to do a Shihatsu.
Please tell me if it's too strong or not.
Okay.
Is there any part you don't want to be touched?
Well...
The back of my legs are a little itchy.
Itchy? Okay.
It feels good.
It feels good?
Yes.
Your back is a little wrinkly.
Really?
Yes.
Wrinkly?
Yes, it is.
Is it cute?
Yes.
Let's see.
Okay.
Wow.
Yes.
It's different from the usual Utsubu-sen.
Yes, it is.
I'm happy.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to massage your back.
Wow.
Is your back okay?
Yes, it's okay.
How was the massage?
Yes.
Was it okay?
Yes, it was good.
It's amazing.
Is it amazing?
It's like a technique.
But it's totally different depending on the girl.
But your body is soft.
Me?
Yes.
My body is very hard.
Really?
Only my hip joints are soft.
I see.
But your body is very soft.
Even though you are a man.
Really?
Yes.
Everyone's body is not bent this much.
Really?
Yes.
Wow.
What's wrong?
No, it's like...
It's like...
That's bad, isn't it?
I get shy in front of the mirror in the back.
Yes, you do.
That's right.
It's like...
???
I don't get embarrassed in front of it.
Yes, yes.
When I read the book, I don't get embarrassed.
That's right.
When we read the book, we don't get embarrassed in front of the mirror, right?
I don't want to make you uncomfortable.
I feel like my legs are longer than before.
It's because of the massage.
It's because of you, Eri.
I'm glad to hear that.
Is the bottom part okay?
Okay.
I'll start.
How long have you been doing this?
It's been about three months.
Three months?
Is that long?
I don't know.
There are many girls who do it in a short period of time.
But I don't think it's long.
It feels good.
Really?
I was wondering if it was long.
It's not long.
I don't think it's long.
There are many cute girls in this store.
I think so, too.
I have another acquaintance.
She's really cute, too.
I was wondering if there were many cute girls on the website.
Is that so?
Did you see a lot of cute girls on the website?
Yes, I did.
It's an individual website.
Really?
I saw a lot of pictures.
But I think Eri is the cutest.
I'm glad to hear that.
Do you know Riko?
Did you see her?
Yes, I saw her.
She's the girl I introduced to you.
She's my senior.
Do you have a job?
I'm a college student.
She's my senior.
She's a college student.
Yes.
If you think it's okay to introduce me, please come in.
I'm glad to hear that.
Really?
Thank you.
Go ahead.
This is a52.
Yes.
It's nice.
I had an image of massage and oil until I entered, but it seems that powder is popular recently.
This feels good.
I'm sorry.
It smells good.
Is it good?
Because I took a shower.
It doesn't smell like that.
It's hot.
Can I have a blue hair?
A blue hair?
Excuse me.
Here you are.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's still a little out.
I'm sorry.
It's funny.
It's okay.
Did you take a shower?
No.
Excuse me.
It's hot.
Did you take a shower?
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's warm.
Why?
Because it feels good.
You look like a starfish.
Like a starfish?
Yes.
What?
Nothing.
Nothing?
You are close to me.
I'm close to you?
Do you like being close to me?
I like it.
What?
I'm sorry.
How was it?
I am the
What's wrong?
I don't know.
No...
lol
oh
yeah
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm going to try it anyway.
What?
Ouch!
I don't know.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
Why?
What?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Ah...
Um...
What?
No, it's okay.
This.
This?
No, this.
Because...
There's no one else here.
Oh, yeah.
You don't know, do you?
What?
Oh, yeah.
I'm sorry.
Ah...
I'm going to cry.
Be more confident.
No, no, no...
Ah...
Ah, it's good, isn't it?
I don't know what to do with myself.
Osu.
I don't know what to do.
Ouch.
My mouth is painful.
This place is painful.
Huh?
Ouch.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
ah
um
I'm sorry to bother you.
Oh, yes.
Welcome.
My name is Ami, and I'll be in charge of today.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Well, let's get started.
What kind of course would you like today?
Oh, there are a lot of things.
I recommend the body course.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Then I'll take this body course.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Then I'll take this 150-minute course.
Oh, I see.
Yes.
Then I'll get ready for the SP.
There's a classroom over there, so please change here.
Oh, I see.
Then I'll go change.
Yes.
Excuse me.
I'm going to apply the oil.
Oh, yes.
Do you have any parts that are stiff?
Oh, well, my back and shoulders.
Oh, your shoulders.
Yes.
I see.
You look pretty tired.
Yes, I am.
I have a lot of work to do.
Oh, I see.
Then I'd like to focus on your shoulders today.
Oh, yes.
I'll add some oil.
It's my first time to apply oil.
Oh, is it your first time?
I do massage, but it's my first time to use oil.
Oh, I see.
Then I'll do my best to make you satisfied today.
Oh, thank you.
How about here?
Oh, it's very stiff.
It's stiff, isn't it?
There's something here.
Oh, is there?
It's stiff.
Oh, I see.
You're good at it.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Thank you.
Is it too long?
No, it's my first time, so it's not that long.
You're good at massaging.
You're good at massaging, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Do you like strong massages?
Yes.
Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
Oh, it's stiff.
Is it for sitting?
No, it's for standing.
Oh, it's for standing.
It must be tiring.
Yes, it's like standing for a long time.
Then I'll put more pressure on your heart.
I'll put more pressure on your heart.
Can I put more pressure on your heart?
Yes.
I'll put more pressure on your heart.
Doesn't it hurt?
It feels like it's working.
How is it?
It's good.
I'll put more pressure on your heart.
Really?
Yes.
I'll put more pressure on your heart.
This massage is relaxing.
Really?
Yes.
Do you usually get tired?
Yes, I do.
I get tired sometimes.
Don't you take a rest?
That's not good.
I think you should get a massage regularly.
I'll massage your legs, too.
Excuse me.
Okay.
I'll put some oil on your legs.
My legs are stiff.
Really?
Yes.
Your legs are stiff.
My legs are stiff.
This part is stiff.
I see.
I'll put some oil on your legs.
It feels good.
This part is stiff.
It's a standing job, so it's stiff.
I'll put some oil on your legs.
I'll massage your legs, too.
Okay.
How is it?
I'll put some oil on your legs.
It feels good.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
I'll put some oil on your legs.
You feel much better, don't you?
Yes.
Please turn your head.
Okay.
I'll massage your front legs, too.
Excuse me.
Okay.
I'll put some oil on your legs.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'll put some oil on your legs.
Okay.
How is it?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
I'll put some oil on your legs.
How is it?
It feels good.
I'll put some oil on your legs.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm used to doing this.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I
won't
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I think it's a good idea.
I think it's a good idea.
I don't think it's a good idea.
I don't know what to do.
Ouch...
Ouch.
I'm sorry.
Is it okay if I do more?
I don't think so.
Oh my gosh.
It's frickin hot.
It's so good.
It's really good.
I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to die if I don't do something about it.
I'm so popular that I've done it twice.
Can you explain it to me?
Of course.
Please come in.
Thank you.
Here you are.
I'm Sayaka.
Nice to meet you.
Here's the menu.
You can choose the course.
I see.
Here you are.
There are a lot of courses.
Yes.
120 minutes?
Okay, 120 minutes.
It's 16,000 yen.
Do you want to pay first?
Yes.
Okay.
Here you are.
It's 16,000 yen.
Thank you.
Here you are.
I'll start the course in 120 minutes.
Okay.
Before I start, I'd like you to change your clothes.
I'll get ready.
Okay.
What should I wear?
You can wear these pants.
Okay.
You can take a shower.
And come back.
Okay.
I'll get ready, too.
Thank you.
Well...
Here you are.
I've changed my clothes.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
I'm embarrassed.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Can I get a massage?
A massage?
Yes.
You must be embarrassed.
I'm not used to it.
Okay.
I'll massage your body.
I'll massage your body first.
Okay.
Are you Sayaka?
Yes, I'm Sayaka.
How old are you?
I'm 22 years old.
I see.
I'm a college student.
Are you a fourth-year student?
Yes, I am.
I've decided to quit my job.
I see.
Yes.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I was nervous until then.
I see.
Have you quit your job?
Yes.
It's been a month since I started this job.
It's been a while.
Are you a new employee?
Yes, I am.
It's my first time to work here.
So, I was nervous.
I see.
I was nervous.
I'm glad that it was easy to work here.
I see.
You must be nervous.
It's hard to get a call.
I can't get a call.
I see.
It's hard to get a call at home.
Yes.
How is it?
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You're good.
Are there many young women who work at a men's clothing store?
Yes, I think so.
There are many young women who work at a men's clothing store.
I see.
Yes.
Are there many young women who work at a men's clothing store?
Yes, I think so.
I see.
There are many young women who work at a men's clothing store during the day.
Yes.
Do you get fired after you get a job?
I don't get fired after I get a job.
I see.
It's been a month since I got a job.
I was interested in this job.
I hope I can continue this job.
I see.
Is it fun?
Yes, it's fun.
I used to like massaging.
When I get a job, I want to do what I'm good at.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Thank you.
I'm getting angry.
I don't know about other things, but I feel like I'm getting motivated.
Yes, you do.
Your body is more motivated.
What's wrong?
No, no. I just thought it was something like this.
Oh, I see.
After all, it's harder for women to get in than for men.
It's more effective to ride this, so I'm riding it.
I'm sorry, but it's a little light.
Don't worry about it. It's just a massage.
Oh, it feels good.
Does it feel good?
You may have loosened up.
My body is getting warmer.
Your metabolism may be getting better.
I looked it up on the Internet.
Is there such a thing?
If you pay a little, it's not a back-up.
Yes, there is.
Oh, I see.
If you please.
I don't do such a thing.
I'm just doing it because I want men to feel good with this massage.
How about you, Sayaka?
In my case, I don't get paid other than the regular salary.
Oh, I see.
Yes.
How about you, Sayaka?
In my case, I don't get paid other than the regular salary.
Oh, I see.
How about you, Sayaka?
I don't get paid other than the regular salary.
Oh, I see.
How about you, Sayaka?
In my case, I don't get paid other than the regular salary.
Oh, I see.
How about you, Sayaka?
In my case, I don't get paid other than the regular salary.
Oh, I see.
How about you, Sayaka?
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
How about you, Sayaka?
What's wrong?
Oh, I feel good.
I don't feel tired.
Are you sure?
Yes, I am.
I'll do it like this.
Okay.
Oh, I see.
I'll put some powder on your face.
Oh, okay.
Are you okay?
Oh, yes.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
It's easier to get rid of the powder.
Oh, I see.
That's rare.
Is that so?
But many people like this.
It's good for the powder.
Liaotang
Recently my back and head are well recovered
Yes
Could you give me a U-turn for a while?
A U-turn?
Could you move as it is?
Yes
How?
Yes.
This part's also part of the massage.
I don't think I can do it.
What's the matter?
I just feel strange
It's a strange feeling, isn't it?
It's ticklish.
Oh, is it ticklish?
It's a strange feeling, isn't it?
Oh, that's right.
It's normal, isn't it?
Oh, it's normal.
It's a part of the menu.
Are you okay?
Oh, I'm fine.
Please relax.
Can I move?
Yes.
Please don't move too much.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
What?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Do you mind?
I'm touching you.
I'm sorry.
I see.
Okay.
Please relax.
Oh, that's right.
I'll lift your leg.
Let's go.
You can stay like that.
Okay.
How is it?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's pretty hard.
It's hard here.
I'm tired.
You are tired.
Is that so?
Okay.
I have to do this regularly.
Otherwise, I'll get angry.
I see.
Okay.
I have to massage your whole body.
I see.
That's good.
I'm doing it after getting a massage.
I see.
I'm doing it properly.
I'm getting money regularly.
I'm doing it as a professional.
I'm doing it properly.
Is it sensitive?
Yes.
It's moving a lot.
I'm sorry.
Some people are not good at being touched.
Don't worry about it.
Can you turn around?
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Really?
Yes.
I'll give you a massage.
Okay.
Can you spread your legs?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
I'll massage your upper body.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'll put a bandage on your slippery legs.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you a massage.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
I'll give you a massage.
Your skin is rough.
Are you okay?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Yes.
Yes...
Good job.
Amazing.
I'm sorry.
How is it?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
This hurts.
This hurts!
Oh.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah , ah
a
corn
me
Please get my dad.
What is this?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to go.
Are you all right?
It felt so good.
I'm sorry.
Please call me again.
Thank you very much.
I'm Riko, and I'll be in charge of the surgery today.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'd like to confirm the course.
Yes.
Is there a mistake in the 120-minute shift-long course today?
Yes, there is.
Thank you very much.
This is a warning.
If you can read the situation and there is no problem, please sign here.
All right.
Please.
I'm a little nervous.
Is this your first time?
I heard it's good for your acquaintance.
I'll do my best today.
Thank you.
Is this all right?
Yes, it's all right.
Thank you very much.
It's amazing.
It's like a calm room.
I'd like you to relax.
I'm sorry I forgot to tell you.
There are two options.
There are oil and powder.
Do you have anything?
I heard that powder massage feels good.
Thank you very much.
I think it feels good.
Are there many people who choose powder?
Yes.
There may be many customers who choose powder recently.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to confirm the cost.
It's 20,000 yen for 120 minutes with powder and massage.
Thank you very much.
I'll put this in.
It's 20,000 yen.
You look more beautiful than the picture on the website.
I'm really nervous.
Really?
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
I think it's better to relax.
I'm really nervous.
I'm nervous because it's my first time.
Is that so?
I'm really nervous.
How long has it been?
It's been about three months.
I haven't been on a business trip so often, so I may not be used to it yet.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to start the procedure.
Please take a shower.
Can you come out wearing a paper pants?
I see.
The shower is at the entrance, so you'll know when you come out.
Thank you very much.
I'll change my clothes.
I'll be waiting for you.
Thank you for your hard work.
I changed my clothes.
Is this the right place?
Yes, it is.
It's a little small, so it may be embarrassing.
Don't worry about it at all.
First of all, can you lie down?
I'm a little nervous.
I'm sorry.
Please let me know if your room is cold.
No problem.
Thank you very much.
I'll put this on you.
Please let me know if you have any questions.
Thank you very much.
It's amazing.
Is it amazing?
It's pretty hard.
I see.
Please let me know if it hurts.
No problem.
I see.
I've never been to a men's spa before.
It's good.
Is it good?
I'm glad to hear that.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
It feels good.
Isn't it heavy?
Not at all.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
I'll continue with this.
Your back must be tired.
Yes, it is.
Is it because of work?
Yes, I often sit on the desk.
So, my back starts to hurt little by little.
I see.
It hurts when you sit on your back for a long time.
I'll massage your back today.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
I'll massage your back.
Is there any problem with the pressure?
No, it's okay.
Thank you very much.
It's good.
What do you do on your day off?
I roll around at home.
You roll around.
Do you watch movies?
Something like that.
That's good.
You want to take a rest on your day off.
I usually stay at home.
You don't have many days off, do you?
I don't think so.
I think I have less days off than other people.
I see.
That's amazing.
It's nothing.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll massage your back.
It feels so good.
I'll apply powder.
Okay.
Excuse me.
What kind of powder do you use?
I didn't apply baby powder when I was a baby.
Baby powder?
I see.
It's like this.
It's smooth.
The previous one was very smooth.
I'll apply this.
That's true.
It smells good.
You can relax.
It feels so good.
Are you good at tickling?
It tickles, but it feels good.
That's good.
You're shivering.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
If you feel good around here, please tell me.
I feel good around here.
That's good.
Around here?
Yes.
Here we go.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
You'll be surprised if I touch you.
I'm sorry.
It's too heavy, isn't it?
But it feels good.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I'll massage your calf.
Doesn't it hurt?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
If you sit down for a long time, your lymph will be frozen.
So, I'll remove the blood flow.
It'll be swollen.
That's right.
That's great.
I heard that massage can remove oil stains.
That's right.
It won't be swollen, so it'll be easier to go home.
I think I can do it at home.
That's right.
You can do it at home, too.
I'll press here.
Do you massage your boyfriend at home?
I don't know.
But I might do it if he asks me to.
That's annoying.
Doesn't it hurt?
Not at all.
It feels good all the time.
I'll massage your upper body.
I'm sorry.
I'll massage your whole body.
It might be cold.
I'm sorry.
It's smooth.
That's great.
Excuse me.
It feels good.
Do you like to be touched gently?
That's good.
Then I'll be gentle.
I'm getting goosebumps.
Please feel good.
Okay.
Does it feel good?
It feels really good.
That's good.
Does it feel good here?
Yes.
That's good.
It's different from the feeling of sleeping.
It's very relaxing.
That's good.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad you feel good.
Where does it feel good?
It feels good where I'm touching now.
It feels better than before.
From here?
My hips are going up.
I'm glad you feel better than I imagined.
Really?
Isn't it too much?
No, it's not.
It feels really good.
It feels good.
I'm glad you feel better than I imagined.
Can you turn your body to the side?
Okay.
Thank you.
Is your head okay?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's out.
I'm going to fix it.
I'm sorry.
It's nothing.
It feels good.
I heard that it feels good when you're sleepy, so don't worry about it.
Can I continue?
Yes, please.
I'm going to fix the upper part.
Okay.
I couldn't see your back.
That's right.
I was wondering how much I was using it.
It's this much.
Excuse me.
Okay.
Is it okay?
I'm going to apply it all over your body.
It feels good.
You don't have to hold your voice.
Really?
Yes.
I see.
If you are surprised, your voice may be cut off.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
I want to go on a diet.
I see.
It's cute.
It's a little embarrassing.
It's okay.
I'm going to apply it on your lower body.
Okay.
Excuse me.
It feels good.
It really feels good.
I'm going to apply powder on your scalp.
Okay.
Excuse me.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Excuse me.
I'm going to massage your scalp.
Okay.
Does it tickle?
It tickles a little.
Thank you.
I'm going to turn you over.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's okay to spread your legs.
Thank you.
Please stay in a comfortable position.
Excuse me.
It's okay.
Thank you.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Thank you.
It feels good.
Your lower back is moving.
I'm sorry.
It tickles.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
It's okay.
It feels good.
Is this it?
Yes.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Okay.
I'll get closer to you.
Oh, I see.
Thank you.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Thank you.
It feels good.
It tickles.
It feels strange.
It feels good.
Yes.
It feels really good.
It tickles.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Did you not like it?
No, it's not that I didn't like it.
It tickles.
It ticksles.
Are you okay here?
It tickles.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Do you feel better?
Yes, I feel great.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Do you like chestnut?
Which one do you like?
I like both.
Please relax and feel good.
Do you know how a girl feels when she relaxes?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Do you like a kiss?
I'm embarrassed.
It's okay. Please move your body.
I'm sorry.
Is it okay?
Yes, it's okay.
You're very energetic.
Here.
It's dirty.
Do you like this?
Yes, I do.
I love it.
Does it feel good here?
Yes, it does.
It feels good.
It's dirty.
Let's wash our hands.
It feels good.
You're amazing.
Can I touch you?
Yes, you can.
You're very energetic.
It's dirty.
Let's go.
It feels good.
It's dirty.
That's it.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
Please wait a little more.
Is it okay?
Yes, it is.
It's dirty.
It feels better when you bear with it.
You're amazing.
Can you see well?
Yes, I can.
It's dirty.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
It's dirty.
It feels good.
You're amazing.
It's dirty.
It feels good.
You're amazing.
It's dirty.
It feels good.
You're amazing.
It's dirty.
Does it feel good?
I can't see well.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
Let's go.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
Please look at me.
This is amazing.
Is this amazing?
Yes.
It feels good.
Stop it.
It's dirty.
Is it dirty?
I'm sorry.
It's dirty.
It feels good.
You're amazing.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm glad that you feel good.
We still have time.
Are you satisfied?
You're still fine.
Yes.
It feels good.
You're amazing.
Are you satisfied?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I can't move.
It's because of the air.
I see.
It feels good.
I'll open my mouth.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Open your mouth.
Really?
It feels good.
I'm hungry.
You slept a lot.
You're sensitive.
It feels good.
How do you feel?
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
Will you do it again?
Of course.
Thank you.
Please tell me the date of the next day of work.
It's Saturday next week.
I see.
Let's sleep well again.
Okay.