It's been a while since I've had a massage, so I'm a little nervous, but I'll do my best.
Are you tired?
Yes, my back hurts.
Is it around your back?
Is it the sound of pushing?
It's desk work, so I sit down for a long time.
Then you'll get tired.
Is your back around here?
Are you done with work today?
You're pretty angry.
You're angry up to your back.
Your body is trembling. Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
You're trembling, but aren't you cold?
If you're cold, please tell me right away.
Yes, I understand.
Is this your first time here?
Yes, this is my first time.
Thank you for coming today.
It feels good.
I'll give you a massage so that you can get rid of your fatigue.
Please go home feeling refreshed.
Can you turn around?
Okay.
I'll put my hands up.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Do you come here often?
No, I don't come here often.
This oil contains a lot of ingredients that help you get rid of fatigue.
I'm sure you'll be able to get rid of your fatigue by the time you get home.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
What?
Yes.
I don't feel anything.
You don't feel anything?
Is this a massage?
Yes, it's a massage for the whole body.
I'll give you a massage so that you can get rid of your fatigue.
Please go home feeling refreshed.
There's a lot of fatigue here, too.
Here?
Yes.
I'll give you a massage so that you can get rid of your fatigue.
Are you okay?
Please let me know if it hurts.
Yes.
I'll give you a massage so that you can get rid of your fatigue.
You look very happy.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I'll apply a lot of oil to your lower body and give you a massage.
Your whole body is stiff.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Did you massage your shoulders?
I think it's a little more painful than the other side.
Where is it painful?
It's in my stomach.
Where?
Where is it painful?
It's in my stomach.
Your waist is moving.
I'm sorry.
Why are you doing your best?
I'm doing my best.
Your body is getting hot.
Is it the effect of the massage?
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
Your neck is stiff.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Your neck is stiff.
Your neck is moving.
It's hard.
It's hard here.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I think you need more oil.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
Is it a massage?
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Do you want to feel better?
I'll do it like this.
What's wrong?
You were shaking.
I'm not shaking.
You're going to sleep again.
Did you shake again?
I have to do my best.
You've been making it bigger since the beginning.
It's getting hot.
You want to feel better, don't you?
Like this.
Do you know it feels good when you do this?
Your waist is moving a lot.
Do you want to see it in person?
Does it hurt?
It's getting really hard.
My body is trembling.
I'm getting excited again.
Does it feel good?
You've been surprised all the time.
I want to put it in again.
It's good, isn't it?
Did you fall asleep again?
Can you still do it?
It's good, isn't it?
Did you fall asleep again?
Can you still do it?
It's good, isn't it?
I'll be okay!
You're tired, aren't you?
I'm sorry.
Do you feel better?
I feel better. I'm sorry.
I'm glad to hear that.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Will you do it again?
Yes, of course.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Hello, I'm Mifune. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Are you sure it's an oil course today?
Yes.
Then I'll use the oil right away.
Isn't it cold?
It's just right.
Excuse me.
Do you often come to this kind of shop?
I come here occasionally.
I come here once a month.
Do you come here once a month?
Yes.
That's a lot.
Is that so?
Do you often get a massage?
I don't want to go to a massage shop.
You have a good body.
Really?
Yes.
I'm glad to hear that.
Do you exercise?
I exercise a little on weekends.
That's great.
It's hard to move your body.
That's right.
It gets stiff, doesn't it?
I'll apply oil to this side, too.
Your skin is white.
It's quite indoor.
Is that so?
You said you didn't have a hobby.
That's right.
I often watch movies at home.
If you feel good, please speak out.
That's good.
Around here?
Yes.
Ah.
That's good.
I applied a lot of oil.
It feels good to apply a lot of oil.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's easy to get stiff around here, isn't it?
Yes.
That's good.
It's shiny with oil.
Around here.
Your arms and hands are surprisingly stiff.
Yes.
It feels good.
The tip of your fingers are cold.
That's right.
I have a high temperature, so please leave it here.
I'll add a little oil.
You're right.
Your body is warm.
Then I'll massage your legs.
Yes.
Okay.
I'll apply oil.
Your toes are cold, too.
I'm sorry.
Your toes are cold.
Do you sit all day?
That's right.
That's my job.
Sometimes, if you don't move, it's hard to sit.
Is that so?
Okay.
Doesn't it hurt here?
It hurts a little.
Is that also a problem?
This is also an internal organ.
Is it a big difference?
I'll do it carefully.
I'll apply oil.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
It's getting warmer than before.
Is that so?
It's getting warmer.
There are a lot of lymph nodes around here.
It's better to apply oil every day.
I feel good around here.
Around here?
Yes.
Okay.
I'll apply oil to your upper body again.
I'll apply oil to this area.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
If you use a smartphone or computer every day, you will get tired here.
That's right.
I'll apply a lot of oil.
Okay.
Doesn't it hurt a lot?
It hurts a little.
It hurts.
Please be patient.
Okay.
How do you feel?
It hurts, but it feels good.
Is something wrong?
No.
Okay.
Please tell me where you feel good.
Around here.
Around here?
Yes.
Okay.
How do you feel?
It feels good here, doesn't it?
That's right.
It feels good.
I'll apply oil under your neck.
Okay.
What's the matter?
No.
This is also a massage.
This?
What's the matter?
No.
Is something wrong?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
It's hot.
Isn't it too hard?
This is more powerful.
Is that so?
Did it hurt?
No.
It's hot.
What's the matter?
It's in my neck.
Is it in your neck?
No.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Ah.
Isn't the massage pleasant?
It's pleasant, but...
Ah.
What's the matter?
No.
The massage is pleasant.
Is the massage pleasant?
Yes.
If you feel good, please say so.
It's pleasant.
Ah.
My voice is...
It's getting hot.
What?
Ah.
I sweat when I massage.
Eh?
Ah.
It's hot.
Eh?
Next, I'll apply sweat.
Ah.
Your hands are cold.
Yes.
Ah.
Can I warm your hands here?
You?
Oh, sorry
I just took a little break
Just let me bite down until I feel the pain
Didn't that give you a scent?
No, it was just nice
What's wrong?
No, um...
The massage feels good.
It feels good?
Ah, you're sweating.
I'll do my best with the massage.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
I'll put on some oil.
Over there?
I'll stretch it like this.
How is this massage?
No, um...
It feels good.
It tickles.
It tickles over there.
Does it hurt?
No, it's not that.
It doesn't hurt that much.
It's coming out.
What's coming out?
Don't do that.
It's coming out.
No, it's not that.
You still look fine.
It tickles.
How is this massage?
No, um...
It feels good.
It tickles.
What's wrong?
It's still hard.
I can't go home like this.
It tickles.
It's hard.
It's okay.
It tickles.
Please follow me from behind.
Can I keep going?
It tickles.
This is a secret.
Okay.
I'm going to apply oil.
Is it cold?
No, I'm fine.
How old are you?
I just started.
I see.
So I'll do my best.
You're not used to it.
No, I'm not.
I want to improve as soon as possible.
You have a good body.
Really?
I used to have a body like that.
What did you do?
I was a trainee.
That's good.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
Is this natural oil?
Yes, it is.
It's a popular scent.
I use the scent of rose.
Many people get sleepy.
Why did you decide to start this job?
I thought it would be fun.
It looks fun.
I like massages.
I want to be a massager.
Isn't it hard?
There are many kind people now.
It's not hard.
Can I have a face-up massage?
Like this?
I'll give you a face-up massage.
Excuse me.
How do you feel here?
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
It feels good.
You have a lot of muscles.
Really?
I respect you because you seem to have a lot of muscle training.
It's fun when I get used to it.
Really?
Are you interested in it?
Yes, I am.
I started to get it recently.
It's difficult.
Where do you want to train?
I want to train my butt.
I want to make it smaller.
Don't you want to make it bigger?
I'm big enough.
I want to make it smaller.
It's good to have a big butt.
Really?
I think it's good to have a big butt.
My body is getting warmer with the oil.
It's an oil that's easy to penetrate.
That's right.
It's also moisturizing.
It's very popular.
It's good for your skin.
That's right.
It moisturizes my whole body.
It's also good in winter.
It's good in winter.
Because it's dry.
It's very good.
How is your collarbone?
My collarbone?
It's very good.
Because I have lymph.
Is lymph important?
It's important.
It's good for your neck.
It's very important.
That's right.
Lymph massage is popular.
It's good, isn't it?
It's good.
How about here?
It's good for massaging.
Can I do it?
Yes.
It's good.
You're very nervous.
Yes.
Which do you feel better, right or left?
That's...
That's better.
I'll massage your thighs.
It's more slippery than before.
How do you feel?
It's very good.
Next, I'll massage your lower back.
I'll massage your lower back, too.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
It's very good.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
Yes.
It's very good.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What's wrong?
Do you feel good here?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Wait a minute.
What should I do?
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
You can move from the bottom.
You're amazing.
It's getting hot.
It's okay.
I'm going to die.
Please move.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Can I do more?
I want you to do more.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Ah ah ah
exercised
Yeah yeah
ううっ
I'll do it one more time.
I think I can do it one more time.
I want to do it one more time.
I can do it one more time.
It's cold.
I'm freezing.
I can't do it.
It's cold.
It's cold, cold, cold!
Did you feel good?
Yes, I did.
I'm sorry.
You did a lot.
I did it twice.
If you don't mind, could you do it again?
Of course.
I'm sorry.
Could you do it again?
Yes, please.
Which do you want, oil or powder?
I've never done powder.
Is that so?
I'd like to try powder.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Is this a baby powder?
Yes, it is.
I did it too casually.
Is that so?
I'm sorry.
It's smooth, isn't it?
I've never done it, so I don't know.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
It feels different from oil, so I'm getting used to it.
I think so, too.
It's my first time, too.
Everyone seems to like oil.
Let's do it.
It turned white.
It's not that bad.
Did I put too much?
No, it's fine.
Really?
That's good.
It's really white.
It smells good, too.
It smells good, but it's different from oil.
But it feels good, so I'm glad.
The amount of force is just right.
Really?
It's amazing.
It's completely white.
Can I take a shower after this?
Yes, you can.
It's amazing.
I didn't expect you to laugh so much.
It's really white.
It looks like I painted it white.
It feels good to apply powder.
Really?
My hands are white, too.
It doesn't tickle, does it?
It tickles.
Really?
I put powder in it.
It's amazing.
It turned white around here.
I'll give it to you.
It's amazing around here.
It's ticklish.
It feels good.
Really?
It tickles a little.
Doesn't it work for you?
It tickles, but it feels good.
Really?
It turned white around here.
It's amazing.
It tickles a little.
Around here.
It feels good.
Really?
I'll apply it with this.
It's in my nails.
I'll put it on your nails.
Around here.
Powder massage feels good.
I want to ask you to give me a powder massage next time.
It's okay here.
I'll do it.
How about other places?
Does it feel good?
I don't go to a lot of places like this.
I'm lonely if you go to other places.
Really?
Don't go to lonely places.
Okay.
It's amazing.
Hey.
Yes?
What kind of massage did you do?
The massage I just did?
The massage I just did felt really good.
Really?
It tickles.
Is this okay?
Like this?
I have to do other places, too.
Okay.
Isn't your muscle amazing?
Really?
I'll touch this.
It tickles.
I'm white.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
It's warm.
Really?
It tickles.
It's okay.
I'll take it off later.
I didn't say anything weird.
It's coming out.
It's coming out a little.
It's okay.
I'll fix it later.
It's powder.
It's the same.
It's time to change your posture.
What do you think?
I'll give you this.
You're white.
Really?
Are you okay?
You're white.
Can I use both?
Yes, you can.
It's nothing.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
I'll use oil.
It's sticky.
Here we go.
Your hands are warm, so it feels good.
Really?
You want to do it, don't you?
It's a massage.
I'll do it for you.
This side?
I didn't think about it.
I made a mistake.
I'll do it for you.
It's swollen around here.
That's true.
I know because you're a girl.
I'm tired because I take a nap.
It's hard for girls.
Yes.
Here we go.
It's nothing.
What's wrong?
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to worry about it.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It's still swollen.
It's swollen.
I'm embarrassed.
Really?
You don't have to worry about it.
I'm going to give you a massage around here.
It feels good.
Really?
I see.
What?
It's nothing.
I'm just giving you a massage.
Okay.
Here we go.
I'm giving you a massage.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'm going to give you a massage around here.
Okay.
It's swollen.
Yes.
I'm going to give you a massage around here.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Really?
I see.
Yes.
I'm going to give you a massage around here.
Here we go.
I'm just giving you a massage.
You said it felt good.
That's right.
Right?
Yes.
Here?
It feels good.
I'm going to give you a massage.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'm going to give you a massage.
I see.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with your stomach?
I feel like I'm gaining weight.
It feels good.
Really?
Yes.
How about your arms?
I'm going to give you a massage.
Okay.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'm going to give you a massage.
I see.
It feels good.
Is this a massage, too?
What?
That was a prank.
I want to eat you.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Do you like this kind of massage?
I like it.
I see.
I'm going to give you a massage.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Does it hurt?
It doesn't hurt, does it?
It feels good.
It's okay.
If I take this off,
do I have to fix it?
That's up to you.
Is that so?
It's okay.
You took it off.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's like this.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm going to make you feel good.
No.
Your voice comes out because it feels good, doesn't it?
Do you like this kind of massage?
I like it.
I don't hate it.
Really?
I'm going to make you feel good.
Yes.
Do you like it?
This part is weak, isn't it?
It feels good.
I'm going to massage your back.
I'm going to massage your face.
It's getting hot.
That's right.
It feels good.
It's getting hot.
That's right.
This room is warm, isn't it?
It's getting hard, isn't it?
It feels good.
This is good.
Do you like this kind of massage?
I like it.
It's hot.
Are you all right?
You're covered in oil.
I'm fine.
It happens a lot.
It's hot.
It feels good, doesn't it?
That's right.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Really?
I wonder if it's true.
It's hot.
You don't look like you're in pain.
It feels good.
You're covered in oil.
You're sticky.
You're sticky, so I'll just take it off.
What?
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I'm just massaging you.
Is this okay?
Yes.
I'll make you more sticky.
Okay.
I thought you were going to sleep.
I'm massaging you.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
Well...
What?
You're not wearing underwear, are you?
What? Where?
I'm wearing underwear.
I see.
You're not wearing underwear, are you?
Yes.
That's right.
I understand.
You know what?
By any chance...
Do you want me to massage you?
Well...
I don't know if I want to or not.
But I want to.
Is that so?
You want me to massage you?
Yes.
You can't.
You can't do it here.
That's right.
You're a pervert, aren't you?
No.
But I can't help it.
It feels so good.
I'm going to be a pervert.
That's right.
Your voice is too pleasant.
I'm sorry.
Is it that good?
Yes.
Is it here?
Does it feel good?
This kind of massage is good, isn't it?
Yes.
It feels good.
Then I'll massage you a lot.
Okay.
Is it here?
Ouch!
Does it feel good?
No.
It feels so good.
I told you I'm wearing underpants.
Did you?
That's right.
It's your fault.
It's my fault?
Yes.
I told you.
I told you it was forbidden.
That's right.
So it's not here.
Okay.
I see.
You feel like it's here.
That's right.
It feels so good.
Is it here?
Yes.
I think it's here, but it's not.
I see.
If it's not here, can I leave?
Do you want to leave?
I want to leave.
Does it feel so good?
It can't be helped.
It's only this time.
Can I leave?
You can leave a lot.
I want to leave.
Can I leave?
Yes.
It's so good.
I want to leave a lot.
You can leave a lot.
Leave a lot.
It's not here.
I want to leave.
What's wrong?
It's open.
Is that so?
You took it off.
You took off your underwear.
It's not here.
I see.
It's dirty.
I have to clean it.
Don't you wipe it with a tissue?
It's not a tissue.
It's getting bigger.
I'm just cleaning it.
It's so good.
This?
This is good.
It's getting bigger again.
Is it clean now?
You took out a lot.
It's dirty.
I'm sorry.
I'll take it off.
It's a mess.
I'm sorry.
It's so good.
Yes.
It's clean.
If you feel so good, I'll give you more service.
Service?
I'm not done yet.
It's already like this.
I don't need this.
Yes.
I'll give you a massage.
I'll make you feel better.
How is it?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's good.
I'm glad I gave you a service.
Is it like this?
You're getting used to it.
Yes.
It's like this.
You're getting used to it.
It feels good.
Does this feel good?
Do you want to put it in?
I want to put it in.
You want to put it in.
You can put it in.
But it's a secret.
Yes, it's a secret.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to put it in?
Yes.
It feels good.
I'll put it in.
I'm sorry.
I put it in.
Do you want to put it in?
I'll put it in.
I feel good, too.
Really?
You're big and strong.
It's the best.
I'll show you where it's in.
You can see it, right?
It's in my body.
It feels good.
Is it spicy?
It's spicy.
It feels good.
You can see it well.
I'll put it in.
It's spicy.
I'll put it in your butt.
My butt?
I moved it.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's hot, so it's heavy, right?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm going to throw up.
Do you want to eat something?
Are you okay?
It's hot.
Did it come out?
It came out.
I got it on my hand.
Yes.
Can you still do it?
Yes, I can.
It's still hard.
It's hard.
I moved it.
This time,
I'll move it the way you like.
Is that okay?
It's okay.
It's hot.
I can still do it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
What's that?
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'm going to throw up.
Wait.
That's dangerous.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Don't do that.
It's hot.
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no...
Oh no!
Ah, wait! Wait!
Hot, hot, hot...
Ah, wait!
Oh no, oh no!
Over there, over there!
No!
Um...
Miss...
I'm sorry to ask, but...
Can I put it on your chest?
Sure.
If you want to put it on, go ahead.
Ouch!
It tickles!
I'll give you a kiss.
It tickles.
It felt good.
It did, didn't it?
Yes.
Hey.
Yes?
Show me your chest again.
Of course.
Then...
I'll give you a lot of service.
Okay.
It's a secret.