How about this side?
Like this?
A little bit like this.
Is this better?
Yes, yes.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
How about you, Yama?
If you have any questions, you can ask me.
If you don't have any, it's okay.
Yama.
You don't have a shadow at all.
Don't you know?
I don't know.
You don't know everything?
I'll tell you everything you don't know.
I don't care.
Can I change it?
No.
It's a little different to change it.
Let's do it right, Yama.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Can I ask you a question?
Yes.
Is this better?
No.
It doesn't make sense.
Is this better?
No.
It's okay.
Is this better?
Yes.
It doesn't make sense at all.
Is this better?
Yes.
You should go home.
It's better to go home.
Is this 3.4?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Is this 5.7?
Yes.
Is this 6?
Is this 6.9?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
It's okay.
You should go home.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
What do you think?
You should go home.
No.
I don't want to watch it.
It doesn't make sense.
I'll teach you.
You don't want to go home, do you?
I don't want to go home.
How long are you going to do this?
If you tell me what I don't know, I'll teach you.
I don't know what to ask you.
What do you want me to do?
I don't know.
You don't teach me well.
I don't know what to ask you.
You talk too much.
I can't hear you.
You should talk more clearly.
If you were a teacher, you would be better.
I don't know what to ask you.
You talk too much.
Say something.
I don't know what to ask you.
What is it?
Did you disappear?
Can you hear me?
Are you sick?
Why don't you go to the infirmary?
Why don't you let go of your hand?
It hurts.
You can't do anything.
What is it?
I'm close to you.
Can you stay away from me?
What?
What is it?
Did you think I was a teacher who wouldn't get angry?
It's disgusting.
What is it?
Can you stay away from me?
What are you wearing?
Are you crazy?
It hurts.
Can you stay away from me?
Are you crazy?
You don't do anything when you go home, do you?
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
Don't touch me.
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
It's hot.
Don't do that.
What?
It's disgusting.
It stinks.
I'm sorry.
It's disgusting.
Is it good?
Of course it's good.
Go to bed.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Get out of my way.
Don't do that.
You're crazy.
Do you want to be in the video?
You said you wanted to be in the video.
I didn't say that.
I'm sorry.
It's disgusting.
You're crazy.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Do you know what I'm doing?
I'm sorry.
Get closer to me.
Get up.
I don't want to.
It's hot.
Get up.
Can you get up?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I don't feel good.
Does it feel good?
I'm saying it feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's hot.
Let me go.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's hot.
Stop.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Can you sit on the chair?
Sit down.
It's hot.
What's going on?
Look at me.
I'm going to cry.
I'm really crazy.
You're still energetic.
I'm not energetic.
You're energetic.
I'm going to cry.
I feel good.
How long are you going to do this?
You're moving your hips.
I feel good.
I'm going to cry.
You're moving your hips.
I feel good.
Are you going to touch me?
I'm going to cry.
You're moving your hips.
I feel good.
I'm going to cry.
Have you calmed down?
Did you feel good?
I feel good.
Really?
You're just studying, aren't you?
You can do it, can't you?
I know.
If there's anything you don't know, tell me.
I'll tell you.
If you want to have sex, let me know.
You can tell me anything.
Are you ready?
I'm going to cry.
Yuzo, you've been in the room for a week, haven't you?
Yes, I am. I'm sorry.
It's not your fault, is it?
I don't know the exact cause.
Yuzo, I heard that you had a quarrel with a boy in your class.
I was in the middle school, too.
I'm sorry I couldn't check your opinions.
You didn't apologize to him, did you?
No, I didn't.
I'm sorry I couldn't talk to him.
You can talk to him from now on.
I wanted to talk to him, so I went to his house today.
Do you always talk to him like that at school?
If you talk to him like that, students will look down on you.
I don't think so.
Can't you talk to him properly?
I'm sorry I couldn't talk to him today.
Hello.
Yuzo, your teacher is here.
Let's talk to him.
What's wrong with you?
Your teacher is here.
Say hello to him.
It's been a long time.
Is he okay?
He's not sick.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with him?
Did he hate school?
No, he didn't.
He's your classmate, isn't he?
Please be a good boy.
You had a fight in class, didn't you?
Yuzo, you're one week late for class.
You have to go to a new school.
I brought you a printout.
I hope you'll be able to go to school next week.
Did your teacher arrange it for you?
It's a week's worth, so it's a lot.
Your teacher also helped me.
Yuzo, you can study.
You'll catch up in about a week.
Don't say that.
You can study.
You can come to school next week.
If you're okay, I'll tell you what I don't know.
Do you have time?
I don't have time today.
Let's study together.
Yuzo, it's time for you to study.
Yuzo, answer me.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it.
I'll tell you something that's hard to say to your mom.
Yuzo, listen to what I say.
Can I ask you to study?
Yuzo, listen.
Let's study for a week.
You've been staying up all night.
You're smart.
What's wrong?
I'm sleepy.
Let's bring a pillow.
You had a fight at school.
I know.
I'm going to sleep.
If you know, leave me alone.
You're annoying.
I heard from Mr. Sakuma.
What did he say?
He said he was sorry.
He's a bad guy.
He doesn't think he's a bad guy.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Sakuma will be sorry.
No, he won't.
He's never regretted anything in his life.
Don't say that.
I hate it.
I can't forgive Mr. Sakuma.
I see.
I'll drop him out of school.
Then I'll go to school.
I see.
I don't want to go to school.
Mr. Sakuma always says that to me.
I can help you if you don't want to go to school.
I don't want to go to school.
Mr. Sakuma.
I want to talk to you.
Then you can talk to me.
I don't want to see his face.
I see.
If you go to school, I'll help you.
I can't rely on you.
You can't rely on me.
I can't rely on you at all.
I wish you were a good teacher.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't talk to you.
It's your fault.
If you were a reliable teacher, I could talk to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm not a good teacher.
You should be a good teacher.
I'm sorry.
I listened to you.
What should I do?
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
You know what?
The old woman with glasses went somewhere.
My mother?
No, the old woman with glasses.
She's looking down on me.
She's worried about me.
That's not true.
Don't talk about that.
You know what?
Will you help me?
Yes.
You said that, didn't you?
Will you do anything for me?
I'll do my best if I can.
Will you really do your best?
I'll do my best.
Then, show me your panties.
I can't do that.
Why?
That's the only thing you can do.
Is that so?
Show me your panties.
You're good at it.
I'm not good at it.
You said you'd do anything for me.
Is that true?
You're not motivated.
You're not reliable.
Is that the only thing you can do?
No.
Show me your panties.
Do you want to see my panties?
Yes.
I see.
What should I do?
Panties.
All of you are boring.
You're not funny.
What's wrong with you?
You're making fun of me.
Yuzo.
Will you wear my panties if I show you my panties?
What?
If you show me your panties, I'll think about it.
I can't show you my panties.
Panties.
Do you like it?
What?
You'll wear my panties if I show you my panties, right?
I can't see your panties.
If you want to show me your panties, show me your panties.
What should I do?
Do you want to see my panties?
What's that?
It's just a normal panty.
It looks like a stocking.
What's that?
I only have this stocking at home.
Do you always wear this stocking?
Yes, I do.
Really?
Yuzo.
Will you come to school with this stocking?
No.
It's not enough.
You should show me more.
Really?
I think so.
Yuzo.
Will you come to school with this stocking?
No.
You'll come to school with this stocking if I show you my panties, right?
Yuzo.
Do you always wear this stocking?
No.
Really?
Let's go to school.
No.
I can't go to school with this stocking.
What should I do?
Show me your panties.
Can I go to school with this stocking?
Are you serious?
Are you out of your mind?
Yuzo told you, didn't he?
No.
You said you'd go to school with this stocking, didn't you?
I'm not embarrassed.
You said you'd do anything for Yuzo, didn't you?
No.
Let's go to school.
Are you serious?
Are you out of your mind?
You'll come to school with this stocking, won't you?
No.
I'm serious.
Let's go to school.
I won't go to school with this stocking.
I see.
Let's go to school.
You'll go to school with this stocking, won't you?
I won't go to school with this stocking.
I'll do anything for you if you go to school with this stocking.
I know.
You said you'd go to school with this stocking, didn't you?
I said I won't go to school with this stocking.
What should I do?
I thought you wouldn't get angry.
You were very angry, weren't you?
What are you doing?
You're talking too much.
What are you talking about?
You can hear me, can't you?
What are you doing?
Stop it.
You're noisy.
I thought you wouldn't get angry.
Mom.
It's going to be hard for you if you call me mom.
Let's be quiet.
Don't be shy.
You look embarrassed.
Do you think I'm embarrassed?
Yuzo.
Why did you grow up so much?
Be quiet.
Stop it.
You were talking behind my back.
I'll show this to Sakuma.
Don't talk about Sakuma.
It's dangerous.
Stop it.
I know.
I'm your teacher.
You were very angry.
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
I was kidding.
I don't want you to see me.
You've grown up a lot.
I didn't know that.
What happened to you?
Stop it.
You're noisy.
You've grown up a lot.
You're provoking me.
Stop it.
You're noisy.
What are you doing?
You're making fun of me.
I know.
Stop it.
You're noisy.
Go to school.
No.
Stop it.
You're noisy.
You've grown up a lot.
What are you doing?
I'll call my mom.
No.
Stop it.
I'll be quiet.
It's all your fault.
You should have told me that you were going to school.
I'm sorry.
I can't say that.
Stop it.
You're naughty.
You're like a girl.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
What?
I know.
Stop it.
You made fun of me.
No.
I'm embarrassed.
What are you doing?
Your buttocks are round.
Stop it.
You've grown up a lot.
You should have told me that you were going to school.
No.
You made me angry.
What's wrong?
Stop it.
You should have told me that you were going to school.
You're noisy.
Stop it.
I hate noisy people.
You're a pervert.
Did you say something?
No, I didn't.
I feel better when you're noisy.
What have you been doing for a week?
Have you been peeing all the time?
Did you poop a lot in a week?
I'm getting excited when I think about it.
What's wrong?
You don't like it?
I know.
I'm going to school.
Stop it.
It's too late.
What are you talking about?
I'm angry.
What do you mean?
Why are you angry?
I'm angry.
Stop it.
You're angry at me.
You're angry at your mother.
Stop it.
You have to punish a bad boy.
I know.
I'm sorry.
It's too late.
What do you mean?
I'm angry.
No, no, no.
Don't say that.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
If you cry, I'll cry, too.
Shut up.
You have a loud mouth.
You're noisy.
I'll shut up.
Stop it.
What?
But...
I've been taking care of you for a long time.
What are you talking about?
Don't lick me.
Stop it.
You have to punish a bad boy.
I know.
You're dirty.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Get out of my way.
You're noisy.
I want you to say that in class.
Don't bother me.
I'm sorry.
Did you understand?
I don't know.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
Did you get angry?
I know.
I have to go to school.
It's late.
Please sleep well.
I'm sorry.
Help me.
The teacher didn't tell you to go, did he?
You made a big noise.
I'm sorry.
I'll punish you.
I haven't punished you yet.
Stop it.
I'll punish you.
You made a big noise.
You're noisy.
I feel better.
Ryuzo.
You're noisy.
You made a big noise.
What happened to the chair?
It's okay.
You can't go without permission.
You made a big noise.
I'll punish you.
It smells good.
It smells like the teacher.
I'm hungry.
Stop it.
You'll get sick.
I'm sick.
What are you doing?
You're sick.
You can't go without permission.
What are you doing?
You're sick.
Stop it.
I feel good.
I got dirty.
It smells good.
I feel good.
Stop it.
Are you talking about me?
I got dirty.
I feel good.
What?
I'll go.
I'll make up with you.
I'm angry.
I can't forgive you.
I feel good.
I'll go.
I'll go to school.
I'll study with my teacher.
Do you want to get up?
I'll put you on my back.
You can do it.
Move.
I feel good.
You can do it.
Do it properly.
Your clothes are going to stretch.
You have to do it properly.
I feel good.
I'll put you on my back.
I want to get up.
You can go to school.
I'm happy.
Let's go to school.
I feel good.
I'll go to school.
I'll go.
I feel good.
Give me your hand.
I'll hold your hand.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
I told you that I'll do anything for you.
What's your answer?
You can go to school.
I'll go to school.
Sakamoto will cry.
I think so.
Yuzo, how are you?
I'm fine.
Excuse me.
How are you doing?
What's wrong?
I'm tired of studying.
I'll go to school.
What?
Really?
Thank you so much.
You look different from before.
We talked a lot.
She wants to go to school.
I see.
Thank you so much.
You're amazing.
I'm a good girl.
Yuzo praised you.
Get ready to go to school.
I'll go to school tomorrow.
I'll go to school tomorrow or next week.
Thank you so much.
It's boring.
I'll go home.
Tatsumi.
Aren't you in class?
What?
Why are you here?
I want to go home.
You can't.
You have to go to class.
Class is boring.
It's meaningless.
It's not meaningless.
I'll go to class when I want to go to class.
You can't.
I'm a teacher.
I can't let you go to class.
I know.
Go to class.
I'll go to class.
You can't.
Tatsumi, what are you doing?
You're in class.
I'm going to go to class.
Go to class.
I'll go to class.
What's wrong with you?
Mr.Kawada, please be strict.
If you don't be strict, you'll be licked.
Do you understand?
Yes.
If you don't be strict, you'll be licked.
Let's be strict from now on.
Yes.
Do you understand?
I'll be careful.
Yes.
Hinagawa was noisy.
I'm sure she's looking around at this time.
I'll kill time here.
I'm bored.
Tatsumi.
Why are you here?
Didn't you go to class?
I went to class for a moment.
A moment?
I went to class.
Don't say that.
I don't want to go to class.
If you don't go to class, you'll drop out of the class.
What?
What if I drop out of the class?
You won't be able to graduate.
Is that okay?
That's okay.
It's not okay.
Let's go out.
Don't look at your cell phone.
It's more meaningful to look at this than class.
This is a school.
You've been looking at your cell phone.
What are you doing at school?
Are you listening?
Tatsumi.
What are you doing?
Don't do that.
Don't play with your cell phone at school.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
Why do you always come to me?
Tatsumi.
What are you doing?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Everyone says that.
Give me back my cell phone.
What's wrong with you?
What are you laughing at?
What are you doing?
Don't touch me.
Give me back my cell phone.
What are you doing?
Don't do that.
Give me back my cell phone.
Did you think you were a teacher who wouldn't be angry with me?
Let me go.
Give me back my cell phone.
What are you doing?
Don't do that.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Do you want to see my cell phone?
What are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing?
It's hard.
I can't touch you.
You can touch me.
You really want to touch me, don't you?
What is this?
You can do whatever you want.
Why are you letting me go?
Don't do that.
It's not what you think.
What do you mean?
Don't do that.
What are you doing?
I'm so happy here.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What are you doing?
I'm so happy that I can't get up.
I'm so happy.
It's hard.
Stop it.
I can't do this.
You can touch me.
Is it hard?
It's hard.
I can't do this.
That's great.
You're so happy, aren't you?
Yes.
It's the first time I've seen you like this.
I can't do this.
It's very hard.
I'm sorry.
I'll put it in your mouth.
It's warm.
I put it in your mouth.
It feels good.
It's the worst.
It hurts.
I can't do this.
Are you moving?
It feels good.
I can't do this.
It's very hard.
Look at me.
It feels good.
I can't do this.
Get up.
Follow me.
It feels good.
Do it a little.
I can't do this.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's very deep.
It's very hard.
I can't do this.
Help me.
Ouch!
Come here.
From this side.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh
Hmm
Yeah yeah
you
I will make them stay here for a moment so you will be held on your mom's arms
I can't go up
She can't make them move
At there, we can't go up
Ouch!
You are sweating a lot.
Are you tired?
I was surprised.
Why?
But...
If you don't come to class,
I'll do this again.
Yes, hello.
Yes.
Well, I think Masakazu-kun is already home.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
I think he'll be home soon.
When he comes home,
if there's anything,
Yes.
Yes, I'd like you to call me again.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Yes, I'll be careful.
I'm sorry.
Yes, thank you.
Excuse me.
Furuta-kun's mother scolded me again.
She always blames me.
Furuta-kun's mother scolded him again.
Furuta-kun, what are you doing?
Did you follow me?
I'm free, so can I go to the teacher's house?
What are you talking about?
It's okay.
I'm free after this.
I'm in trouble.
You don't have any plans after this, do you?
What?
It's a very clean room.
It's already organized.
Did you plan to hang out with your boyfriend after this?
Furuta-kun, didn't you go to school today?
Yes.
I bought you orange juice.
Thank you.
I got a call from my mother today.
She told me that my son didn't go to school.
She asked me what was going on.
I see.
You should go to school.
I don't want to go to school.
Studying is boring.
That's not true.
Besides, I'm worried about my mother if I don't go to school.
You shouldn't make her worry.
I don't want to.
She always tells me to study.
You're worried about her.
Why do you think about her when you answer the phone?
I don't think about her.
I don't care.
I think she's annoying.
I don't think so.
You don't like her, do you?
No, I don't.
Tell her that you don't like her.
Don't do that.
I won't stop until you tell me to.
Let's stop.
This, too.
If you don't tell me, I'll tell the teacher that you brought me here.
No, I won't.
Let's stop.
Tell her that you don't like her.
I don't think so.
Just tell her that you don't like her.
Let's stop.
Show me your panties.
Don't do that.
Your panties are nice.
Tell her that you don't like her.
I don't like her.
You're not always clear-minded.
I've never seen you angry.
I don't like her.
All the students are saying that you're not clear-minded.
I'm on your side.
Let's be confident.
I don't like her.
Tell her that you don't like her.
I want to quit school.
If she says that she doesn't like me, I might be able to quit school.
Tell her that you don't like her.
It's easy to say that you don't like her.
Why?
I want you to tell her that you don't like her.
Tell her that you don't like her.
Will you show me your panties?
You can show me your skirt.
Why are you taking off your top?
Are you listening to me?
What are you doing?
What are you doing with your underwear?
You can take off your underwear.
Did you think that I was a weak teacher?
No, I didn't think so.
What are you doing?
Did you think so?
A little.
What are you doing?
Look at me.
I'm going to tell her that you're a weak teacher.
It's okay.
I'm going to tell her that you looked pathetic in front of the teacher.
Don't do that.
I'm in trouble.
I see.
What are you doing?
Open your mouth.
Is the teacher's daiki delicious?
Is it delicious?
Answer me.
Did you get a hard one?
Are you excited because I'm a weak teacher?
I'm going to take a video.
It's okay.
You can't afford it.
You're getting bigger.
What's wrong?
Time is running out.
Stop it, teacher.
I can't stop it.
Where is the teacher?
Stop it.
Why are you so energetic?
I'm embarrassed.
Are you excited?
Are you?
You're getting harder.
What's wrong?
You're feeling better.
The teacher...
What's wrong?
If you have something to say, you should say it.
It's nothing.
You like boobs, don't you?
You like it, don't you?
Lick it more.
Is it painful?
It's not enough.
You can't do that.
Make the teacher feel better.
I'm going to push you more.
More.
Is it painful?
I'm not going to stop yet.
Lick your own nipples.
I'm going to push you more.
Does it feel good?
Do it yourself.
How do you do it?
You look pathetic.
But it's not over yet.
I'm going to push you more.
You're not as strong as before.
Lick it more.
I'm sorry.
You can't lick it like that.
I can't hear you.
Do you want to lick it more?
I'm going to push you more.
Is it painful?
That's great.
You've got a lot of pus.
Did you feel good?
Did you say that?
That's right.
It's not what I usually do.
It hurts a lot.
Why are you so energetic?
What is it?
Does it hurt?
Tell me what it is.
Are you going to eat it again?
You have to be patient.
It's getting harder and harder.
Does it feel good?
What is it?
I can't hear you at all.
Does it hurt?
You're so energetic again.
What is it?
I can't hear you at all.
You're at your limit.
You're so cute.
Hey.
Do you want me to put it in your ear?
That's not good.
Are you going to say that?
Your ears are wet, right?
I'm a teacher.
I'll put it in your ear.
That's amazing.
It's deep inside.
Does it feel good?
I'll make it harder.
Do you want me to put it in your ear?
Does it feel good?
That's amazing.
It feels good, right?
It feels good.
That's amazing.
Does it hurt?
You look so pathetic.
I'm in trouble, too.
What is it?
Are you regretting coming home?
I don't think so.
That's amazing.
Does it feel good?
If you lick my neck, it'll get really hard.
It feels good.
Let's go.
It feels good, right?
I'm a teacher.
Look inside.
Here.
I'm in trouble.
It feels good.
I'm a teacher.
I'm in trouble.
Open your mouth.
It feels good.
I'm in trouble.
What is it?
Are you going to go?
Let me out.
I'm in trouble.
It feels good.
You can still go.
What are you doing?
I don't know what's going on.
It's still hard.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Do you always make it so hard?
Don't go.
Don't study.
You're making it hard.
You're an old man.
It feels good.
Don't run away.
I'm going in again.
It feels good.
You're a good athlete.
I'm in trouble.
How far are you going to go?
Can you see where I'm going?
I'm in trouble.
It feels good.
I'm going in again.
Come on.
You can still go.
Wait a minute.
It feels good.
Touch my butt.
Do more.
It feels good.
More.
Do more.
It feels good.
I'm in trouble.
I'm going in.
Can I stop?
No.
Let me be satisfied.
It feels good.
Move your hips more.
Like this?
It feels good.
I'm in trouble.
Do more.
It feels good.
I'm going in.
I'm sorry.
I won't let you go yet.
Move your hips more.
Like this?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'm going in.
Move your hips more.
Listen to me.
It feels good.
Move your hips more.
Does it feel good?
I'm going in.
I'm sorry.
I'm too nervous.
Get me out of here.
I'm sorry.
I'm going in.
You're right.
I got you out so many times.
You got me out so many times.
You can listen to me, right?
You can listen to your mother, right?
You can go to school, right?
It's a promise.
If you want to do it, I'll let you do it anytime.
Okay?
What should I do?
I'm so tired.
I have 10 hours of free time.
I'm going to take a break.
Let's go now.
Did I have money?
I'm here to get a turn-in.
It's okay.
I'm not going to beat you.
I'm on the phone now.
It's okay.
I'm a strong person.
I'm sure you will get a turn-in.
Don't call me.
Yeah.
You're okay, aren't you?
I'm not okay.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
I'll hang up.
I'll call you back.
Misano, you're noisy.
No.
It's Masuda's class.
What?
I hate Masuda.
I hate him, too.
If he is a teacher, he should be useful to students.
I don't like him.
But it's not good to ignore him.
I don't care.
I don't use math.
I won't ignore him.
Come here.
What?
Hurry up.
I'll take a class.
Come here.
Next.
I don't like him.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Come here.
You surprised me.
I want you to look at me.
No.
Okay, I won't look at you.
What color are you?
What?
Black?
Red?
I don't know.
Purple?
Your face is red.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't know.
What size are your boobs?
What?
Boobs.
Tell me the size of your boobs.
Okay.
Hey.
What?
A?
B?
What was it?
D?
C?
Your boobs are bigger than mine.
What are you talking about?
You should tell me the size of your boobs.
Oh, no.
I'm late.
I have to go to the hospital.
You should tell me the size of your boobs.
No.
I'm sorry.
I didn't win.
I couldn't get in the scoring, I lost many games.
However, I returned to the school.
I should play with my cell phone too.
My hand hurts.
I don't want to do this anymore.
What the hell is this?
What are you doing?
I'm playing a mobile game.
I used up all my money.
I have nothing to do.
I'm in class.
I don't want to do this anymore.
What are you doing?
You should go to class.
I don't want to do this anymore.
I want to play a mobile game.
What?
I don't want to play a mobile game.
I don't want to do this anymore.
Do you want to go to the bathroom?
That's okay.
I don't want to go to the bathroom.
I'm not going to go to the bathroom.
I'm not going to do this anymore.
I don't want to do this anymore.
Misano.
You should do something.
I don't want to do this anymore.
Then you should go to class.
I don't want to go to class.
Do you understand?
You should do something.
Then you should go to class.
If you don't go to class, Misano will blame you.
Let's play a mobile game.
The probability is low.
Let's play 10 times.
What's wrong with you?
Are you sick?
What?
I understand.
You like me.
That's why you're with me.
I'll play with you.
Tell me the color of your underwear.
Misano.
What?
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
I thought you were a teacher who wouldn't get angry at me.
Hey.
You want to see the color of my underwear, don't you?
Can you show me?
I'll show you.
Show me.
Do you like this?
I don't want to see it anymore.
You can see it.
I'm dying.
You're curious, aren't you?
I'm fine.
I'll show you more.
Do you want to see the color of my underwear?
I'm fine.
This is the color of the cup.
What?
A, B, C...
A, B, C, D, E, F, G...
Hey, look at me.
Have you ever licked me?
Come on, lick me.
Put your tongue out and lick me.
I'm worried about your boobs.
I'm sorry.
By the way, Misano...
Your boobs...
You like them, don't you?
They're getting hard.
I think about dirty things every day.
That's why I'm like this.
What are you always doing?
I can't answer that.
What?
I can't answer that rude question.
You're throwing up a lot.
Why are you throwing up so much?
Hey.
Wow.
Misano.
You're breaking up.
Have you ever been licked?
Yes.
Really?
It feels good.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You look pathetic.
It's hard, so let's take it off.
I've never seen such a big boob.
It's hard.
Do you like it?
Do you like big boobs?
Yes.
I like it.
You're a good boy when you're naughty.
Yes.
You have a weak nipple.
It's cute.
Koe-chan.
You're mumbling a lot.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
You sound like you're going to puke.
I'm not going to puke.
I'm going to puke.
Can I go?
What is it?
I'm going to puke.
Your eyes are white.
You look like you're going to puke.
I'm going to puke.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'm going to puke.
Your eyes are wide open.
I couldn't stand that time.
My eggs hurt.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Why did you get up like that?
Please forgive me.
I know I can't help you.
It feels good.
I'm scared.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I'm scared.
I'm sorry.
Do you want it?
No, I don't want it.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
Here.
Wait a minute.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
It doesn't feel good.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I understand.
It feels good.
No, no, no.
Here.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
It doesn't feel good.
I love you.
I'm happy.
You're not happy.
Do you hate me?
No, I don't hate you.
I don't want to stay like this.
I'm sweating.
It feels good.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to be scolded.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to be scolded again.
I want you to pay me.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
I'm going to be scolded again.
I can't stop.
I'm sweating.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Hey.
I washed the bread with the water that was in the house.
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's so delicious.
I'll give you one more.
You stay here.
Oh no.
I'm okay.
I'm still standing.
It's okay.
I'm going to cry.
I'm scared.
I can't do this.
I'm going to die.
I can't go.
It's from behind.
I'm going to die.
I've got a lot of powder on my back.
Oh, it's so hot.
It's so hot.
Hey, you have to use it.
Oh, it's so hot.
I can't do anything because I'm so tired
I still have to do my housework
I feel so tired
It hurts.
Stop it.
It tickles.
I'm sorry.
More.
It tickles.
Stop it.
I can still do it.
You can still do it?
Yes.
Hey, doctor.
Yes?
Put a bandage on his chest.
Are you sure?
Please.
Yes.
Stop it.
Are you okay?
It tickles.
Put a bandage on his chest.
Stop it.
It tickles.
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
It tickles.
I want to stop it.
Stop it.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah , ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, oh, oh ah, ah, ah,
toroahn
Ah I went message
I
Ah
Does it tickle?
If you get more serious,
I'll always be there for you.
Really?
You have to take classes properly from tomorrow.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'm going to sleep.
Okay.