Nice to meet you. I'm Minami. Nice to meet you.
I'm Yuto, my son.
Yuto-kun.
Hey, Yuto. Say hello.
Nice to meet you.
As you can see, my life is not going well.
Especially my grades.
Oh, really?
I'm in a situation where I can't do anything about it, so I'd like to ask my teacher.
What kind of subjects do you have in particular?
Overall, I'm not good at math.
Oh, math?
But I think I can teach you if it's math.
Oh, really?
Yes. Right, Yuto-kun?
Well, yes.
You're not good at math?
I'm good at math.
Huh?
I'm okay.
What are you okay with?
I'm okay with math.
Huh?
You mean you can do it yourself?
Yes.
Your grades are not good because you can't do it, right?
No, that's not true.
Actually, I'm not good at tests at all.
Oh, really?
It's really hard to deal with.
Do you mean you're studying?
Yes.
But you're not good at tests?
Huh? Is that what you mean?
If you can't do it because you're studying, you're an idiot.
I like studying.
If you like those grades, then there's nothing you can do about it.
My dad is annoying, so I hate studying.
Ask your teacher to teach you again.
Are you studying properly?
Well, just in case.
Oh, really?
But I'm sure you know the formula, so I'll teach you everything from now on.
Okay.
I'm not going to say anything harsh, so let's do our best together.
Yes, thank you.
Right, dad?
Oh, really.
Please start from the basics.
From the basics?
Yes.
That's right.
I'd like to fix what I hate studying.
Thank you.
No, thank you too.
Yuto, watch me closely.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
Yuto, I'll take good care of you from now on.
Thank you.
Let's do our best.
Yes.
Next is this.
First, let's write the formula.
Okay.
Yes.
This is...
Write it.
Yes, I'm sorry.
This.
What is this?
What?
Is this S?
No, no.
This is a space.
First, write A here.
A.
That's right.
Write minus.
What is this?
This is difficult.
It's difficult.
But you have to be able to do this much for the exam.
Did you write it?
Yes, I did.
Okay.
Then, divide this by the number of spaces and the number of kicks.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
Then, let's divide this.
Let's divide this.
Divide?
Yes, divide.
You can divide this up and down, right?
Yes.
You can divide this up and down.
Is that so?
Yes, that's right.
That's right.
You can proceed like this.
Then, can you solve this as it is?
Yes.
Then, solve it.
The boobs are so big.
It's so round.
It was soft before.
I'm glad you got it right.
I wanted you to get it right.
Did you solve it?
Yes.
Yes, I did.
What is the problem?
This?
Yes.
Excuse me.
I can't read it, so can you write it again?
This?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Can you write it again?
Yes.
This?
Yuto, did you solve it?
What's wrong? Your hand is frozen.
Yuto?
Are you okay?
Is your hand frozen?
Yes, it is.
Shall we continue?
I'm sorry.
Yes.
I'm glad you got it right.
Thank you.
What's wrong? Your hand is frozen.
I'm sorry.
Do you have a problem with your voice?
No, I don't.
Are you okay?
I'm a little dazed.
Are you dazed?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Really?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
The dough is too hard.
Did you wash it?
Yuto?
Shall we take a break?
Yes.
Let's take a break.
Shall we take a break?
Yes.
Let's take a break.
Yuto?
Why isn't it open?
Why is it half open?
Is it to take a picture?
Yuto?
What's wrong?
What are you thinking?
What?
You've been opening your clothes.
Your clothes are wet.
What should I do?
Stop it.
But...
I'm in trouble.
This kind of clothes are popular now.
I can't help it.
I can't help thinking about it.
Please don't do that.
But...
Everyone is wearing this kind of clothes now.
I often see it at university.
I think there are many people who are going to take the exam and are wearing this kind of clothes.
But...
What would you do if you saw a boy wearing this kind of clothes at the entrance exam?
It's a waste of time to work so hard.
Don't you think it's a waste?
It's okay.
Right?
Yuto.
Then...
Minami's...
To get used to this kind of clothes...
Well...
Let me touch your boobs.
Boobs?
Yes.
Does that...
Does that increase your concentration?
Yuto?
Yes.
Well...
Then...
It's okay.
Really?
Yes.
Minami.
Then...
Yes.
Let me...
Let me touch your boobs.
Yes.
Then...
It's amazing.
It's soft.
Minami, it's amazing.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Really?
Sensei.
Well...
From the back...
Can I touch your boobs?
Here?
I want to touch your boobs.
Does that increase your concentration?
Then...
Yes.
Sensei.
I want to touch your boobs.
Can I?
Yes.
It's softer than before.
Really?
It's soft.
It feels good.
Then...
Yuto-kun.
Is it okay?
You can concentrate now, right?
No.
Well...
Directly...
I want to touch your boobs directly.
Directly?
Does that increase your concentration?
Yes, it does.
Then...
This time...
Sensei.
Thank you.
Yuto-kun.
Can you take this off?
I'll try.
Can you do it?
It hurts.
Can you take it off?
Does it hurt?
It hurts.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I took it off.
Does it bother you?
I can take it off.
You can take it off?
Yes.
You can touch my boobs directly, right?
It's okay.
It's...
It's soft.
Is it soft?
It's very soft.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I was surprised.
Yuto-kun.
I've been touching your boobs all the time.
What's wrong?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
What's wrong?
At this rate, we won't be able to continue studying.
Right?
Aren't you going to study?
I have to study.
Right?
Yes.
I'll take it off.
Okay.
I'll do something more pleasant for you.
Let's study together when it's over.
Okay.
Let's study.
Are you embarrassed?
It's not embarrassing.
It's okay.
You're fine.
It's not embarrassing.
Put your hand away.
It's okay.
Right?
Yes.
Have you ever been licked here?
Have you?
No.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
Are you surprised?
Hey, Yuto.
You like boobs, don't you?
Yes.
Give me your leg.
My leg?
Your leg.
It's okay.
What are you doing?
I'm pinching you.
I see.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It does, doesn't it?
It's dangerous.
Is it dangerous?
What's dangerous?
Don't do that.
Do you want me to put it on your clothes?
It's hot.
It's dangerous.
Is it dangerous?
I'm going to sleep.
Are you going to sleep?
No.
Don't put it on my clothes.
It's hot.
I'm going to sleep.
Are you going to sleep?
Yes.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Is it warm?
It's hot.
It's dangerous.
Do you want me to take it off?
Don't do that.
Hey.
Then...
Let's do the endurance training with me.
Endurance training?
Endurance training.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Endurance training.
Don't go until I say it's okay.
Okay.
I'll make you some tea.
It feels good when I hug you.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It feels good when I hug you.
It's dangerous.
Don't go until I say it's okay.
It's training.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to puke.
It's dangerous.
It's hot.
I'm going to puke.
It's dangerous.
Oh...
Suzuko...
Please don't look inside.
What?
Inside?
It's dangerous.
What?
The doctor didn't say it's okay, did he?
I don't feel good.
Did he leave?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I...
I can still do it.
Please let me do it again.
I'll be patient next time.
Do it again?
I'll be patient.
Be patient.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Please be patient.
I'll do it again.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I couldn't help it.
You haven't said it's okay yet, have you?
I thought I could handle it if I moved by myself.
Really?
Yes, really.
I thought I could handle it if I moved by myself.
Can you really handle it?
Yes, I really can.
Can you move by yourself?
Just a little bit.
I want to get used to it.
I'm sorry.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
I'll get up.
I want to see your face.
I'm sorry.
Can I go now?
I want to go.
Hey, Yuto.
Did you get used to my breast?
No.
I'm not used to it yet.
Not yet?
But you'll be fine if you get used to it.
Let's train from now on.
Yes.
You've found a good way to study.
Thank you.
Not yet?
I wonder what kind of clothes the teacher will wear today.
The previous knitwear was really good.
But I can't concentrate on studying if I wear that.
But I want to see it.
I wonder what kind of clothes it is.
Yes, I'm open.
Nice to meet you, teacher.
Nice to meet you, too.
Did you solve the previous problem?
Yes.
Can I see it?
Show me.
Teacher.
Your breasts are amazing today, too.
Look at this.
Which one?
I can't see it today.
I want to touch your breasts.
How is it?
The last problem.
The answer is correct, but the way to solve it is a little different.
Really?
Can you tell me?
I got it.
This is the problem.
Yes.
This is 3.
And here, too.
Don't add it, multiply it.
There are breasts on your arms.
Which one?
I want to see it.
Do you think you can solve it with this?
Yes, I'll try.
I wonder if the breasts will be on the table.
Teacher.
Did you show it to me?
It's amazing.
Everything is done.
Thank you.
You're good.
If you know how to solve it, it will be easier to solve the next problem.
I see.
A plus B.
Root.
L, right?
Breasts.
It's the closest so far.
Here.
Can you see it?
Yes.
What should I do with this?
Apply this.
Apply this and add it.
Then you'll get the answer.
I see.
I want to put my face in the pie.
It's a little difficult.
Solve the practice problem and repeat it several times.
I got it.
Can you solve it?
Let's take a break.
Yes.
You're reading a difficult book.
I'm reading more and more.
Can I see it?
Yes.
What is it for?
Why is it in there?
Is it a bra?
I can't concentrate.
I can't concentrate at all.
You can solve this problem.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
What is it?
I was talking about solving this problem.
Are you talking about this question 2?
It's question 1.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Are you tired?
Or are you worried about the exam?
You're fine.
You've solved so many problems.
What's wrong?
Can I ask you a question?
Yes.
I've been wondering for a long time.
Is your clothes your hobby?
This clothes?
Yes.
I often wear such clothes.
There are many people around me, so I tried it on.
In your case, you have a good body line.
Is that so?
Yes.
Are you worried about this clothes?
No.
I'm fine.
What will you do if there are people who wear similar clothes to you?
Well...
It's a waste if you can't solve the problem.
Don't you have the ability to concentrate?
Well...
I don't think it's good to wear such clothes in front of the students.
And...
Your clothes today...
Your back...
My back?
Your back is bare.
I thought it was cute, so I wore it.
It's too stimulating.
Can't you concentrate because you're worried about your back?
Or can't you concentrate because you're worried about your clothes?
Do you want to touch your boobs?
What?
Well...
Is that okay?
If you can't concentrate with this clothes, it's a waste if you can't solve the problem.
So you can practice to solve the problem while touching your boobs.
I see.
I'll test your concentration with your boobs.
Yes.
I'll give you a question.
Answer it in one minute.
Okay.
111 times...
25.
What?
Can I really touch my boobs?
What is this?
It's impossible.
Takumi...
If you don't do it quickly, you can't practice.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Wow.
Today's bra is pink.
What's going on in front of me?
I'll touch my boobs.
Okay.
Wow.
It's so soft.
Your boobs are too soft.
What's your answer?
What?
Is it time?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
What was the question?
Come on.
I'll give you another question.
Concentrate this time.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Well...
225 times...
50?
No.
I can't concentrate at all.
But...
I have to touch my boobs.
Wow.
What's your answer?
My answer?
Well...
10,250.
You're right.
Really?
You're amazing.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Can I continue this training?
Why?
I want to improve my level.
Can I touch your boobs directly?
What?
What do you mean?
I want to improve my level by touching your boobs directly.
What?
I want to touch your boobs directly.
What should I do?
If you pass this test, you can take the entrance exam.
If it's for you...
Really?
I'll do my best.
Can I have your bra?
Okay.
She took my bra in front of me.
Is she a teacher?
I'll ask you a question.
Okay.
333 times...
44?
Excuse me.
She's a teacher.
She's sweating a little.
Is she nervous?
She's sweating a lot.
Her neck is stiff.
Can I touch your neck?
She's sweating a lot.
Can I touch your boobs anytime?
Is she a teacher?
Don't be so hard on me.
I'll be gentle.
How do you feel?
What's your answer?
I don't know.
Don't be so hard on me.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to take the endurance test?
Endurance test?
Excuse me.
You have to take the endurance test.
She's sweating a lot.
Are you okay?
Do you want to take the endurance test?
It's hard, isn't it?
I'll help you.
She's sweating a lot.
Were you looking at my boobs?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to wipe the sweat off your boobs.
It would be nice if you pinched my boobs.
Can I do that?
Okay.
How do you feel?
It's hard, isn't it?
This will make you feel better.
How do you feel?
It's hard, isn't it?
Are your boobs soft?
It's soft.
It's hard, isn't it?
She's sweating a lot.
It's hot.
Takumi.
Yes?
Do you want to see my boobs in person?
Yes.
I'm going to show them to you in person.
It's hot.
Do you want to lick my boobs?
What?
Do you want to lick them?
Yes.
Okay.
It's hot.
Really?
May I put some ointment on your neck?
Yes.
It's hot.
Are you lonely?
No.
No, I'm not.
What do you want me to do for you?
I need to do something for you.
Okay?
It's hot.
Are you lonely?
I can't take it anymore. Can I put it in?
It's okay, Takumi-kun.
Your face is so hot.
Really?
Okay, I'll put it in.
Just a little more.
I did it.
It's hot.
Takumi-kun.
I can't take it anymore.
Just a little more.
Okay.
I can't take it anymore.
I said it's okay, but you're going too fast.
But you're so nice.
Next time, don't go until I say it's okay.
Okay.
I'll put it in.
Takumi-kun, be patient next time.
Okay.
I'll put it in.
It's hot.
You're so nice.
I can't take it anymore.
I'll put it in.
It's hot.
Takumi-kun.
Can I do more training?
Okay.
It's hot.
I'll put it in.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
.
Next If you exercise a little more, you will be fine,
Anyway, you've found a good way to study, haven't you?
Yes, I have.
Hehehe...
I wonder if Rika-sensei will come soon.
I can't calm down at all.
I wonder what kind of knitwear she'll wear today.
The knitwear I was wearing the other day...
I couldn't see the line of my body.
I was worried about my boobs.
I can't concentrate at all.
What should I do?
Yes.
A is the effect of two pieces.
B is the effect of three pieces.
The one with the most pieces of the effect on the front wins.
At this time, let's look for the probability of A winning.
However, if the number of pieces of the effect on the front is the same,
or if there is only one piece of the effect on the back,
let's draw.
Toru-kun, is there anything you don't understand?
Toru-kun?
Did you hear that?
Yes, I heard.
Is there anything you don't understand?
For now, it's okay.
It's okay?
It's a coin.
Do you understand?
Is it okay?
Yes.
2 plus Y...
The number of pieces of the effect on the front is 1, 2, 2.
The number of pieces of the effect on the back is 1, 3, 3, 3.
Is it okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I don't understand at all.
If you use this formula, you can solve it.
That's right.
I'll use the formula here.
The formula...
The number of pieces of the effect on the back is 1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 9, 12, 18, 27, 36, 54, 108.
108.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What's wrong?
My eyes are tired.
You look a little strange today.
Is that so?
Are you nervous because it's before the exam?
Don't you have enough concentration?
I'm sorry. I wonder if that's a little too much.
Do you want to take a break?
Just a little.
What's wrong?
Why is it open?
Are you wearing a bra?
It's like you're asking me to get out of there.
No.
I can't concentrate at all.
What's wrong?
What?
I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
I can't concentrate because of you.
Because of me?
Yes.
You're wearing a bra that emphasizes your boobs every time.
What's wrong with your back today?
My back?
It's open.
You're wearing a sexy bra.
If you wear something like this, you can't concentrate on your studies.
Isn't it normal now?
Everyone wears this kind of clothes.
No, it's not normal.
In your case, your body line is like this.
If you look at this, you can't concentrate on your studies.
What are you going to do in the exam room?
You can't concentrate if you wear such clothes.
I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
It's your fault that I can't concentrate on my studies.
But it's normal now.
I can't concentrate on my studies.
In order to be able to concentrate on your studies, you need to get used to it.
If you can get used to your boobs, you can concentrate on your studies.
How?
If you rub your teacher's boobs, you can concentrate on your studies.
Rub?
If you do that, you can concentrate on your studies.
Can you really concentrate?
Of course.
I can't concentrate on my studies because I'm worried about my boobs.
If you rub your teacher's boobs, you can concentrate on your studies.
Can you concentrate on your studies if I cooperate with you?
Of course.
Okay.
I'll cooperate with you.
Are you sure?
Please concentrate on your studies.
Okay.
Excuse me.
It's cold.
Can I touch your boobs directly?
Directly?
I think I can touch your boobs directly.
You can touch my boobs from the top of my head.
Okay.
It's cold.
Can I touch your boobs?
Okay.
It's cold.
Can I touch your boobs from the top of my head?
From the top of my head.
It's cold.
I'll touch your soft boobs.
Can I touch your soft boobs directly?
It's okay.
It's amazing.
I'm sweating a lot.
I feel like I'm being cut.
It's amazing.
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
Not at all.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
This is...
It's getting harder.
I'm sorry.
It's too attractive.
Next, let's train your endurance.
I'm going to sleep.
Don't go until the doctor says it's okay.
What?
I'm sorry.
Don't go yet.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
You're very nervous.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Don't go yet.
You like boobs, don't you?
I love boobs.
Next, let's train your endurance with boobs.
What?
What are you doing?
How is it?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
How is it?
Don't go yet.
I'm sorry.
Be patient.
Don't go yet.
I'm sorry.
Train your endurance.
Don't go yet.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it directly.
Directly?
It can't be helped.
Be patient.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Be patient.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Don't go yet.
Let's move on to the next training.
The next one?
I'm sorry.
Don't go yet.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Don't go yet.
Be patient.
It's a training.
I'm sorry.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I didn't tell you to go yet.
Why did you go out?
I'm sorry.
But you're still a baby.
You can still do it, can't you?
I didn't tell you to go yet.
You can't.
You're still training.
I'm sorry.
Don't go yet.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
You can go now.
It's a little numb here.
I heard a strange sound.
I can't stand it.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
You're sweating a lot
You can still do it, right?
You're always panting
You can still do it
That surprised me
You didn't say you can still do it, but you did
You can still do it, right?
This time, you do it yourself
She's sleeping
You can still do it
You're sweating a lot
I'm sorry
You're sweating again?
Next, I'll do it from behind
Try putting it in from behind
Put it in quickly
You can still do it
It feels good, right?
You can still do it?
You can still do it
It feels good, right?
It feels good
You can still do it
Toru-kun
Did you train your strength and concentration?
I trained it with the help of the teacher
Really?
Then, let's do this again in the next class
I'll do my best
Is the teacher here yet?
I'm looking forward to it
I wonder what kind of clothes she'll wear today
Last time, her boobs were really round
I want her to wear something amazing
Is she here yet?
Ryo-kun
Is it okay to come in?
Is she here yet?
The teacher was waiting
Good morning
Are you okay with what you did last time?
Yes
Were you studying?
Yes, I was
That's great
Then, what should we do?
Do you want to start from a new place today?
Or do you want to do it in the same way as last time?
Or do you want to do it in a different way?
Last time, I copied her clothes
So, I want to start from a new place
Really?
That's great
What kind of clothes is this?
Her boobs are really round
I want to see it up close
Ryo-kun, you're pretty good at copying
You're good at it
If there's a part you didn't understand, you can do it
Do you want to do it around here?
No
Here?
Yes
Okay
I'll read it
It's a bit difficult
Because I have to use words
I'm not good at expressing myself
Oh, you're not good at it
I see
But in the entrance exam, the points around here get pretty big
I think it's better to start from a place where it's easy to get points
That's good
You got it right
You're good
Let's try a bit harder
Okay
What's wrong?
Do you understand the problem?
Yes, I do
You do?
You don't look well today
No, it's not like that
You're not feeling well
I'm okay
Let me check your temperature
You look fine
If you don't feel well, let me know
Okay
You can do it
You seem to be okay
I'd like to re-evaluate the one you solved last time
Can you do the one you're not good at?
Okay
You're not good at it
I think this one is good
Okay, I'll do it
Please solve this one
Okay
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Are you wearing a bra?
It's like you're asking for help
No, I can't concentrate
Ryo-kun, you got it right
Okay
You're not good at it
I think it's similar
Let's leave the one you got right
and study it
Okay
I'm so happy
You got it right
You're not good at it
I think it's similar
Let's leave the one you got right
and study it
Okay
You're not good at it
I think it's similar
Let's leave the one you got right
and study it
Okay
You're not good at it
I think it's similar
Let's leave the one you got right
and study it
Okay
Ryo-kun
What's wrong?
Are you nervous about the exam?
Don't worry
We've studied a lot together
It's your fault
My fault?
Did I teach you badly?
You can't concentrate
Sorry, did I say too much?
It's not like that
This is what you always wear
Clothes?
You can't concentrate
if you wear such clothes
And your back is open
I'm worried about you
But it's normal for her
It's not normal
You're just worried about her
I am
I can't help it
A lot of college students wear this
Are you that worried?
Yes, but I can't solve the problem
You can't concentrate?
No
Then
Do you want to test your concentration?
What?
Concentration test?
You can't concentrate
Okay
Don't be nervous
What if there's a girl like you?
You'll fail
Right
If that happens
I'll test your concentration
Okay, Ryo
Just one minute
Okay
I'll do it
Do whatever you want
Like this
Just one minute
Okay
Like this
Ryo
It's been a minute
Are you satisfied?
Yes
Okay
Let's study
Ryo
Sorry
What's wrong?
Is there a problem?
You know how I feel
I can't forget how I felt
I can't concentrate
So
Can you do it again?
Again?
No?
Okay
Really?
If you can't concentrate
You can hold my boobs
Okay
Are you sure?
Yes
I'll touch you
Okay
Ryo
Are you satisfied?
Yes, thank you
Hey
You know
If you do this
You'll fail the exam
No, I won't
Hey
Do you want to test your endurance?
Test my endurance?
Ryo, focus on this
You can concentrate on studying
I'll touch you
Okay
You can't do it, right?
Ryo
Let me see
You can't do it, right?
You have to endure
Okay
With me
I'll test your endurance
You can't do it
You can't do it, right?
Ryo
Ryo, your hips are moving
You have to endure
Okay
If you do this
You can't concentrate
Okay
I'm teaching you
You're a good boy
Ryo
You have a stain on your pants
Hey
When I teach you seriously
Do you always do this?
What do you want me to do?
Ryo, are you satisfied?
Do you want to do it?
You have a stain on your pants
You're a bad boy
You can't do it until I say so
This is a test of your endurance
Show me more
You can't do it
Endure it
Ryo, take off my pants
Okay
Touch me
You can't do it
More
Ryo
Does it feel good?
I love your hips
You can't do it
Touch me directly
Don't do it
You can't do it
It hurts
You can do it
Do you want to play with my boobs?
Please
You can't do it
Does it feel good?
Are my boobs soft?
They're soft
Okay
I'll hold you with my favorite blanket
Wow
It's soaked with blood
Ryo
Do you know I'm hugging you?
Does it feel good?
Wow
Blood is coming out
Do you like it more when I hug you directly?
I'll give you some air
It's hot
It's very hard
You can't do it?
You have to hold it
You can't do it
You're good at it
Can you hold it any longer?
Let's do our best a little more.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
You look so miserable.
Let's do our best for the last test.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
You can't bear with this alone, can you?
Let's bear with this.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
Does it feel good?
More, more, more.
Let's go!
Does it feel good?
Do you want me to do more?
You didn't say you could do more.
Can you still do your best?
Can you move as you like?
I'll move here.
Here?
Does it feel good?
Oh, no.
Let's go!
Did you go already?
I couldn't stop.
You didn't say you could do more.
I'm sorry.
Can you continue?
Does it feel good?
Let's go!
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
Did you go again?
Yes.
You didn't say you could do more.
No.
Can you still do your best?
Yes, I can.
Can you do your best?
I'll do my best.
I love you.
Oh, no.
Does it feel good?
Let's go!
Oh, no.
I'm sorry, teacher.
You've said a lot.
But you've trained your patience, haven't you?
Yes.
You've found a way to study.
Teacher.
Can you do it again?
Again?
Yes.
Oh, no.