I mean, I did take two rooms. You know what I mean, right?
Huh? Oh, yes.
I don't have that kind of attitude.
I don't even have an air conditioner in this room.
What's going on?
It's the worst.
When I'm on a business trip and I want to relax, I don't have an air conditioner in my room.
Yes.
Tenma, you want to relax, don't you?
But you don't listen to me at all.
It's all my fault.
What's going on?
I'm sure I took two rooms.
I'm in a bad mood.
This will affect my work.
Oh, I see.
You think so, don't you?
Yes.
I'm not being nice to you.
I'm a guest here.
It's natural for me to feel depressed.
What am I thinking?
I don't know what to say.
Tenma, are you listening to me?
Yes.
You're angry, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
And don't tell the company about this.
Okay.
I don't want you to be criticized.
You don't want to be criticized, do you?
Yes.
I have to go home.
I have to take a bath.
It's hot and I'm sweating.
Okay.
I have to take a bath and drink alcohol on a day like this.
Yes.
Don't you think so?
I have to take a bath.
I have to take a bath and drink alcohol on a day like this.
It's hot.
Tenma, you don't have to drink alcohol.
I'm fine.
It's hot.
I think so.
I have to drink alcohol on a day like this.
You're not sweating at all.
I'm not sweating at all.
I envy you.
I sweat a lot.
I can't stand this heat.
Can I turn on the fan?
It's hot.
I have to turn on the fan.
I don't have a fan.
I'm back to life.
I've lost a lot of weight.
I'm going to bed.
I'll wake you up tomorrow.
Okay.
I'm going to bed.
I can't stand this heat.
I can't wait to go to work tomorrow.
I have to turn on the fan.
I can't help it.
I have to sleep.
I drank a lot.
I'm going to bed.
I have to wake up early tomorrow.
I have to wake up early in the morning.
I don't want to go to work.
What is this?
This is wet.
Is this sweat?
This is too much sweat.
This is terrible.
My butt is wet.
Are you okay?
Are you sick?
Is it hot outside?
This is definitely sweat.
Is it hot?
I have to turn on the fan.
I have to turn it on.
I have to increase the temperature.
I'm going to turn it on.
This is cool.
I don't want my hands to be wet, so let it dry.
Hurry up...
I'm so sorry.
Should I get a blanket?
I'm getting worse.
Are you all right? Do you want some water?
Water?
You have a lot of hair.
Why don't you turn on the fan?
I'm sorry.
It was hot.
Please wait a little longer.
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
I'm sweating.
Is it hot?
It's hot.
I can't sweat.
It's Suzuki's fault.
I'm sorry.
Suzuki.
Please touch my butt.
My butt?
It's crazy.
It's hot.
My butt is getting hot.
I'm sweating.
It's crazy.
I'll wipe it off.
Is it hot?
It's hot.
Please touch my butt.
I'm sorry.
I'll wipe it off.
It's hot.
It's shiny.
I didn't want to do it.
It's crazy.
It's hot.
I'll wipe it off.
It's crazy.
It's hot.
I'll wipe it off.
I'm sweating.
My body is hot.
It's crazy.
I'm sweating.
This way.
Please come here.
How do you feel?
It's hot.
It's crazy.
How do you feel?
Hurry up.
It's crazy.
Did you sleep?
What are you doing?
How do you feel?
What should I do?
I can't.
Mr. Suzuki.
Come here.
I'm here.
I want you to sleep here.
I feel good.
I can't.
It hurts.
I feel good.
I can't.
Mr. Suzuki.
I feel good.
I want you to sleep here.
Your waist is moving.
I feel good.
It hurts.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It hurts.
It hurts a little.
Does it feel good?
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's hard.
Please touch my butt a lot.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Please look at me.
It hurts.
Please touch my butt a lot.
It feels good.
Please look at me.
It hurts.
It's okay.
I want to do more.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Please look at me.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Please look at me.
It hurts.
It feels good.
My legs are sweating.
It hurts.
Can I do it one more time?
One more time?
I need to take a break.
I'm not ready yet.
Can I do it one more time?
I think I can do it.
One more time.
I want to do it harder.
Excuse me.
It's okay.
I'm busy with work.
I can't clean up.
That's right.
It's a mess.
I don't know what to do.
It's okay.
Excuse me.
My air conditioner is broken.
I can't use the air conditioner.
Is it okay?
Yes.
It's okay.
It's tough.
It's hot in this season.
It's okay.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I know it's hard.
My room is a mess.
Thank you.
Yes.
If I go to your room while you're cleaning up, I'll be in the way.
I'm going out.
Please let me clean up in the meantime.
Okay.
I'll be back in about an hour.
I'm going out.
Okay.
It's okay.
If you're alone, you can wake up early.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Men are like this.
What should I do?
I have to clean up.
But...
It's okay.
Is it broken?
What are you doing?
That's mine.
What are you looking at?
I'm listening.
I'm sorry.
I'm not sorry.
I'm sorry for being close.
I'm sorry for not making a sound.
I'm sorry.
Please stop.
AHHHH
I thought I-I-I thought
I thought I f-f-f-f-for the time being
Can I just clean up?
Can I go home now?
what?
hey hey
ah, cle-
What's wrong?
What did you do?
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
What?
What's this?
I'm so excited.
I can't stop my butt.
I'm sorry.
It's like a hot air balloon.
I'm so excited.
I can't stop my butt.
Wait a minute.
Don't say that.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
​I'm...
​It hurts.
Oh
Yeah
Hmm
Um
Wait a moment, wait a moment.
Just a sec.
That's enough for now.
Come here!
Wow!
I'm sorry.
Damn it.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
What are you taking off?
Surarararararararare
Raro
Arrare
Rar flat
They
Ke
Oh my.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Ahhhhiness
I don't want water!
Ahh
I don't want to...
It's okay.
Hang in there.
Sit on my lap.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm still sweating.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
What time is it today?
I want to take a break.
I don't want to leave the company.
Good morning.
Trisomy
Impersonating
Why was she so speedy?
Was it the person upstairs?
Oh she was quite gorgeous
It's hot. It's getting late.
What?
Wait a minute.
Are you okay?
Huh?
This is the guy.
I met him this morning.
He's from the upper floor.
What are you doing here?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
What?
Why are you wearing a T-shirt
with a round butt?
Why are you wearing a T-shirt with a round butt?
What?
You're so wet.
You're sweating.
No one sweats like this.
What?
You're cold.
Excuse me.
Are you okay?
The floor is wrong.
It's probably upstairs. This is my house.
It's dangerous to sleep here.
Why didn't you ask for my number?
Your number?
I don't know what you mean.
I wanted you to ask for my number.
Are you okay?
I'm lying down.
I told you to be brave.
It's dangerous.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
Wake up.
Are you okay?
It's upstairs.
I drank a lot of alcohol that I don't usually drink.
I drank a lot, but no one asked for my number.
I don't know what you mean.
Are you serious?
Why didn't you ask for my number?
I don't know what you mean.
I'll take you upstairs.
Let's go upstairs.
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you ask for my number?
I don't know what you mean.
I'm sorry.
I brought you a tea bag.
A tea bag?
Look at this.
You know what this is, right?
Touch it.
Okay.
Why are you crying?
This is sweat.
It's dripping.
Touch it.
Okay.
Give me a kiss.
What should I do?
My butt is very sensitive.
I want you to touch my butt.
Are you okay with this sweat?
I sweat a lot when it's hot.
Your butt?
I'm sorry.
I'm getting hot.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Are you sleepy?
No, I'm not.
I'm sorry.
I sweat a lot when it's hot.
Look at me.
Touch me.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Look at me.
It's uncomfortable.
My butt doesn't sweat at all.
I'm sorry.
Don't sweat.
It's uncomfortable.
I'm sorry.
I want to lick your butt.
Do you want to lick my butt?
Yes.
All of it?
I don't like this part.
Wait a minute.
It's uncomfortable.
My neck is stiff.
Wait a minute.
It's comfortable.
It's uncomfortable.
I don't like this part.
Wait a minute.
It hurts.
Get up.
It's uncomfortable.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
Wait a minute.
Is it uncomfortable?
It's uncomfortable.
It's very good.
It's good.
What's wrong?
I don't want you to see me.
I don't want you to see the camera.
I'm sorry.
It's uncomfortable.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
It's uncomfortable.
It hurts.
Are you okay?
From behind.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Are you sure?
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
It's uncomfortable.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
It's uncomfortable.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I'm in trouble.
I can't help it.
It feels good.
I'm in trouble.
I can't help it.
It feels good.
Hold on.
Okay.
Get up from the back.
I want to take a bath.
Take a bath.
It feels good.
I can't help it.
Can I take a bath?
Yes, you can.
Okay.
I'll take a bath on you.
Ouch!
I feel so good.
Did you take a bath a lot?
Yes, I did.
It felt good.
I felt good, too.
I can't help it.
Excuse me.
Wait a minute.
It's open.
What should I do?
Make a triangle with the point between Q and P.
It's getting smaller, isn't it?
If you make one, it will come out soon.
Okay.
Yes.
That's right.
How did you know?
You can see it right away, can't you?
Yes, it was easy to see.
Really?
That's good.
You can do the next one, too.
Because it's the same.
Okay.
Yes.
How is it?
Oh, it's right.
It's perfect.
I'm glad.
It's great.
You're good at teaching and it's easy to understand.
Really?
That's good.
After all, I'm glad that I asked a teacher for a home class, not a cram school.
Don't you go to a cram school anymore?
I don't go to a cram school.
I think it didn't suit my personality.
By the way, you talked about it before.
After all, if you can't ask a question, you can't move on.
And I'm not good at meeting people.
Oh, I see.
I think I can concentrate in my room.
Well, it's hard to go to a cram school in such a hot season.
It's hard.
I'm not good at hot weather.
Oh, I see.
It's the same.
I don't like hot weather.
Do you want to continue?
Yes.
It's right.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Don't mention it.
You're serious and excellent, so it's worth teaching you.
Thank you.
Wow.
Excuse me.
Can I go to the bathroom?
Oh, the bathroom?
Go ahead.
Excuse me.
Let's take a break.
Okay.
By the way, it's very cold.
It's 18 degrees.
It's cold.
I'll turn on the air conditioner.
I'll turn it off.
Mai, you always turn on the air conditioner too much.
I'll catch a cold.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, it's okay.
Well, next...
Oh, it's dark.
It's getting cold.
I turned off the air conditioner.
I don't think I'll be sick if I leave it on all the time.
I think so, too.
Well, let's try a new test.
I'm sure you'll get a test.
Okay.
This is a textbook.
What should I do?
It's the first test.
I'll solve the problem around here.
Here.
Okay.
I'll try it.
I'm sure you'll get a test.
It's close, isn't it?
Yes.
I think it's better to use this formula here.
There's a graph here.
I'll draw a graph here and put the x-axis and the y-axis together.
Okay.
Isn't it hot in this room?
No, it's just right.
Is it hot?
No.
I turned on the air conditioner until a while ago, so it's just right.
I'm glad.
You haven't progressed at all.
I'm sorry.
You can take your time.
Let me know if you have any questions.
Okay.
I'll solve the problem around here.
I think it's better to get used to it.
I want you to solve this problem today.
There's a good problem here.
Do you want to solve this problem next?
Are you okay?
Yes.
You haven't progressed at all.
I'm okay.
You haven't progressed at all, but it's difficult.
Are you okay?
Are you sick?
Yes.
What's wrong with you?
You don't look well.
I'm sick.
You don't look okay.
I went to the bathroom earlier, but if you're really sick, let's take a break.
Let's take a break.
Let's calm down.
You're sick, aren't you?
I'm okay.
You don't look okay.
You don't look well.
I'm okay.
Let's take a break.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
Wait a minute.
Let go of me.
What's wrong with you?
When I'm hot, I sweat a lot on my butt.
It's hot.
I'm sweating a lot.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I was holding back my cough.
My butt is wet.
I'm sorry.
I need you to touch me.
Touch me.
Can I touch you?
What are you doing?
You're sweating a lot.
Are you hot?
What is it?
Is it here?
It's definitely not good.
Don't be nervous.
How are you?
It's hot.
Is it here?
It hurts.
Are you okay?
Doctor.
What?
Please.
Doctor.
Let me go.
Calm down.
What's wrong?
Let me go.
Doctor.
Here, too.
Here, too?
Please.
You're not sweating, are you?
It's hot.
Are you really okay?
You're okay, right?
Please help me.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
Why did you make such a loud voice?
It's hot.
It's really hot.
Doctor.
It's hot.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
This is...
Doctor.
What are you doing?
It's hot.
Doctor.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
Doctor.
Please.
It's hot.
Doctor.
Save me.
Don't be angry.
Forgive me.
It's hot.
Doctor.
I'll put a bag on you.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I'm hot.
I'll put a bag on you.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Thank you for your hard work.
What happened to you?
You're on a business trip.
Yes.
What did you do on your day off?
I worked.
You're still serious.
Yes.
I'm on a business trip again.
I see.
How was your business trip?
As usual.
As usual?
I heard it was an important business trip.
Did you have a good time?
Yes.
I'm glad.
You went on a business trip the other day, didn't you?
Yes.
It must have been hard for you.
I got used to it.
You're serious.
You're great.
It's hot today.
Yes.
It's hot.
I'm sweating just by walking.
You're right.
It's hot.
I wish it was cold at night.
It's hot during the day and night.
You're right.
It's hot.
Well...
Yes?
Is the air conditioner out of order?
No.
It's broken.
What?
I don't know because I was on a business trip.
It's broken.
It's going to be a weekend.
It's going to be a hot weekend.
No one has a job.
You don't sweat at all.
No.
I wonder if you sweat.
I sweat.
You sweat a lot while walking.
Hey.
I'm fine.
I'm going home.
What?
Wait, wait, wait.
Can you check this for me?
What is it?
I have to give this to the manager.
I want you to look at it.
Here you go.
I think it's fine.
What? Did you close your eyes?
Look at it again.
I don't want the manager to get mad at me.
I remember you did something similar to this before.
Yes.
So I thought it would be reassuring if you looked at it.
Please check it.
I think you'll be able to put it together well.
I want you to look at the details.
What do you think?
What is it?
YOSHIOKA.
Are you all right?
What?
I'm fine.
You're panting.
What?
I'm tired because I have to go back to work.
I'm fine.
No.
No, you're not fine.
You're panting.
Do you want to take medicine?
No.
I'm fine.
What's wrong with you?
You're panting more than before.
I'm fine.
Is it because of the weather?
What should I do?
YOSHIOKA.
Are you all right?
What's wrong with you?
It's hot.
YOSHIOKA.
Are you all right?
Wait a minute.
Why are you so wet?
It's hot.
You're wet.
If it's hot, I'll sweat on my butt.
Your face is sweating.
Why are you so wet?
YOSHIOKA.
No.
What's wrong with you?
YOSHIOKA.
Take off my clothes.
What?
Take off your clothes?
That's not good.
Are you all right?
YOSHIOKA.
You're sweating a lot.
Are you all right?
YOSHIOKA.
What's wrong with you?
It's hot.
Wait a minute.
Are you all right?
YOSHIOKA.
Wait a minute.
Are you all right?
YOSHIOKA.
I can't take it anymore.
It's hot.
Look at YOSHIOKA.
YOSHIOKA.
It's hot.
What's wrong with you?
YOSHIOKA.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm going to vomit.
It's hot.
YOSHIOKA.
What's wrong with you?
It's hot.
YOSHIOKA.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
It's hot.
My butt...
If you're sweating, please don't say a word.
I got it.
Please don't say a word.
I won't.