OTSURI YOKA DESHO Daihatsu Family Farm
Fuel break
Turn off the engine and release the activates block
Let's change seats.
Put the seat down for the next person.
Did you check the back seat?
Check the back seat.
I didn't check it.
Did you check the back seat?
Put the seat down for the next person.
I want to go to the bathroom.
Did you check the back seat?
I'm nervous.
It's tough, isn't it?
Did you get used to it?
I haven't gotten used to it yet.
It's boring, isn't it?
That's right.
I haven't played.
It's boring, isn't it?
Matching app?
I haven't met yet.
A matching app.
There are such children.
I'll try to contact them.
I can't get back in touch.
I don't know what the person is doing.
I've had enough of it today.
I have a lecture tomorrow, too.
Really?
Good morning.
Please sit around here.
This is a very good room.
I think so, too.
I think this is a cheap room.
My room is very ordinary.
What do you mean?
I have a bed.
That's not fair.
It's good to have a positive attitude.
I'm not praising you.
I bought something, so would you like to drink it?
Let's drink it.
Apple, lemon, and lemon.
I'll have a lemon.
I'll have two lemons.
Which one do you want?
I think both are good.
Thank you.
Can you open it?
Let's have a toast.
Cheers!
It's good.
It's good, isn't it?
It's good to drink like this.
I think so, too.
We had a lot of free time.
We do that, don't we?
Do you use many apps?
Which app?
I used to use it in my hometown.
But I had too much free time.
I think so, too.
That's why I used it.
Your name is Yoshida, right?
Yes, I'm Yoshida.
I think you used to use it, too.
I used to use that app a long time ago.
But I haven't got any reply at all.
Really?
It was the first time I got a reply.
That's crazy, isn't it?
I don't know what it is.
Really?
I was surprised because I got a reply right after I sent it.
I was surprised.
Were there too few people who replied?
I think so.
But there were some cute girls.
Really?
That's good.
There were no girls who replied.
You mean the guys?
Yes.
There were a lot of guys who worked around here.
But I didn't get a reply at all.
There are a lot of rice fields around here.
I think so.
On the other hand, it was rare in the app.
So you were lucky to get a reply.
Yes.
In fact, I think people around the same age will come to the training camp.
I think so.
I thought so.
Was there anyone who thought it was good?
Yes.
Did you have a girlfriend?
You shouldn't do that.
I think so.
Then you have no choice but to use the app.
Did you use the app because of that?
Yes.
Did you meet a lot of people using the app?
In your hometown?
Yes.
If there were good people.
Good people?
Yes.
I don't know the criteria of good people.
I think they are good people.
I believe in intuition.
Intuition?
I see.
I don't know.
We haven't matched yet.
We haven't matched yet, so I want you to tell me how to match.
I don't know.
The training camp will be over in a week.
There was nothing around here.
I searched for it at first.
Really?
There was nothing around here, so I thought it was no good.
I think so.
Then.
I have to do it.
I think so.
I see.
Did you decide to do it?
I was too free.
I didn't expect to meet people like this.
By the way, today's training camp was the same.
Training camp?
We had the same training camp.
Wait.
I was surprised when I met you.
You're right.
Did you know it right away?
I knew it right away.
We have the same training camp.
You don't remember it at all.
I was too focused on the training camp.
I was too angry today.
He is scary.
He was strict.
I was angry.
I was worried if he would get angry.
I should have done it with him.
I'm sorry.
I'm worried if I can graduate.
You can do it.
I think so.
He is strict.
I might meet him again.
I'll study with him.
Are you going to study?
I have to study.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
Wait a minute.
More than that.
More than that?
Don't you have sex?
Sex?
You were using a sex app, right?
I was using it.
It was before you had sex.
So, it was not good.
Is that so?
Yes.
I didn't mean it.
Can I?
You had sex with me.
You had sex.
You came to my room.
You drank alcohol.
So, you have to do it.
I think so.
Isn't it?
I didn't know it.
Don't you want to do it?
Yes.
You have nothing to do around here.
You have to do it.
Drink it.
Yes.
Do it.
Come on.
It's very big.
Can I do it?
Yes.
Drink it.
You kissed me sexually.
It's very soft.
Thank you.
How many cups are there?
Seven.
Seven cups?
Yes.
It's very soft.
It's J cup.
Do you like boobs?
I like boobs, too.
Boobs, too?
Do you like boobs?
How to touch it.
I can't touch it with one hand.
How about this?
It's good.
It's very beautiful.
It's very hard.
Don't say that.
It's good, isn't it?
Yes.
Oh, my gosh.
It's very hard.
It's very hard, isn't it?
Behind the hip.
Wow.
Do you want to see it?
What?
What is this?
It's a tea bag.
Do you usually wear this?
Yes, I do.
It's very soft.
It's very cute, isn't it?
It's cute.
It's very erotic.
Is it cute?
The butt is very beautiful.
Thank you.
It's very smooth.
I can't stand it.
Look at this.
I'm eating a lot.
You're good at touching.
It's very soft.
Is it soft?
Yes.
I can't stand it.
Can I touch you a little more?
What?
What are you looking at?
I thought you didn't care at all.
Yes.
I'll touch you all over here.
It's very beautiful.
It's very pink.
It feels good.
I can't stand it.
I'm sorry.
I'm so excited.
I'll touch you a little more.
I'll take this off, too.
You're very energetic.
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
It's very painful.
It looks painful.
Can I take this off?
Show me.
It's very good.
You're energetic.
But...
But you showed me such an erotic figure.
Do you want me to do that?
I thought you had a good face.
What kind of face is that?
You have a good face.
I'm glad.
It feels good.
It feels very good.
It's very good.
Does it feel good?
I want you to do more.
No.
It's very good.
Does it feel good?
I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
Can you sit here?
Okay.
Raise your head.
Like this?
Yes.
You are touching me.
It feels good.
You are the best.
Do you like me?
It's very good.
No, it's not.
Do you usually do this?
I don't know.
Does it relax you?
I've never done this.
Really?
It's amazing.
What is it?
I want to lick you.
You should sleep.
It's hot.
I want to lick you.
It feels good.
I feel good, too.
Really?
I want to lick you.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'll do it.
Wake up.
I knew it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Wait a minute.
It feels good.
I'm glad we matched.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's been a while.
Move more.
More?
More.
Move more.
It feels good.
Wait a minute.
It's really deep.
Move more.
It's dangerous.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I like this feeling.
Don't stop me.
It feels good.
It's dangerous.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's dangerous.
Do you want to do it again?
I want to do it again.
Do you want to start from the back?
Yes.
It's good.
Slowly.
It feels good.
It's dangerous.
Do as you like.
Yes.
It's dangerous.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's dangerous.
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
It hurts.
It feels so good.
It's moving.
It's over there.
Oh, no.
I'll do it.
It feels so good.
Oh, no.
Is my neck okay?
It feels so good.
Oh, no.
It's moving.
It feels so good.
It's so hot.
You're trembling.
Did you fall asleep?
I couldn't stand it anymore.
You can still do it, right?
You can do it, right?
It feels so good.
You can still do it, right?
Oh, no.
Come here.
Come closer.
Closer.
It feels so good.
Oh, no.
I can't do it.
Ai-chan, Ai-chan.
It feels good.
Come here.
I can't do it.
It's warm.
Did you poop a lot?
You pooped a lot.
Do you want to do it again?
Yes.
It feels good.
Do you want to do it again?
I don't know.
You're matching.
I think so.
You said you've never done it before.
I've never done it.
You did it.
That's good.
I was surprised.
I thought I'd seen you somewhere.
Why are you there?
Sit down.
I see.
I've seen him before.
Really?
He looks like an adult.
I haven't talked to him.
I don't know who he is.
He looks like an adult.
Thank you.
We're going to the roadside school today.
Yes.
We're going to the highway school today.
Be careful.
Start the engine.
Hello.
Check your ID card.
Yes.
How do you feel?
Be careful.
I was surprised.
I thought I'd seen you somewhere.
I didn't know we were in the same school.
I was surprised.
It's a coincidence.
Yes.
You were good at driving.
Really?
I didn't know that.
I'm glad.
I didn't know anyone.
I was relieved.
Really?
I was nervous.
It's true.
I didn't know there was such a coincidence.
I didn't know anyone.
That's right.
Do you use that app often?
No.
In this school, everyone is older than me.
So, there aren't many people I can talk to.
I'm a college student, so I don't go out much.
So, I thought it would be nice to use that app.
I thought so.
I thought it would be nice to use that app.
I was surprised.
By the way, you are Mari, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Did you remember me?
Can I call you Mari?
Of course.
Is your name Yoshida?
Yes, I'm Yoshida.
I'm nervous.
Why?
I'm nervous when you call my name.
You are beautiful and sexy.
Thank you.
How old are you?
Are you asking me?
I'm sorry.
Really?
I thought you were older than me.
I'm about 23 years old.
No way.
I'm 28 years old.
28 years old.
I see.
You are mature and sexy.
You are older than a college student.
I thought so.
You are beautiful.
You are good at talking.
I'm serious.
How old are you?
I'm 19 years old.
19 years old?
You are young.
Aren't you young?
You got a driver's license when you were 18, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
That's great.
Why did you get a driver's license?
Me?
I live in a rural area.
If I don't drive, it's inconvenient for me to go somewhere.
I thought I had to get a driver's license soon.
I see.
I thought it would be better to get a driver's license at a camp.
I can get a driver's license in a few days.
I see.
I thought it would be nice to get a driver's license with everyone.
I thought it would be fun.
I think I was right.
That's good.
I don't have to do anything.
I don't have to do anything except for training.
I agree.
I don't have to do anything.
What should I do?
I have a day off tomorrow.
I was wondering what I should do.
I see. You have a day off tomorrow.
Yes.
I have a day off, too.
Do you have a day off, too?
Yes, I have a day off tomorrow.
I see.
I was wondering what I should do.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to study.
Really?
You are serious.
I was worried if I could get a driver's license.
That's great.
What should I do?
You don't have to do anything, do you?
I don't have to do anything.
Then...
I have a suggestion.
Do you want to have sex?
Sex?
You said you had a day off tomorrow.
I see.
You have a day off, don't you?
You can do it until the morning.
Until the morning?
Yes.
But...
Is it okay?
I just had sex.
Don't you want to have sex?
I want to have sex.
Do you want to have sex?
Okay.
Get up.
Is it really okay?
You don't have to do anything.
You don't have to do anything, do you?
Don't you want to have sex?
I don't want to have sex.
Then...
You don't have to do anything.
Your lips are very soft.
Can I kiss you more?
Okay.
Your lips are very soft.
Can I touch your lips?
Is it okay?
It's okay.
Oh, I see.
Your lips are very soft.
Do you like boobs?
I like boobs very much.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed to see you like that.
Your lips are very soft.
I'm sweating.
I'm excited.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
It's cold.
It feels good.
It's difficult.
I can't stand it.
It's cold.
It feels good.
I'll give you a massage.
Are you okay?
Do you want me to do it?
Does it feel good?
It's dirty.
Are you excited?
It's sensitive here.
Does it feel good?
You're very energetic.
I'll feed you a lot in return.
It's cold.
It's very hard.
You're energetic because you're young.
I'll give you a massage.
Does it feel good?
It's very soft.
It's very hard.
I'll rub you more.
Does it feel good?
It's very soft.
It's hot.
Do you like my boobs?
What about the butt?
I'll massage your butt.
Does it feel good?
It's very hard.
I'll massage you more.
I'll put this on you.
You're very good at it.
You brought it here?
I brought it here.
I'll put this on you.
Thank you.
Did you feel good?
I'll start with this.
You can still do it, right?
I'll start.
I'll put this on you.
It feels good.
Thank you.
Did you feel good?
It's true.
I'll put this on you.
You still can do it.
It feels good.
I'll put this on you.
It's a waste.
It's sweet.
You still can do it.
It feels good.
I'll put this in from behind.
You can do it many times.
Let me do it.
I'll put this in from behind.
It's hot.
I'll help you.
Don't do that.
It's hot.
It's still hot, isn't it?
Let's see how hot it is.
Give me more.
It's hot.
It feels so good.
Give me more.
It's hot.
It feels so good.
Are you out of breath?
I'm fine.
How many times have you done this?
I want to do it more.
I'm out of gum.
I'll do it for you.
I don't have any more.
Do you want more?
No, I'm fine.
It's hot.
Try it.
It feels so good.
It's hot.
Are you out of breath?
I'm sorry.
You're sweating a lot.
It feels so good.
Are you sleepy?
I'll get on you.
It's hot.
It feels so good.
I'll get on you.
Let me go.
You're sweating a lot.
I can't stop sweating.
It feels so good.
I'll get on you.
I can't get on you.
I still have a long way to go.
It feels so good.
It hurts.
I still have a long way to go.
What's wrong?
It's morning.
You can still do it.
It feels so good.
I'll get on you.
There's something on your face.
What are you looking at?
You're wearing matching clothes again.
What kind of girl is she?
She looks cute.
Are you going to see her again?
I'm going to see her.
You can't.
I'll get on you.
It feels so good.
The next one is...
The position of the stop line is...
Where there is a stop line, say the stop line straight line.
Say the stop line straight line.
How was this?
This is the correct answer.
Is this the correct answer?
The stop line is straight.
Not at the stop line, but just before it.
That's right.
It's quite confusing.
There's a lot of tricks.
That's all there is.
That's right.
What was this?
The formula is here.
The dotted line is the stop line.
The diagonal line is the stop line.
Was it difficult?
There are a lot of tricks, but...
If you solve the problem, you'll get a similar problem.
You're still a college student, so you're studying.
Is that so?
I haven't studied like this in a long time.
It's hard to study again.
That may be the case.
Studying all the time.
But if you can do it now, you'll definitely pass.
Is it okay?
It's totally okay.
I was in trouble because I couldn't study at all.
I'm glad I was able to match with someone who taught me like Yoshida.
That's right.
I thought we were definitely in the same training camp.
I was surprised, too.
I was surprised, but I'm glad.
I wanted you to teach me how to study.
I didn't know there was such an app.
It's convenient.
If you say so, your neighbors will meet you.
That's right.
That's what happens around here.
I was thinking about the dating app for men and women.
I see.
I was prejudiced.
I'm sorry.
That's right.
I want to have a healthy relationship.
I wanted you to teach me how to study.
I'm sorry it's not like that.
No, no, no.
It's fun to talk like this.
That's good.
I'm having fun, too.
I'm glad I had a good time studying.
I'm glad I got a lot of revenge.
That's good.
What was this?
Which one?
This one.
Which one is this?
I can't imagine.
Is this it?
What is this?
This is...
It's written here.
It's a pass.
I was wondering if a bicycle was okay.
This is for vehicles.
A normal bicycle is fine.
I think so, too.
Let's move on to the next question.
Which one was this?
I don't know.
A little more.
I'm sure you've heard of it.
I think this is the correct answer.
I see.
Do you know which one it is?
Did you see it?
This is it.
I'm sorry.
I've been thinking about a lot of things.
This was the correct answer, wasn't it?
That's right.
Now that we're done with this page,
shall we take a break?
Yes, let's take a break.
Do you want some sweets?
I think it's better to have some sweets.
Thank you very much.
Let's have some sweets.
Sweets are good when you're tired.
That's right.
Let's have some sweets.
It's good, isn't it?
This is good.
I'm glad I got the right answer.
It's good.
If you keep studying, you'll get tired.
You'll get tired.
By the way, you've already had an audition, haven't you?
I did, but it was difficult.
It's scary to be asked to drive all of a sudden, isn't it?
That's right.
I made it manual, so I should have made it automatic.
Is that so?
That's right.
But it's amazing.
It's rare for women.
I don't seem to be around much these days.
I'm going to save money and drive a sports car.
That's cool.
Sports cars are expensive, aren't they?
What do you do for a living?
I'm a nurse.
I see.
That's nice.
I think so.
I have the image that you seem to be busy.
But if you have time...
I have a part-time job, so I have a hard time.
But I finally got a job and came here to get a license.
I see.
But I can't get used to it because I'm acting at all.
That's right.
There are various classes.
It's difficult.
I'm used to being automatic now.
I don't choose automatic anymore.
That's right.
Is that normal?
I don't know.
But sports cars are cool, aren't they?
That's right.
I think so, too.
I'm jealous.
I want to get a manual car, too.
Really?
I don't have enough money to buy a sports car.
That's right.
You're still a student.
I want to get a job in the future.
It's after you work.
That's right.
You look like an adult woman.
When I talk to you, you look like an adult woman.
I don't talk to college boys like this, so I get nervous when I'm conscious of them.
That's right.
I'm getting hot.
I'm a little nervous.
Can I take off my top?
It's hot, isn't it?
That's right.
Can I learn again?
Let's study.
The next question is...
When you change lanes, make sure the car in front of you is coming from the back.
That's right.
When the car behind you is trying to overtake your car, don't start overtaking your car.
That's right, too.
There are so many correct answers.
I don't know the correct answer.
The next question is...
Thank you.
Can I ask you again if I don't know the correct answer?
Of course.
Thank you for today.
See you.
Can I eat this?
Is that okay?
Yes.
See you.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
The next day.
Is Yoshida here?
Yes.
Can I come in?
Of course.
Excuse me.
Thank you for the other day.
Not at all.
I came here because I wanted you to teach me how to study.
Is that okay?
Do you wear glasses today?
I'm wearing contact lenses today.
I see.
You noticed that, didn't you?
I noticed that right away.
Really?
I like glasses, too.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'll read the rest of the questions.
I studied a lot by myself.
I see.
Well...
There are a lot of hooks in this picture.
I see.
It's strange, isn't it?
Is this around here?
Yes.
There are a lot of hooks.
There are a lot of hooks around here.
By the way, when are you going to graduate?
I'm about to graduate.
After I get my diploma.
Really?
Yes, it's over.
I'm going to miss you even though I've known you for a long time.
I know.
I've known you for a long time.
I'm sad that you've got along with me.
I'm glad to hear that.
But I still have time.
I see.
I'll teach you how to study.
Really? Thank you.
But I managed to come this far without returning the stamps because you taught me.
I see.
You're amazing.
Really?
I'll study hard today, too.
There is a traffic light.
After the traffic light passes, turn right.
What are you looking at?
Is it a traffic light?
What is it?
It's a traffic light.
What?
Did I say something?
It's a traffic light, isn't it?
After the traffic light passes, turn right.
I'm checking the safety in front of me to see if I'm overtaking or not.
Wait a minute.
Where were you looking at?
Were you looking at me?
I'm sorry.
I wasn't looking at you.
Next, please.
You were looking at me, weren't you?
Are you curious about me?
Is there something wrong with me?
No, it's not that.
Sakura-san, this is a no-bra.
Did you notice that?
I've been looking at you for a long time.
What?
Is it transparent?
It's transparent.
Are you curious about me?
I'm sorry.
I was looking at you.
Is it hard for you to study?
No, it's not that.
I was just curious about you.
I don't look at you anymore.
Next, please.
This is the third question.
The third question is over.
I'm going to ask you a question.
I'm driving at 60 km per hour.
What should I be careful about when I meet you?
Hmm.
Hey.
No, it's not that.
This is the first question.
Hey.
Yes.
I don't want to touch you because you look at me so much.
No, it's not that.
That's right.
Is it okay just to look at me?
No, it's not that.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
When we first met, you wanted to do something like this.
What?
You can't look for someone to study with on the app.
Right?
That's right.
To be honest, this app has an answer, so you can do it by yourself.
Is it okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm counting on you.
I'm sorry.
Is it okay to look at me from above?
No, it's not that.
Look at me directly.
I'm sorry.
It's very thin.
It's standing like this.
Do you like it here?
Don't make me say embarrassing things.
It's very hard.
I'm sorry.
Do you like me?
I like you.
I'm sorry.
It's very hard.
It's hard to be a college student.
I'm sorry.
It's very hard.
It's getting harder.
I don't like it.
I'm sorry.
It's very hard.
My butt is the best.
Do you like my butt?
I like your butt, too.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's very hard.
I'm embarrassed to look at you.
Don't look at me like that.
It's very hard.
I'm sorry.
Don't look at me like that.
It's very hard.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's very hard.
I can't look at you anymore.
I lost my rubber band.
What do you mean you lost it?
Is that so?
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
Do you want me to put it in your mouth?
It's not good for your teeth.
That's right.
But you look so healthy.
You can put it in your mouth.
You're very healthy.
It's very hard.
Does it feel good?
Do you like it?
It's very hard.
Does it feel good?
It's a waste not to put it in your mouth.
It's very hard.
I think it's okay.
I want to put it in your mouth.
But I can't stand it.
Put it in your mouth.
Come on.
Give it to me.
It's very hard.
Does it feel good?
Can I lick here?
Touch my mouth.
Does it feel good?
That's right.
Don't touch me.
It feels good.
It feels very good.
oh shit
I can't use it
More.
Come here.
Give me.
I'll pull you.
More.
Give me more.
I'm so nervous!
What should I do?
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm so nervous!
Ouch!
I got a lot of it.
It's good.
You can still do it, right?
I want to do it again.
It's still hard.
Do it again!
I want to do it again, please!
I want to do it again!
Ouch!
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It felt good.
It's hot.
I'm glad I got a lot of it.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
You can still do it, right?
I'm sorry.
I feel like it's not good.
Why?
Concentrate.
You're mean.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
You can still do it, right?
I bought this for you.
Let's drink it together.
May I?
Yes.
Okay.
Did you put it in?
Can I drink it with wine?
Yes.
Do you want to drink it?
I'll have a little more.
Thank you.
Okay.
Cheers.
I didn't expect it.
I didn't expect to match with you.
How many years has it been?
I didn't go to the reunion.
It's been about two years since I graduated from high school.
Why didn't you come?
I didn't have anyone to talk to at the reunion.
I couldn't help it.
I see.
You were bullied a long time ago, weren't you?
I wasn't bullied.
I don't remember much.
You didn't have many friends, did you?
I don't think so.
I didn't have many friends.
I see.
You don't seem to have changed much.
Do you think so?
I think so.
You were in the center of the youkai group.
I didn't expect you to talk to me like I did.
You were playing match with other youkai.
But you didn't play with anyone.
You just happened to be there.
I see.
Why do you know that?
I didn't play with anyone.
I came to the training camp.
I had nothing to do.
There's nothing around here.
I was bored.
I see.
I thought so.
But I didn't expect to play match with you.
I'm really happy.
You are cute.
You were very popular in the class.
I didn't expect to talk to you like this.
I think it's a good day.
I don't think I can meet you if I were in your hometown.
Do you think so?
It's been a long time since I've met you.
You are still beautiful.
You have a good style.
I've only seen you in your uniform.
You look good in your uniform.
You look cute in your uniform.
Your hair is shiny.
You smell good.
I don't know you.
What?
But you said you wanted to play match with me.
Don't you want to have sex with me?
Why? I don't know you.
What?
I'm kidding.
I don't care.
I don't think so.
Are you misunderstanding something?
No, I'm not.
I've always thought it was like that.
Matching app?
No, I don't know the person who I met on the matching app.
I used to do it, too.
But I can't do it with you.
What should I do?
Do you want to do it with me?
Yes, I want to do it.
Are you sure?
I'm just kidding.
Are you kidding?
What should I do?
Just a little.
You said you couldn't do it with me.
I said no.
I can't do it.
You said you couldn't do it with me.
You're showing me.
You're inviting me.
You can't do it with me.
You're showing me.
I'm embarrassed.
You're embarrassing me.
I don't want to do it.
You can't do it with me.
You're showing me.
I can't do it.
You're embarrassing me.
You can't do it.
What's wrong?
You can't do it here.
I can't do it here.
You said you didn't want to do it.
Do you like boobs?
You have a lot of boobs.
Show me more.
I can't do it.
Do you like boobs?
Boobs are delicious.
You're showing me.
I don't know why I'm crying
I don't know why i'm crying
I don't know why
I don't know why I'm crying
You like it, right?
Let me take a look at you
That's good
Wait
Mhm
Peace out
Okay.
Good boy.
Please stick out your buttocks more.
It's tight, isn't it?
Your lower back is moving.
Look at me.
It's tight, isn't it?
It feels good.
Do it more.
It's hot.
Can I lick you?
I want you to lick me.
It feels good.
It's hot.
You like it, don't you?
I like it.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
How is it?
Do you want more?
Yes.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
It feels good.
Do you want more?
Yes.
It feels good.
very good
look so cute
yes , very good
Let's go.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah ...
Oh, my goodness ...
Ah ...
I'm gonna cry ...
Please ...
Lucy, that's enough.
Daddy, daddy.
Daddy.
Does it feel good?
Please open your elbow.
Please do more.
Does it feel good?
What?
It's nothing.
You are always doing this.
What is it?
You are matching.
No, no, no.
Stop it.
What is it?
I'm sorry.