The next day
One of them is broken.
I'll get the rice ball.
The rice ball.
It's broken.
I'll have this.
Thank you.
I'll have this, too.
I don't have a boyfriend.
I'm saying this because I've been in a relationship.
I only have three.
You have three.
I'll have a bag, please.
Thank you.
I'll have this.
I don't have a boyfriend.
Excuse me.
Can I use the bathroom?
No.
It's over there.
Thank you.
It's clean.
What?
It's out.
No way.
What?
What are you doing?
Is it sinking?
Thank you.
Do you want to kiss me?
Can I kiss you?
Thank you.
It's broken.
I'm sorry.
She's...
She has a bag.
Really?
I'll deal with it.
Can I use the bathroom?
Yes, you can.
Thank you.
See you.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Don't look at the porn.
Are you standing up?
Are you licking me?
I'm sorry.
Are you standing up?
I'm sleeping now.
Are you licking me?
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
Don't lick me.
Lick me.
What's that?
Haven't you seen her before?
No, I haven't.
She's our regular customer.
She's a big fan of us.
So, she always pees in our house.
I see.
She pees in our house because she wants us to pay attention to her.
I've never seen her before.
She always comes here.
Remember her.
I'll remember her.
She's like that.
I was surprised.
Are you licking me?
Yes.
It's amazing.
What should I do?
I'll buy two.
Thank you.
What should I do?
Don't lick me.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Could you open the product?
It's okay.
I'll pay for it.
Thank you.
What?
Excuse me.
Could you open the product?
Yes.
Could you open the card?
She brought the card.
The card.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Is it okay?
Yes.
Could you open the product?
What?
Excuse me.
Put your finger in it.
My finger?
Yes.
It tickles.
Do you want to touch it directly?
Can I?
What?
All of a sudden?
How are you doing?
Are you getting used to it?
I'm getting used to it a little.
That's good.
Thank you.
Do you have a boyfriend?
What?
All of a sudden?
I've been wondering about it.
I don't have a boyfriend.
You don't?
You look like you have one.
I'm a virgin.
Is that so?
What?
I got dumped yesterday.
Is that so?
I thought it was bad for my boyfriend.
But I didn't care.
I'm not good at rejecting.
I can't refuse.
Are you that kind of person?
Thank you.
It tickles.
You can put as much as you want.
Please put as much as you want.
That's great.
Thank you as always.
You can't put it in your mouth.
Good morning.
This is Moriki News Japan.
The staff seems to be doing well.
Hello.
They are cute.
Look at this.
These days,
Oden is popular.
Look at this.
It makes a sound.
Yes.
I can't eat this.
This card.
I'll have this.
Oden.
Are you ready?
Can you put your tongue out?
Everyone, look at this.
Look.
A cute girl is putting her tongue out.
Look at this.
How is it?
My finger.
It feels good.
Can you lick this?
You are cute.
You are getting better.
Thank you.
Can you put your tongue out?
It's okay.
You are cute.
Boobies.
You are getting better.
I'm surprised.
Now, a cute convenience store clerk is taking off her jeans.
She even took off her pants.
I'm ready.
She seems to be ready.
Here you are.
Excuse me.
Oh, this is good.
I'm ready.
What do you think?
Is it hotter than Oden?
The clerk's Oman is hotter than Oden.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
I feel very good.
Do you feel very good?
Get a hold of yourself.
In the cute clerk's Oman.
I'm ready.
How do you feel?
I'm glad.
I'm glad you come here every day.
No.
Can I deliver this?
No problem.
Yes.
Can I have that cute mouth?
No problem.
It's not normal.
Can I have that mouth?
No problem.
It's painful.
I'm taking a rest.
Touch me.
It's not normal.
Thank you for the meal.
That's all for the delivery.
I change the camera.
Please subscribe to my channel and click the bell mark.
Thank you for the meal.
It's hot.
Please touch me.
I'm going to show you what I'm eating now.
So, please eat a lot.
Okay.
Please eat a lot.
She is good at eating.
Do you do this for training?
If I have a hope, I do this.
It's hot.
How do you like this part?
It's all good.
Thank you.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I can see your beautiful butt from here.
It's good.
I want to see your butt, too.
I want to see your butt on the counter.
Okay.
You can do it slowly.
Can I ride this?
It's hot.
This is a premium release.
You should eat a lot, too.
Okay.
It's hot.
You should drink more.
Drink it.
Drink it well.
It's hot.
Drink more.
It's great.
Please eat it.
It's hot.
Please eat it well.
It's like this, right?
It's normal.
She got a piece.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
It's hot in the bowl.
It's like a register trouble.
It's hot.
It's dirty.
It's Ai-chan's dance.
Everyone wants Zen-Zen.
I don't want to.
I'll take this, too.
It's more fun to play with a horse than to play with oden.
I don't want to.
Are you okay?
I fell into the forest over there.
I don't want to.
Can I kiss you?
Yes, you can.
This is my first time.
Thank you.
Be gentle.
It feels good.
Can I kiss you?
I don't want to.
Look at the camera.
Can you see me kissing you?
I have an idea.
Can you look at me?
Does this feel good?
I can't.
I'll move next.
Does this feel good?
I can't.
Give me more.
There is a cute clerk in the back.
Fukuda?
Yes, I'm Fukuda.
There is a cute clerk in the back.
I can't.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
O
Ah ah ah
A
Ah ah ah ah ah ah nas
Hahaha
m
It hurts!
She's doing it inside the cage.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
It hurts!
I can't do it anymore.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Ah! ah!
Yua Mikami's scheduled pregnancy checkup
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
A, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a.
A, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a,
A, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a,
What is this?
Help me!
It tickles!
I like it there!
I can't get up!
It tickles!
It hurts!
I can't get up!
What did you just do?
It tickles!
What is this?
What did you just do?
It tickles!
There are so many people!
They come here every day.
It tickles!
It hurts!
What did you do?
It tickles!
You don't have to put it in your lower mouth.
Lower mouth?
Now, put it in your lower mouth.
If you get 40 points, you get a finger.
If you get 60 points, you get a finger.
If you get 90 points, you can put everything in your mouth.
We'll be waiting for you.
90 points?
1 point is 1,000 yen, so...
90,000 yen?
Yes.
It costs 90,000 yen?
If you calculate it by day, it's about 3 points a day.
If you do that, it's 3,000 yen a day.
We'll be waiting for you.
Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Bye-bye.
We'll be waiting for you.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Thank you very much.
This is the PR?
Yes.
1,000 yen per person.
Please come.
I see.
Do you want to buy something?
Yes.
Please.
From today?
Yes, from today.
I see.
Thank you very much.
Welcome.
Cute.
It's clean.
Welcome.
Do you have a point card?
A point card?
Yes.
Here you are.
Thank you very much.
Yes.
How much is the bag?
The bag is...
Well, please.
Okay.
It's 980 yen.
980 yen?
Yes.
By the way, how many points do you have now?
I have 88 points.
88 points?
Yes.
Well, you have two points left.
Here you are.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Please take this.
Yes.
The total is...
It's 3,450 yen.
Oh, well...
Does that mean...
Yes.
I have 90 points now.
You can buy it today.
I see.
Yes.
Can I...
Can I buy this?
Yes, of course.
You can buy it for a month from today.
Oh, a month?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
This...
This girl...
Yes, of course.
This...
This clerk, too?
Yes, it's okay.
Well, this...
This person is...
Oh, of course.
This is our clerk.
I see.
Oh...
This...
Of course, this...
Ms. Kimura?
Yes.
Ms. Kimura, too?
I'm here.
Oh, Ms. Kimura.
Yes.
Is she the manager?
Yes, she is.
Oh.
Is she the manager?
Of course.
Oh.
What should I do?
Well...
You can do whatever you want.
Oh.
Well...
Oh...
You can do whatever you want.
Well...
Is this okay?
Of course.
Oh.
Well...
Oh...
Yes?
Well...
Oh.
Oh...
Ah...
Well...
Oh...
Sorry for the wait.
That's OK.
I'll leave you alone...
Let me see your nose.
This is good, too.
Of course.
As you like.
Ouch!
Excuse me.
Yes?
Are you back?
Where are my shoes?
They are over there.
Thank you.
Here you are.
Excuse me.
Ouch!
This way, please.
Yes.
Ouch!
Do you want some tea?
Here you are.
Thank you.
May I help you?
Excuse me.
Ouch!
May I take your shoes off?
Yes.
Of course.
Ouch!
Thank you.
I see.
Did you find your favorite manko?
I'll start with the ceiling.
How is it?
It's good.
I'll start with the ceiling.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Could you look behind you?
I see.
Kimura-san, Seichi-san, Fukuda-san, Takaeda-san, and Kuroda-san.
I learned how to use my butt.
I'm sorry.
I'm looking this way.
Could you shuffle?
Did you do it?
I did it.
I'll touch your butt.
Takaeda-san.
Kimura-san.
Kuroda-san.
Seichi-san.
Fukuda-san.
Could you look this way?
That's correct.
I'm sorry.
Which one was your favorite?
What are you going to do?
I may not be able to decide unless I try it.
Do you want to try it?
I'm sorry.
Before I try it, could you touch my butt?
Could you shuffle?
Kimura-san.
Kuroda-san.
Fukuda-san.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Could you stick out your tongue?
Which one should I choose?
It's up to God.
Shiki-san.
Can I stick out my tongue?
Of course.
Please enjoy.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Where are you going?
Just go and rest.
...
Fukuda-san, you still have a long way to go.
Yes, I still have a long way to go.
Please enjoy the lower part of your mouth.
Yes, I will.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Yeah.
Do you want to enjoy the audience?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my chest.
It's okay.
Oh, my God.
Please, relax.
Be comfortable.
Oh, my God.
Ah!
I got a cramp in my back.
Oh...
Eh?
Ah!
Oh!
Is this the condom you bought at home?
Yes, it is.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
It was a little out of stock.
This time, it's special.
No rubber.
Is it okay if I do it?
What?
I'm really sorry.
No, no.
I'm sorry.
Oh, Han-chan.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
I'm fine as it is today.
It's not over at once, is it?
No.
I can do as much as I want, so I can do as many times as I want.
Oh, Han-chan.
Can I?
Yes, of course.
Han-chan.
You look very comfortable.
Oh, it feels good.
Ah.
Hmm.
Okay.
Oh!
Oh.
Uh.
Wow.
Ah.
Eh.
Oh my god!
It's so bad!
Oh, well...
Ah...
Oh!
I can't breathe!
Oh my god!
Oh!
Ah!
Uh
Ah
Uh...
Ah!
Ah, grandma
Um
Can I really take it out like this?
Of course!
Please take it out as much as you can!
Ah!
Um...
Takaya-san...
Excuse me, could you move up a bit?
This way, this way.
Wow!
Ah...
Alright!
Oh, no.
It's coming out again.
It's coming out again?
Here we go.
Ah!
Is it still that strong?
At this shop,
I've been saving it up to give it to you.
Ah!
It's cute.
I can still do it.
Thank you.
Here we go.
I'll put it in.
Thank you.
Ah!
It's still hard.
Ahh!
Ah!
Relax relax Relax
I am going to sleep
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Please feel it more.
Are you going to sleep?
Yes, I'm going to sleep.
Please let me in.
It hurts.
I'm lonely.
I'm still lonely.
Are you lonely?
Yes, I am.
Can I touch you?
Yes, you can.
I'm still lonely.
Can I touch you?
Yes, you can.
It hurts.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Does it hurt?
Yes, it hurts.
It's very hard.
It hurts.
You're risking your life.
You're amazing.
You're the best.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Can I touch you more?
Yes, you can.
It hurts.
Are you okay?
What are you going to do next?
I'm going to do this.
Can I do it?
Yes, you can.
It hurts.
It feels good.
You're risking your life.
You're amazing.
Thank you very much.
I'll be back.
I'll be waiting for you.
I didn't know what was going to happen.
I'm glad.
It's all thanks to you.
Thank you very much.
You were doing your best.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
It was a lot of fun.
Yes, it was.
Look at this.
Do you know what's wrong?
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Really?
There's coffee on the top.
Then there's coffee again.
Then there's a soft drink.
The shelves are full of coffee.
I'm sorry.
If there's so much coffee, you'll run out of stock.
Yes, I'm running out of stock.
You should reduce the amount of coffee.
You should increase the amount of juice.
You don't have much alcohol.
You should increase the amount of alcohol.
Yes, I understand.
I'm sorry.
What's this?
It's too late.
I'm sorry.
I don't have enough employees.
You should dispose of these.
Yes, I understand.
I think you should increase the amount of supplies.
Is it strange?
I understand.
What should I increase?
I think you should increase the amount of snacks.
I think you should increase the amount of coffee.
There's a lot of space.
I think you should put a lot of things.
I understand.
Thank you.
When did you get this magazine?
This is the magazine of last month.
You shouldn't put the magazine of last month here.
I'm sorry.
Change this magazine to a new one.
I understand.
People won't come here.
I'm sorry.
Well...
I think I should take this magazine.
Actually, we're still in the experimental stage.
Yes.
There's a system to increase the sales.
A system to increase the sales?
Yes.
We're still in the experimental stage.
So, we don't have a system to increase the sales.
I think we should try to increase the sales.
I see.
What kind of system is it?
It's a system to increase the sales.
That's what it is.
So, it might be boring at first.
But, I'll help you at that time.
I see.
Can I think about it?
What should I do with you?
Are you really going to do it?
Yes.
I'll do it.
Well...
I've never done it before.
I'll do it.
I'm going to teach you how to do it.
Yes, please.
Put your finger in your upper mouth.
Yes.
You put your finger in your upper mouth.
Can I put my finger in my customer's mouth?
You can put your finger in your customer's mouth.
This is your upper mouth.
So, you put your finger in your upper mouth.
I see.
You can put your finger in your chest.
You can put your finger in your lower mouth.
I see.
Can I put my finger in my chest?
I'm not sure if it's a good idea.
I see.
When a customer comes in, you can put your finger in your chest.
But, you can't put your finger in your chest.
That's not good.
I know.
You can put your finger in your chest.
But, you can't put your finger in your chest.
I see.
When a customer comes in, you can put your finger in your chest.
Can I put my finger in my chest?
I see.
I'm getting anxious.
You can put your finger in your upper mouth.
You can put your finger in your lower mouth.
Do all the staff do that?
Yes, all of them.
I see.
But, I don't think many people come to the store at this time.
So, I'll increase the time a little.
And, I'll do it when there are not enough people.
Do you do that, too?
Yes, I do.
I work with the staff.
I put my finger in my chest when a customer comes in.
Thank you.
But, you're in charge of the store.
So, you have to do your best.
It's your store, isn't it?
You decided to do your best, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
Welcome.
She's so cute.
Is she a clerk?
Her name is Kurose.
Hello.
Look at her panties.
It's white.
Please take off your white panties.
She's so erotic.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Do you want to take off your bag?
It's okay.
Thank you.
The total amount is 1,840 yen.
I'm going to introduce you to a point card.
A point card?
Yes.
It's a point card that you can get for 1,000 yen.
I made a plan to give you as many points as you want.
As many as I want?
Yes.
Depending on the points, you can put your finger in the top of the clerk's mouth.
What?
You can put your finger in the top of the clerk's mouth from 15 points.
15 points?
It's 15,000 yen.
Yes.
It's 500 yen.
Can I put my finger in the top of the clerk's mouth?
Yes.
If you put your finger in the top of the clerk's mouth, you can put your finger, tongue, and penis in the top of the clerk's mouth.
Can I buy things for 90,000 yen?
Yes.
You can buy things for free for a month.
I see.
Can I buy things that I don't need?
No.
You can buy things for 90,000 yen on this card.
You can get points if you use it.
So, you can buy things for free.
If you charge it, you can use it from today.
If I charge 90,000 yen here,
you can use this card.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Can I buy things for 90,000 yen?
Yes.
I charged 90,000 yen.
Thank you very much.
Can I use this card for a month?
Yes.
You can use this card for a month.
It's good, isn't it?
Yes, it's good.
Is this only for this store?
Yes, it's only for this store.
I see.
What is this?
It's white.
Thank you very much.
Can I use this card for a month?
Yes, you can.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Can I use this card for a month?
Yes, you can.
Thank you very much.
Can I use this card for a month?
Yes, you can.
Thank you very much.
No problem at all.
You're welcome.
I m sorry.
No problem.
Thank you very much.
Is this for a person?
This is for a person.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Can I use this card for a month?
Yes, you can.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
The total is 200 yen.
There is a plan to make it as much as possible.
1 point is 1,000 yen.
What are you going to do? Can you make it?
Is that so?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Can I use this?
Yes, you can.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
Is this a bandage?
Yes, it is.
I'll go to the bathroom.
Please use it.
Welcome.
I'm sorry.
Did you get this?
Yes, it's a double.
Thank you very much.
Can I use this bandage?
Yes, you can.
Thank you very much.
It's very beautiful.
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
That's amazing.
You're very erotic.
Can I use this bandage?
Yes, you can.
If you're a staff in the store, you can do whatever you want.
I'm sorry.
You can do it.
I'd like to buy something.
Do you have a condom?
No, I don't.
I'd be happy if you could buy it here.
I'll buy it.
Really?
It's here.
I'll pay you later.
Yes, please.
You have a good butt.
I'll buy a condom.
Thank you very much.
It feels good.
You can do whatever you want.
Yes, I can.
It hurts.
Open your mouth.
It feels good.
Can I use this bandage?
Yes, you can.
I'd like to buy a condom.
Can I use this bandage?
Yes, you can.
It hurts.
Open your mouth.
It feels good.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Kiss me.
Can you sit on my lap?
Yes, I can.
I want to see your butt.
Thank you very much.
Did you hear my explanation?
Yes, I did.
You can put any staff in the store.
Yes, I heard that.
Can I do that?
Yes, you can.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Can I use this bandage?
Yes, you can.
Open your mouth.
I did it.
Can I use this bandage?
Yes, you can.
Thank you.
Can I use this bandage?
Yes, you can.
Excuse me.
Can I use this bandage?
Yes, you can.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to use this bandage, but I'm still shaking.
Excuse me. Can I use this bandage?
Please look at me.
It hurts.
Thank you.
Can I use this bandage?
I'm doing my best.
Thank you.
Why are you doing your best?
I'm doing my best because I have a staff.
Thank you.
I'm going to use this bandage.
Seki-san?
He may be in the back.
Can I call him to the back?
Are you sure?
It's delicious.
Oh!
Excuse me.
What can I do for you?
The staff at the store told me to ask the staff about the bandage.
The bandage?
They told me that you were in the back.
Thank you.
I'll do it right away.
If you register, you can use the bandage right away.
Are you going to do both?
I'll give you 90 points.
I'll give you a double heart bandage.
Thank you.
Oh!
Can you do it?
Yes, I can.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
ah , ah
edge
Ah, ah, ah Ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I can go
Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy
She's coming out
Oh boy, oh boy
Sorry
I don't know what to do.
ah?
Sick
in
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
ah, ah, ah, ah
Aah
valley
Ah ah
Ah, ah, ah
Ah, ah
Ah...
Ah ...
Nnnn..
Nnnn...!
Ahh!
So good...
Ah!
Nnnn
Feels good!
Nnn...
Ah!
Ah...
Ah...!
Ah!
Ah...
Ay!
Oh, my God!
I'm sorry.
Are you married?
I'm in my thirties, but I got married last year.
I'm about to forget him.
I'm sorry.
If you don't mind, please stop crying.
I feel good.
Good night.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
OK.
Can't she get out of your mouth?
If she do, she'll be in here.
I don't know what to do.
You can't lick this, can you?
Where are you licking?
I'm licking your butt.
Can I put this in your mouth?
I have to put gum on this.
I'm a woman.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Moon, MOON~!
Ghost...
Let's go away!
Lost in a picturesque fairy tale
Oh nooooo!
NONONO!!
Moon1
Ghost1
I can't see anything
Ghost2
I don't see anything
Ghost3
I can't see anything
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'll buy you some tea.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
ayane
I did it!
I'm sorry!
Let go of me!
Oh, oops!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Ow!
Ow-ow-ow...
It's that time of the month?
Yeah, I couldn't remember it properly.
We are single friends too, right?
No, it was the month before our wedding.
OMG!
How did you know!?
It's been ages since we started dating.
I'm sorry.
You can come again tomorrow, right?
Can I come again?
You can come again tomorrow.
Really?
I'll come again tomorrow.
I'll be waiting for you.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
You can come again.
Can I?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
I'm so nervous.
I'm going to cry.
It's okay.
Don't cry.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
It's okay.
I decided to do my best.
That's amazing.
I like you.
Please answer me.
Me?
Yes.
I can give you a seat.
But I can't give you a seat.
I'm sorry.
I'll come again tomorrow.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'm sorry.
I can give you a seat.
But I can't give you a seat.