Please wait, teacher.
Professor is yes.
Please go in the head.
I will beat.
Yes please please.
Tell the person who hurt.
Oh yes yes.
You were looking forward to today, right?
Is it yes?
Have you worked for 6 days?
I do not know.
You don’t know if you entered.
Do not ignore it a little.
It feels good there.
What do you usually do? – What do you usually do?
The women’s race?
What is your name? name.
I think you should tell me your name.
It is cold.
Next we will go on foot.
Yes
So, do you have a boyfriend?
Is it not there now?
Your skin is beautiful.
Do you do this massage yourself?
Please stop it.
There is no such message.
No, but it is a bit good.
Stop it, really.
No, it is written.
Look at it, it is not right.
No to
Please give it a little bit.
Oh, I would like to say I too.
The manager said this is not the shop.
No, no, no to
A little, a little, a little, a little.
Oh, this is
A little, a little, a little.
What are you doing.
Which one touched him first?
No, but
Please go up first.
Go up first, right?
No, a little bit of that.
Oh, oh oh oh oh
Oh no longer
Really, really good, this is
Oh is?
Oh, oh oh oh oh
Oh well, oh well
Please be quiet a little.
I will stop.
Oh yes yes
A little
A little, a little
What? what?
be quiet.
Yes
Oh yeah
by M.
A little
Yes
A little with us.
Back to back.
It is in.
is in.
Yes
Is it okay here?
Yes is
A very good atmosphere shop.
Thanks to.
Is there something you don’t like?
It is OK.
It feels great oil.
How old are you?
How many do you see?
You are 24 years old to look so young.
Or is it 24.
Okay, is that enough?
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Massage is good.
Have you been in this store for a long time?
No, is it recently?
It feels very good.
Style is good, right?
It is often said.
Are you being sported or hurt?
No, not recently though.
But if you have that style, won’t it be so fun?
How about?
No, it is definitely fashionable.
It is very beautiful.
My friends, this is not a very good shop.
Oh sorry to.
Try to sleep fun.
Oh yes yes.
The guest
Sorry to
Amber please.
sitting today.
It feels good.
He is holding feet.
Is it OK?
Yes is
Very good feeling.
Sorry to sorry.
Yes is
The tree was very beautiful.
Please read well.
Sorry to
I am just writing this.
Sorry to no longer.
No to no.
What do you mean?
No, I really did not regret it.
You will touch it many times too.
No, really no longer.
Please give it.
A little bit of.
I too have to endure.
Oh, a little, what are you saying?
Please do it.
I wanted to do that, and I went into this store.
The manager said that such a noise is forbidden.
I have been patient, why do you touch me so much?
I have endured it all the time.
Really, please do it.
Oh, oh, oh, what do you say, a little bit?
So, what happened to you?
Listen to a little...
A little...
No, not that kind of thing.
Okay, is it okay?
Please keep quiet.
Sorry to
Is it because you touched me?
touched his ass several times.
Sorry to you.
Can’t read the text?
Should I push it a little?
If you know this, you are a private person.
Not bad is it?
Because you touched it.
Really okay, do this.
One day, you will know how many times you will say it.
A little, no.
You have touched it.
Please try it.
Please take responsibility.
What are you doing?
But I hit it a little.
What is this, this.
I do this.
Because you are doing this.
Are you in this swimsuit?
Because you touch it hard.
Why should I do it, too.
I have endured it for a long time.
A little
I am sitting a little faster.
Please be quiet.
Even if I say it is quiet.
If I was told.
Beyond the room.
There are people.
Please wait, sorry for that.
Anything, anything is good.
Please be quiet.
Thanks for the viewing.
Please wait, teacher.
Professor is yes.
Please go in the head.
I will beat.
Yes please please.
Tell the person who hurt.
Oh yes yes.
You were looking forward to today, right?
Is it yes?
Have you worked for 6 days?
I do not know.
You don’t know if you entered.
Do not ignore it a little.
It feels good there.
What do you usually do? – What do you usually do?
The women’s race?
What is your name? name.
I think you should tell me your name.
It is cold.
Next we will go on foot.
Yes
So, do you have a boyfriend?
Is it not there now?
Your skin is beautiful.
Do you do this massage yourself?
Please stop it.
There is no such message.
No, but it is a bit good.
Stop it, really.
No, it is written.
Look at it, it is not right.
No to
Please give it a little bit.
Oh, I would like to say I too.
The manager said this is not the shop.
No, no, no to
A little, a little, a little, a little.
Oh, this is
A little, a little, a little.
What are you doing.
Which one touched him first?
No, but
Please go up first.
Go up first, right?
No, a little bit of that.
Oh, oh oh oh oh
Oh no longer
Really, really good, this is
Oh is?
Oh, oh oh oh oh
Oh well, oh well
Please be quiet a little.
I will stop.
Oh yes yes
A little
A little, a little
What? what?
be quiet.
Take a camera.
Why is?
Okay is
What is?
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Me is
No to
Yes please please.
Yes is
Is it okay here?
Sorry to sorry.
A good atmosphere shop.
Thanks to.
Will you become concerned?
is okay.
It feels great oil.
How old are you?
How many do you see?
Oh yeah
But it looks so young.
About 24 years old.
24 years old.
Is that enough?
Massage is good.
You have been in this store for a long time.
Have you recently?
Very good feeling.
Style is good.
Are you being hurt by any sports?
No, recently
But if you have that style, isn’t it so cool?
How about.
No, it is definitely fashionable.
It is great, it is beautiful.
My friend, I am not in that store now.
Sorry to sorry.
Sorry to
Have fun sleeping.
Oh yes yes
The guest
Sorry to
Please do please.
Oh yes yes
Guests, it is good to sit.
Can I take my feet?
Yes is
Very good feeling.
Sorry to sorry.
Yes is
by
It was clean.
Please read well.
Sorry to
I am just writing this.
Yes, I do not ask.
Sorry to
What do you mean?
Sorry to not.
You will touch it several times.
No, really, I don’t want to say it anymore.
Please reduce it.
I also have to endure.
Oh, what are you saying?
Please please.
I also wanted to do this,
When I went into the store, the manager said that this kind of noise was forbidden.
I have been patient, why do you touch it so much?
I have been patient for all the time.
Please give it a little.
Oh, oh, oh, what do you say, a little bit?
Oh, and a little, what happened?
I hear it, a little, a little.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
A little, okay?
Please be quiet.
Sorry to sorry.
by
Because you touched it.
Touch it several times.
Sorry to you.
Can’t read the text?
A little bit of?
If I know this, I’ll drink.
It hurts if it is bad.
Because you touched it.
Really okay, do that.
One day I will know how many times I will tell you.
A little, a little, a little, a little, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You have touched it.
Try it though.
Please take responsibility.
Even if you are responsible.
What are you doing?
I am hit, though.
What is this.
Do it this way.
No, because you are doing this.
What do you really want to wear in this dress?
Because you touch it hard.
I’ll start by first, sorry.
Why should I do it, too.
I have endured it for a long time.
A little, a little.
You are getting a little faster, right?
If you say to be quiet, I say.
There is someone outside the room.
Sorry to
Anything a little.
Please come quietly.
I am saying that it is forbidden to touch here.
Oh yeah
Do you see?
I think, sorry
Have you heard about it recently?
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry
Next time, please turn off the sound.
Yes is
I will do it halfway.
Great – is good.
I will go up halfway.
Can I call the shop?
Sorry, a little
I also want to have sex.
But I can’t do the shop rules.
I am patient.
Because it is your fault.
Sorry sorry sorry sorry
Is it your fault?
Wait a moment, wait a moment, wait a moment.
Difficult to find out.
I had endured.
No to
Because it is your fault.
I have endured it all the time.
Isn’t it my fault?
No to
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Yes Yes Yes Yes
Isn’t it my fault?
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah
I brought it.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah
well well
Yes Yes Yes Yes
Yes
Definitely not tell.
Please do not tell anyone.
Try to get down here.
Yes is
So I will put oil.
Yes please.
It is so good, this shop.
Your sister’s clothes are yours.
No, this is a shop.
Oh yes, I think it’s great.
How long do you work here?
Or about 4 months.
Very long and short.
Does it hurt?
Oh, it is great. it feels good.
What do you do on vacation or what?
Next we go down.
Yes is
If it hurts, go away.
What time will you end here today?
The shop itself is up until 9 o’clock.
No, the sister’s seat.
Until 7 o’clock.
It is forbidden to sit here.
Sorry, but be careful.
First, turn back and then down.
Yes, please, this is great.
Thanks to.
Okay this is.
I am so slow today.
Is it really not hurt?
It feels great.
You know you?
Yes, I am sorry
Sitting is forbidden.
Sorry, sorry to
Can I call the shop?
No, sorry, but please do not tell.
Please continue.
Next time, I will actually call the shop.
Sorry, sorry to
Please give it.
I also have a lot of patience.
I wanted to work here for my work.
I said it is not a shopping mall, so I said it is not.
You are already home, right?
What are you doing?
Sorry to
It is the customer’s fault.
No to?
My sister, right?
I said no.
I have repeated clients.
Oh, but what do you mean?
expand so much.
No, this is
Customers are wrong.
otherwise.
When I go to the store, I will be in my head.
Please do not.
Yes is
A little bit.
Really okay?
Okay is?
greatly
Three years ago.
It is awesome.
Warmly
It smells healing.
I will return.
Hide in the voice.
I go until I go.
Gentlemen, I can’t do it.
I go to
Go to
cannot cannot
Moving and moving.
Move on.
Feel good
It will melt.
Mom, you are worse than I was.
There is a pancreatitis inside me.
Mom is bad.
Damn to Damn.
They are messing.
The dog sound.