The company was boring.
I'm going to buy something.
Where's the key?
I don't have it.
You don't have it? You gave it to me.
I didn't give it to you.
You gave it to me?
Why? Where is it?
I don't have it.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed to be seen by a neighbor.
You shouldn't have done that.
I'm sorry.
I don't think you should have done that.
You shouldn't have driven a car.
I'm sorry.
You haven't bought it yet.
I was busy.
I didn't notice it.
I didn't notice that I was driving a strange car.
I don't like that.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to do that.
I'm embarrassed to be seen by a neighbor.
I don't have to do that.
Why are you standing up?
I'm standing up.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't do that.
You want to touch me, don't you?
I want to touch you.
Can I touch you?
Just a little.
Just a little?
You have a runny nose.
Can I touch you?
You'll get runny nose if you do that.
Why?
You can't do that.
You have a runny nose.
I'll pat your head.
I don't want to hear it.
I don't want to hear you crying.
Come here.
What?
Wait.
I'm asking you about Yurikawa.
What?
Actually,
I'm asking you about this.
I heard it from him.
Yurikawa is having an affair.
Affair?
Yes.
No, no, no.
And he's with his neighbor.
But he's single, isn't he?
Yes.
That's why he's so nice.
He's so kind.
He's so nice.
He's a good neighbor.
Yes.
We're all married.
We have a place for kids.
We're all single.
We only go to that room.
Yes.
He's doing a good job.
Are you interested in him?
Stop it.
I don't have that kind of courage.
I didn't know that.
Are you interested in him?
My husband gets angry easily.
I see.
I can't do that.
It's convenient.
I don't have that kind of courage.
But I heard that...
My husband gets angry easily.
That's why.
He gets angry easily.
He doesn't have any feelings.
He is like that.
Hey.
Don't tell this to anyone.
No.
I told you because it's you.
Let's keep it a secret.
I wonder what's going to happen to Yurikawa-san from now on.
What if I get a girlfriend?
What should I do?
Is it Yurikawa-san?
Hello.
Who is it?
Hello, I'm Nakao from the lower floor.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Yes.
I've been hearing a strange voice lately.
Is something wrong?
No, not at all.
By the way, do you have a wife?
No, I'm single.
Then, do you have a girlfriend?
No, I don't.
By any chance, do you have an affair?
Affair?
No, I don't.
Really?
Yes.
I think I've heard a voice from the lower floor.
Well, I watch pornographic videos.
I'm single.
Do you have a crush on someone you know?
Well, I don't know.
I've heard a voice from the lower floor.
I'm wearing earphones, so I might have heard a voice.
Do you hear a voice from your earphones?
I don't know if it's coming from the TV.
Is that so?
It's strange.
What is strange?
I don't know.
Do you have an affair in this apartment?
No, I don't.
Excuse me.
Hello, I'm Arioka, a maid.
Ms. Arioka.
May I come in?
I came here because my laundry was on the veranda.
Why did you come here?
Your apartment is on the edge.
I can't stay here.
It's windy today, isn't it?
That's why I came here.
Why are you here?
I came here to talk to you.
I have something to ask you.
What is it?
I don't know what it is.
Are you interested in me?
Did you come here to talk about that?
I don't know.
Do you want me to ask you directly?
You know what it is, right?
What is it?
I don't know what it is.
I don't want to bother you.
I just want you to lend me a little.
We are married.
I didn't tell you my name.
I haven't told you my name recently.
Me, too.
That's why I came here.
I'm sorry.
Can you lend me this?
I won't tell anyone.
I'll keep it a secret between the three of us.
But...
I don't like it.
I got it.
If the three of us do it, we can save time.
That's a good idea.
Let's do it together.
We can save time.
We're running out of time.
Excuse me.
Who are you?
Wait a minute.
Why?
You can't do that.
What are you talking about?
Wait a minute.
You're sensitive.
You'll find out.
Are you serious?
I'm sorry.
I don't want you to talk about my mother.
Please don't do that.
My mouth might be light.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
But if you lend it to me, I'll keep it a secret.
If you lend it to me, I'll keep it a secret.
That's all I need.
What do you think?
That's what you want to do, isn't it?
I heard you have a good one.
Are you sure?
Are you sure you won't tell me?
I won't tell you.
I'm not looking forward to it anymore.
I'll lose money, too.
Let's go to the hospital together.
Let's go home.
That's a good idea.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
All you have to do is feel better.
How do you feel?
You feel better, don't you?
Give me your hand.
Let's make both of us feel better.
Both of us?
Both of us.
I'm counting on you.
I'm sorry.
Did you do it?
No, I didn't.
You didn't do it.
Did you do it on purpose?
In front of this door.
Just once.
You're so mean.
You have a very cute neck.
This neck.
It's a beautiful color.
I'm surprised.
Can I eat this?
That's a good idea.
I can't eat this.
You can't eat this because you feel good, right?
You have a very sensitive and good reaction.
This is going to be fun.
I want to see you soon.
I can't do this.
You're amazing.
You're so cute.
You look delicious.
Did you always do such a good job?
This is amazing.
Don't say that.
This looks delicious.
What should I do?
We have to eat this together.
I can't do this.
This is delicious.
This is the best, isn't it?
Let me eat this.
You're a good drinker.
This is the best.
This is delicious.
I can't do this.
This feels good, doesn't it?
Let's do something more pleasant.
I can't do this.
I'm doing a great job.
You're a beautiful woman.
I want to be wrapped in this.
I want to see it, too.
If I see that, I'll get hot.
If I see all this, I'll get sick.
It's hard and hot.
Look at this.
I wiped it all off.
I'm wrapped in this.
Look at this.
This looks delicious.
You've never tasted anything like this, have you?
I'm wrapped in this.
I can't do this.
This is the best.
Can you look at my chest?
I'm doing a good job.
You're a beautiful woman.
I'm wrapped in this.
Look at this.
You were doing a great job.
You're a beautiful woman.
I'm wrapped in this.
Mom...
Please calm down.
Don't say that...
They are cute...
Don't...
It's okay.
They are cute.
I can't...
You can't forget the food.
You have food.
It's okay, okay?
I'll give you more...
I don't have enough...
Grrr...
Ah...
I looked at you from the box.
After that, two days later, I fed him as he put up,
and that's when I knew he was still stuck in that box.
Why?
I can't.
You can't.
Don't put it out yet.
Wait a minute.
I can't.
You already put it out?
Is it good?
I put it out.
It looks good.
I can't.
It's strong.
Isn't it strong?
It looks good.
You need to put it out a little earlier.
Let me have a little more fun.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm going to hide it.
You can't.
It's strong.
I can't.
I'm embarrassed.
How is it?
I'm going to hide it.
I can't.
You can't.
There's still a lot left.
I hid it.
Look.
I know.
I can't.
There's still a lot left.
If you don't put it out, you'll get caught.
You have to put it out.
Put it out.
You'll get caught.
I can't.
We're not having fun yet.
You have to put it out.
You'll get caught.
I can't.
You have to put it out.
You don't have to say anything unnecessary.
Put it out.
You have to put it out.
I can't.
It doesn't feel good.
You have to put it out.
That's not enough.
There's still a lot left.
You have to put it out.
It doesn't feel good.
Here, mother.
Here, here.
Here you go.
Try to bite it!
Try to bite!
You look happy.
Look!
Actually,
What's wrong with you?
You're hurting me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What are you talking about?
You're drunk, aren't you?
And you have a nice butt.
You're so close to me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You're getting heavier.
You have a nice butt.
My butt is getting heavier.
Can you mix our butts?
What should we do?
But...
Can you mix our butts?
I'm getting heavier.
Here?
Yes.
What's wrong with you?
Can you mix our butts?
I feel good.
I'm getting heavier.
I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
I'll wipe your butt.
I can't do that.
I'll clean your butt.
You have a nice butt.
I can't do that.
Can you do that?
I'm sorry.
I can't do that.
I feel good.
I'm getting heavier.
I can't do that.
You have a nice butt.
I've never seen you like this before.
My body is moving.
I can't do that.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
I can't do that.
Great!
Now, stop crying.
I did it!
Great!
Oh, my God!
One more time...
Look...
Ah, I'm gonna do it again...
Look, look, look...
Ah, the gushing gushing...
I love this!
It's so good...
Ah...
Ah, I'm so happy...
Ah, there, there, there...
Ah, it's getting serious!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
Ah...
Ah, ah, ah...
Ah, ah, ah, ah...
Ah...
Ah, it's getting serious, it's so good...
It was so good like that...
Ah...
Ah, Hey, let's do it together, let's do it together~!
Here I go!
Ah, ah, ah...
Oh, my God.
What should I do?
It's okay.
Oh, my God.
You're badly injured.
Why...
Sorry.
I'm going to sleep now.
ücht.
Stay there until I say goodbye.
I want to close my eyes too…
If she says once, it's 1 0th time it's off.
No, I want it to be the last.
Come on, come on.
I can't stand it anymore.
I can't stand it.
You'll satisfy us both, won't you?
Well, I guess so.
You're still a baby.
You'll satisfy us both, won't you?
I can't stand it.
It's shaking so much.
It's coming off.
Please clean it up.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's coming off again.
I can't stand it.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's coming off.
Please clean it up.
It's coming off again.
Yes, yes, yes.
I can't stand it.
Please clean it up.
It's coming off.
I want to sleep from the back, too.
Look...
énè...
It's great, isn't it?
We're amazing.
It's coming off.
Please clean up my face.
You don't seem to be able to talk.
Does it feel good?
You're shaking your hips like a dog.
You're licking your nose.
Does it feel good?
You don't seem to be able to talk.
You're licking your nose.
Does it feel good?
You don't seem to be able to talk.
Oh, no!
Ahh, so sad...
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Ummm
Ohhhhh
OMG
Oheri
Ouch
I'm so scared.
I feel so good.
What are you saying?
I'm sleepy.
Are you still sleepy?
I can't do it anymore.
You're still sleepy, aren't you?
What?
You can still do it, right?
Come on.
Give me your hand.
Oh, no.
Are you still sleepy?
It's funny.
You're still sleepy.
You look like you've had a bath.
It's so cold.
Come here.
Official Daichi
You're awesome. Mr Akiyama…
Yamada
Daichi
Amaze
G.
Watanabe
Subaru
Yamada
I want some tangerines too.
Oh, it's effective.
Excellent.
How do you feel?
Excuse me.
Do you feeloughtful?
What are you doing?
Stop it!
More! More!
Do more!
It's cold.
I'll hold you.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's cold.
You're drooling.
Stop it.
You're pink and cute.
It's cold.
You're drooling.
My drool is coming out.
It's cold.
It feels good.
It's tickling.
It's cold.
More.
It's coming out again.
Help me.
It's turning white.
It's still cold.
It's getting worse.
I want to do it a little more.
A little more?
Are you sleepy?
No, I'm not.
It's still this cold.
No, but...
I want to do it a little more.
It's getting worse.
It's amazing.
It's four times worse.
I want to do it a little more.
It's getting worse.
It's coming out again.
I want to do it a little more.
It's still dripping.
I'll do my best.
It's okay.
Do you understand?
It's a secret between three of us.
I'll do my best.
I wonder if that scent will make you feel better.
It's okay if you take a bath for a while.
Please lend me your face when you were a baby.
I understand.
Let's get along well from now on.
It's getting worse.
If the whole apartment finds out about this, my husband will hear it.
What should I do?
It's okay.
What is it?
It's Yusuke.
I heard it from Arioka and Nakano.
What did you hear?
You said you'd lend me your face.
I can't do that.
I heard it.
I heard everything.
You said you'd lend me your face.
I just happened to hear that.
I didn't do that.
I can't do that.
My husband will hear it.
If the whole apartment finds out about this, my husband will hear it.
I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
I'll be right back.
I'm not coming back.
I'm working.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
If the whole apartment finds out about this, my husband will hear it.
I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I can't do that.
I'm begging you.
I'm sorry.
I can't do that.
Why can't I do that?
If we live in the same apartment, I can't do that.
I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
I really want to do that.
I can't do that.
It's so warm.
I'm so hot.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It's so hot.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It's so hot.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
It's so hot.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I want to do it.
It's so hot.
I can't do it.
Wait a minute.
It's so hot.
I can't do it.
I won't be found out.
It's okay.
Are you really going to do it?
Oh, my God.
I can't do it.
I feel sick.
I can't speak.
I'm sweating.
andhing...
I feel good to laugh like this.
but...
But...
I can't.
It's okay.
It's a terrible body.
It's moving.
I want to move.
I feel good.
It's going out.
I'm gonna throw up
Ewww
Yawn
You need to get up
It's hard, isn't it?
Mama.
What?
You're still sleeping, aren't you?
No, but...
Mama, are you sleepy?
Oh, I'm sleepy.
Oh, I feel great.
Oh, it's hot.
That's great.
You're talking in a quiet voice.
Oh, I feel great.
Why!?
Ouch!
Oh, what the hell.
I can't stand up.
Okay, okay.
My legs are so tired.
My hips are so tired.
Give me a hug.
It feels so good.
This is amazing.
Give me a hug.
I can't do this.
I can't stop moving my hips.
It feels so good.
It's been a long time.
This is amazing.
I can't do this.
I want to stand up.
It feels so good.
Really?
I can't do this.
It feels so good.
What should I do?
I can't do this.
It feels so good.
What should I do?
Are you sure?
Can I ask you again?
I'm home.
You're home early.
I was at the store.
What are you wearing?
I'm going to take a bath.
You're sweating.
Isn't it hot today?
It's hot, but...
It's summer.
Can I take it off?
It's hot.
I look forward to working with you again.
Yes.
No.
It's not good.
My voice is coming out.
As Ayako said, you have a good reaction.
I'm helping you.
If I go home...
It's not good.
It's hot.
It's time for you to go home.
There are a lot of people living in this apartment, right?
No, there aren't many.
I'm here, too.
My hands are getting hot.
It's okay.
Please touch me.
It's really hot.
Be gentle.
It's okay.
It's just a little hot.
It's hot.
It's getting hotter.
I'm so excited.
It's hot.
Let me help you.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's amazing.
It smells good.
I'm going to lose my voice.
It's okay.
It's amazing.
It's delicious.
Thank you.
I ate too much.
It's delicious.
I'm going to lose my voice.
What's wrong with you?
I'm really hungry.
I'm hungry.
I don't usually eat out.
I don't usually go to the entrance.
It's okay.
If I go home, I won't be able to escape.
I'm going to lose my voice.
It's okay.
Takehiro, you're too hard on me.
You can't do that.
It's okay.
It's amazing.
I just got out of the bath.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's clean now.
You can take a bath.
Can I take a bath here?
It's okay.
It's amazing.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
I'm going to take a bath.
I'm tired today.
I don't think I can take a bath today.
That's right.
I'm going to take a bath.
Let's take a bath next time.
Okay.
I'm going to take a bath.
Thank you.
What?
Ah, I will go to office right now.
Did you try to enter them?
I just realized that I forgot this.
OK, I'll leave now.
Please wait.
My husband is late today.
No, no.
I have to go to work.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I have to go home tomorrow.
Wait a minute.
Please sit down.
I have to go to work.
I heard from Takeuchi.
What did he say?
He said many things.
Many things?
I don't mind.
No, no.
I want you to go to work.
I haven't decided yet.
You can go to work today.
What about today?
It's okay.
No one will come back.
I won't tell anyone.
Really?
I don't want to hear more rumors.
If you don't go to work today, I'll go to work.
Wait a minute.
You're lying.
What do you think?
Well...
I'll go to work.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute?
You don't mind, do you?
Well...
I won't tell anyone.
You don't mind, do you?
Well...
I think it's not good.
You don't mind?
You don't mind, do you?
You said you didn't mind.
I don't mind.
You don't mind?
I'm sorry.
You're so mean.
I'm so excited.
Go home and sleep!
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
It's big.
It's big, isn't it?
It's as I said, isn't it?
Do you all rent this house?
That's right.
I'm jealous.
Can I touch it?
You're already touching it.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
I'm going to lick it.
I can't do it.
It's a good feeling.
You're touching it.
It's getting hard.
I can't do it.
It's the best.
It's hard.
I can't do it.
Let's drink together.
It's hard.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I can't do it.
It's hard.
Oh, my.
It hurts.
Oh, no.
Are you sure it's yesterday?
I feel so good.
Please stand in a line.
Stand in a line.
Stand in a line?
I feel so good.
Come here.
I can't hold it anymore.
You can't?
Your husband will come back, right?
No, he won't.
It's so hard.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
I feel so good.
I can't hold it anymore.
It hurts.
Are you okay?
It is here It is here
I was born
Next
Hmm
It's good, isn't it?
Oh, my God!
Oh, God!
mom!
Mom, wake up!
I'm exhausted
Soo exhausted
I transportation too tired
Don't cry
I don't feel so good
Mommy, I can't stand it
Mom
I can't see anything but it's amazing.
It's amazing.
It's so tight.
It feels so good.
It's coming out.
It's so tight.
It feels so good.
Thank you.
Thank you Thank you.
It's so good.
It's so tight.
It's okay.
You're so heavy.
It feels so good.
I'm so happy.
It hurts.
I can't do it.
You have to do it.
I don't want to wake my sister up!
Ah!
I don't like it!
I think she's getting a sword shot.
Oh my mom!
Ah, ah, ah!
Ken!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh oh oh
I'm so happy.
this is hard
it's so hard
I'm so tired
I'm sorry.
You have a bad back.
Let's go to the hospital.
Get a hold of yourself.
I see.
It's okay.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Yeah you should get some rest
Do it
Give it some rest
You can do it
It's awesome
You did it
Oh, it still hurts.
Are you okay?
It's not over yet.
Be careful.
Come here, Kanae.
Are you feeling better?
I'm sorry about this.
Everyone's here.
When we see your boy,
always hold on to this hand.
We'll have a consultation with the doctor
It feels so good.
I can see a lot.
It's amazing.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to do that.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
I feel strange.
Do you feel strange?
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm sleepy.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
If you do more, you'll feel better.
I feel good.
Did you feel good?
Yes, I did.
You're a strong girl.
Please don't tell anyone about this.
I don't know what to do.
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Let's do it again.
No, no, no.
If we can do it again, we'll be happy.
Yes, we will.
I'm sorry.