I'm really sorry.
It seems that I sent you the past material.
Yes.
But I also sent you a new one, so please check it out.
I also sent you a new project, so please check it out.
Yes.
Thank you.
I'll be careful from now on, so please take care of me from now on.
Yes.
Then, excuse me.
What? It's noisy.
Yes.
Do you think you can finish it when the call is over?
I'm angry because of you.
Please reflect on yourself.
Yes.
It's hard to do the next one.
Is it painful?
Yes.
It's painful.
Please reflect on yourself.
Yes.
I'm always irritated because of you.
Do I have to do it?
Yes.
I'm at my limit.
I have to work properly.
Yes.
I'm in trouble.
It's noisy.
Yes.
What?
I don't know what you're saying.
Please speak clearly.
What?
It's noisy.
What's wrong?
I can't breathe.
You can't breathe?
Is it so painful?
Yes.
I'm at my limit.
How many times have you done this?
I don't know.
You do it every day.
Yes.
Do you really reflect on yourself?
I reflect on myself.
You don't reflect on yourself, do you?
Yes.
What are you going to do?
You reflect on yourself, don't you?
Yes.
Show me your reflection.
Hurry up.
Yes.
Is this okay?
Do you think it's okay?
Don't underestimate me.
You always do this, don't you?
Remember this.
That's why you can't get a job easily.
Is it painful?
Look at this.
You're underestimating me, aren't you?
Do it properly.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Do it more.
Do it properly.
Is anyone there?
What are you doing?
Kaneko seems to have lost the key to the locker.
Kaneko?
What are you doing?
Thank you for your hard work.
Is it a key?
Can I help you?
Is it okay?
You have something to do, don't you?
I can help you.
It's okay. I can help you.
Is that so?
Then I'll go back.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
Do you think you can escape?
No.
Hey.
Yes?
You tried to escape, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
I was going to finish it.
But you made me angry again.
No, I didn't.
Hey, sit on the chair.
There is a chair here.
I sat on it.
That's enough.
I'm telling you to sit on the new chair.
Hurry up.
Do you want me to do more?
Yes.
Sit on the chair.
Hey.
What?
You're noisy.
I can't hear you.
Do you want me to laugh?
I'm really annoyed.
I'm annoyed just by looking at your face.
What?
I can't hear you.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Sit on the chair properly.
I can't hear you.
What?
Sit on the chair properly.
It's a punishment for trying to escape.
What?
Sit on the chair properly.
I can't hear you.
What?
It's over.
Don't be noisy.
Will you sit on the chair properly?
I'm happy.
It's comfortable.
Don't be angry.
It's a good chair.
I can sit on it.
What's wrong with your face?
You look miserable.
What?
It's hard.
Is it hard?
What are you doing?
I'm sure I'm harder than you.
What's wrong with your face?
Don't you reflect on yourself?
What are you doing?
You like it, don't you?
It's hard.
Sit on the chair properly.
You look miserable.
It's hard.
What are you looking at?
Are you looking down on me?
What's wrong with you?
It's hard.
What are you doing?
I'm going to die.
I'm talking to you.
It's hard.
It's good that you can't breathe.
Do you want to do it properly?
What?
Do it properly.
It's hard.
It's good.
You don't reflect on yourself, do you?
No.
Do it properly.
You don't reflect on yourself, do you?
It's hard.
It's hard, isn't it?
I'm irritated.
Let me relieve my stress.
Why are you leaving me?
I'm sorry.
But?
Do you want me to do it directly?
It's hard.
What are you licking?
Are you reflecting on yourself?
No.
Do you want me to reflect on myself?
It's hard.
Hey.
You're drinking a lot.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'll make you suffer more.
You licked me.
I was irritated again.
It's hard.
I'll be irritated for a long time.
What?
Don't move.
You licked me.
I didn't ask you to lick me.
Do you want me to be irritated?
It's hot.
It's hard.
You're disgusting.
Don't you stand up?
Why are you irritated?
What?
I didn't ask you to make excuses.
I'm sorry.
What?
Is it hard?
I'm sorry.
I didn't ask you to talk to me.
If you want to lick me so much, do it.
What?
Don't move.
Why are you irritated?
I'm sorry.
Cover your mouth.
Is it hard?
I'm sorry.
What?
You're disgusting.
I have more.
Don't breathe.
Is it hard?
You don't hate me.
I have more.
You lick me a lot.
You're like a dog.
Why are you excited?
Don't move.
I'm in a good mood today.
I'll look at you.
Look at me.
I'll irritate you again.
No.
Come here.
No one is coming.
I'm irritated.
I'm sorry.
What are you hiding?
You've been hitting me.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
What?
Can you touch me?
I told you I was in a good mood today.
Don't touch me.
Do you want me to touch you?
No.
I want you to touch me.
What?
Nothing.
I'm apologizing to you every day.
Praise me.
Thank me.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you for apologizing to me.
Thank you.
You can say it.
You should have told me in advance.
I'll tell you every day.
Really?
You should have told me in advance.
I'm sorry.
No.
I still have it in my mouth.
I'm sorry.
You have a lot of it.
Your breasts are big.
Are you happy?
Let's play with this.
How do you feel?
I just said it.
You said it without knowing it.
No.
I didn't say it.
I'm sorry.
What?
Don't get up.
It's hard to get up.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll give you a surprise.
It's quiet now.
You like this better.
You're noisy.
What?
Do you want me to do it, too?
No.
Please do what you want.
You were going to do it, weren't you?
No.
Do you want me to do it?
I'll do it in here.
What?
You want me to do it, don't you?
But...
What?
You want me to do it, don't you?
I want to do it.
Okay.
I'll do it in here.
I want to do it, too.
Okay.
You want to do it, too, don't you?
But...
Go to sleep.
I'll do it in here.
Okay.
You're honest.
You want me to do it, don't you?
Yes.
You usually do it in here.
What's wrong with you today?
I can't do it here.
It's too late.
What's wrong?
You feel good, don't you?
You're happy, aren't you?
Yes, I'm happy.
What's wrong?
You're weak.
I didn't do it for you.
What's wrong?
Don't run away.
You're loud.
Is it okay if someone comes?
No, it's okay.
You feel good, don't you?
What's wrong?
Why do you look so sad?
You feel good, don't you?
It's okay.
Do you want me to hit you harder?
Oh, no.
Don't do that.
Do you want me to hit you harder?
No.
You're so violent.
What's wrong?
Stop it.
You're so violent.
What's wrong?
I didn't know that.
You're so violent.
Stop it.
What's wrong?
You feel good, don't you?
I love you.
You feel good.
It's dangerous.
What's dangerous?
Is it dangerous?
Tell me what's dangerous.
Let's get out of here.
Is it dangerous?
You feel good, don't you?
Look at me.
What's wrong?
Do you want more?
You feel good, don't you?
Do you feel good?
You're in my way.
You can sit down.
How do you feel?
It smells bad.
It smells bad?
It's yours, isn't it?
I'll do my best.
You feel good, don't you?
What's wrong with your face?
Did you think you could take a break?
You feel good, don't you?
You look round again, don't you?
Look at me.
You feel good, don't you?
How do you feel?
I feel good, don't you?
It hurts.
Tired ...
Go away ...
It is important to make you feel better.
I feel really good!
I cannot run anymore!
It's torture!
Ouch!
Why do you stop?
Do you want me to move like that?
Hey, don't run away.
Ouch!
Are you happy to come to the stage again?
Yes.
Ouch!
Do you feel good?
Yes.
You like to move violently, don't you?
You move violently, don't you?
Yes.
It's OK.
You are in a good mood today.
Ouch!
It's hard, right?
I love you. I want to be with you forever.
I love you.
You're sweating a lot.
You'll make me beautiful, won't you?
Do you like sweat?
I love you.
What's wrong?
What's this?
Do you want me to do it again?
What's wrong?
You're excited, aren't you?
Do you want me to do this?
Are you doing it on purpose?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I'm in trouble if you don't do this much.
Can't you do it?
I'm always doing this.
I'm in trouble.
Do it properly.
Are you listening?
I'm in trouble because you don't do it properly.
What's wrong?
Are you in trouble?
Do you want me to do this?
You're in trouble.
I'm always doing this.
I'm in trouble.
Why are you sweating so much?
You're always sweating.
What's wrong?
I'm in trouble.
I can't move.
You should be working properly.
I'm sorry.
You're always doing the same thing.
I'm in trouble.
Do you want me to do this?
Can you do it instead of me?
I'm in trouble.
I can't do it.
You're sweating so much.
I'm stressed out because you don't work properly.
If you don't do this, you can't have a baby.
Do you understand?
I'm sorry.
I'm not sorry.
You made a mistake again.
I'm in trouble.
How many times do you make a mistake?
I'm sorry.
You're stressed out again.
Why are you lying down?
I'm really annoyed.
Come here.
What are you doing?
Hurry up.
I don't complain about this.
I can't move my neck.
It's not that hard, is it?
I'm in trouble.
It's not hard, is it?
I can't move my neck.
I'm in trouble.
I'm not happy.
I'm not in trouble.
I'm in trouble.
It's not that hard.
I can't breathe.
Don't do it again.
Wait.
Asaki-san.
I'm sorry.
That's enough.
What?
You think I'll forgive you?
Wait.
I'm not done yet.
Don't run away.
I'm leaving.
Don't do it again.
Wait.
That's enough.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'll leave again.
What's up with you?
Hey, hey.
W-What?
Cut it out.
I don't know if I can do it, but I'm going to do my best.
I'm going to do my best.
I'll do my best.
Don't grumble just because it hurts.
Please forgive me.
I won't forgive you.
Please lick me.
I can't breathe.
I won't forgive you.
Please lick me more.
I can't breathe.
Please get up.
Please open your mouth.
I can't breathe.
Please forgive me.
Please lick me more.
I can't breathe.
Please put your fingers in my mouth.
Please get up.
I can't breathe.
What are you hiding?
You always hate it, but you can't breathe.
I can't breathe.
You've grown up so much.
I'm sorry.
Did you always do this?
I can't breathe.
You must have wanted to do this.
This is the last time.
I can't breathe.
I don't think I can do this.
You have to drink it.
I can't breathe.
Put it in from behind.
I'm so scared.
I can't breathe.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh.
Why is this what
you can meet?
Have you been deceived for a little?
It's still under the bed.
No, it's completely under the bed.
I still have a document left.
Can I make it?
Here you are.
From now, it's my turn.
Huh?
Here you are.
What?
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
Wait, wait, wait.
Ouch!
You've been re-watching it every time.
Yes, I have.
You told me that I can ask Matsuoka-kun to make the documents.
It's all thanks to your help.
No, no, no.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
By the way,
the graph from last week has been changed.
Could you check it again?
Yes, I see.
It might be fixed.
Yes.
Please check it.
I see.
The rest is fine.
Yes.
Thank you.
I'll finish it by tomorrow.
I'm sorry for taking so long.
No, no, no.
It's nothing.
Yes.
You can go now.
Thank you.
Hey, Murata.
Thank you for today.
You're welcome.
You've been re-watching it every time.
You should be careful.
I know that.
I'm glad to hear that.
Yes.
Murata-kun.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Bring it to me.
Here you are.
Murata-kun.
What's this?
What?
What do you mean?
Are you licking it?
No, I'm not.
You haven't fixed anything, have you?
I'm sorry.
Do you remember what you were told?
No, I don't remember.
Have you ever seen Matsuoka-kun's castle?
No, I haven't.
Why?
You can't do it yourself, so you have to steal what you can.
Right?
Yes.
Murata-kun is the only one who brings such a thing.
There are a lot of 50s and 80s.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Why is the color different on the first and second pages?
It's hard to see.
Well, that's...
What's that?
Sasahara-san.
Yes.
I have to go now.
Okay.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Don't mention it.
Thank you for your hard work.
Think about who you are and fix it again.
Yes, I will.
Damn it.
Murata-kun.
Yes?
Can I do it in 10 minutes?
What?
In 10 minutes.
I'll do what I always do.
Do you understand?
In 10 minutes?
Yes.
I'll finish this, too.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
I can't finish it at all.
Seriously.
Why do I have to do this job?
Whose fault is this?
Sigh...
It's not working here.
What?
Don't move.
It's terrible to disturb me when I can't do my job.
Are you listening?
Yes.
What are you going to do when someone comes?
What are you going to do?
Hey.
Answer me.
What are you going to do?
Hey.
What? I can't hear you.
What?
I can't hear you.
What is this hand?
Don't touch me.
Sigh...
I can't finish this job.
It's noisy.
What?
Are you giving up already?
I'm sorry.
You should be patient.
Today...
I...
What?
Nothing.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing now?
Nothing.
You can't do your job.
You can't make medicine.
You can't fix your house.
No.
No?
What?
Nothing.
Tell me clearly.
I...
What?
Look at me.
I...
What?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I...
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I...
You're so sticky.
I'm sorry.
You're looking at my panties.
No, I'm not.
I can see them.
Can you?
No.
You don't have to.
No, I'm not.
You're looking at my panties.
I...
You're a pervert.
Are you listening?
I'm sorry.
You're sleeping.
I'll wake you up.
Good morning.
Are you awake?
I'm awake.
What?
Don't run away.
I'm awake.
Get up.
Come on.
I can't take it anymore.
You're happy.
Look at them.
You might lose some of your breath.
What?
Do you want more?
Here.
Do you want this?
You like it this way.
Do you remember? From the beginning, you've been pooping a lot.
Are you excited again?
Hey, are you pooping again?
Look, look, look.
What?
Are you pooping?
Then I'll give you more.
Like this?
Wow, your face is crushed.
Are you in pain?
Look, look, look.
You're in more pain.
It's painful, isn't it?
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're getting excited with this, aren't you?
You've been a pervert all along, haven't you?
More?
Look, look, look.
Oh, my God.
Hey, your nose tickles.
Stop it.
Are you in a coma?
Look, look, look.
What?
Wait a minute.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm at my limit.
What's the limit?
I can't do this anymore.
What?
What's the limit?
No, no, no.
Get your hands off me.
What's this?
Touch it yourself.
What's going on?
Oh, my God.
It's like you're pooping yourself.
What's this?
Hey, you're a liar.
No, I'm not.
What's the difference?
I'll punish you for lying.
Look.
What?
You're shivering again.
What's going on?
Are you happy?
Do you like this?
You're shivering.
What's this?
What is this?
You're a real liar.
You're a liar.
Yes.
Do it right.
You said you can't eat it, didn't you?
I can't eat it.
You have to stretch it out.
Stretch it out.
Move it.
You have to lick it.
More.
Great.
You're doing great.
Lick it more.
It feels good.
You can do it.
Get up.
Why are you resting?
Lick it more.
Are you excited because of this?
What?
Your butt.
You like to suffer, don't you?
Was it painful?
It's painful, isn't it?
I'll do it again.
What?
I can't hear you.
What are you doing?
It's not painful, is it?
That's right.
It feels good.
What?
Did you fall asleep?
That's right.
Hey.
Did you fall asleep?
Good morning.
What?
Are you awake?
I'm awake.
Why are you sleeping in the office?
That's...
You can't sleep in the office as a social person.
I'm sorry.
Then...
What?
You like this, don't you?
I'm sorry.
Did you feel good?
Were you excited?
You were excited.
I'm sorry.
You're so excited.
Chinchin.
Come on.
What?
Look.
You like this, don't you?
What? You don't like it?
Do you really hate this?
Look.
I got it.
You like it raw, don't you?
Look.
You like this, don't you?
What?
Look.
You don't like it, do you?
You're amazing.
Your nose is running and your chest is sweating.
Look.
I've been touching you for a while.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sorry.
What?
You're going to get in there.
Oh, you're in there.
It feels good.
Look.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
I love this.
It hurts.
It feels good.
What are you doing?
What?
This?
That's right.
Do you want me to do it hard?
Look.
It's close.
Here.
There.
It hurts.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
It hurts.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
It hurts.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
It hurts.
What?
Are you scared?
It's okay.
You're amazing.
Something came out.
Look at this.
I'm sorry.
Did it come out?
Clean it up.
Take it out.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
You can do more.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
You're amazing.
I'm sorry.
You can do more.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Move your hips more.
More?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
You can do more.
Go away.
I'm sorry.
Did you do it again?
Hey.
Look at this.
Rub your feet.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I'm so tired.
I'm sorry.
It's been a while, so it felt good.
It felt good, didn't it?
Right?
How about tomorrow?
What?
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Yes.
You can do it tomorrow, right?
Don't you like it?
No.
I don't dislike it at all.
I got it.
See you tomorrow.
Hey.
Nishiyama.
Yes.
Are you done?
I'm sorry.
I haven't finished it yet.
Let's go to Maizuta.
It's a girl's bar that Bunny made.
I'm sorry.
I can't finish it today.
You can do it tomorrow.
Let's go.
But I can't today.
I went to a cute girl's bar.
You can do it.
I can't do it today.
You can do it today.
You can't miss it today.
Well.
That girl is going to work today.
You can do it.
Thank you for your hard work.
Are you working overtime?
No.
I'm done.
I'm going to work the next day.
I see.
I'm tired.
What's this?
You haven't finished it yet?
Yes.
It was a long day.
I have to do this.
Are you done?
What?
If you're done, it's a hurry.
Can you do this?
I told you.
I want you to do this.
I'm sorry.
That's what I was talking about.
I have to do this.
I see.
I'm done.
Thank you for your hard work.
What do you think?
Hirano?
Yes.
The one you talked about.
The one you talked about?
Hirano.
Hirano?
Isn't her house far from here?
It's about three stations from here.
What do you think?
I think she can walk home.
Hirano always lies.
I don't know.
I don't know what she's thinking.
The meeting was long and I'm irritated.
I'm tired.
I want to do this.
I don't want to do this.
Hey.
What?
Are you going home?
No, I'm not.
You have a bag.
No, I don't.
I'm going to put a pen in my bag.
I thought you were going home.
No, I'm not.
Why can you go home in this atmosphere?
On the contrary.
I've been listening to you.
You said you had to do this as soon as possible.
You said you wanted to do this instead of me.
Can't you say anything you want to say?
Can I do that?
Anyone can do that.
The meeting is over and I'm busy.
Why can't you say that?
Anyone can do that.
I have to call you back.
I'm sorry.
I'm tired.
Hey, NISHIYAMA.
Yes.
Let's do what we always do.
Let's do that.
I have to get up early tomorrow.
Don't you want to do that?
I don't want to do that.
Do you make excuses like that?
I'm not making excuses.
You're making excuses.
I'm fine.
You're the same as me.
Do you really think you're okay?
Of course.
I'm fine.
You should have said that from the beginning.
That's right.
Why did you say that at the beginning?
I don't like it.
I'm sorry.
Let's finish this as soon as possible.
I have to do this.
A famous actor got married.
Really?
Did you know that?
Yes.
I haven't seen it for a long time.
There is no interesting news.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Don't touch me.
Are you in pain?
Your face is moving.
Look.
I'm sorry.
You're noisy.
Are you in pain?
Do you want to pee?
Look.
I'm sorry.
You look like you're in pain.
What's wrong?
Are you already at your limit?
I'm sorry.
You're not good at all.
I didn't expect you to come today.
I told you to be ready at any time.
I'm sorry.
You're useless.
That's enough.
I'm sorry.
I'm tired.
Are you in pain?
You sweat a lot today.
You smell bad.
What's wrong?
Are you in pain?
Answer me.
I'm tired.
I'm irritated today.
Why?
You're noisy.
Shut up.
It's not closed properly.
I'm stressed out.
You're getting bigger.
You like pain, don't you?
I'm in pain.
You're so excited.
You're getting stiff.
It's painful.
Why?
Do you like heels better?
Don't you like it?
Are you listening to me?
You're getting bigger.
Why?
Are you in pain?
You like pain, don't you?
What do you want me to do?
I want you to do more.
Do you want me to do more?
You're too sweet.
I'm sorry.
You like pain, don't you?
I can't help it.
I'll give you a massage here.
Are you in pain?
Take off your clothes.
What?
Are you in pain?
I can't help it.
You're getting stiff.
You're a pervert.
I can't help it.
I'm not being nice to you.
You like it when I hug you with my nails, don't you?
Yes.
You're a pervert.
It feels good.
It feels better when you're in pain, doesn't it?
Open your mouth.
What do you want me to do?
Answer me.
Are you listening?
You like it, don't you?
You're getting stiff.
Why?
Does it feel good?
Does it feel good when you're in pain?
You're reacting a lot.
You're a pervert.
Lick my finger.
Lick my finger harder.
Close your mouth more.
Does it feel good when I bite your neck?
Does it feel good?
Touch me.
You're getting stiffer.
Why?
What do you want me to do?
You're getting stiff.
I'll make you suffer more.
Hold your breath.
Does it hurt?
It feels good, doesn't it?
You like it, don't you?
It's hot.
Don't you want to be pressed again?
Are you happy?
Lick my boobs.
Come here.
You can lick my boobs if you want.
Does it hurt?
I'm listening to you, but I can't hear you.
I can't hear you at all.
I can't hear you.
You're getting stiffer.
Why?
Does it hurt?
You like it, don't you?
Are you happy?
You're happy, aren't you?
Is it really painful?
No, I'm sorry.
I don't think so.
Does it feel good?
I'm asking you if it feels good.
It feels good.
Why are you doing it on your own?
Does it hurt?
Is it impossible?
I think you can do it.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it feels good.
Then make me feel good, too.
Okay.
I'll have you lick here again.
I'll do it.
Okay.
Put more pressure on your face.
More.
Can't you lick it properly?
I'm sorry.
You can't do that at all.
You have to put more pressure on your face to lick it.
I'm sorry.
Is it painful?
Come on.
I'll make it more painful.
You like this, don't you?
I'm sorry.
Are you at your limit?
No, I'm not.
I don't think so.
Come on.
Put more pressure on your face.
Is it painful?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
If you have something to say, say it.
You can still lick it, can't you?
I can't stop yet.
Are you at your limit?
You licked it longer than before.
What? Do you want me to do it again?
I'll make it more pleasant.
Come on.
I'll start from the bottom of your head.
I'll start from here.
It's easy for you to lick it, isn't it?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Move your head more.
Let me do it again.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Use your fingers.
It's going to be painful soon, isn't it?
Are you listening?
It's painful.
It's painful, isn't it?
That's right.
Move your fingers properly.
To the back.
If you do it properly, I'll make you feel better.
I'll make you feel better.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to feel better.
How can I make you feel better?
Why don't you say anything?
I want you to touch me with your hands.
I want you to lick me.
Do you want me to lick you?
Yes.
You licked me a lot, so I'll lick you in return.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Did you spit out something?
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Who said you could do it?
I'm sorry.
What do you want me to do?
Do you want me to do it?
I want you to do it.
Yes.
I want to feel better.
Please do it properly.
Let me do it.
I'll do it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Say it louder.
Electric shock
dark
Why does it feel so weird?
You like it painful, don't you?
Yes, it's painful and feels good.
Feels good?
Look, this neck is also tightened.
Why did you make it so hard here?
I'm sorry. It feels good.
Why did you get excited?
It's painful, but it feels good.
You like it, don't you?
Yes.
It's painful, isn't it?
Get up.
Look.
I'm going to massage your upper and lower body.
It feels good.
You have a scary face.
Why are you so excited?
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Why didn't you say yes?
I'm sorry.
You let it out on your own.
I let it out on my own.
Look.
Look at me.
More.
Sasaki, come here.
Look.
Nishiyama, come here.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
You can do it, right?
I can do it.
Relax.
It feels good.
Next, do it from behind.
I can do it.
I can do it, right?
More.
Harder.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
It hurts.
How is it?
My back hurts.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
Do it again.
What?
The first one.
The one you did.
It feels good.
It felt good.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
I'm tired.
It's hot.
I'm going home.
Please take care of me.
Get home safely.
Do you understand?
Yes.
See you.
I'm tired.
I haven't finished my work yet.
Even if I get home soon, I have to take care of my boss.
I have to do that.
It's going to take a while.
Is Kana there?
Really?
I wanted to go there.
I know.
I don't like it.
But, Kana is so cute.
I'm going to finish my work and go there.
I'll do it again.
Thank you for your hard work.
Where is Shion?
He'll be here soon.
You were on the phone, weren't you?
Who is Kana?
There is a pretty girl.
Let's sit down.
Thank you.
You were slacking off, weren't you?
I'm sorry.
I was slacking off.
Are you reflecting on yourself?
Yes, I am.
Why don't you look at me?
I'm sorry.
Who are you apologizing to?
Nagano.
Are you really apologizing to me?
Yes, I am.
Then, apologize to me.
I'm sorry, Nagano.
What are you apologizing for?
I'm apologizing for slacking off at work.
You are, aren't you?
Are you reflecting on yourself?
Yes, I am.
If you are reflecting on yourself, show me your attitude.
What?
My attitude?
Show me your usual attitude.
Are you going to do it now?
I have to do it now, don't I?
You know that, don't you?
Hey.
I'm really irritated today.
I'm really irritated.
Why don't you study?
I'm really sorry.
You know that, don't you?
This is what happens when you don't reflect on yourself.
Does it hurt?
What?
You know that, don't you?
It's much more painful to have a subordinate who doesn't listen to you.
Do you understand?
I'm really sorry.
Can you study properly?
You're making a fuss.
Don't make a fuss.
Are you really reflecting on yourself?
I'm really sorry.
You're not, are you?
If you were, you wouldn't make a fuss.
Be quiet and reflect on yourself.
Don't make a fuss.
It's painful, isn't it?
It's hot.
Is it painful?
It's painful.
What?
You mean this penis is painful?
No.
You're saying it's painful.
But it's so big.
No, it's not.
It's not?
Why is it not?
What's this?
It's not?
What's different?
I'm sorry.
Are you really reflecting on yourself?
I'm really sorry.
Then you wouldn't make a fuss like this.
What's this?
What?
It's not.
This is...
What?
I'm sorry.
What's this?
I made a fuss.
You made a fuss, didn't you?
I'm really sorry.
You made a fuss without reflecting on yourself, didn't you?
Look at me.
What's wrong?
I made a fuss.
Don't reflect on yourself.
Look at me.
I made a fuss without reflecting on myself.
Is it painful?
Yes.
It's painful.
Is it painful?
Your body is stiff.
I'm sorry.
Are you reflecting on yourself?
I'm reflecting on myself.
I'm sorry.
Why can't you do your job honestly?
I'll do my best.
You always say that.
Yes.
You always say that, but you don't do it, do you?
No.
And you always get angry.
In the end, you make me angry like this.
You always do that, don't you?
Look at me.
You make a fuss again.
What?
Hold on for five seconds.
One.
Two.
Why can't you hold on?
I'm sorry.
It's painful.
I'll hold on.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
You can't hold on, can you?
Why do you make a fuss?
I'm sorry.
It's painful.
I see.
I have to educate you more.
It's hot.
You know what I'm going to do, don't you?
Yes.
I'll hold on for five seconds.
Will you hold on?
Yes.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
You haven't held on for five seconds yet.
I'm sorry.
Did you hold on?
You didn't hold on.
I'm sorry.
Look.
I see.
You don't have to say it.
Hey.
Come here.
Do you know what I'm going to do?
I don't know.
You don't know?
No.
What is this?
This is...
Hey.
It's very hot.
I'm sorry.
I said I'm sorry.
You get used to it as soon as you say it, don't you?
No, I don't think so.
You can't fix it just by saying it, can you?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Every time you say you're sorry, you make it so hard.
Look, it's getting bigger again.
I'm sorry.
You like it when it's hard, don't you?
Is it hard?
It's hard, isn't it?
It's supposed to be hard.
Why can't you do it?
Are you doing it on purpose because you want to be scolded?
No, I'm not.
You're not?
I guess you're not.
Hey.
Look.
Ouch!
Why are you rattling?
Why?
Ouch!
Is it hard?
It's hard.
Ouch!
What's wrong with you?
Come on.
Show me.
Ouch!
Come on, take it off yourself.
You're making me do it.
What are you looking forward to?
You're becoming a woman.
Did you think I'd make fun of you?
You're looking forward to it.
I'm not doing it to make you feel better.
Do you understand?
I don't understand.
Do you really understand?
Really?
This?
This? Do you really understand?
Yes.
Come on.
Ouch!
You've been making me feel good for a long time.
I'm not.
I'm not doing it to make you feel better.
You're not doing it?
Really?
Yes.
Ouch!
Do you want me to kill you?
You're making me do it.
Ouch!
You're not doing it?
No.
You're noisy.
What?
Are you noisy?
You're doing your best.
You're doing a great job.
Your head is floating.
Do you like it so much?
Ouch!
You felt good, so you didn't say anything.
You're doing a great job.
What did you do?
Why are you the only one satisfied?
I'm not doing it anymore.
You know what you're doing, don't you?
I know.
But if someone from the company comes...
They won't come.
Everyone is going home.
You're the only one who can't do it, right?
Ouch!
You're noisy.
Don't make a sound.
What?
I know.
I won't make a sound.
Really?
Ouch!
Why are you resting?
Do it properly.
Ouch!
You're noisy.
Be quiet.
Ouch!
You're noisy.
Why are you more noisy than me?
Ouch!
Did you make a sound again?
Let's do it again.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
I made a sound.
You made a sound right away, didn't you?
Yes.
Lie down here.
I made a sound.
Please make it clean.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for making you suffer.
No, it's not true.
I'm sorry.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
Pew pew pew Pew pew pew
I'm sorry.
I'll be back in an hour.
Again? You just came back.
No, no.
Let's go.
I'll be back in an hour.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'll be back in an hour.
It's hot.
Why do you feel better?
Not yet.
It's hot.
Don't push me.
Can't I?
It's hot.
You surprised me.
I'll give you a massage.
Can you sleep?
Yes, I can.
What is it?
Come on.
Be quiet.
Hurry up.
Okay.
It's hot.
What are you doing?
Are you taking a break?
It's not time to take a break.
Come on.
Let me feel good.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
You're a good boy.
Hurry up.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Why are you making a loud voice?
Come on.
It's hot.
I'm a little better.
You should clean up.