Nice to meet you, I'm Riko.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you.
Is this your first time?
Yes, this is my first time.
Oh, I see.
Thank you.
I'm a little nervous.
Are you nervous?
Yes.
Don't be nervous.
You're so cute.
Thank you.
Let's get started.
Yes.
I'd like you to choose a course.
I've already decided.
Yes.
Did you look at the website?
Yes, I did.
Yes.
120-minute luxury course.
Here it is.
Yes.
I'd like you to sign in first.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I'd like you to take a shower first.
Yes.
After you take a shower,
you can use the towel and hair band.
Oh, I see.
Yes.
I'm waiting for you.
Please put your shoes in there.
Here?
Yes.
Do I have to change?
It's okay.
Okay.
I'm going in.
Thank you.
Here you are.
Can I tell you this?
Hm?
No.
Can I tell you this?
You meant that?
No.
Can I tell you this?
I'm pretty serious about this.
Yes?
Please sit here.
Is the room temperature okay?
Yes, it's fine.
Please sit here.
Yes.
Is the room temperature okay?
Yes, it's fine.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Please tell me if it's too strong.
Is there anything you want me to focus on?
I'll give you a strong massage at first.
My shoulders and waist.
I see.
Is it okay?
Yes.
Is this okay?
I'm so happy to hear that.
Are you less nervous now?
A little bit.
A little bit?
Yes.
I saw you in a photo.
Thank you.
You look more beautiful than I imagined.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you.
You must be very popular.
No, I'm not.
It's only been half a year.
I see.
Yes.
Do you go to this shop sometimes?
Yes, sometimes.
I see.
I go there once a half year.
Did you see me on the Internet?
Yes.
I'm glad to hear that.
Is it too strong?
No, it feels good.
Is it okay?
Yes.
Can I lean on you?
Thank you.
Did you exercise today?
No, I didn't.
You didn't?
Your body is warm.
I thought you exercised.
It's hot today, isn't it?
Yes.
It's humid.
It's easy to sweat.
I took a shower.
Yes.
Is your room okay now?
Yes, it is.
Is it okay here?
Thank you.
Are you still a beginner?
I'm not sure.
I think I'm still a beginner.
I think so, too.
Did you work as a sales assistant?
Yes, I did.
You don't work as a sales assistant now.
I don't work as a sales assistant now.
How old are you?
I'm 25 years old.
I can't see your age.
I'm happy to hear that.
You're still young.
Thank you.
Can I ask you how old you are?
Yes, you can.
I'm 35 years old.
Really?
Yes.
I can't see your age.
I'm sure you sweat a lot.
Just a little.
Okay.
Your skin is damaged.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you.
My lower back hurts.
Here?
Can I press harder?
Yes.
Like this?
Does it hurt?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Do you do this at work?
Do you often sit down?
Yes.
I see.
I always sit down in front of my computer.
I feel like I'm stiff when I notice it.
Your back gets tired when you sit down.
I'm going to massage your upper body.
Okay.
Excuse me.
How do you feel?
I feel calm.
Really?
A little more.
Is this your first time using powder?
Yes.
I see.
It's unusual.
I think so.
You use oil a lot, don't you?
Yes.
Does it tickle?
It feels good.
Why did you quit your job?
I used to bear the pain of my boss' sexual harassment.
But I quit it a few years ago.
It's not a serious story.
I see.
Yes.
You are cute and beautiful.
No, I'm not.
What did your boss do to you?
At first, I was sexually harassed by my boyfriend.
I see.
He asked me when I had sex with my boyfriend.
Did he?
Yes.
I see.
He asked me if I had sex with my boyfriend alone.
It's confusing.
That's right.
At first.
But you couldn't tell him?
I couldn't tell him.
You are kind.
I see.
Do you get angry?
Me?
I don't get angry easily.
In the end, he touched my body.
He touched my buttocks.
Did he?
Yes, he did.
Yes.
Excuse me.
I see.
It was the right thing to do.
Yes, it was.
I'm going back to the classroom.
Yes.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Does it tickle?
Yes.
Why?
I thought it was cute because it was moving.
It's not that bad.
It's not.
Excuse me.
Your skin is white.
Really?
Yes.
I don't get tanned easily.
Really?
Do you have a lot of customers?
What kind of customers do you have?
I have a wide range of customers.
I don't know.
But I have a lot of kind people.
What kind of people do you have?
I haven't thought about it.
What kind of people do I have?
I have a lot of people who are easy to get tanned.
I have a lot of people who talk to me like my brother.
I have a lot of quiet people.
You like quiet people.
I like quiet people.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
It's different from oil.
It's ticklish, isn't it?
It's the best.
I'm glad to hear that.
Are you okay?
It's ticklish.
My back is moving.
I'm sorry.
Please tell me.
It feels good.
It tickles and feels good, doesn't it?
That's right.
I've had a girl do it for me.
It's ticklish.
It tickles.
It tickles and feels good, doesn't it?
That's right.
It tickles.
I have a strange feeling.
Your buttocks are beautiful.
Thank you.
I'm not praised.
Really?
I want to show off.
I think so, too.
Excuse me.
Can you make me look like a four-leaf clover?
Four-leaf clover?
Yes.
Like this?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I see.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I was taking a video.
My mouth hurts.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
How do you feel?
Is it hard?
No.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
Please turn your head.
Turn my head?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Your shoulders are tense.
Yes.
I'm nervous.
Your skin is really smooth.
Thank you.
Do you do anything?
No.
Do you work out?
Really?
Your chest is firm.
You can touch my chest.
Excuse me.
I like it.
Around here?
Is it ticklish?
I like it.
Do you feel good?
It's bright.
What?
Is it here?
How about here?
Is it ticklish?
I'm sorry.
I'll massage your legs.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Do you feel relaxed?
I'm glad.
You look at my face.
I'm popular, aren't I?
No, I'm not.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No, I don't.
Really?
Yes.
Do you answer like that?
No, I don't.
But I'm often told that.
I'm often told that.
No, I don't.
How about here?
Can I touch here?
I'm sorry.
Is your body okay?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
It's been a while since I've been touched by a woman.
Your body?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm going out.
Can you get on?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Isn't it heavy?
I'm okay.
Is it hard to do?
No, I'm okay.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's getting hotter and hotter.
I'm sorry. I'm sweating.
It's okay.
I don't hate it.
You're kind.
You're so cute.
It's a little hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
I'll massage your shoulders, too.
Okay.
Isn't it heavy?
I'm sorry. I'm okay.
Are you okay?
Is it hot?
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I'm sweating.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Is it hard to get up?
It's okay.
I'll do my best.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I'm sweating.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
I'm sweating.
It's hot.
Sleeve, please.
Sleeve.
It's hot.
Let me cover your eyes.
I don't know why, but I think it's because I'm not used to it yet.
I'm sorry. I'm sweating.
I'm sorry.
It's hard.
Does it hurt?
I'm sorry.
Is it okay?
It feels good.
I'm sorry I can't stand it.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
Can I do this?
Can you see this?
How is this?
Does it feel good?
It's my first time.
It feels good.
How is this?
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I can't do this.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Can I get up?
Can I get up now?
I don't want to go out.
I can't take the pressure anymore.
If you can't take the pressure,
What can I do?
Can you make it cry?
Is that OK?
Yes.
It's OK
...
Are you okay?
Yes.
Do you have time?
Yes, I do.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I'll go away.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Please come here again.
I'll come here again.
Can I have your contact information?
I can't.
I'm sorry.
I'll bring your car.
I'll wait for you.
I'm sorry.
I'm Aoi.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'll check your course.
Okay.
It's a standard course, right?
Yes.
Can I have 25,000 yen first?
Okay.
Here you are.
Thank you.
This course is
You can do it on the bed, too.
Which one do you want?
I don't care.
I'll do it on the bed.
Okay.
I'll prepare for it.
I'll use
powder and oil.
It's a bed, so
oil may be left.
I'll use a towel.
You can relax with powder.
I'll use powder.
Okay.
I'll prepare for it.
Please wait.
Please change your clothes.
Please take a shower.
Okay.
I'll change my clothes.
I'll massage your back.
Excuse me.
How is the pressure?
I'm fine.
Please let me know if it hurts.
Your back is stiff.
I'll get a massage.
Are you tired?
I'll massage your back.
Are you Aoi?
How old are you?
I'm 26 years old.
You're young.
I'm young.
How long have you been working here?
I've been working here for about a year.
Until then, you had another job?
Yes.
What did you do?
I was a shop assistant.
Were you a shop assistant?
Why did you quit your job?
I started because I liked clothes.
My seniors were strict.
I couldn't get used to it.
You were strict.
Yes, I was strict.
Were you bullied?
I was ignored.
That's tough.
It was tough.
I couldn't stand it.
I see.
You don't have a job.
I don't.
I'm a single person.
I'm relieved.
Do you feel good?
I feel warm.
I feel good.
Do you have any other concerns?
I see.
I'll massage your feet.
Okay.
Does it hurt?
By the way,
do you have a boyfriend?
a boyfriend?
Yes.
I don't have one now.
Really?
Yes.
You should have one.
I don't have one.
You don't have one.
Don't you miss him?
Well, I do want to have a job, but I'm busy with work, and I need someone who understands me.
So you need someone who understands you.
Yes.
Do you have any customers?
Customers?
Yes.
I wish I had a good person.
I wish I had someone who would say yes to me.
You are very beautiful, so I want to date you right away.
Really?
Yes.
I'm happy.
How is your lower body?
My lower body is getting warmer.
Yes, it's getting warmer and your blood circulation is getting better.
Thank you.
I'm going to apply powder.
Yes, please.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Is this how you apply powder?
Yes, it is.
Have you ever used it?
No, it's my first time.
It feels good.
Yes, it feels good.
Thank you.
For example, if I ask you to go to a restaurant with me, will you go with me?
If we get along well.
I want to be close to a beautiful person like you.
I hope so.
I don't have a girlfriend yet.
Is that so?
I see.
You are very kind, so I thought you might have a girlfriend.
Not at all.
Is that so?
How long have you been in a relationship?
Well, when I quit my previous job, we broke up.
It's been more than a year.
So you haven't had a girlfriend for a year.
Is that so?
Yes.
I see.
You must be lonely without a girlfriend.
I do feel lonely.
I see.
The next one is the fourth.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Is it hot?
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It's a little embarrassing.
It's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
Are you relaxed now?
Yes.
I see.
Are you still nervous?
It's my first time to do this.
Yes.
I'm still a little nervous.
I see.
Please don't be nervous.
Okay.
Next, I'll do the face-up.
I see.
It was a little hard.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Does it hurt?
Not at all. It feels good.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Yes.
You are good at this.
Thank you. I'm happy.
It feels good.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
The area of my panties is...
It's small.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Is it heavy?
Not at all.
Are you okay?
I think it's lighter.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's a little hot.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
It's hard.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Is it heavy?
Not at all.
It's okay even if it's heavy.
Thank you.
I'm glad you put your shoulders together.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Is this okay?
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
What?
This is...
I'm sorry.
I can't stand it anymore.
I don't know what to do.
This feels good.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's so good.
I can't stop eating.
Are you okay?
It's so good, isn't it?
It's so good.
I can't stop eating.
It feels good.
I'll go.
Oh, it doesn't feel good!
I can't do this
Ah, so gross.
Ah, gross.
Ah, no.
Gross.
Go in, go in.
Go in!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, wait a minute...
Wait a minute...
Ah, no, no, no...
Ah, I'm going to fall...
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
feel!
Ah, ah, ah, oh, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah feel
!
No, no, no.
I feel sick.
I'm going to go to the toilet.
I'm going to the toilet.
I'm sorry.
Ah! I feel so horny!
Uh...
Oh, runny nose.
I'm coughing and panting so much.
Wait a minute.
Let's go.
1 hour later
I hope it will be helpful
Oh, it feels good!
Let's go, let's go!
Ah, it feels good!
Let's go! Let's go!
You still have time, don't you?
Can I do it again?
I have a lot of time.
I feel sick.
Can you tell me your contact number?
My contact number?
Please call me again.
Okay.
Nice to meet you. I'm Saki.
Thank you for coming today.
Nice to meet you, too.
You look much cuter on the website.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll explain the course.
The course is 60 minutes, 90 minutes, 120 minutes, and 150 minutes.
Which one would you like to take today?
Can I take the standard course for 90 minutes?
The standard course?
Yes.
I see.
The options are hot gel, hydrogen peroxide, oil, wipe, and powder.
Which one would you like to take?
I'll take the powder course.
Okay.
The standard course for 90 minutes and the powder course will be 15,000 yen in total.
Please wait a moment.
Okay.
I'll take this.
Thank you.
Okay.
Are you going to do the surgery on the bed or on the sofa?
Can I do it on the bed?
On the bed?
Okay.
I'll prepare a towel and other things.
I'll give you the paper shorts.
Okay.
Please take a shower and change into the paper shorts.
Please wait a moment.
Okay.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Okay.
I'm going to loosen your whole body.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Your body is tense.
Really?
Yes.
You're very good at it.
I'm happy.
Is it long?
No.
I've just started it.
Really?
Yes.
I'm studying every day.
By the way, how long have you been doing it?
I've been doing it for about half a year.
Is that so?
Yes.
You're very good at it.
I'm happy.
What did you do before you started it?
I've been doing it for about a year.
You're still young, aren't you?
Yes.
I'm still 25 years old.
So, you went to university, did it, and quit it.
That's right.
I see.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I just have a pain here.
I see.
Was it hard?
It was very hard.
I had a lot to learn.
I see.
Yes.
It must be hard.
Is it okay to ask you why you quit it?
Yes.
To be honest, I had an affair with my boss.
Really?
Is that so?
Yes.
My boss found out about it.
So, I had a hard time.
I see.
Did your wife find out about it and sue you?
No, she didn't.
But, I had a hard time, too.
I see.
Yes.
Really?
But, I'm doing massage now.
You're very good at it, so you'll get a job.
I'm glad to hear that.
Your boss told you that you're cute, didn't he?
My boss?
Yes.
He told you that you have an affair with him.
I thought it was good, too.
But, I couldn't refuse him.
You like men older than you, don't you?
I like men older than me.
I see.
How old were you when you got a job?
Well, I was about 20 years old.
Oh, I see.
Yes.
But, he was very tolerant and nice.
I see.
So, I thought I couldn't refuse him.
I think it's good.
Yes.
Do you think so?
I like men older than me.
Really?
Yes.
What if you get attracted to me?
Don't worry.
Do you have a boyfriend now?
No, I don't.
Oh, really?
Yes.
But, my wife found out about it.
So, I can't get close to him.
I see.
Your wife found out about it.
Yes.
I'm lonely.
Do you have a boyfriend now?
No, I don't.
Oh, really?
Yes.
I think you can get close to him soon.
But, he is a strange man.
I think so.
I hope so.
But, I can't get close to him.
Do you want him?
Yes, I do.
Sometimes, I feel lonely.
Do you feel lonely?
How do you feel?
When I'm busy with work, I feel lonely.
But, as I get older, I have more friends who have children.
I see.
So, when I hear such stories, I feel good.
I want a partner.
You are a lonely person.
Yes, I am.
Didn't you feel lonely when you were working?
Well, I didn't have a chance to talk to such a man.
I had a chance to talk to such a man.
But, I didn't have a chance to talk to such a man.
Did you feel lonely?
Yes, I did.
I felt embarrassed.
I see.
I'm going to apply powder.
Okay.
Do you like powder?
Yes, I do.
I see.
Have you ever applied powder?
No, I haven't.
But, when I work in this industry, I learn how to apply powder.
Then, people tell me that it feels good.
I want a partner.
That's good, too.
I want a partner, too.
I admire you.
We massage each other.
I see.
Do we get along well?
We get along well.
What?
I'm going to massage you.
Okay.
I see.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
You have beautiful skin.
Thank you.
Your skin is soft and smooth.
Really?
I'm embarrassed.
Your skin is smooth.
Don't people tell you that?
I think so.
I think so, too.
I see.
Didn't you feel uncomfortable while doing this job?
Did I feel uncomfortable?
Yes.
I don't think so.
Many people are kind to me.
Excuse me.
Okay.
Do you often get a massage like this?
Yes, I do.
I see.
Do you do any sports?
No, I don't.
I see.
Do you have any problems?
You have great muscles.
Thank you.
I was wondering if you had any problems.
Can you raise your hips?
Okay.
Can you raise your hips a little more?
Thank you.
I'm going to massage your scapula.
Okay.
Can I ask you a strange question?
What is it?
You cheated on me a while ago, didn't you?
Yes.
You said you liked older men.
I heard older men have better techniques than younger men.
I see.
I'd like to ask you how you felt about that.
Well, I did feel that older men have better techniques than younger men.
Oh, really?
It's embarrassing to talk about it.
I see.
I got a lot of advice from older men.
I liked that kind of advice.
I see.
I couldn't get away from them.
Oh, really?
You look popular.
No, I'm not.
Really?
I think you're going to be invited to the following competition.
Do I?
You look lovely.
Embarrassing.
Will they say something?
They might say something like that.
Shall we go now?
Yes.
I see.
Don't you get that kind of invitation?
Well, sometimes I do.
I see.
Can you turn around?
Yes.
I see.
Excuse me.
Yes.
I can't turn around.
I'm sorry.
I see.
Do all of you get this kind of invitation?
Yes.
Many people do.
I see.
Excuse me.
Yes.
I see.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Many people get this kind of invitation.
What do you do in such a case?
I just hang it.
I see.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Not at all.
Actually...
Actually what?
Nothing.
I see.
Excuse me.
Yes.
I see.
Okay.
I'm going to start working on your shoulders.
Excuse me. I'm going to work on your lower back.
Oh, like this?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
What's the matter?
I feel like I'm hitting you.
Oh, really?
I'm sorry. I don't want to do that.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry to ask you this, but...
Yes?
Don't you get tired of it?
Oh, well...
I do get tired of it.
You do, don't you?
Yes.
What do you do when you get tired of it?
Well...
That's embarrassing.
But you're not saying anything.
What?
What's the matter?
It's nothing.
It's nothing?
Oh...
I'm getting a lot of pressure.
Is it bad?
No, it's not.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Can I do it again?
I'm sorry.
I'm like that.
Don't move.
Excuse me.
I was too soft.
It's OK.
I don't know which one to drink.
Please call me again.
Thank you for your appointment.
I'm Misaki.
Nice to meet you.
Is this your first time to come here?
Yes, it is.
It's your first time, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
I thought you were very young.
I've always wanted to come here.
It's rare.
Really?
It's rare for a young person to come here.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't be nervous.
Is it okay to have a 120-minute course plus an appointment?
Yes, it is.
There is an option.
Yes.
You can add powder massage, hot gel and oil.
I heard that powder massage feels good.
Yes, it is.
I'll add that, too.
Okay.
It's 120 minutes and 18,000 yen.
Yes.
It's 20,000 yen for an appointment and a powder massage.
Okay.
Is it okay now?
Yes, it is.
Thank you.
Do you need a receipt?
No, it's okay.
Okay.
I have a request.
I want you to take a shower first and get changed here.
Okay.
Let's get started.
It's hot.
It's done.
Is it okay?
Is this okay?
Yes, it is.
It's quite small.
Can you lie down here?
Yes.
Excuse me.
I'll put a towel on you.
Thank you.
Isn't it cold?
No, it's okay.
I'll open your legs.
Okay.
I'll press lightly.
Doesn't it hurt?
No, it doesn't.
My back stretches.
Does it?
Yes.
It's hard, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I may have exercised too much.
Did you do muscle training?
Yes, I did.
I've been doing it recently.
Your hips are plump.
Really?
Your legs are hard, too.
I think so, too.
Are you standing?
Yes, I am.
Your legs are plump.
Doesn't it hurt?
No, it doesn't.
I'll do the other side.
Okay.
Your left leg is more plump.
Yes, it is.
My left center of gravity is more plump.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Are you still nervous?
Yes, I am.
Your hips are plump.
Yes, they are.
I'll apply powder.
Excuse me.
It's okay.
It's weird, isn't it?
It's powder.
Are you okay with allergies?
Yes, I'm okay.
I have goose bumps.
Excuse me.
I heard that you have goose bumps.
Yes.
Are you okay with tickling?
Yes, I feel good.
Like this?
Yes.
You have a needle in your nose.
Really?
There are many elderly people.
I see.
Do you feel ticklish?
Yes, I feel good.
Yes, I do.
You're holding it in.
Are you holding it in?
I feel good.
I'm holding it in.
I'll apply powder on your hips.
I see.
You're holding it in.
Your hips are amazing.
Is it because you're young?
Is it important?
Your hips are amazing.
It's like a woman's hips.
It's difficult.
Do you feel ticklish?
Yes, I do.
I'll apply powder on your legs.
Excuse me.
I'm going to stretch it out.
Okay.
Doesn't it tickle?
No, not at all.
Have you really never been here?
No, I've never been here.
I've never been here.
You've never been here, have you?
No, I've never been here.
Where did you find out about this place?
I looked it up on the internet.
Oh, I see.
I found out when I first came here.
I see.
So you were looking it up on the internet.
Yes, I was.
Doesn't it tickle?
No, not at all.
Your waist is moving a lot.
Okay.
Can you stick out your butt and make a quadruple?
A quadruple?
Yes.
Is this okay?
Yes, it is.
Stick out your butt like this.
Like this.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Does it tickle?
Yes.
You're not used to it, are you?
It's embarrassing.
Doesn't it tickle?
Yes, it tickles.
It tickles.
This powder has a relaxation effect.
Excuse me.
Is something wrong?
No.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm not used to it.
You're not used to it.
Excuse me.
Is this okay?
Is it too high?
No, it's fine.
Does it hurt?
No, it doesn't.
Does it feel good?
It's a popular menu, so I recommend it.
You're surprised, aren't you?
I'm surprised.
It feels good when I massage around here.
When I apply this powder around here.
Yes.
How is it?
Isn't it too hard?
No, it's fine.
I'm sorry.
Can you face me?
Face you?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm sorry to apply too much powder.
It's okay.
Can you let go of my hand?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to apply powder around here.
Yes.
Can you face me?
The powder looks like this.
You couldn't see it because of the reflection.
Doesn't it smell good?
It smells good.
Doesn't it itch?
No, it doesn't.
It doesn't itch.
This powder is very good for the skin.
Is it?
Yes, it has a beauty effect, and it's very popular.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to apply it.
Doesn't it hurt?
No, it doesn't.
I'm sorry.
You have a lot of muscles.
Do I?
Around here.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
You don't have to worry about my voice.
I'm sorry.
I'm totally fine.
It seems that a lot of people speak out loud.
Yes, that's right.
There are lymph nodes around the collarbone, so it feels good when I do this.
I'm sorry.
My hands are a little dirty.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to apply it.
Please be careful.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to continue.
My hands are a little wet.
Oh, I see.
Is it okay to apply it?
Your hands are cold.
I'm sorry.
I have to apply it around here.
I'm sweating.
Can I apply it on your chest?
Yes.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
Is it okay?
Yes.
Does it hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Your hands are shaking.
I'm sorry.
It happens to everyone.
Please relax.
Yes.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
It's not cold, is it?
Are your hands shaking?
No, it's not.
It happens to everyone.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
How do your ears feel?
They feel good.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I want you to leave. I'm sorry.
I just noticed.
I'm sorry.
I can't wait any longer.
Oh, okay.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't know what to do with myself.
Thank you...
I'm sorry I can't stand it so much.
I'm sorry...
We are so happy.
I can't do it.
I don't think I can do it.
It feels so good.
I can't do it.
It's your second time, but it was so good.
It felt so good.
I felt so good, too.
Really?
But I don't usually do this.
What?
But I want to do it again.
Please come again.
Yes.