Have you ever eaten a bean called pistachio?
You often put it on a fancy coffee, don't you?
Snacks.
Snacks?
Don't you put it on a cake?
It's sold with cashew nuts.
Snack corner.
Do you know?
It's the one you eat when you're hungry.
Really?
If you ask the teacher, you'll know.
I thought pistachio was more delicious.
There's no pistachio.
But pistachio has a flavor, doesn't it?
It's sour.
You're a heavy drinker.
I can drink it.
Alone.
I'm sorry. I'm a little hurt.
No, no, no.
It's better to be told that.
But it's been a while since you got a divorce?
About two years.
Two years?
Isn't there anyone new recently?
Is there anyone?
I haven't told you yet.
I don't know that.
I have a father who contacts me.
I've become a matchmaker.
I see.
Let's move on to the next one.
It's too late.
I've been with you for six years.
I've been with you for three years before I got married.
I'm tired of it.
I think it's amazing.
You've been married for 10 years, haven't you?
It's impossible.
I'm not tired of it, but...
We both want kids.
We have the same opinion on that.
So we've been sticking to it.
I see.
I'm sure you'll have a husband.
That's right.
I should have noticed it in a year.
It's tough.
I envy you because you're still single.
I'm still single.
I'm always on a business trip.
Do you like it?
I like it.
I'm still single.
It's okay.
You don't have to be at home.
You were the happiest when you were single.
You were the happiest.
It's impossible.
It's been a year.
I've been married for a year, but I'm still tired of it.
It's impossible.
I envy you because you're still single.
You two are just fighting.
Listen to me.
Sex is boring.
What should I say?
I don't want to deny it, but...
I want something exciting.
Do you play hard to get?
I don't know what to play hard to get.
I'm lost.
I play hard to get, but I don't know what it is.
I don't know what the right answer is.
You'll be fine when you come back, right?
I'm tired, so I'll be fine.
I'm tired, so I want to sleep.
You're annoying.
Wake me up.
I can't do that.
I'm sleepy, so I'll sleep.
You're spoiled.
I don't want to sleep.
We don't meet because we don't have a community.
We don't meet.
We'll be together for the rest of our lives.
We don't change at all.
I want a man to come here.
Cooking and dancing are popular these days.
That's right.
Is it hard to get in?
Good morning.
Who is it?
We have new students today.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Koji Ito.
I'm an office worker.
I don't have a hobby.
I want to cook.
So, I came here.
Nice to meet you.
Please tell me where the dormitory is.
Please.
Please sit in the chair over there.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Today, I'm going to make Spaghetti Napolitan and Hamburger Steak.
I'm going to make tomato sauce.
That's great.
I'm going to make peppers.
I'm going to make spinach.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
You don't look like you have a girlfriend.
I'm going to prepare vegetables.
I'm going to prepare carrots and onions.
I'm going to prepare milk.
I can only remember this.
I'll explain it later.
Is that so?
I'm sorry.
I'm not good at cooking.
That's right.
Basically, I can only cook.
What's the name of the person below?
Koji.
That's great.
I'm going to make tea.
It has only us, isn't it?
It's Itaho.
It's okay to eat tea.
Itato, this is hard to see.
I can see it.
Please understand.
I can see this better because I'm a teacher.
Can you see it?
I can see it.
You can't see the letters when you put it on.
Ko-chan, are you going to put it on?
How old are you now?
I'm 28 years old.
28? I can't see it.
You look older, don't you?
I can see it.
Why?
Why did you choose this cooking class?
When I introduced myself,
I said I wanted a hobby like cooking.
To be honest, I heard that
it's more popular to be able to cook.
It's true that men who can cook
are very cool.
That's right.
How old are you?
It's not a very cool story,
but I'm about to forget
when I was born.
I can't see it.
Tsukishima-san.
Tsukishima-san, are you listening?
I'm listening.
Are you taking notes?
I usually take notes.
I've made pasta before,
so I take about two teaspoons
for one liter of water.
That's great.
You cook a lot, don't you?
Not at all.
You're a real cook.
Are you a beginner?
No, I'm not.
I'm really a beginner.
Really?
But you want to be popular, don't you?
Do you want to crack an egg?
Don't you want to crack an egg?
Are you okay?
Oh, no.
Be gentle.
That's right.
Like a woman.
Be gentle.
Okay.
Look at this.
The skin came off cleanly.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
You're good.
That's great.
The water looks fresh and delicious.
What's wrong?
No, the egg.
You don't need that much egg.
What?
You're going to crack it like this, aren't you?
That's right.
Don't do that.
You have to be gentle.
Be gentle.
You have a nice muscle.
Are you working on it?
I cracked three eggs.
Did you crack three eggs?
Yes, I did.
Next, let's do onion.
Onion.
I'll peel the onion.
That's enough.
It came off cleanly.
I have to eat it.
Can you peel it?
Please peel it.
Let's peel it together.
You're good.
Please peel it while turning it.
Do you know how far the skin is?
Are you nervous?
There are many women with strong habits.
Are you all right?
You're cooking, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
I'm sure you're a beginner.
I'm going to boil it.
You have short nails.
That's fine.
I'm careful when I cook.
I see.
It's OK to peel it this far, isn't it?
Are you OK?
Please be careful.
What's wrong?
What?
There was an onion.
Is it here?
What?
It fell somewhere.
Onion.
Kitty.
Come here.
Help me.
There are many things to cut here.
Wait a minute.
OK.
I'm going to use a cutting board.
Here you are.
OK.
Put the cutting board here.
Is it clean?
Is your hand all right?
It's dangerous.
Well...
Yes?
I bought fresh carrots this morning.
Fresh carrots?
What do you mean?
It's amazing.
You just finished cutting the carrots, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
But...
I want to eat them.
They look delicious.
Oh, no.
Well...
Why did you speak so loudly?
I didn't say anything.
Did you cut your finger?
No, I didn't.
What's this?
It's amazing.
Why is this here?
What's this?
What's going on?
It's bigger than a zucchini.
Is it a zucchini?
It's bigger than a morning glory zucchini.
It's bigger than a morning glory.
It's amazing.
The egg is amazing, too.
It's big.
Is it L-sized?
It's L-sized.
It's amazing.
I'll cook it deliciously for you.
What do you mean by cooking it deliciously?
What do you mean?
I'm just saying.
You're happy, aren't you?
You know the answer, don't you?
I'm sorry.
You can do it later.
It's full.
It's full here, too.
It's amazing.
What's going on?
If you don't work properly, it won't end in time.
I'm working.
I've already cut a lot.
Let's move on to the next task.
You haven't cut anything yet.
No, I haven't.
I can't cut everything.
The Napolitan spaghetti and hamburger you made today.
Please try various things at home.
Yes.
Please clean up.
We still have some ingredients left.
If you want to be revenged, please work.
It's okay if you work.
Yes.
I'll close this office in an hour.
Please clean up until then.
It's an hour.
Yes.
If there's anything I don't know, I'll be in the office.
Please let me know.
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
We still have some ingredients left, right?
Yes.
Can we use this office for an hour?
Do you always have some ingredients left?
Of course.
It's an important practice.
We learned that it's important to prepare and revenge.
That's right.
Let's do it together.
Yes.
It's amazing.
We can use this office for an hour.
It's nice.
It's spacious.
Yes.
Can we use this office freely?
We can cook with the remaining ingredients.
Yes.
I see.
Of course.
It's a little itchy, isn't it?
Yes.
I'm happy.
I'm happy because there are so many girls.
We always have the same member.
Yes.
Do you guys have some ingredients left?
We're going to practice.
Why did you take off your apron?
Ko-chan.
I'll tell you about the apron.
What?
Earlier.
You grew up, didn't you?
You all saw it, didn't you?
Yes.
What?
Why?
No.
Did we do something?
We were just peeling vegetables.
I'm sorry.
We still have some washing liquid.
Why?
Show me.
It's amazing.
What is this?
It's a mess.
It's a mess, isn't it?
What are you thinking?
What are you imagining?
I'm happy.
You said you had to work.
Did you think about it?
Yes.
I knew it.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't be so stiff.
I was embarrassed to cry.
You look like you're in pain.
You have a stiff neck.
It's cute.
Do you want to touch it?
It's my favorite apron.
It's the best.
More.
It's amazing.
I like it.
The teacher will come back.
The teacher won't come back.
Mom.
What are you feeling?
You're wearing panties.
What?
It's amazing.
Kou-chan.
Can I just touch it?
A little bit.
Where is your favorite place?
Where?
You can say it.
It's free.
I want to wash it.
What?
More than washing.
You have something to worry about.
You have.
What?
You're smiling.
No.
Don't be shy.
You don't care about washing, do you?
I like that face.
Look.
It's coming.
How is it?
Kou-chan.
Kou-chan, look.
Kashiwagi-san's big butt.
It's rubbing.
It's bigger than before.
It's true.
I can see it.
Panties are coming out.
It's coming out.
It's showing its face.
No.
Panties are showing its eyes.
It's painful.
It's amazing.
What are you going to do?
Can I touch it?
You can touch it.
No.
You're good at peeling.
Really?
I'm called a genius of peeling.
Kou-chan.
Excuse me.
It's amazing.
It has a lot of skin.
Look.
It's amazing.
It's smooth.
It's true.
It's amazing.
It's smooth.
It has a lot of meat.
No.
I'll eat it first.
What's wrong?
It's delicious.
It's smooth.
When did you last eat this?
It's been a while, hasn't it?
That's right.
I'm glad.
It's very rich.
It's the best.
Is it delicious?
It's very delicious.
It's good to eat other than Dan.
It's true.
No.
It's noisy, so please add a lot of soup.
What do I do suddenly?
This sound is getting louder and louder.
I'm hot now.
Do I make drinks?
How do you want to do it?
What do you want to do?
She's saying something.
I can't hear her.
She's asking you to lick her.
Oh, wow.
That's mean.
Oh, it's delicious.
I can't help it.
I'll eat it.
Oh, that's mean.
She's licking her.
Are you licking your husband's dick like that?
It's seedless, though.
I can't help it.
But you're going to have a lot of seeds.
She's got a lot of seeds.
She's got a lot of cute seeds.
She's surprised.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's good to be honest.
It's good.
I thought you were throwing away a wooden cup.
Oh, it's cute.
It's been a while since I've seen you.
How do you like it?
It's a cooking class.
That's right.
You're cooking now, aren't you?
Preparation
It's good, isn't it?
Oh, it's delicious.
Oh, it's cute.
Does it feel good?
It's cute.
It feels better when you're honest.
That's right.
Why are you suddenly being attacked?
I feel like I've been defeated.
Oh, did it feel good?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
What's delicious?
It's cute.
It's like this.
What's that reaction?
It's delicious, though.
Not at all.
That's why I'm not interested.
That's right.
I'm sure you are.
When did you do it?
I want to know.
What are you looking at?
How do you do it?
Tell me.
I don't do it at all.
You don't? Really?
When was the last time you did it?
I don't remember.
You don't remember?
It's so strong.
It smells so good.
I hope it's good.
I want you to put it in mine.
No, I'll get it first.
No, I want seeds.
I know you don't have seeds, but if you do, it'll be a problem.
It's okay.
Are you licking it forever?
You want to eat it, don't you?
I'll give you a lot.
Touch it.
You're holding it tight.
You like it, don't you?
I'll do it for you.
This is amazing, too.
It's a lot of stimulation from the tail.
It feels good.
I can't hold it all by myself.
Everyone, help me.
Me, too.
It's so hot.
What's this?
I feel something.
What's wrong?
I can't stop.
Can I stop?
You want me to continue, don't you?
Not yet.
Let me touch you more.
It feels good.
It's cute.
Do you feel better?
Show me more.
Do you want me to teach you more?
I want you to teach me.
That's right.
Let's get along with each other.
What's wrong?
You look so comfortable.
I'm nervous.
It's hot, but are you okay?
That's great.
What is it?
Look, there's chocolate on it.
It's chocolate.
How does it taste?
It's delicious.
It smells so good.
This taste is addictive.
It's overflowing.
It's delicious.
Is it all out?
Not yet.
I have to tie it up for you.
First, I have to clean it up for you.
That's right.
How is it?
It's bright red.
Is it pink?
It's pink.
Please tie it up for me.
Please leave some for me.
It's okay.
There's a lot of chocolate.
I see.
Do you want to give me more?
No?
That's great.
Please leave some for me.
There's a lot left.
It's coming out.
That's true.
There's someone who wants to squeeze it out the most.
Are you okay?
It's amazing.
There's some left.
It's delicious.
It's coming out again.
There's some left.
It's delicious.
It's everyone's favorite, isn't it?
It's the first day, isn't it?
That's right.
You have classes tomorrow, too.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's done.
We'll close in 10 minutes.
What were you doing?
We were making a movie together.
We didn't have time to talk.
Where's Ito?
He said he'd be back soon.
He said he had something to do.
I see.
I'm going to clean up.
Okay.
Thank you for your hard work.
Be sure to come back tomorrow.
Absolutely.
Okay?
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll make you cuter than today.
It's delicious, isn't it?
I wonder if cooking is popular.
I'm sure it's popular.
I'll do my best.
I'm coming in.
Ito.
Did you remember me?
I'm glad you remembered me.
Thank you.
Everyone's gone home.
Is that so?
It's too late.
Do you want to do it again?
I don't know how to do it.
You're studying hard.
That's not true.
How was it earlier?
It's a cooking class, isn't it?
Don't make fun of me.
We all made a noise earlier.
How was it?
It feels good.
You look happy.
To be honest, I was surprised.
Everyone's gone home.
Do you want to do it again?
It's just the two of us.
The teacher is gone.
You don't like that, do you?
I don't mind being listened too much to you pretty women.
I don't mind being listened to you pretty women.
I recently broke up with my husband.
Are you sure?
You have a surprisingly good body, don't you?
No, it's not like that.
Oh, I'm sorry. It tickles.
No?
No, but this is a cooking class.
Well, that's what I'm doing.
It's okay. It's a secret to everyone.
Yeah.
The kiss with Sasaki is very pleasant.
Don't you hate it?
Yes.
Yeah.
You have a lot of boobs.
You want to touch them, don't you?
Touch me.
Yeah.
Wow.
You're so mean.
No, I'm not.
If you move your hips like that...
What?
No.
You don't like it?
No, I don't.
That's good.
Is that so?
You haven't had a girlfriend for a long time, have you?
No, I haven't.
You haven't done that for a long time, have you?
Then, it's the same.
Yeah.
You'll have a lot of girlfriends.
Do you have a lot of girlfriends?
Yeah.
You have a lot of girlfriends.
I have a lot of girlfriends.
Wow.
You have a beautiful skin.
Do I?
Yeah.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
You like it.
Ah.
Your hips are moving again.
Yeah.
Wow.
Because...
I'm so excited.
Hey.
I'll hold your hand.
I'm so excited to be with you.
Does it feel good?
Ah.
Yeah.
You're so cute.
Ah.
Wow.
You're getting bigger.
Yeah.
You're so sexy.
Really?
Yeah.
I'm glad.
Wait a minute.
Where are you touching?
What?
Wow.
Ah.
You're getting bigger.
Wow.
Ah.
Does it feel good?
Yeah.
Ah.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Ah.
Do you like your nipples?
I'm being teased too much.
It's getting weird.
Ah.
That feels good.
I'm getting sick.
Ah.
Hey.
Yes.
Touch my nipples.
Ah.
Do you want to touch me directly?
Yes.
I want to touch you.
Ah.
Hey.
That feels good.
Ah.
That feels good?
Scary.
Ah.
Wow.
How is it?
Ah
Wow
I feel good too
Ah
Wow
Hey, what did you say?
Ah, yes
Ah
I feel good
Wow
It's crazy
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I got carried away.
This side is also moving a little.
Are you okay?
Do you want me to lick you?
I like to be licked here.
My legs are hot.
My chest feels good.
Do you want to feel good?
I want you to lick me more.
Do you like my butt?
I like your breasts, but I also like your butt.
My butt is getting bigger.
Can I lick your butt?
Look at me more.
My butt is getting bigger.
My butt is shaking.
My butt makes me feel good.
It feels good.
I licked you too much.
I feel good.
Really?
I feel like I'm being touched by a man.
Raise your legs.
It feels good.
Do you like my breasts?
I like your breasts.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I want you to lick me more.
Do you like my breasts?
It feels good.
It's gone.
Look at me.
It feels good.
What should I do?
It's gone.
Are you okay to live like this?
You really don't need anyone, do you?
Everyone is going home.
It feels good.
Touch me.
Touch me a lot.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I can't do this.
It feels good.
Let's go.
You like my butt, don't you?
I like it.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
How do you feel?
Does it feel good?
It's the first time I've been touched on my nipples in elementary school.
Is it your first time?
I want you to feel better.
Calm down.
It feels good.
Mr. Sasaki.
I'm going.
I'm going, too.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Did you feel good?
Yes.
What should I do?
You can still do it.
Wait a minute.
Are you sure you can still do it?
I'm still fine.
It's in.
I just took it out.
What?
Is it bad?
No, it's not.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
How about you?
I feel good, too.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
No.
I'm going again.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
You're still fine, aren't you?
Are you still doing it?
I want to do more.
It feels good.
It was good.
Does it feel good?
It hurts.
It's moving.
I understand.
It feels good.
No.
More.
Go.
It feels good.
It's fine.
Let me go.
It feels good.
You're still fine, aren't you?
You're still doing it, aren't you?
Did you just do it?
More.
Move more.
Closer.
It feels good.
Go!
It felt really good.
Me, too.
How was it?
If you don't mind, would you like to go to my house for dinner?
Your husband?
Oh, I see.
He's divorced.
Then, I'd love to.
Really?
I'm glad to hear that.
It feels good.
Mr. Ito.
Yes?
You're still here.
Yes.
Are you studying?
The hamburger I taught you today is well-shaped.
And it was served well, so I took a picture.
You're enthusiastic.
I'm glad you're enjoying it.
I'm having a lot of fun.
I have to go to the office.
Please let me know if you need anything.
Okay.
I'd like to make a dessert.
Let's clean up.
Ko-chan.
Are you studying?
Well...
You're studying hard.
The hamburger looks delicious.
You did a good job.
Did you do your best to make it?
You made it round.
Yes.
It's beautiful.
Ko-chan, are you good at making it?
Is that so?
No, I'm not good at it at all.
Show me.
I'm not good at it at all.
Your hands are thick.
It's warm.
Is that so?
Your fingers are thick, too.
It's time to clean up.
I'm going to tell the teacher that I've finished using it.
Are you going home?
You don't want to go home, do you?
No.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Ko-chan.
You only remember cooking.
You have to learn how to treat girls in the future.
That's right.
What do you think?
This is a cooking class.
Do you want to cook for girls?
No.
I learned how to make hamburgers today.
Is it okay to eat only hamburgers?
What do you mean?
Are you going to be full after eating hamburgers?
No.
You have to take a girl's essence.
Otherwise, you won't be satisfied.
You're right.
Hey.
I'm going to melt.
Are your ears weak?
My ears are weak.
Your ears are weak.
You're cute.
Is this your ear?
Hey.
You're so cute.
Thank you.
I told you to wear an apron that was easy to take off.
That's right.
No.
I only have this apron.
Didn't you buy it?
You can't see it.
If you can't see it, you'll be very sensitive.
Did you know that?
You're twinkling.
You're so cute.
You're very sensitive.
What's wrong with you?
Are you looking forward to it?
I see.
Do you want me to drop it?
You're so kind.
I'll drop it.
You're twinkling.
You're so kind.
I'll tell you what's going on now.
I put a lot of mud on your nipples.
Are you happy?
You feel good, don't you?
You're happy, aren't you?
She's still in the office.
Be quiet.
It's delicious.
You have a lot of mud on your nipples.
You're twinkling.
Do you like to be touched?
I can't feel my legs.
You're so cute.
What's wrong with you?
Don't you feel embarrassed?
You're happy, aren't you?
Do you want to see what I'm doing?
Do you want to see?
Look at this.
Look at this nipple.
You thought it was boring to cook, didn't you?
Be quiet.
If you don't be quiet, the teacher will come.
Are you okay?
You'll be seen.
You can't breathe, can you?
Look at this.
You're so cute.
You have a lot of mud on your nipples.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
It's because of you two.
Because of us?
You're right.
If you keep doing this, you won't be able to breathe.
You're touching your nipples.
I'm sorry.
Are you touching your nipples?
No, it's because of your hands.
You're right in front of me.
Don't you want it?
Are you okay?
Are you okay with this distance?
What do you want to do?
It's like this.
That's great.
It's getting harder and harder.
Are you okay?
You can't run away.
I'm not okay.
One nipple is not enough.
You're greedy.
What do you mean?
You want my nipples, don't you?
You're greedy.
Show me.
Please.
You want to see it, don't you?
Please show me.
Here you are.
Here it is.
Look.
There are four of them.
That's great.
How is it?
How about a big marshmallow?
I don't want to.
You don't want to.
Come here.
I don't want to.
Are you okay with a cloth?
Kou-chan.
I want you to lick my nipples.
My nipples are swollen.
Lick my nipples.
Show me your tongue.
Show me.
That's great.
How is it?
Is it good?
There are nipples over there.
I want to kiss your nipples.
That's great.
That's cute.
Does it feel good?
I don't want to.
You are licking my nipples.
I'm in trouble, too.
I think you are suffering.
What's going on?
Kou-chan.
Why are your nipples swollen?
You look like you're in a good mood.
You smell good.
You don't smell like you're in a good mood today.
Can you tell by the smell?
I can tell.
What kind of nose do you have?
How many nipples do you think you've eaten?
Are you two married?
Don't say that.
Does it feel good?
You thought so, didn't you?
No, I was just studying.
I don't want to.
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
It's delicious, isn't it?
You're wearing such defenseless panties.
Look at this.
It's amazing.
You're wearing such defenseless panties.
It's getting really hot.
You're sweating a lot.
You're soaking wet.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
I want to see it.
Can you show me?
It's amazing.
No, it's not.
What's the difference?
Is it really different?
It's amazing.
You're drooling.
It's cute.
You're drooling, too.
It's amazing.
You're drooling.
You're drooling a lot.
Does it feel good?
Is it delicious?
It's amazing.
It's hard.
You're drooling.
It's cute.
What's wrong?
You're drooling.
It's really bad.
Is it really bad?
I'm drooling, too.
You're drooling.
It's delicious.
What do you think?
It's amazing.
It's embarrassing.
You're drooling.
You're wearing such an embarrassing outfit.
No, it's not.
What's the difference?
Raise your butt.
It's cute.
Where do you want to lick?
Do you want to lick?
It's good.
It's delicious.
You're drooling.
Please lick Tama.
Do you like Tama?
You're drooling.
What's the matter?
You're always in my way.
Please lick me more.
I licked you a lot.
Please lick me the same way.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I don't like the way you lick me.
Please lick me.
You're drooling.
Please lick me properly.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
You're good at using your tongue.
Please lick me more.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
You're dirty.
Please lick me properly.
It feels good.
You're dirty.
Please lick me properly.
It feels good.
You're drooling.
You're drooling again.
It's disgusting.
Please show me your wet nose.
Do you know I'm wet?
Do you know?
It feels good.
Please lick me properly.
You're licking me.
It feels good.
Please lick me more.
You're drooling.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
You're drooling.
You're drooling again.
It feels good.
Please lick me properly.
You're drooling.
It's disgusting.
Look at this.
It's messy.
You're drooling.
It's amazing.
Can I touch you?
It's not fair.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
You're drooling.
It's messy.
It's amazing.
Please touch me.
You're drooling.
You have to lick what you put out by yourself.
Don't you know the word self-sufficiency?
Self-sufficiency.
It's amazing.
Please show me more.
I'm always fine.
I'll lick you.
You want me to eat it, don't you?
I'll eat it.
It's disgusting.
You can't do that.
You're drooling.
It feels good.
It's disgusting.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
What is this?
It's disgusting.
It's amazing.
You're drooling.
It's disgusting.
It feels good.
You're drooling.
It's amazing.
It's getting hot.
I'll take this off, too.
It's amazing.
Touch me more.
It feels good.
You're drooling.
I'll take this off.
It feels good.
I'll wipe your nose.
I can't stop my back.
It's amazing.
I remember when I was a student.
You're drooling.
It feels good.
I'll take this off, too.
You're drooling.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
Look down.
It's amazing.
You're drooling.
Kou-chan, you're so cute.
Oh, you're still so cute.
You're so gentle.
I have to make you beautiful.
Kou-chan.
Let me see you.
Come here.
Help me, Kou-chan.
Come on.
I'm going in.
Oh, you're here.
You're here.
How do you feel?
Wow.
You're in.
Are you happy?
Come on.
Help me, Kou-chan.
How do you feel?
Are you happy?
I'm so happy.
Are you happy, Kou-chan?
How do you feel?
I'm so happy.
Good morning!
Good morning.
I feel sick.
Good morning!
Good morning, Sora.
Good morning.
It's so nice.
Say you wanted to sixteen pounds.
You can have mine.
You can have Sacchan's Circadian published.
It's good for you.
Come to me.
Wow.
So comfortable.
Me too, me too, me too.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Give me a hug.
Son-chan is gone.
Look at me.
Mac-chan too?
Then look at me.
It feels good, doesn't it?
No, no, no. You can't lick me like that.
I'm going too.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
I'm sorry.
You're so mean.
It feels good, doesn't it?
What's wrong?
She's in trouble.
Wow.
You're still in trouble?
I'm still in trouble.
Wow, wow, wow.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
She's gone.
It's hot, isn't it?
It hurts.
Wow, amazing.
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming.
You're amazing.
It's strong.
I'm scared.
You can't do this.
You're trying to make me angry 100%.
I can't stand it.
You can't stand it?
Wow.
Are you still standing like this?
No.
No, you're the best.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're amazing.
You're still in trouble.
I'll put it in.
Wait, wait, wait.
Come on, come on, come on.
What's going on?
What do you think will happen?
Let's cook.
Huh?
Do you think this is a good place?
Yeah.
This is not enough, is it?
You're still standing like this.
I'll put it in.
You're amazing.
It's coming.
It feels good.
You're cheating.
Hey.
You're running away.
You're amazing.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
You're amazing.
Hey, Saki.
Play with Kintama.
No.
You said you like Kintama.
Oh, my.
You like it.
I can have a nap?
Ok.
I'm almost going to the toilet
Would you show me?
OK.
I will show you.
How spectacular.
Oh, no!
You're wet again.
I'm so happy.
Hey, To-chan.
Come here.
Come here, too.
No, you can't.
You'll drop it.
I'm sorry.
Yes, yes.
Hey, from this side, too.
Come on.
Yes.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, no.
It feels so good here.
Give me more.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good here.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Hey, give me more.
More.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good here.
Oh, no.
Oh, it feels so good here.
Oh, my God.
It's okay.
Give me more.
Give it to me.
Please.
Oh, my God.
Do you can also feel a slight burn around urethra oraszifice?
It stops with a stretch as soon as he falls, so keep pushing him as fast as you can.
Oh, my God, it's so dirty.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, I'm so happy.
Oh, I'm going to lick you.
I'm going to lick you. It's a waste of time.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, I feel so good.
You can't do that yet.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, I feel so good.
I'm going to put a coin in the entrance.
It's open.
It's hard.
Hey.
Hey, Koharu.
Yes.
You've been trying to get the coin spirit here.
The spirit you drew out.
I'm scared.
Draw it out.
The spirit.
It's not a spirit.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it feels good.
It's so good.
More, more.
Oh, it feels good.
It feels good.
I'm getting a little bit of a tingle.
It's a little bit of a tingle.
Lick it.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, my God.
Damn it!
Oh.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's a pain.
Oh, it's okay.
My father's gone crazy.
He's been playing by the rules.
You're gonna be dumb.
This is dead easy.
Huh?
Oh, my God.
Go slowly.
Here we go.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's a pain in the ass.
It's so hot.
Really?
Show me.
Look at this.
It's amazing.
It's melting.
I don't like it.
It's amazing.
Hey, Kou-chan.
It's melting.
It's amazing.
It's delicious.
Can you still eat it?
No, I can't.
Really, Kou-chan?
Really?
You can still eat it, right?
Wait a minute, Kou-chan.
I'm so sensitive.
I'm going to clean up.
Wait a minute.
It's closing time.
It's amazing.
I told you so many times.
What did you say?
Kou-chan.
Let's get along well.
I'm looking forward to your new sperm.
Okay?
I can't get my sperm.
Hello, Kashiwagi-san.
What are you doing here?
I thought I'd go home.
You're going home?
Yes.
By any chance...
Yes?
Did you do something with Takeshima-san and Takeshita-san?
No, I didn't.
You smell like them.
Do you know them?
I know them.
Can you come here?
Kashiwagi-san.
What are you talking about?
By the way,
this is a hotel, isn't it?
Yes, it's a hotel.
Well...
It's an important story.
What is it?
Well...
I want Ito-kun's life and death.
What do you mean?
I don't understand.
I want Ito-kun's baby.
But you're married, aren't you?
I don't know if you're listening.
My husband is a seedless.
I can't have a baby.
I've been trying for 10 years.
When I saw that there were so many babies,
I was very moved.
I know.
No, no, no, no.
Um...
But...
It's weird, isn't it?
What's weird?
Well...
Because I'm the wife?
No, that's not what I meant.
If you're saying marriage is wrong,
why did you marry Takeshita Tsukishima?
Well...
That's what you're saying, isn't it?
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to force you to do it.
You didn't mean to force me to do it?
Yes, I did.
You didn't mean to force me to do it, did you?
You used to be so nice to me.
You listen to me right away, don't you?
No, I don't.
Hey, your nose is getting hard.
No, I'm just trying to calm down.
That's how you blame a woman.
No, that's not what I mean.
You don't resist anymore, do you?
It's okay. It's your fault.
You're going to get a lot of pimples.
Your nose is getting so hard.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
If you apologize, your nose will break.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to do it?
Are you okay?
Are you really okay?
It's easy to get a pimple.
I'm sorry.
I can't calm down.
That's amazing.
Your nose is getting so hard.
It feels so good.
It's good for your body.
I'll squeeze it out for you.
I'm sorry.
You came into my room because you wanted to be popular, didn't you?
Yes.
You can be popular.
You're getting so wet.
You're so wet.
I'm sorry.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
You're so wet.
I'm sorry.
Even if I squeeze it out, you'll still be fine, right?
As I said.
How is it?
It feels so good.
It was so fluffy.
How many times did you squeeze it out? Tell me.
I don't remember.
You don't remember?
Three or four times.
That much?
Then I'll squeeze it out more.
I'm sorry.
But it's a shame that everyone's bath is over.
It's really big.
Everyone was so wet.
How is it?
It's so good.
It's so wet.
When we first met, you squeezed it out like this, right?
It's so good.
It brings back memories.
It's really piling up.
Do you understand that?
It's a lie that I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
Let me see.
Is this it?
It's so good.
You're soaked, too.
I imagined that I could get into this bath.
I have to make it slippery so that it can reach the back of the ear.
It's so good.
More, more.
It's so wet.
It's so good.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Let me see.
More.
Do you want more?
Let's get into the bath.
Into the bath?
Yes.
How is it?
It's wet.
You've been waiting, haven't you?
Yes.
It's wet.
I can't do it.
Please open a lot.
It doesn't make sense if I can't reach the back of the ear.
It feels good.
It's wet.
How is it?
It feels good.
You can't take it out yet.
If you take it out many times today, the seeds will be thin.
I have to take good care of each one.
Look.
It feels good.
It's wet.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's wet.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'm glad.
I can feel that this person feels good.
It's easy to have a baby.
Really?
Yes.
I have to feel good.
I can't do it.
I have to raise my hips.
If I move it so much, it will go away.
Don't move it.
It's stuck.
How is it?
It's like a real baby.
Is it full?
If it's full, put it in my belly.
Give it to me.
I want it.
It's going.
Put it in my belly.
I can't do it.
I have to put it in my belly.
You know it's not enough, don't you?
I did it once.
What?
Are you going to do it again?
It's decided.
You're still so energetic.
If you rub it like this, you'll get better soon.
It's so good.
It's going to overflow.
Oh, my God.
It's so good.
It's low.
You're so cool.
I can't do it.
I can't do it either.
Are you going to sleep again?
But you're still so energetic.
It's going.
Oh, my God.
I'm so happy.
You're giving me a lot.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Hey, get a lot in there.
What's in there?
It's in there.
It's going to get in there anyway.
Are you still doing it?
Oh, my God.
If you put it in, it'll get harder.
Come on, push it in more.
Oh, my God.
I feel so good.
I can't do it anymore.
No, it's not empty yet.
Oh, my God.
If they put out three or four times, I'll put out five or more.
Otherwise, I won't forgive you.
Oh, my God.
I feel so good.
Give me more.
No, more.
No, don't take a break.
I can't get out.
Oh, my God.
It spilled again.
Why does it spill?
Oh, my God.
What?
It's getting bigger.
Oh, my God.
I feel so good.
I've put out three or four times.
Oh, my God.
I can't get out.
Look at this.
I have to put it in my water bottle.
Oh, my God.
It's not enough yet.
It's not enough yet?
No.
Oh, my God.
Where are you motivated?
I'm so happy.
You're so intense.
I'm getting excited.
It's okay.
You're a soldier. You can't complain.
Oh, my God. I feel so good.
Oh, my God.
It's low.
Put it back in there.
I'm going to fall asleep.
Oh, my God.
It's moving a lot.
I can't breathe.
Put it back in there.
You're a soldier.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. I feel so good.
It's low.
Oh, my God.
It hurts.
I can't breathe.
Oh, my God.
Until the last moment...
Can I do this?
Oh, my God.
I feel so good.
I can't do this.
It's low.
Oh, my God.
You promised me, didn't you?
Until the last moment...
I'll do my best until the end.
Oh, my God.
I can't do this.
I'm nervous.
My jaw is broken.
I feel so good.
Oh, my God.
I can't do this.
I feel like I'm going crazy.
Hey.
Yes.
You're still so independent.
You're still going to do it, aren't you?
No, well...
You can do it for a long time.
You're amazing.
No, I'm not.
You put so much pressure on me.
You're not going to do it anymore, are you?
Hey.
Oh, my God.
I got in so easily.
I feel like I'm going crazy.
Oh, my God.
Let me go.
I can't do this.
Wait a minute.
I want more.
Oh, my God.
I feel like I'm going crazy.
I can't do this.
Oh, my God.
You have to take a shower.
No, I can't.
Please.
Please, one last time.
Give me one more chance.
Please.
Oh, my God.
Please, one last time.
Give me one more chance.
Really, one last time.
I won't say it anymore.
Please, one last time.
This is the last time.
Oh, my God.
Please, one last time.
I slept a lot.
Oh, my God.
You slept so well.
Did I?
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I'll do my best, from now on.
Oh, my God.
Hey.
Are you alright?