Has anyone shown up?
It seems that Tan is beingLAUGHS
Who?
I see
I'm surprised
The other day at the gym ...
Great job, JYP!
Here's your musical kit.
That's what Amiri-san, who is right in front of me, brought with her.
What are you talking about?
What do you think it is?
It's good to say that, so I'm busy before the exam.
That's right.
Then, I'll introduce you to the person in charge.
I'll remarry.
I'll introduce you to the person in charge.
This is Amiri-chan.
Nice to meet you. I'm Amiri.
Are you Hie-kun's child?
That's right.
It doesn't look like you at all.
Is that so?
You look like a young man.
I used to feel like that, too.
Really?
I was cooler.
You're lying.
You're so handsome.
Amiri-chan is from Tokyo.
You're supposed to come here.
I went to Tokyo for the first time.
You're destined.
I'm embarrassed.
Kouki, I'm going to live my own life.
I'm not trying to have fun.
Amiri-chan came to me.
I'm surprised.
You're my mother.
Nice to meet you.
Say hello to me.
This is my first meeting.
I thought it was a lie.
I didn't know where my father was attracted to.
And this is a rural area.
Why did you come to Tokyo?
I thought it was a fraud.
But a week later.
Amiri-chan started to live.
I'm home.
I'm wearing silly clothes.
Why are you wearing your cool back?
And your underwear is so erotic.
Day one
I'm getting older and older,
so every day I'm in a bind.
I was doing muscle training.
You were a little heavy, weren't you?
I do it sometimes.
Let me touch you.
I'm sorry.
You are amazing.
You look better when you are quiet.
Oh, you were calling me.
I couldn't take a bath.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
10 minutes later.
It looks delicious.
I'll enjoy it.
Everything looks delicious.
Eat this.
I'll eat this.
Is it delicious?
It's delicious.
Eat this.
You are good at eating.
Really?
It's delicious.
You always eat deliciously.
So, I'm getting tired.
I want to eat more and more.
Really?
I'll do my best.
And...
I used too much food.
Really?
How much is it?
200,000 yen.
Is it too much?
If you don't mind, I'll eat more.
It's okay.
You can eat as much as you want.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'll eat this.
Eat this.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
See you in the next video.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
See you in the next video.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
See you in the next video.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
See you in the next video.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
See you in the next video.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
See you in the next video.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
See you in the next video.
Bye bye.
Good morning.
Did you sleep?
You are awake.
Why are you snoring?
You are
Wait, wait, wait.
Where do you want me to put it?
No, wait.
No, no, no.
Where should I put it?
Wait, wait, wait.
You shouldn't make too much noise.
Or you'll wake Hii-kun up.
Oh, wow.
You're so hard.
How about here?
Does it feel good here?
You're more sensitive than Hii-kun.
I want you to be quiet.
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
You're so hard.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Do you want me to put it here?
Wait, wait, wait.
You're so hard.
Open your mouth.
Look at me.
Do you want me to touch your cheek?
Oh, it came out.
Here you are.
It's so soft.
You're so hard.
My hands are shaking.
Do you want to see my butt?
Do you like my butt?
You're so hard.
It's your first time, isn't it?
My legs are getting harder.
You're so hard.
My hands are shaking.
Does it feel good?
Touch my butt.
You're so hard.
It's getting harder.
It feels good.
You're so hard.
It came out.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
You're so hard.
Why is it so hard?
It feels good.
You're so hard.
It came out.
I want you to hold on a little longer.
You're so hard.
Let's celebrate.
I have to go back to my room.
Good night.
You're so hard.
Welcome back.
I woke up too early today.
I was so sleepy yesterday.
You were so brave yesterday.
You were next to me.
I wanted to do it with you.
I want to do it with you.
Can't I?
You're so hard.
It feels good.
I'll give you a kiss.
You're crying.
You're so hard.
Can I look at you?
I don't want to look at you.
You're so hard.
Can I look at you?
You can look at me.
You're so hard.
Can I look at you?
You can look at me.
You're so hard.
Whew
Wow, it's hot
My stomach...
It's so hot.
I'm so glad.
I can't stand it.
Are you glad?
Yes.
I'm glad that I can have a baby.
I'm glad.
Hurry up!
This is so erotic.
I'm so sleepy.
Why are you in there?
It's gross.
You're getting bigger and bigger.
I'm so sleepy.
It's gross.
It hurts.
I'm so sleepy.
I'll do it from the back.
This is so erotic.
I'm so sleepy.
It hurts.
Are you okay?
I'm so sleepy.
I'm okay.
Sex with you was the best.
I'm so sleepy.
How did you feel?
It was intense, wasn't it?
Why are you shy?
You're not honest.
Look at me.
I'm embarrassed.
Why?
You said you were shy.
I'm embarrassed.
Why?
Look at me.
You're still standing up.
You just did it.
You're energetic.
I'm always sexy.
Do you want me to do it again?
Again?
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're amazing.
You just did it.
It still feels good.
It's hot.
You're honest when you feel good.
I'm honest.
Do you want me to do it again?
It's hot.
It's hard.
Do you want me to do it again?
It's hot.
I'm home.
Mom.
What is it?
Did you take a bath?
Yes.
Okay.
I'll take a bath with you.
I'm about to take a bath.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I see.
It hurts.
Does it hurt?
Are you okay?
You were licked.
I'm okay.
But I can't get out of the bath.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it after I get out of the bath.
It feels good.
Do you want to get out of the bath?
Is it hot?
You can get out of the bath.
Can I get out of the bath?
Get out of the bath.
Okay.
It's hot.
Can I get out of the bath?
Okay.
I'm about to get out of the bath.
I'm going to get out of the bath.
You're amazing.
You had a lot of scary things in the bath.
Do you want to get out of the bath?
You're amazing.
I'm sweating a lot.
You're sweating a lot.
I thought it was bad for my father.
I fell into Amiri's trap.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
You're gonna be fine.
I'll do it once again.
Go ahead.
What's wrong?
You're so drunk. Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
Sit down.
I got drunk.
I'll get you some water.
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
Get a hold of yourself.
I'll put the water here.
I fell asleep.
What are you going to do?
I don't want to leave you alone.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Ahh, good!
Ahh, yeah.
I'm gone.
I'm done.
My buttocks…
Ugh, uhh…
Ahh…
Ahh
It's so good that I can't stop eating it.
I can't stop eatening it.
It's so good...
Oh my goodness.
Let's see.
It's hot.
It's okay.
Go to sleep.
I'm hungry.
Did you fall asleep?
I fell asleep.
I'm going to take a bath.
I went to the bathroom, so I made a lot of noise.
Go to sleep.
It's hot.
I'm happy.
I'm in a good mood.
I feel good.
It's hot.
I'm in a good mood.
I'm sweating.
It's hot.
I'm going to go home.
I feel good.
Go, go, go!
It feels good.
It's good, isn't it?
I want to get out of the room.
I want to get out of here.
I want to go to the coffee shop.
It feels good.
I want to go to the toilet.
I want to get out of here.