I'm going to put a sticker on the back of the book.
I just assembled and put it away.
I'll keep you updated on the completed version of this series.
I'm going to make a hole in the middle of the bag so that it doesn't open when I put it in the bag.
When it boils for the first time, add 5g of convenient shortening,
which is suitable for making Larue, and mix.
Once it has boiled thoroughly, put it back to a pot,
bring it to boil, and it's ready.
When you're done coloring, cool it in the fridge
It's well-mayo-like, so it's delicious
Really a great churro
Right.
I'm not comfy with you, am I ?
健康料理
There's better night beer than alcohol because I don't drink alcohol when I go to camp...
He's eating...
Didn't you go to the homeless shelter yet?
Yes.
You have to study properly.
Or your father will scold you again.
I'm not feeling well.
You have a cold?
Do you have any medicine?
I'm fine.
It's not that serious.
I got a call from my father today.
He said he would come home early today.
Thank you for the meal.
Mom, I want a baby.
What?
Thank you for the meal.
You're wearing purple today.
Did he say something?
Thank you for the meal.
Wipe the also-cleaned himself.
Wipe also-clean himself.
Wipe himself for the sake of also-clean.
For those who serve also-clean,
A present of A present of A
A present of A
Hajime-kun, I brought you some laundry.
Hey!
No, no, no!
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait a minute!
No, no, no!
I'm sorry, Hajime-kun!
Wait!
No, no, no!
Hajime-kun!
I'm sorry that I opened the door without knocking.
I didn't expect to have such a relationship with Hajime-kun.
Hajime-kun, I'm sorry that I opened the door without knocking.
Why did you do such a thing?
I'm your mother.
Our blood is not connected.
That's not the problem.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
The first person I loved was my mother.
What?
I want my mother to have a baby.
Today is a good day.
I know.
I love you.
I want to do it again.
I can do it as many times as I want with my mother.
I can't do it anymore.
But your mother is greedy.
Your father is not on a business trip.
I will satisfy your mother.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for your father.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sorry.
You feel good, don't you?
No.
I can't do it anymore.
What?
I love my mother.
I can't do it anymore.
But...
Why?
I can't do it anymore.
You feel good, don't you?
I'm sorry.
I'm not feeling well.
I'm sleeping.
5 more minutes.
No.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it for you.
No.
I'm sorry.
It's over.
What?
More.
No.
I want to make you feel better.
Wait.
No.
You had a lot of blood here.
I had a lot of blood here.
What is this?
Wait.
No.
What?
Your body is the best.
No.
Wait.
It's getting hot.
No.
Wait.
It's hot.
No.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
No.
Stop.
That's it.
I'll stop.
I'm sorry.
I pushed your髪 out.
You promise?
you can't, you can't, you can't.
This is..
I'm going.
Stop!
No!
Hey!
Stop!
I can't do it.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Why?
I can't do it.
Stop it.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm almost done.
No, no, no, no, no.
Let me get out of here.
I can't take it anymore.
I'll make you a cake.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's dangerous.
No, no.
I can't take it anymore.
Please, I beg you!
Please!
I beg you!
Please, please!
Please!
I beg you!
I'll make you a cup of tea.
No!
Don't do that!
Don't!
Stop it!
Damn it!
No, no, no!
Stop it!
No!
Damn it!
Don't do that!
Are you okay?
What should I do?
Hey, what?
What?
Hey!
What are you doing?
I can't do this.
Don't.
Come on, accept it!
Don't!
I didn't know that him wanting to die was something that has no beginning,
I was possessed by him all night long.
One day, I stopped resisting.
I tried to cut the cell phone out of my wrist.
My friend said,
Look here!
You need to visit us today.
Excuse me...
Wait... What are you doing?
It's hot.
I don't have a mother.
What?
I can't do that.
Don't be in a hurry.
I don't have a mother.
You don't have a mother.
I'm not looking good.
I can't open it.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
I'll kiss you.
That's all.
Okay?
I'll kiss you.
I'll put this down for you.
It's hot.
I want you to hug me.
When you feel good, you should go to the bathroom.
It's hot.
I'm home.
You're home early.
Welcome home.
Yes.
I'll be ready soon.
Today's menu is ramen.
You like ramen, don't you?
Yes.
Thank you.
It's hot.
It looks good.
You like it, don't you?
I'll enjoy it.
Do you eat here?
It's good.
You should eat, too.
I'll enjoy it.
It's hot.
What are you doing?
You'll stretch your eyes.
But...
What are you doing?
Hey.
Don't you eat ramen?
It's hot.
Don't you eat it?
You can eat it.
What?
Don't you eat it?
Hey.
It's hot.
It's embarrassing.
It's fun.
It's hot.
I can't see you at all.
What's wrong?
Don't do that.
What?
Are you okay?
I'm scared.
Is this it?
I think I can get it.
You can't do that.
I think I got it.
I got it.
Look over there.
Your ears are red.
I'm okay.
This?
I think I can get it.
No?
You didn't get it.
Did you get it?
What?
Did you want to get it?
No?
Your nose is running.
Are you okay?
I like this gap.
What?
I love you.
It's over.
What?
Do you want to kiss me?
Do you want to lie down?
Do you like me?
I'm sorry.
Do you want to kiss me?
I'm going to sleep.
You've had a lot of hair.
Did you feel good?
You're back earlier than I thought.
Be careful.
It's 17 o'clock tomorrow.
Shall we pick you up at the airport?
Be careful when you get home.
After a month, my husband finally came back from a business trip.
I was perplexed by the change in my feelings.
I was deeply moved by the change in my feelings.
I'm going to make a hole in the back of the case.
Half a year after my husband returned from his business trip, I gave my stomach a new life.
I'm going to give birth to a healthy baby.