It's been a while since I've been here, so I'm a little nervous.
The normal sound of this room is loud.
A sealed system is installed in this room.
Herman is in charge of the operation room.
Oh, honey. Welcome home.
I'm home.
You're early today.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's going to take a little longer to cook, so take a bath first.
Okay.
I wish I could be a member of the family, even if it's just a little.
My wife recently started a rental girlfriend, which is popular now.
I looked it up on the Internet, and it's about 3,000 yen per month on average.
It's not a strange marriage, it's a healthy job.
I understood that my wife would start it.
But I didn't care what my wife's part-time job was like.
I love my wife very much.
I don't talk much about work.
I wasn't worried because she hadn't changed at all.
It's lonely.
Yes, it's lonely.
It's a little hot.
Yes.
You're Mamoru, right?
Are you a student?
I'm going to college.
I just started recently, and I don't know much about it, but there are college students.
I don't know.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No.
I've never had one.
I see.
That's unexpected.
I don't want to fail my first date when I have a girlfriend.
So I want to practice.
I see.
But if you like it, you don't have to worry about failure.
It's almost time.
Yes.
Thank you for today.
I had fun.
Me, too.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Hey.
Yes?
Are you going to work tomorrow?
Yes.
You're going to Osaka, right?
I see.
I'm going to work in the evening.
That's nice.
I wanted to go to Osaka, too.
It's your job.
I see.
My wife seems to be seeing a young man recently.
My wife didn't say anything.
I didn't hear anything, either.
I see.
This is for you.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
You look nervous.
Are you nervous?
Well...
You're Mamoru's girlfriend now.
Isn't it strange to be nervous?
Is that so?
As I said before, I'm married.
I'm not his girlfriend.
Then, you're his rental wife.
Rental wife?
That's nice.
Thank you for this.
You're welcome.
By the way, you said you've never had a girlfriend.
Does that mean it's your first time coming to a girl's house?
That's right.
I see.
Why did you invite me to your room today?
I don't know.
I don't know why.
Maybe it's my mood.
Your mood?
I don't know.
Besides, if it's just a date outside, you won't understand.
You said you wanted to practice at home.
I see.
You said you wanted to see me again.
I think you're that kind of person.
I see.
Thank you.
By the way, how do you feel about coming to a girl's room for the first time?
It smells good.
Really?
Thank you.
By the way, is it okay?
I'm here even though my husband is here.
That's okay.
My husband isn't here during the day.
And he's been on a business trip since yesterday, so he won't be here until tomorrow.
I see.
Well...
What's wrong?
I don't know if I should ask you this, but...
This is about practice.
If I had a girlfriend and went to her room for the first time, what should I do?
Well...
I don't know.
You're funny.
What?
I don't know.
But...
I think it doesn't matter what we do.
We can watch a movie, watch TV together, and eat together.
I think it's fun to be with someone you like no matter what we do.
By the way, what do you want to do?
Well...
That's...
I want to hold hands...
I want to flirt with her...
I want to do that.
Well...
I don't know what to do if she hates me.
I don't know when to do that.
I see.
I don't think I can practice that.
What did I say?
It's okay.
What?
But you can't say it.
You can't flirt with her.
Okay.
Hold my hand.
How is it?
It's soft and warm.
It's great.
You're cute.
Can I hug you?
I want to practice that.
What?
No.
Okay.
You can't kiss me.
I'm sorry, but...
That's it.
If you do that, she'll hate you.
Well...
You can wear a mask.
It's a practice.
Okay.
How is it?
You can't practice that.
Do you want to do that?
Okay.
What's wrong?
Your face is red.
I'm sorry.
You can't do that.
I can't stand it.
Then...
I'll do it with my hands.
Please bear with me.
You can't do that.
I'm sorry.
Are you sure?
But...
It's hard here.
I'm sorry.
You're getting bigger.
I'm getting bigger.
Aren't you happy?
I'm happy.
Then...
Are you okay?
I'm embarrassed.
It's okay.
You wanted to do it, didn't you?
You have a scar.
I'll wipe it off.
Please wear a lot.
It's getting harder and harder, isn't it?
Yes.
It's twitching.
It's getting harder and harder, isn't it?
Yes.
Mamoru-kun.
Is this the first time you've been touched by a woman?
Yes.
You're cute.
Mamoru-kun.
Please feel better.
Yes.
It's hard, isn't it?
Do you want to take this off, too?
Yes.
Are you embarrassed?
Wow.
You don't have to be so embarrassed.
Please feel much better.
Yes.
Wow, Mamoru-kun.
It's warm.
Mamoru-kun.
Where do you feel good?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Do you feel good here?
Yes.
Do you feel better here?
I'll give you a lot of this today.
Yes.
Wow.
Mamoru-kun.
It smells good here.
What?
It's delicious.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Wow.
Mamoru-kun.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
I'm glad.
Wow.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Wow.
It's getting harder and harder.
Yes.
Wow.
I'll give you a kiss.
Yes.
Wow.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Wow.
Do you like this?
Yes.
Wow.
You slept a lot, didn't you?
Yes.
Did you feel good?
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I was wondering what you were making.
I'm making a potato.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
It's dangerous, isn't it?
Wait a minute.
I'm not waiting.
I'm cooking now.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry for being late.
It's fine.
Is the food good?
Yes.
You are a good wife.
What are you going to do?
Are you okay because you haven't gone home yet?
Yes.
Just a little more.
Then, do you want to practice a little more?
What? Are you sure?
Yes.
But,
I'll only do it once.
Okay.
Do you understand?
I'll teach you gently.
Yes.
Is it good?
Follow me.
Here?
Yes.
Ah.
Do you feel your ears?
Yes.
Is it good?
It's good.
Ah.
Do you feel your nipples?
It feels a little good.
Ah.
It's tingling.
Are you embarrassed because you're not used to it?
Ah.
A little.
This is a practice, isn't it?
It's a practice.
Are you nervous?
Yes.
You have to get used to it when you have a new girlfriend.
Ah.
If you have a girlfriend, I'll tell you that it feels good here.
Yes.
Do you like your left nipple?
Ah.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Ah.
It's cute.
It's sensitive here.
Ah.
It's bigger.
Your nipples are easy to understand.
Is that so?
Yes.
I'll put it out here, too.
Ah.
Did you feel something down here?
Yes.
Ah.
You reacted.
Yes.
I did.
It's cute.
It's warm.
Yes.
Ah.
Your skin is smooth.
Hey.
You're a virgin.
Have you ever seen a girl's boobs or nipples in person?
No.
Do you want to see?
Yes.
Then, let me see.
Ah.
I'll try.
This is a practice.
Ah.
Let me see.
Like this?
Ah.
It's beautiful.
What are you holding back?
Ah.
You want to see more, don't you?
Yes.
Can you take off your underwear?
Underwear?
Well.
There's a hook here.
Yes.
Take it off.
Like this?
Yes.
Ah.
You wanted to see it, didn't you?
Yes.
Ah.
How do you feel?
It's the first time to see boobs.
It's amazing.
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
Ah.
Can you touch it?
Yes.
Ah.
Like this?
I'm going to touch it gently.
Gently?
Yes.
Like this?
If a girl licks her nipples, she'll be happy.
Nipples?
Yes.
Can you lick it?
Ah.
It's amazing.
Your nipples are standing up.
Yes.
I got excited when I looked at your nipples.
Ah.
I'm going to lick it.
Yes.
Ah.
Ah, it feels good.
Like this.
Can you kiss me?
Kiss?
Like a baby.
Ah.
It feels good.
You're good at it.
Ah.
It feels good.
Can you lick it?
Yes.
Ah.
Ah, it feels good.
Roll it a lot.
Like this?
Yes.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah.
I'm thirsty.
Namoru-kun.
You're drooling.
Ah.
When a woman gets excited, she drools.
Is that so?
Yes.
Ah.
Let me see.
Can you look at me directly?
Ah, yes.
Then, let me see.
Yes.
Ah.
Namoru-kun.
You can look at me.
Ah.
Can you see me?
Yes.
Ah.
It's very sexy.
You're wet, aren't you?
Yes.
Is it disgusting?
It's very disgusting.
Ah.
You can touch me.
Yes.
Ah.
Touch me.
This is the clitoris.
Ah.
Yes.
Wow.
It's wet here.
Can I put it on you?
Yes.
It feels good.
Here.
It's slimy.
Yes.
Ah.
It feels good.
Is it good?
Yes.
Ah.
This is where you put pee.
Pee goes in here.
Yes.
You can put your finger in here.
Ah.
You're spitting.
It feels good.
More up.
Yes.
Ah.
Is it good?
It feels good.
Ah.
While licking like this.
Do it gently.
Like this.
Yes.
Ah.
Make it more pleasant.
Like this.
Ah.
It feels good.
While licking like this.
Yes.
Like this.
Ah.
It feels good.
More.
Ah.
Put a lot of saliva on it.
Well.
Ah.
Wow.
Oh.
Ah.
Wow.
I feel better.
Ah.
Don't look at me like that.
It's your own, isn't it?
You did a good job.
I'll give it back to you.
You've been in pain for a while, haven't you?
Yes.
Mamoru-kun.
You're sweating a lot.
Mamoru-kun, you're sweating so much.
Yes.
You're sweating a lot.
I'll give you a drink.
Yes.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Mamoru-kun, it's delicious.
It's delicious.
Yes.
Mamoru-kun.
Do you want to put it in soon?
Yes, I want to put it in.
Then...
Let's put it in once.
Yes.
I put it in.
Just once.
Yes.
Do you know where to put it?
Is it here?
Yes.
It's here.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's the first time I've felt like this.
It's hot.
To the back.
It feels good.
Do it more.
Do it more comfortably.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'll put it on you.
Yes.
Are you ready?
I'll put it in.
Yes.
It feels good.
Do you want me to put it in your bag?
I'll put it in here.
It feels good.
I'll put it in your bag.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's harder than before.
It's hard.
You slept a lot.
Your sperm came out a lot.
Yes.
It came out.
You graduated from the virginity.
Yes.
Thank you.
Did you feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
I'll wipe it for you.
Yes.
I felt good, too.
I'll wipe it for you.
Can I kiss you?
Can I?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's getting bigger.
Yes.
Let me see.
Does it feel hot?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
I feel the gas.
Ah, it feels so good.
Now, lay down.
Good morning.
It's morning.
Wake up.
I fell asleep.
Yes.
How long did you sleep?
I fell asleep.
Yes.
We spent the night together.
But,
were you happy with me?
I'm an old lady,
and I'm older than you.
You didn't want to practice with me, did you?
No, I didn't.
I'm glad I met you.
I would have proposed to you if I wasn't married.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
You practiced a lot, so you can be my girlfriend, right?
Yes.
Are you going home?
I see.
You must be lonely.
Then,
hold me one last time.
Hold me.
I'm your rental wife,
so you can do whatever you want.
Yes.
It's hot.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah,
oh, ah, ste to
for
you without
That hurts!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Oh
Hmm
Ah ah
l
I'm going to eat it all.
Huh?
Can I?
No, you can't.
Ouch!
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Ah, it feels good.
Ouch!
Ah, it's hot.
Ah, it feels good.
It feels good.
Ouch!
Ah, it feels good.
Ah.
Ah, it's hot.
It feels good.
Ouch!
You're still fine, aren't you?
Yes.
Can you do more?
Ah.
Ah, it's hot.
Yes.
Ah.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah.
Ah, it hurts.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Ah, it hurts.
It hurts.
Ah.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah.
Ah, it hurts.
It hurts.
Ah.
Aaahh!!
It feels great!!
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
hhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
"[Icause the inaMUDI".
AHHHHHH
ah ah ah
ah ah
ah
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
AH
OH MY GOD
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Oh
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
well
Yeah
No
Ah, it hurts.
I'm tired...
Cheers.
It feels good!
I did it! I did it! I did it!
Ah, it feels so good!
Let's eat!
It was so hard.
What was hard?
I bought meat buns as a souvenir.
Really?
I'll eat it later.
Yay! I'm so happy!
By the way, how's your part-time job?
What do you mean?
I'm just wondering what you're doing.
It's normal. I'm just doing healthy things.
What do you mean by normal?
Well, I eat, go on dates, and do a lot of things.
A lot of things?
I'm curious.
You're curious?
Yeah.
I'm a rental wife, so I'm only going to be your wife at that time.
Of course, we're a couple, so we'll have sex.
I won't put a condom on you, and we'll be good friends.
What?
What would you do if I said that?