Will you eat the shit?
What has happened has happened.
So, did you sleep again?
Because I have nothing to do.
Well, the weather is good too.
I’m a bitch in my field, eat?
Oh yeah then.
It was a hot summer vacation for Iris.
I have been back to this home in Tonga for a long time.
Oh, Oh, you have come here.
What a good shit.
Today is the field over.
It is hot today, so take a break.
When you have a break, don’t borrow it again.
Oh, and so on.
Yes to.
And, for a while, all of them have grown bigger.
Oh yes yes.
Are you college student now?
Yes to.
Oh, and so on.
Once in Tokyo, I went on a lot of things.
Working in Tokyo?
Yes, in any case.
Have you decided?
No, it is not determined.
You don’t have to get to Tokyo.
You can follow me to our field.
No to that.
Why is this house broken?
It is hot and I will die.
No need for cooler.
This is the best wind to come in.
But it is too hot.
What about?
Mr Taro and Mr Taro.
Yes, thank you very much.
Oh, you, if you did not, you were here.
Oh, my friend, Mr. Taro and this day.
Hi to you.
Remember, I used to play in the river, with insects, and with them.
Was it so?
Why do you remember?
No, it was a long time ago, remember.
Yes, so go slowly.
This is Mr. Taro, this one we picked up in our field.
Eat if you want.
I always apologize.
It looks delicious.
See also.
It looks so delicious.
Okay, the snack is also delicious.
Yes to Yes.
Okay is?
It tastes.
Tastefully
Very sweet.
Long time ago at home for summer vacation.
All around the field.
No games and no shops in this country.
I hope there is such a wonderful meeting.
How is it? good?
Go home and even eat a lot.
If my mother had said I would have eaten something better.
My dad is delicious.
Tomorrow is better, cooking.
What are you doing tomorrow?
What they are doing, nothing in particular.
I go to the pharmacy tomorrow, so I can go with you.
The pharmacy takes about an hour.
Oh well, it is delicious.
You can stay home and sleep, but we can go with you.
Okay, I’m slow at home.
I am not there, so if I am hungry I want to cook something.
Yes I understood.
Hi Mr. Taro, Mr. Taro
Find it.
I’m sorry, sorry, I woke up.
What about Taro?
I am going to the pharmacy and have something to do.
How long will he come back?
I am your father’s relaxing home.
I hope to come back in the evening.
Mr. Taro said he would have lunch with me.
You have forgotten.
It was so.
Forgetting to be parents.
So, fuck me, what about me?
I will make something.
Oh, but I am sorry.
No, it is a belly bite.
Wait a little.
Oh yes yes
How is it delicious?
Yes, it is very tasty.
I haven’t made friends, but okay.
I think it will be okay, I think I will eat somewhere.
Why are you a student? – Why are you a student?
Yes to.
That’s what happened, the boy was so good at that time.
Did you say you came from Tokyo?
Yes is
How long are you here?
I am not thinking especially.
I hope to slow down a little.
Tokyo is great, I admire it.
Yes, but it is also good air.
The food is delicious.
Yes, but there is nothing.
Oh, Mr. Shiva, and so on.
My name? I really don’t remember.
It is a whirl.
Mr to
I was born and raised here.
I admire Tokyo.
It was quick and you are well.
Is there a advantage with her?
Cool and appear cool.
No, it is not there.
Oh yeah, so is it.
What about a aunt like me?
Oh, oh, what are you saying?
Mr. Sly, are you married?
A joke.
But you are late, though.
You should use pineapple.
I use a pineapple.
You can use stick.
You can use pineapple.
Oh, my dear, what are you doing?
In the countryside, nothing is like that, right?
You are silent, right?
No, and all of it.
It feels good.
It is good to be young.
What are you saying?
Sorry to sorry.
Oh a little.
Wait a little.
Why is?
badly is
Do you do this?
Are you bored sleeping here?
I thought he was silent.
So what do you do?
You don’t have hair, right?
Look at the hair.
It is sweating.
Are you sweating?
It is hot.
Is it difficult?
Saigon, you are very hot.
You are hungry.
Mr. Tarrant, the chickler is broken, it’s hot.
It is dirty.
Full of.
Oh is
There is no Taro, so it is okay.
You are sweating a lot.
Emily, what would you do if you knew?
Tom, you will not come back.
He may come back.
I say okay.
He is sweating very much.
A little there.
Oh yeah
He is very standing.
Really young.
well is.
Oh yeah
No to
Please Sir, I too.
It is very crowded.
Please try it.
Try it.
It is fully blurred.
Feel good
I want to do it.
Oh yeah
Elves is
For
A is
Oh is
Oh yeah
Which one to do?
Scrolling down
Tue to
No is
Which one to do.
Which one do.
hardly
No, let’s go on.
Oh is?
More than
Okay, do not go on.
Okay, Taro hasn’t come back yet.
came to
It is awesome.
He is hungry.
Lack of filling.
Hungry here.
bad to say.
I can no longer.
Can I enter?
No, but a little bit.
This is how it is, noise.
No, but not here either.
Oh, oh, a little bit
Oh, a little
by Mr.
It’s in the countryside, there’s no afternoon.
Oh is?
Sorry to sorry.
I did, probably
Oh yeah yeah
Do not say that.
Finally
Stop to stop.
It feels good.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
My stomach hurt.
It is hot, right?
I will take you off.
Very sweaty
Kimchi is
Great this.
It is full of sweat.
Feels good?
No to?
Full of sweat.
What are you doing?
What are you doing now?
Before the other side.
I will rest a little.
It feels good.
Exit once.
Yes
No to
Oh is
by
Go to
Oh is
Nune
Oh yeah
No to
by
Oh...
Oh well...
Eat now...
This is good.
Yuzuki was following him from behind.
Feels good.
Oh yeah yeah
Oh, there is a lot of it.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Oh yeah yeah
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh.
Oh well 😂
Feels good?
It feels good, because of it.
Oh, because of
It feels good.
previously pictures.
Renewed
Moving to
Look back
Heat is
Joshua stands before you.
Feel good
greatly
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Oh awesome.
Oh, I felt good.
Sweat is good.
Tarot, you are not back yet.
Shower together.
well is
Let me go, right.
Yes
Was it good?
It felt good.
Yes to?
Yes
But it was really good.
But
Didn’t you ever be there?
Yes
Is it okay?
really is?
Yes
He is hungry.
Feel good
The best breast.
Feels good?
The hunger is growing.
You are sleeping.
Please go out.
I wanted to get out.
You are sleeping.
You do it?
Okay is?
You are scratching.
The scooter?
Okay to?
Yes well
Then I am
The neighbor’s wife.
With Mr. Todd
I have sex every day.
Sorry to you, Mr. Dudley.
I had to clean it up.
No No No No
Hello, I’m alone and I’m always getting fucked.
Then I go.
Yes, come to me.
You are...
It is good.
It was hot today.
I envy you from summer.
You have a good wife, what?
Now is the time, what about?
No, I am
Talk about your relationship occasionally.
Good, I didn’t care so much.
by
Come ahead, get well.
Oh yeah, I did it.
Stop it...
Still is?
Yes is
Wait how.
Wait what.
I am also making cooking now.
Wait a little.
I will eat.
Looks good.
Eat to Eat.
Mr to
I will help too.
I want a potato potato.
Can you?
Full of stomach.
It is hot.
No to.
sweetly
I have a small face.
It is dirty.
I like good men.
No more fake.
No fake is out.
Oh yeah, while drinking
Is the summer fishing a black way?
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
There, there and not yet.
Today’s video ends here.
Thank you for watching until the end.
I think it will happen again, and then I think it will happen again.
I prefer to go to the station.
I would like to be stronger in front of the station.
Even if it is already here,
really is?
It takes about once at all.
It hurts, really.
I feel healed.
Cut off the electricity.
You are already a weak electricity.
You have become.
No, no, it is so.
Don’t go, go with us.
Can I play?
There must be a barter.
by
Let’s go out again.
With her mother.
Oh, Mr. Shay, did you drink that?
So, get up, I’m going home.
If this happens, you should stay.
Just got a bath and you are a lady.
Take the machine from home.
I stayed.
Because of that, because of that.
Get up.
Looks like tired.
It is a little bad.
What is?
Maybe to wake up.
be quiet.
I was shy and couldn’t sleep.
Yes to?
I want you to touch me a lot.
I am not small.
Oh, my sister, you are getting out.
I have to bite.
Do you want to lick it again?
Lick it out.
Lick it.
No to
Oh yeah
Gathering
Go to come.
Not just a good, but a good day.
Okay, come to me.
Oh well, she is beautiful.
Oh, it is over.
My parents went to the party.
Shit, do I have to go?
I am good.
I don’t like many people very much.
I also disappoint.
It will fit.
My parents are still drinking.
I definitely drink.
I look forward to the celebration every year.
by
But they are both close together.
Good luck, you’re going home tomorrow.
I miss you.
Do not forget about me forever.
of course
And for the last time, once more.
by Mimi
No longer
Figure is
Chinese language
Oh yeah
It feels terrible.
My mom loves me.
I love the chronicle.
Cronic is very loved by me.
You are so loved for me.
They are loved by knowledge and love.
Knowledge is loved.
It feels good.
Feel good
Very interesting
greatly
Feeled
It became messy.
Heat is
It feels good.
It is cold, cold, cold.
I want to eat too.
It smells of sweat.
It smells good.
and AR
Oh oh oh
Oh is
and AR
Oh oh oh
No, no man
Mowgli cannot.
My sister, I also try hard.
Feel badly.
I want to put in.
Put it in.
Feels good.
Feel good, feel good.
Feel good
I am scared!
Feels good!
Take out the hair.
Please take hair out.
Follow the hair.
Feels good!
Levi, can you do more?
Just go away, miss it.
Can I go home?
I have stayed here now, so I am still staying here.
Great effort, it feels good.
It feels good.
I was hungry.
Just a great pain.
Hurt very much.
Feel good
Feels good?
That is
Represents the Leg
The bones...
Oh well...
Pressing to push.
Pressed Pressed
The bones...
Oh yeah
and 2 seconds.
Oh well
Realised  Realised
by
Oh yeah
Oh well
It feels good.
Feel good
is base
Oh oh oh oh oh oh
Oh is
by
Bar is
Oh yeah yeah
Oh yeah
No to
Oh is
greatly
The tea
by
No to
Are you sleeping full of stomach?
I have not slept yet.
Are you still sleeping?
Yes
Next, I want to follow you from behind.
Sleep to
Can I give up?
Oh well fucking.
Sorry to.
Oh, the lie
Oh well fucking.
More of
Feels good
Lie and feel good.
This is good.
Lying and hurt.
Feel good
I still want to know great.
About the previous
Feel good
Oh, and feel...
Oh oh oh oh...
The feeling...
Oh...
Oh well...
Be harsh...
I want to see...
Go to
I want to go too.
Thanks to.
I remembered the last good.
Thanks to me too.
It has been about a year since then.
I remember that summer every day.
No games and no shops in the area.
I had nothing to do.
I am truly grateful to Miss.