Hey, Kou-chan!
Do you want some watermelon?
Hey.
You're up.
I got it from my own field.
It's good.
Thank you.
Do you want some?
How is it?
It's so sweet.
Is it?
The summer break is over.
I'm back to my hometown.
You're back.
It looks so good.
Are you done with the field work?
It's hot today.
Let's take a break.
It's so hot.
Be careful not to catch a fever.
Eat some watermelon.
Thank you.
Kou-chan, you've grown up.
Are you in college now?
You went to Tokyo by yourself.
It's not a big deal.
It's so hot.
Turn on the air conditioner.
The air conditioner?
It's broken.
It's okay, the windthrow system.
It's so hot.
I went to Tokyo.
It's not a big deal.
Hello.
I didn't think you were here.
Ko-chan, who works at Shin-san, is here.
Hello.
You've grown up, haven't you?
Yes.
Grandpa, these are vegetables from my field.
Oh, they look delicious.
Thank you.
Aren't you eating too much?
I'm fine.
You like fruits.
I didn't know that.
It's been a long time since I spent a summer vacation at home.
There were only fields around me.
There was no game center or convenience store.
But there was a reunion after a long time.
How is it?
Is it delicious?
Yes.
There are a lot of side dishes.
You should eat them.
Your mother is happy that you came back.
Yes.
I'm not as good as your mother, but I'm getting better at cooking.
It's delicious.
I'm going to work tomorrow, so take your time.
Okay?
Okay.
Hello.
Shin-chan?
Is he not here?
Ko-chan, did you wake me up?
Where is Shin-chan?
He went to the pharmacy.
I see.
How long will he be back?
If he comes back soon, I'll wait for him.
Okay.
How is it? Is it delicious?
It's delicious.
You said you didn't eat dill.
I made it myself, but it's okay, right?
It's okay.
Thank you.
What is it?
Koichi, you are a college student, right?
Yes.
It's great to be in Tokyo alone.
No, it's not.
How long are you going to stay here?
I'm going to take a break this week.
I see.
Tokyo is nice.
I want to go there.
But it's nice here, too.
I don't think it's bad.
But there's nothing here.
That's true.
Koichi, do you have a girlfriend?
No, I don't.
I see.
You look like one.
No, I don't.
Anyway, you are late.
Yes, I am.
I see.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to offend you.
What were you trying to do?
Well, that's...
You're cute, Koichi.
You can continue.
What?
There's nothing else to do.
But...
Are you going to let me worry about it and end it?
What?
You can do it until the end.
But...
It's not good.
Do you like me a lot?
No, that's...
You like me, don't you?
But...
Why are you getting so big?
Let's hurry up before Shin comes back.
You like me, don't you?
You can touch me.
You wanted to touch me, didn't you?
You like me, don't you?
Does it feel good?
Is it okay to do this?
We're married, aren't we?
There's nothing else to do.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
Is it good?
It's good.
It's hot, so I drew a lot on your face.
Lick me more.
You can't lick me like that.
You're so beautiful.
You're getting bigger.
It stinks.
But it feels good, doesn't it?
It doesn't smell that bad.
It's getting so hard.
You're so beautiful.
You like me, don't you?
Does it feel good?
Look at me.
It's too hot.
Touch me.
It's hot.
The festival was fun, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Did you go to drink?
It's a festival I'm looking forward to every year.
I see.
I think I'll still drink today.
You're going home tomorrow, aren't you?
Yeah.
You'll be lonely.
Let's do it again at the end.
Yeah.
I don't know when I'll see you next time.
Hold me tight.
It's hot.
I don't want to go home, Kana-chan.
Why don't you stay here forever?
She's crying.
She's suffering.
Get out of here.
Oh my god!
Oh my, oh my god!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah, no
Hmmm
Ah...
Wow, you've grown so much.
Mm...
Ah...
Wow...
Mm...
Oh...
Ah...
Mm...
Oh...
Ah...
It's okay.
Look at my chest.
It's hot.
Good morning .
Oh great.
Good morning.
It's bright outside.
Ahhh...
Ahhhhhhhhhhh...
You're still gentle!
You showed how gentle you are!
So, I'll do it one more time!
Ohhhahahahahahahaaaaaa
That was too close!
AH
WAAAAAAAAAA
AAA
AH
AAAA
It hurts so bad
It just keeps going
!
oh
oh oh
It's almost nightmare
Stop
It hurts
Crap
...
.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
あああああ ああああああ あああああああああ
ハハulen
dee
Ahhhh
Ahhh
Ahh, it hurts
Ah don't worry, Ichiban is here
Ah, ahh
Ah, it really hurts
Ah ah ah
Ah
Aaaah
Ah, Ah, Ah, Ahh
Thank you very much.
You've got a lot on your back.
Kou-chan, I want to do it again.
Let's do it again.
Ah...
Please come from the bottom...
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
aaaaaAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
poke
poke poke poke poooook
I lapd
jeil
Holy shit!
What's going on?
Ok, you're ready.
If I'm done with you, oh, you're done.
Ok, you're done.
I can't do it anymore.
Wow, you did it twice.
But I still want to do it.
Can I do it one more time?
Ah, it feels good.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I want to do it more.
One more time.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels good.
Take care of yourself.
Will you come back for the New Year?
I don't know yet.
If you go there, give me a call.
Take care of yourself.
See you.
Bye, Dad.
It's been a while, Dad.
It's been a while since I went back to my hometown.
I had a great time in the countryside without a game center or a convenience store.
I'm really grateful to you, Kaede.
I hope we'll talk when we meet again.
Okay.
Next...
I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to die.