5 minutes later
Yosseym you did it!!
Hey, you eat so much today
I wonder if I was hungry.
I have a lot of side dishes, so please eat a lot.
Thank you for the meal.
What's wrong with him?
After eating, he went back to his room.
Nao, I'm sorry.
He's always been lonely.
I don't hate you.
Yes.
It's not too late to get back together.
And...
And?
He recently got a girlfriend.
So I think he wants to make a phone call with her.
Maybe.
Well, it's called youth.
I see.
It's been almost a month since I married Mr. Yurusuguru.
My husband and I are doing well in our marital life,
but my son, Yusei, is in a difficult time.
So I was worried about communication.
One day, Yusei talked to me.
I'm sorry.
Mom.
Thank you for today.
The sweets were delicious.
I'm glad.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to bother you.
I'm glad you're here.
What's your name?
Nao.
Oh, your name is Nao.
You have the same name as me.
I heard it from my dad.
What did he say?
He said it was his first girlfriend.
That's nice.
I'm going to bed.
You're already a great adult.
Well...
What?
I'm a little embarrassed.
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
Tell me anything.
Well...
I've never had a girlfriend.
I finally had a girlfriend.
But...
I don't know how to communicate with her.
She's not my friend.
I'm worried about that.
I see.
I don't have a girlfriend who I can talk to.
I'm worried about that.
Did you have sex with her?
Are you okay?
What are you talking about?
We haven't had sex for a week.
I see.
Does that mean...
Do you still have feelings for her?
Yes, I do.
I'm embarrassed that I didn't consult with her.
It's my first girlfriend.
I don't want her to hate me.
But I want to have sex with her.
I'm home.
My dad came back.
I'll go back to my room.
Okay. I'll tell you next time.
I'm home.
Welcome back, Yusei.
You're early.
Yes.
What do you want for dinner?
I'll go shopping later.
If you want to eat something, let me know.
Okay.
By the way...
I'm sorry.
I wanted to ask you until the end.
My dad came back.
Did you have sex with her?
Did you kiss her?
No, not yet.
I see.
Well...
I don't know how to make you feel like that.
I see.
Anyway, don't force yourself.
You shouldn't force yourself.
You should look at her gently.
But if you like each other, you'll have sex someday.
Someday...
But...
I'm not confident.
Well...
I'm a virgin.
Then...
Why don't you give up being a virgin?
What?
You're not confident, aren't you?
You shouldn't do that.
But if you practice, you'll be confident.
No, I can't do that.
If my dad finds out...
I'll keep it a secret from him.
We're not related.
I'll teach you how to have sex.
What's wrong?
Is it your first time to kiss?
I'll teach you.
Okay.
You're shaking.
Are you nervous?
Yes.
Are you okay?
Can I let you go?
Mom.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'll keep it a secret from my dad.
Okay.
Show me your tongue.
My tongue?
Is it your first time to kiss?
Does it feel good?
Show me your tongue again.
I'm sorry.
This is how adults kiss.
Like this?
Good.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that to her.
She'll be surprised.
I see.
Be gentle.
I'm sorry.
You're good.
Really?
How do you feel?
I don't know.
Ouch!
You have to be gentle to her.
Look at me.
Ouch!
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Ouch!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You've grown up.
Can I look at you?
You look great.
Let me see.
This is a sensitive area, isn't it?
Girls are the same.
So you have to be gentle.
Can I take off my clothes?
Okay.
Don't stare at me.
It's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
Can I touch you?
Can I?
It's a practice.
Be gentle.
Like this?
Okay.
How do you feel when you touch a girl's chest for the first time?
My feeling?
It's soft.
Can I touch you more?
Okay.
How do you feel?
Well...
Can I touch you?
It's embarrassing.
It's amazing.
Can I touch you?
Okay.
It's shaking.
Can I touch you?
Can I touch your nipples?
My nipples?
Be gentle.
It's easy for you to feel my nipples.
Is that so?
Yes.
Can you lick my nipples?
Okay.
How do you feel?
Here?
Does it feel good?
How do you feel?
Can I touch you?
Have you ever seen a girl's chest?
No, I haven't.
Let me see.
How do you feel?
It's embarrassing.
Can I touch you?
This is called clitoris.
Here?
It's a sensitive part of a woman.
Is that so?
Can I touch you?
Here?
Yes.
Don't stare at me.
Mom.
Why don't you have hair?
I don't like it.
You don't like it?
It's prettier without hair.
I see.
It's easy to lick, isn't it?
Can I lick your nipples?
Yes.
Men touch women's nipples to make them feel good.
Is that so?
Yes.
Can I lick your nipples?
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Like this?
Yes.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Mom.
Is this okay?
Yes.
Is it okay?
It tickles a lot.
Mom, I feel good.
Mom.
It's slimy.
What is this?
It's...
It comes out when a woman feels it.
When a woman feels it?
Yes.
You're amazing.
You're good at it.
Really?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Touch the wet part.
It's wet.
Yes.
There's a hole here, isn't there?
I'll put it in slowly.
Here?
Yes.
I'll put it in slowly.
It's warm.
Is it warm?
Yes.
I'll put it in here.
Here?
Yes.
I'll put it in slowly.
Mom, what's going on?
It's slimy and wet.
It's warm.
It feels good.
It's comfortable.
It's bumpy.
Is it bumpy?
Yes.
What is it?
It sounds disgusting.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Put two fingers in it.
One more.
I'll put it in.
Do it slowly.
It's amazing.
I put it in.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It's bumpy.
It's disgusting.
I'll put it in slowly.
I'll put it in.
Mom.
Yes?
How long do you practice?
Until the end.
Until the end?
You don't know, do you?
No.
It's disgusting.
I'm sweating.
Sweat?
Yes.
It's disgusting.
Mom.
It's dirty.
I'll clean it for you.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'll put it in.
What's wrong?
Don't lick it.
Does it feel good here?
I don't know.
It tickles.
Does it tickle?
If I do that, it'll come out.
Will it come out?
What's wrong?
It tickles.
Wait a minute.
It's amazing.
It looks like it's going to come out.
It tickles.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Lick it more.
It tickles.
Do you want to put it in?
I told you earlier.
I'll put it in here.
Do you understand?
Can I put it in here?
It's okay.
It's a practice.
I see.
No.
Down here.
Here.
You can't do that.
It's hollowed out.
Move it slowly.
Slowly.
Here.
It's warm.
Is it warm?
It's in your stomach.
Does it feel good?
This is sex.
How does it feel to have a girl's penis for the first time?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
You're very good.
I'll put it in here.
Put it in and out slowly.
Here.
Does it feel good?
What's wrong?
Did you go out?
I went out.
It's all right.
It's a good day for you.
Here.
Did you put in a lot?
I'm sorry.
I put it in.
It's all right.
How was it?
It felt good.
This is sex.
I can still do it.
Can you still do it?
I want you to lick me again.
It's a practice.
You're getting bigger again.
You're fine.
Go to bed.
This time it's your mother's turn.
Look at me when you get in.
I'll remember this.
This is the place.
I'll put it in.
I'll remember it slowly.
How is it?
It feels good.
I'll put it in.
Can you see it?
It's wet.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
You can touch me now.
It's cold.
It feels good.
Take your time.
You'll get wet again.
I'll put it in.
You can touch me now.
Do you want me to put it in?
It's still wet.
You can see it.
I'll put it in.
It feels good.
Stop it.
I feel it, too.
Get up.
You can see it better.
It feels good.
Do you want me to put it in?
You can see it better.
It feels good.
I'll put it in.
Rub it.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's cold.
I'll put it in.
It's here, isn't it?
Yes, a little lower.
I'll put it in.
You can move a lot.
Really?
You're improving.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'll put it in.
It feels good.
Wait a minute.
Do you feel like you're going to puke?
It's cold.
You can see it.
It feels good.
It's cold.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll put it in.
It's cold.
Where did it go?
I'm sorry.
It's cold.
It's okay because I'm okay.
You have to wear a rubber band when you're with your girlfriend.
I see.
This is a practice.
It's cold.
You're getting better.
Really?
Did you feel good?
Yes.
Are you confident?
I think so.
You can challenge with this.
I'll do my best.
Congratulations on your virgin graduation.
I see.
Thank you.
It's perfect.
Nao-san, do you have any beer?
Do you have any beer?
I'll bring it.
On that day, while Suguru was taking a bath, Yusei called me to his room.
Yusei told me that he was able to kiss her, but he couldn't touch her breasts a little more.
He said he didn't know how to make a mood, and he didn't know how to bow.
He was so cute.
I decided to teach him a lot of things.
I see.
You've improved a lot, haven't you?
Were you nervous?
Yes.
I don't know.
I think it's important to treat a girl gently with love.
That's what I think.
I think that's the best way.
I see.
I know it's embarrassing, but let's practice with your mom.
Okay.
I'm sorry, mom.
But can I do it again?
Sure.
Okay.
Do what your mom taught you.
Be gentle.
Okay.
You're very good.
Be gentle.
Try to knock your mom down.
When your girlfriend is around, you should turn off the lights.
Okay.
Mom, can I take this off?
Take it off.
Is this your first time to take off your bra?
Yes.
I see.
Wait a minute.
Take your time.
Do you know how to take it off?
Yes.
I looked it up.
Did you?
Did you take it off?
Yes.
Like this?
You're getting better.
Keep it up.
Don't fall in love.
Okay.
Which one is easier to feel?
The right one?
The mouth.
The mouth?
How about the face?
It feels good.
Mom, I'm standing on my nipples.
Because you're good at it.
Really?
Next,
Be gentle.
Touch the top of your panties.
Okay.
Kiss me.
Mom, what's going on with your nipples?
It's getting hot.
Like this?
Yes.
Be gentle.
Take a good look at where it's getting hot.
Okay.
What's going on?
It's getting wet.
Does it feel good?
Because you're really good at it.
Let's take a look at your panties.
Okay.
I knew it.
You don't have any hair.
Because I don't like it.
I see.
Do what I taught you before.
Be gentle.
Okay.
Like this?
I see.
It's getting wet.
Does it feel good?
You're good at it.
You're getting better than before.
You're getting better.
Really?
Yes.
Put your fingers in.
Okay.
Slowly.
You're really good at it.
It's tight.
Is it?
Yes.
Don't do it so fast.
I'm sorry.
Be gentle.
Do it slowly at first.
I'm sorry.
You can lick your mom's face.
Okay.
You're good at it.
Does it feel good?
Mom, if you speak out loud, dad will hear you.
Because it feels good.
I can't stand it.
I feel like I'm going to die.
Dad.
This time, try licking from behind.
Okay.
I can't do it.
I can see it well.
I'm embarrassed.
I can even see the hole in your butt.
I can't do it.
Don't look at me.
I'm embarrassed.
It's very slimy.
It feels good.
Put your fingers in slowly.
I put my fingers in.
Mom.
Can I really do this?
It's okay.
It's a practice.
Like this?
Yes.
You're very good at it.
It's very tight.
You're good at it.
Mom.
I'm more sensitive.
Like this?
Yes.
Like this.
That's right.
It's a practice to get your mom to do it.
I'll do it.
I can't do it.
Mom, I did it.
Did you just do it?
It's tight, isn't it?
It's tight when I do it.
One more time?
Yes.
Put your fingers in again.
Like this?
Yes.
It's a practice to get your mom to do it.
Mom, I can see well because I don't have hair.
You can see well, right?
It's a little embarrassing.
Doesn't it hurt?
No.
It feels good.
That's right.
It's a practice to get your mom to do it.
Let me talk about my mom again.
Yes.
You're doing great.
I'll do it.
I can't do it.
It's hard.
Yes.
You're amazing.
I told my mom twice.
Really?
You've improved a lot.
Thank you.
It felt so good.
Are you confident?
Yes.
Just a little.
That's good.
Will dad come out of the shower?
He's quiet.
Wait a minute.
I'll do it.
Run away once.
Damn it.
Right.
Left.
You can do it.
You did it.
Damn it.
You haven't done it yet.
You're amazing.
You're right.
Here you are.
Both of you really like games.
I bought a lot because I like you.
Eat a lot.
Thank you, mom.
You two are getting along well.
Really?
I don't think so.
What's going on?
Nothing.
I see.
You're going on a business trip again this weekend.
Again?
Suddenly?
Where are you going?
Sendai again.
Are you going to Sendai again?
I think I'll be back in a day or two.
I see.
Don't drink too much again.
I know.
Dad, let's do it again.
Okay.
Here.
Right.
As soon as Suguru left for a business trip, I practiced sex with Yusei again.
I'm sorry.
He's young, so he'll be back in a day or two.
So I'll do it over and over again.
It feels good.
It feels good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Unlike my husband, I've fallen in love with him who comes to me many times.
It's warm.
It's warm, isn't it?
It's good.
I've been having sex all night and it's morning before I knew it.
Hey.
Did you say something to your father?
What do you mean?
I felt like you were feeling something.
I can't say that.
It's warm, isn't it?
By the way, why are you getting so big again?
Because it's morning.
You're fine.
Stop it. It's embarrassing.
By the way, you haven't had sex with your girlfriend yet, have you?
You need to get your soul back.
Even if you feel better, hang in there.
I'll train you to overcome your soul.
It's hot.
I feel better.
What?
It's a wonderful world.
I'm going.
It's hot.
That's not good.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Do it again.
It's not good.
Hang in there.
You're trembling.
It's hot.
It's okay.
Hang in there.
It's hot.
It's hard.
Hang in there.
It's not good.
You need to get your soul back.
Hang in there.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's not good.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, but...
If I do it so fast...
Wait a minute.
It's coming out.
It's not good.
Why not?
Hang in there.
It's okay.
Do it again.
I'm tired in the morning.
I'll do it again, so hang in there.
You're getting better at putting up with it.
Can you do it a little faster?
It's still okay.
Can you do it?
It's okay.
You're getting a lot better at putting up with it.
You have a long lasting effect.
Persistent?
Persistent.
It's persistent.
Eat it.
Mother.
It's disgusting.
It was close.
That's amazing.
It's disgusting.
Are you okay?
Do you want to take it out soon?
You've been through a lot, so you can take it out.
You've been through a lot.
You can take it out.
Really?
She was still aware of the pain...
little by little, she became more sensitive to the pain,
and continued to chew more.
It's coming out.
A lot came out.
Look.
Even if you show it to me.
I'll clean it up for you.
You put out a lot.
Maybe it's because you put up with it.
It's morning.
I put up with it a lot.
Thank you.
Isn't it perfect when you do it with your girlfriend?
Mom, thank you.
I'll do my best.
Did you feel good?
Yeah, I felt really good.
That's good.
Thank you.
How was it?
You had sex with her today, didn't you?
I couldn't.
I gave her back today.
Didn't you have sex?
I'm sorry.
Why?
You practiced a lot, didn't you?
No, I made a mistake.
I noticed it.
What?
I liked her.
You know what?
What I really care about is...
Maybe it's my mom.
What?
Yusuke.
How do you feel?
Do you understand how I feel?
I'm glad.
But...
I want to practice with you again.
Yusuke.
I can't practice anymore.
Why?
My mom likes you, too.
So I'm not practicing anymore.
I'll be serious.
Mom.
This time, I'll practice loving each other.
But...
I'm not practicing anymore.
If you don't do it right, I won't know.
I'm sorry.
Yusuke.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
Ouch.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Eat more.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Look at me.
I'll take it off.
Sit down.
Yusuke.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Ouch.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Sit down.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What are you doing?
Ouch.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Don't touch me.
Ouch.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
Touch me.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
Ouch.
You're wet.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Here?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Did you want to sleep?
I did.
Put your legs up.
Okay.
It's hot.
Put your legs up.
I'll put your legs up.
Are you okay?
Be gentle.
Okay.
Ouch.
Does it feel good?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Look at me.
You have beautiful eyes.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Ouch.
I'm sorry.
Let me do it.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Ouch.
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
Get up.
Ouch.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Come here.
Lie down.
Lie down on my back.
Ouch.
Let me do it.
Wow.
It's overflowing.
Ouch.
Let me do it.
What?
Okay.
Ouch.
Let me do it.
I'm sorry.
Ouch.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Ouch.
Let me do it.
It feels good.
What?
I want to kiss you.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Let me do it.
Here?
Ouch.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Ouch.
Let me do it.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
Ouch.
May I help you?
I want to help you.
What?
Okay.
Let me do it.
Ouch.
I'm going to sleep.
You fell asleep.
Did I fall asleep?
Did I put you in bed again?
I'm going to sleep.
I think I can still sleep.
You're amazing.
You slept a lot today.
I'm so happy.
I want you to move.
Can I touch you?
I'm so happy.
I want you to move.
Does it feel good?
Your stomach and mouth feel good.
I'm so happy.
I'll give you a massage from behind.
From behind?
I'm so happy.
Does it feel good?
Give me your hand.
I'm so happy.
Does it feel good?
Give me your hand.
I'm so happy.
Does it feel good?
Do you like me?
I like you all.
I'm so happy.
Does it feel good?
Mom...
Let's go together
Let's go
Mom...
It felt good
I'm sad
But I can't help it
I'll be with you forever