I'm going to show you how to do it.
First, I'm going to show you how to do it.
Hello, this is Kudo.
Thank you for last time.
Really?
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
I'm glad.
You look happy.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I have to go home and say goodbye.
Are you going home late today?
I have to go to Fukuoka.
I'll go home tomorrow.
Fukuoka? Tomorrow?
I understand.
I'll go home early.
I have to go.
I'll call you again.
It hurts.
Is this your first time?
Yes.
I'll teach you how to do it.
Please stand up.
It's difficult.
Hold here.
Not here.
Be aware of the inside.
Like this.
It's amazing.
Be aware of here.
Look closer.
Thank you.
It's moving.
It's amazing.
You'll understand if you touch it.
Touch?
Touch here.
It's okay.
It's my chest.
It's okay because it's your pectoral muscle.
Really?
It's moving.
How is it?
It's amazing.
It's getting harder.
Be aware of here.
You can train well.
It's easy to understand.
It stretches and shrinks.
It's easy to understand if you touch it.
It's easy to be aware of.
Let's do it.
Hold here.
Be aware of here.
Good.
Yes.
It's good.
More.
Until here.
Return it slowly.
Yes.
It's good.
Again.
Yes.
Keep it here.
Return it slowly.
Yes.
Put strength inside the pectoral muscle.
Don't put your head down.
Put it straight.
Yes.
It's hard.
It's good.
Return it slowly.
Thank you for your training.
Shun-kun, you used to play sports, didn't you?
I used to play baseball.
I see.
I trained a lot at that time.
But my body got smaller as soon as I stopped training.
I see.
How much weight did you have in the past?
How much fat did you have in the past?
In the past?
In the past, I weighed 12 to 13% when I weighed 65kg.
Wow.
You have a strong body.
Do I?
Yes.
But it's okay.
You have muscle memory.
If you train for 3 months, you'll get back to normal.
Really?
Yes.
Let's train together.
Can I?
I want to be as big as I was at that time.
I want to be bigger than I was at that time.
I see.
Let's do it.
But you have to eat well.
I'll eat well.
Before that, you have to work out.
It hurts.
You have to work out.
Do I have to work out?
You have to train hard.
I'll do my best.
Do you want to train with me in the afternoon?
Yes, please.
First, squat.
I'll show you how to do it.
Look at me.
Okay.
Push your hips to the back.
And squat down.
I have to squat down.
Yes.
If you squat down, it'll work on your hips.
So, squat down.
Wow.
Don't lean forward too much.
Okay.
Lean forward a little.
A little?
Yes.
I have to straighten my back.
Yes, straighten your back.
It looks difficult.
Okay.
Let's do it.
It's quite heavy.
Yes, it is.
Yes.
Push your hips to the back.
It's hard.
Squat down a little more.
Really?
Yes.
Like this.
Squat down a little more.
Yes.
Squat down.
Straighten your upper body.
Yes.
Be careful.
It's difficult.
Is it getting harder?
I'll help you.
Okay.
Squat down.
Yes.
Push the ground with your feet.
Good.
A little more.
It's hot.
Yes.
Is it hard?
Yes, it is.
You have to train after it gets hard.
Yes.
Push your hips to the back.
It's getting shallow.
Yes.
You can do it.
My legs.
Be aware of the form when it gets hard.
Be careful.
It's hot.
Yes.
You can do it.
Is it okay?
The last one.
You can do it.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
Yes.
My legs are hot.
It's hot.
It's true.
It's getting hot.
Can I stretch my legs?
Yes.
It hurts.
It's better to stand up.
You can't turn your legs.
Stretch your legs.
It's hot.
It's great.
The hamstring is very tight.
What is ham?
The hamstring is the back muscle of the thigh.
Yes.
It's great.
Be aware of the hamstring.
Yes.
It's great.
It's hot.
The gluteus maximus is very tight.
The gluteus maximus.
The gluteus maximus is the hip muscle.
It's the evidence that you have been squatting.
Yes.
Is it the gluteus maximus?
The gluteus maximus.
I'm sweating.
It's cold.
It's hot.
It's very warm.
It's the evidence that it's effective.
It's great.
It's hard.
What are you doing?
I said it's hot.
It's hot.
It's not good if you have a fever.
Is it correct?
It's correct.
It's all right.
You have a great butt.
Really?
Yes.
If you train more, your butt will be tighter.
Thank you.
It's a little wet.
Are you sweating?
I'm sweating.
Yes.
It's a little wet.
What are you doing?
I'm sweating a lot.
It's hot.
It's all right.
This is also a training.
This is also a training, so it's all right.
You don't have to be embarrassed.
Yes.
Just listen to me.
My butt.
It's all right.
This is also a training.
Yes.
Just listen to me.
You have a great muscle.
It's hard.
What are you doing?
I'm sweating.
It's all right.
You can't squat anymore, can you?
No, I can't.
This time, I'll make you feel good.
What?
You're sweating a lot.
You're very energetic.
Were you like this during the training?
No, it's not like that.
It's because of the touch.
Your muscles are hot, but I'm hot, too.
You can't do that.
This is a training.
It's a training to make you feel good.
You can't do that.
You're sweating a lot.
It's hot.
You have a great muscle.
You're sweating a lot.
I did my best.
It's all right.
This is a training.
You have a great muscle.
You're sweating a lot.
You don't do this training, do you?
I'm weak.
Are you weak?
You just have to train.
You're sweating a lot.
This is a training.
Not yet.
Touch my back, too.
Wow.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Touch my back, too.
This part is big, too.
Wow.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Let's do this training, too.
Okay.
What are you doing?
You are good at this.
You can lick more.
You are good.
You are good at this, too.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
I feel like I'm going to die.
What?
Look at me.
Can I touch you?
Yes.
It's true.
How do you feel?
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Look at me.
It's hot.
It hurts.
Are you okay?
I feel like I'm going to die.
You have cute panties.
It's embarrassing.
Touch my panties.
It's wet, isn't it?
Can I touch your panties?
It's true.
It's hot.
It's wet.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Can I touch your panties?
It hurts.
It's wet.
Can I touch your panties?
Touch my panties.
Directly?
Yes.
It's hard.
Do you know what this is?
It's amazing.
It's red.
Do you know where the hole is?
Yes.
Can you put your finger in it?
It's there.
It feels good.
It's wet.
Can you put your finger in it?
It feels good.
It's heavy.
It's messy.
It feels good.
Don't move.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's messy.
Can I touch your panties?
It's wet.
Are you nervous?
If you do as I say, your muscles will get stronger.
You'll be fine.
Are you sure?
It's training.
I want you to put your finger in it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's hard and hot.
Move your waist.
My legs are tight.
It's okay.
Move your waist.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's not that bad.
It's okay.
Now, sit on the bench.
Okay.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Isn't it hard?
It's training.
It's hard.
It's hot.
It feels good.
My legs are tight.
It's hot.
It's shaking.
Now, sit on the bench.
Can you move?
I'll do my best.
It's hot.
It feels good.
My legs are tight.
It's training.
It's hot.
Move your waist.
Okay.
My legs are shaking.
It's hot.
Move your waist.
My legs are shaking.
It's training.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's hot.
Move your waist.
Don't be sad after this.
Don't be sad?
It's hot.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's hot.
I can't do it.
You can do it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
More.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Protein is good.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Do you want to drink protein?
It's too much.
It's a waste.
You have to drink protein after exercise.
Drink it.
It's hot.
Is it good?
It's good.
You have to drink protein after exercise.
You drank protein.
How do you feel?
Do you feel warm?
I feel warm.
You have a stiff neck.
You don't have enough protein.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It hurts.
You have a stiff stomach.
It's swollen.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to feel good.
Do you want me to feel good?
Yes.
It's hot.
You're drooling.
I'm sorry.
It's good.
It's swollen.
I'll eat this.
It's good.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You have a stiff stomach.
It's hot.
I don't want to do this.
You can't do this.
It's very sensitive.
I don't know.
You can't do this.
Turn your butt this way.
It's embarrassing.
It's okay.
You have a nice butt.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's hot.
You have a nice butt.
It's very sensitive.
It's hot.
You're cute.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
Put your shoulder blades together.
Put your back muscles together.
It's very good.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Does it feel good to touch your neck?
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
You can't do this yet.
It's hot.
It's very hot.
You can't do this yet.
It's hot.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
You have a nice butt.
Do you want to do this?
It's hot.
You can't do this yet.
Turn your head again.
Turn your head this way.
If you hold on a little longer, I'll give you a massage.
This is also a training.
It's hot.
What do you like to do?
I want to drink a lot.
Do you want to drink a lot?
Yes.
How do you feel?
It's hot.
Your neck is swollen.
It's very painful.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Does this feel good?
It's hot.
You have a nice butt.
Does this feel good?
You have to tell me when you're going.
It's hot.
You can't do this anymore.
I drank a lot.
It's hot.
It's not over yet.
Is this also a training?
My waist is moving.
What are you doing?
Is it ticklish?
It's hot.
My body is messed up.
Are you going to the gym tomorrow?
Yes.
Thank you.
See you tomorrow.
Yes.
This is how you train your back.
Touch your back.
That's right.
It's hard.
I feel like I have a crack in my back.
Is that so?
You have a big body.
Thank you.
I'm good at this.
Really?
But I'm happy.
I feel like I have a cramp in my shoulder.
Is that so?
Please give me strength.
Wow.
How is it?
It's hard.
Are you happy?
It's like a melon.
My legs...
Your legs?
It's hard.
It's very hard.
Is it hard?
I feel like I'm a creature.
I feel special.
You say funny things.
I see.
How is your upper body?
I'm scared.
It's hard.
I feel like I'm on Mt. Fuji.
Thank you.
My arms hurt.
It's hard.
You're brave.
I'm brave.
I'm scared.
You're shaking.
That's all for the training.
That's all?
Yes.
It's hard.
Do you hate it?
I love it.
Touch my back.
It feels good.
It's hitting here.
I love it.
It feels good.
It's hitting here.
It's hard.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's hard.
I want to feel good.
Do you want to feel good?
Yes.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I want to sleep.
Take care of yourself.
Yes.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's hard.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's wet.
I'm happy.
It feels good.
Can I touch you more?
Touch me more.
Make me feel good.
It feels good.
There.
Make me feel good.
It hurts.
It's wet.
I'm happy.
It feels good.
Let's lick each other.
It's wet.
It feels good.
It's painful.
It's wet.
It feels good.
It's painful.
It's wet.
Let me.
I don't want to do this anymore.
I don't want to do this.
Give me more.
Make me feel better.
It feels good.
I don't want to do this anymore.
Can I take a break?
Break?
Yes.
But I still have a lot of work to do.
Do you need a break?
You don't need a break, do you?
I don't need a break.
It feels good.
I don't want to do this anymore.
It's okay.
I can't do it.
You can't?
You can still do it, right?
I can't do it.
What should I do?
One, two.
This way.
This way?
It's still not enough.
I want to feel better.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It hurts again.
Hurry up and go.
Ouch.
My stomach hurts like hell.
I want to make it more pleasant.
It's unpleasant.
Ouch!
Are you all right?
It's unpleasant.
I want to make it more pleasant.
Let me go.
It's unpleasant.
Did it come out again?
Yes.
It came out a lot.
It's unpleasant.
I want to do it more.
You want to do it more, right?
Yes.
It's unpleasant.
I want to make it more pleasant.
Do you want to do it more?
It's unpleasant.
I want to do it more.
Can you still do it?
Yes.
I've been doing it a lot.
But it's still unpleasant.
It's unpleasant.
I can't move.
I'm fine.
Do you want me to do it from behind?
Yes.
It's not enough.
It hurts.
It's unpleasant.
He's amazing.
I can't take it anymore.
Please!
Help!
This is amazing.
I'm going to faint.
You can still do it, can't you?
I won't let you say it's over.
But it's too much.
You can still do it.
It feels good.
Give me more.
It's too much.
It hurts.
It's too much again.
It's not refreshing yet.
It's not enough yet.
You can still do it.
I want more.
You can still do it, can't you?
Welcome back.
Oh, you're back.
I was surprised.
I'm sorry I'm late for training.
I'll make dinner right away.
Wait a minute.
Thank you.
Hello.
Thank you for yesterday and today.
I think we had a good conversation.
I'll do my best to live well.
Please continue to support me.
Excuse me.
Who is it?
Today's person.
I have to thank you.
I see.
I hope you get a job soon.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
This is what I promised you.
Thanks to you, I was saved.
Thank you for embracing my wife.
Thank you for watching.