Congratulations on your entry.
I will be taking English classes here today, so welcome.
I want to start my class quickly.
Please open the two pages of the textbook.
Did you open two pages?
The teacher reads first.
He caught a big fish in the river. I saw him at the station yesterday. Give me this ready.
Next, the protection. description of the subjective or target word to complete the meaning of the verb.
In other words, protection is a name or an adjective.
There are many words about employment.
All of them write in notes.
This is a photo of our house.
This man is strong.
We are Lina’s dog.
I found a new dog.
Very reassuring is.
Next is number 6.
Modify the main language and purpose language and protection.
Now the next.
Her eyes are very good.
Can anyone translate this?
Yes to.
So try it quickly.
She loves me very much.
A little different.
It is written ICE.
Her eyes are cute, that is.
It was scary.
Teachers write, so look at them all.
I hate the next class teacher, I think he’s a math teacher.
The teacher is strict, but beautiful, so you will not bother.
So, Tanja, you’re also graduating from here.
I graduated and went to study in Canada.
You know this school, you know this school, you know this school.
Ask your brother.
Next class soon, right? We are moving, so get early.
Oh my sir.
Oh what?
No, it was okay.
Yes to?
Teach him.
Show me your teacher’s feet.
The feet?
I like my teacher’s feet.
Elo
Doctors, I can’t stand it.
What about your father and mother?
I am working, because my brother is working.
Really?
No one comes at this time.
Is it okay?
is OK.
I want to take a picture of this today, can you?
Do you film?
Yes to.
No to?
Okay but.
I want to do a lot of stuff and after it’s done I want to do it.
Oh yeah yeah yeah?
Okay to?
So, my teacher, this is a haircut.
Show the teacher’s feet.
The feet?
I like the teacher’s feet.
and ERO.
I want to see the teacher’s feet.
Is it so?
What happened?
Oh, it is already this way.
I would have missed you if you hadn’t met me lately.
I was missing too.
Show me a lot of faces.
Look at it licking.
Very good feeling.
Feels good?
Teacher, let me oppose you.
Or opposed?
Yes is
It feels good.
Are you more consistent than usual?
Why do you say nothing?
by?
It looks a bit uncomfortable.
Sorry to
Because the teacher is on his feet.
Teacher, touch your feet, don’t make such a joke.
I am very uncomfortable, I want to lick too.
Let me lick.
Take this out.
Look at me, show me out.
Can’t take it?
Oh is?
Okay but
Very beautiful
Lick it.
Mr Coke
Oh yes
That feeling.
I cannot get a site leak.
What is feeling?
Mr is
I want to take the teacher’s stuff.
Do you try?
No to
I want to get a lot of teacher stuff.
Okay then okay.
Let me take you.
The teacher’s cute.
Will you be this child?
It looks awesome.
Do you touch me?
Teacher is messy.
Don’t spread it that way.
Can I lick or touch?
OK is.
Here you will see how you create it.
and now.
My sister.
Oh yeah
Oh is
by 正
by
Well, what about it.
Oh yeah
Oh, so I was rotted.
It feels good.
Drinking is hurt.
Oh oh oh oh oh!by
Oh, so hard.
Oh, it is going to be crazy.
Do you want to drink?
I want you to drink.
Show me a lot of drink.
Teacher, it feels good.
Feels good?
It’s getting bigger, you guys.
If you are so licked, it is bad.
Can you endure?
cannot be
But the teacher cannot endure.
If I can put it in, I too.
Feel good
It feels good here too.
It feels great.
Feel good
Can you see me in here?
See it?
Do you see the teacher?
Great, I see
It feels good.
Look at a little.
Oh is
Show me there.
Tango, do you like this?
I like this.
Oh, is awesome
Feel good
Oh yeah
Oh awesome.
It feels good first.
Yes
I feel good too.
Oh is
Yes
Oh well well.
Feel good
It feels good.
Oh is
Very good feeling.
Feels good?
It hurts.
I want to go out.
Take out a lot.
at the teacher’s feet.
Have a foot?
Yes is
Oh yeah
Oh is
Professor is coming.
Oh yeah
Something was full.
Do not show it to anyone.
I understand sir.
Yes
My first class was just studying.
Good thing, get revenge.
Yes, and goodbye.
and goodbye.
So then I too.
Oh, Sir, do you know me?
He is a student in my class, so I know.
Do you remember your brother?
I was very surprised by the similar.
Are you well in Canada?
Yes, that was good.
Try to enter.
Mr. Tango, this was a pretty bad test.
Yes to Yes.
I think you should get a little bit of a backup, so get a backup today.
The training? yes I know.
After today’s school.
Yes is
Not an example at all.
Sorry to
She has a haircut with her brother, but her school skills are very different.
Sorry, but I don’t want to compare.
What happened?
Nothing is anything.
Try to solve it here.
Yes is
What happened? it seems not to happen.
Oh sorry to.
It’s different between brothers.
Yes to.
I can make sure you.
Mr and Mr.
What happened here?
This is Mr. Professor.
You always watched my feet.
Yes to.
If you want to do this, you should not be so tight, if you want to do it, you should not be so hard, if you want to do it, you should not be so hard, if you want to do it.
You can’t focus on studying, right?
Yes to.
Let them concentrate on studying.
If you are with your brother, the teacher will check.
to check?
You always wanted to do this, right?
Yes is what.
Strengthen this stuff.
Not to no.
You can’t concentrate very much.
Yes is
Why so
Yes
Not to be, right?
Yes is
Feel good
You always watched the teacher’s feet.
Sorry to
It feels awesome.
Feels good?
It feels good.
Very hot.
Sorry to
Still be patient.
Yes is
Seriously?
Yes
It feels great.
Tanja likes her feet.
Sorry to
Great bread.
is here.
What happened?
I feel sorry.
Tango is great.
You are alive, sir.
Put yourself on the teacher’s feet.
Oh, it looks alive.
Yes, I have gone out.
I think I will need more repairs from now on.
I am not going to repair the supermarket today.
Oh yes yes
What are you standing up on?
A little, this is
What did you?
No, Mr. See you
Why are you standing up?
I went in a teacher’s swimsuit.
Did you look at the teacher’s dress?
really is?
Wait a little.
Oh Mr Mr.
Do you like your teacher’s feet?
I like it.
Yes
What is the teacher’s feet?
There are plenty of cupcakes too.
It has become this way.
You will have to walk through the teacher’s feet.
Feels good?
The teacher felt consistent.
You can put the block in and move it.
In my eyes, for my understanding,
Because I had a pocket.
When the words come out,
It is included in your voice.
Yes to.
is delicious?
Then lick it from behind.
Full of stomach.
Oh is
Feels good?
Let me still try.
Do not go yet.
A lot of rubbing.
Yes is
I actually go.
Go to.
Feel good
is sleeping.
So warm and so bad.
Really feel bad.
Feel badly
Everything is doing so.
Mr is
by
still standing up.
Clean up the pearl.
by
I was tired.
Let me refresh a little.
Drink with a full stomach and feel good.
Full of stomach.
Use it with full stomach.
Is this good too?
Ok to.
It is wonderful.
very beautifully
Very big.
Great Spice
cute
A little more.
Teachers don’t do much anymore.
I have to go to the next class.
I can’t stand it, sir.
I want to be a teacher, sir.
I have to talk to you, brother.
Are you great?
is cute?
But not now.
Very, very beautiful
Do you care?
It is crazy.
down there?
OK is.
Do you care?
Just care about?
No to
Oh is
Did you push?
Hold it back!
Just needed that.
Hold it back?
I held it.
Let us go.
The explanation is,
Please support some.
Let us go.
Oh Oh Oh
It hurt a little.
No to.
Next class is here today.
Next time again.
Yes is
Thanks to the teacher.
You knew about your brother.
I found it.
Shit video
in your brother’s room.
Now it is my room.
That room.
Tango is using it.
Yes is
Sorry for last time.
Today about the teacher.
You can like a lot.
Sorry to
Teacher’s feet are delicious.
is delicious?
It is delicious.
Mr is
Lick me too.
No longer trouble.
is delicious?
It is delicious.
Very hard
hard hard hard
No longer is
It is hard already.
You want to come to the fuck.
sadly
well was
Make this more direct.
OK is.
Is it OK?
Sorry to
Stand up feet.
Feel good
Licked a lot.
Tastefully
You want to lick it from behind.
Oh, I will not wait.
Can I get in?
I also wanted the teacher.
Put it in.
Feels good?
The teacher is also very good.
Stay more full.
Teachers are also good.
The stomach is hard.
greatly
It is awesome.
Feels too good.
I still cry.
Sorry to Mr.
Wait a little.
Sorry to
This is a big brown bread, I know.
I was excited.
Are you excited?
Teacher is also very good.
I am hungry.
Oh well feel good.
It feels good, sir.
Sorry to
Good feeling Mr.
You are in the back, you feel great.
Teacher, wait a moment.
I have a chicken tasting taste.
Very delicious.
As usual, while continuing to sleep.
I am thinking what you think.
My stomach hurt.
Feel good
Oh awesome.
Very good feeling.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Great device
Feel good
Enormously good feeling.
It feels good.
It feels good, I went out.
I will be collecting a lot of them from now on, so be ready.
Yes is