Add the fungus fallen from the bowl boiled over high heat and heap it up.
Sliced lobsters and scallops are done!
How to make Gomak Alter Ji aboutllof
Pour hot water into the wok
When the water comes up to the top, close the lid and cook.
They are such sweet fruitful pears...
I will never forget how good they taste.
And I'll always try to make them more beautiful and sweeter as time goes by.
Good morning.
Good morning
Are you going to the store?
Wait a minute
I'm so sleepy
I slept too much yesterday
By the way, where are you going today?
Today?
I think I'm going to Nakajima 3-chome
I'm going to work
I see
Good luck
Are you going to work today?
I have a day off today
This week is the last day of the month
Why are you so late?
I went to work at 7 o'clock
Good morning
You're late
Come on
You're early
I went to work at 7 o'clock
Did you oversleep again?
No
The road was crowded
I see
Did you pack the equipment for the scaffolding in the car?
I went to the office in the morning
I packed it
You're an apprentice
One by one
You have to study at the site
I'm sorry
Let's go
Before that
I'll go to the bathroom
You're early every morning
It's hard
It's okay
What time do you get up?
I get up at 5 o'clock
5 o'clock
It's hard
I'm used to it
No
It's hard
I think you're doing your best
Thank you
What do you do for lunch?
I go to a convenience store
I eat cup noodles
Sometimes
I eat ramen
You can't do that
You have to take care of your nutrition
I see
Your health is the most important
What about your girlfriend?
Do you ask her to make lunch for you?
I don't do that
I see
Then
I'll make lunch for you
But
It's not good for you
It's not like that
I'm sorry
It's okay
I see
I'm sorry
I can't talk to her
What are you doing?
I'm going
See you
Hurry up
A month later
Yes
I'm in front of your house
It's a document
Right?
Yes
Can I ask your wife?
Okay
Excuse me
Yes
What's up?
My senior told me
I'm here to get a document
I see
Thank you
Come in
Excuse me
Hello
Makoto is here
Yes
It's a document
Where is it?
In the living room
The second one?
Yes
I found it
Can I write my name on it?
Okay
I'll try
Can I give it to you?
Okay
Thank you
See you
I'm sorry
It might take some time
I see
Can you take a break?
I'm sorry
It's okay
I woke up at 5am
It's hard to work
I see
If you take a break
for an hour
it might be different
I see
What?
Makoto, what's up?
You're getting hot
What?
Are you excited?
Makoto, you're always
working hard
I'm proud of you
Makoto
You're always
working hard
You're so
passionate
What?
You're getting hotter
Don't come
close to me
because I'm sweating
Why?
I think you're cool
when you're working hard
And
I like this smell
Your nipples are reacting
I didn't
say anything special
but you're
a little pervert
Because
you're wearing panties
but I can see
your nipples
I can see
If I told you that
you would have
reacted again
Do you feel your nipples?
Yes
Do you like being touched like this?
Your nipples are getting
hard
I like people
who feel their nipples
Your reaction is cute
I'm just touching you
but your body is
twitching
I wonder
what's going on
What should I do?
Should I lick you?
But you're
satisfied
with just this
Do you want me to lick you?
Do you feel good?
You don't have to tell me
but I can tell
because you're reacting
I'm just touching you
but your nipples
are twitching
Your panties are getting hard
Do you want me to take them off?
I'll take them off
It's big
Do you know?
It's getting hot
Do you feel good?
You feel much better
This side
Both of your nipples are twitching
You're getting more excited
Do you want me to do this?
You wanted me to do this
so I did
I think you understand
Do you also want to see my boobs?
Then, I'll keep it a secret.
It's a special one.
You'll get more excited when you see my boobs.
Here.
How is it?
You've been worried about it for a long time, haven't you?
Hey, hey.
It feels good to rub your nipples together like this.
Your nipples are so big.
Does it feel so good?
I'll rub your nipples a lot.
Here.
Do you want to rub my butt?
You're greedy.
It's a secret.
Here.
It's a little embarrassing, so don't stare at me.
Just staring at you makes my nipples bigger.
Here.
You're sticking your nipples on my butt.
Wow, your nipples are getting bigger.
You're getting more and more excited.
Wow.
You're rubbing my nipples.
And...
It feels good to rub your nipples together like this, doesn't it?
Do you want to get more excited?
Here.
Do you like to rub my nipples like this?
Or do you like to rub my nipples like this?
You look like you like everything.
Everything feels good.
Wow.
You're rubbing my nipples like this.
I think my head is going to melt.
You have a lot of nipples.
Your nipples are getting bigger.
Your hips are moving a little.
You like it here.
Here.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Have you been holding it in all this time?
You don't have to hold it in.
You're always doing your best.
Don't hold it in now.
If you want to hold it in, you can do it.
I'm going to rub your nipples a lot.
Here.
It feels good, doesn't it?
All right.
Do as much as you want.
Hey.
It's all right.
Hey, Makoto.
You have a lot on your body.
Look.
Makoto.
Makoto, wake up.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
It's okay.
I'm going to the tax office with this document.
Okay.
I'm going.
I'm not sleepy. Get to work.
I'm sorry.
Makoto, you're up.
Did you sleep well?
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Did you sleep well?
Thanks to you, I feel better.
That's good.
I was talking to my senior.
What was it?
I heard you went to the tax office with this document.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Well...
How long have you been married?
How long?
It's been almost five years.
I see.
It's been that long.
Yes.
By the way, you came to the theater, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Do you remember I confessed my love to you?
I didn't know that.
I was a teenager at that time.
But I was rejected by you.
I miss that.
I didn't know that.
But I was happy that you confessed your love to me.
I was shocked that I married you.
I see.
I owe you my private life.
But...
I don't know if I should say this.
What's wrong, Makoto?
Come closer.
What's wrong?
I still love you.
Wait.
Come closer.
What's wrong, Makoto?
Wait.
Don't do that.
Don't do that, Makoto.
Wait.
Don't do that.
But...
I have a husband.
If my husband finds out, I'll be in trouble.
He won't find out if you don't tell him.
But if he finds out...
I'll be in trouble.
Just once.
Don't do that.
It's not good.
You're so soft.
Don't do that.
You're always like this.
It's embarrassing.
Wait.
Don't do that, Makoto.
Don't do that.
Come here.
I'm serious.
I'm serious. Don't do that.
Don't do that.
It's embarrassing.
I'm serious.
Don't do that.
You're always like this.
Please don't tell him.
Don't do that.
You're so soft.
It's embarrassing.
Just once.
Don't do that.
Does it feel good?
I'm serious. Don't do that.
It's embarrassing.
Can I do something?
Don't look at me. It's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing.
You're beautiful.
You're wet.
Don't do that.
You're beautiful.
You're wet.
Don't do that.
Please make me feel good.
I'll keep it a secret from you.
It's hard to be known by others.
Please make me feel good.
I can't stand it anymore.
Please let me in.
I can't stand it.
It's hard to be known by others.
Don't do that.
She's drooling.
Calm down.
Give me a kiss.
Which do you feel better?
Why do you ask me that?
Give me a kiss.
She's drooling.
Don't do that.
I'll lick you.
She's drooling.
I can't stand it.
Open your eyes.
Let's take a bath.
You're dirty.
I'll wash my hands.
But you're going to get a fever.
You're going to get a fever.
Let's take a bath.
I'll wash my hands.
It's okay.
I'll wash your hands.
It's a little embarrassing.
You're back to normal.
Wash your clothes, too.
I'll do it.
It's faster to do it to each other.
Are you okay?
I'll wash your clothes.
I think you should wash your clothes.
You've been drooling a lot.
I'll wash your clothes.
You're getting bigger.
I'm sorry.
Wash your butt, too.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
You're not responding.
Wash your mouth, too.
It's a little embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
You're not responding.
I have to get rid of the dirt.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
Is that so?
It's already like this.
I'm sorry.
You're getting bigger and bigger.
I'm still very wet.
I'm sorry.
You're getting bigger and bigger.
You've been drooling a lot, but you're already like this.
You're amazing.
I'm sorry.
I'm getting hungry.
Let's take a shower.
I'll wash your face.
I'm sorry.
You're getting bigger and bigger.
I'm still very wet.
I'm sorry.
Don't run away from me.
Raise me!
Have you been like this all the time?
It feels good.
Wait a minute.
You've been like this all the time.
I've been like this all the time.
I can't stop eating.
Does this feel good?
It's amazing.
I just got out of bed, but I fell asleep again.
I'm going to bed now.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
What is this?
Are you sure?
Isn't it a luxury thing?
He's working hard, so...
I see.
It doesn't matter.
You're so quick.
This morning, I started building the piping in front of the Kamijima station.
I've loaded all the necessary equipment into the car.
Oh, I see.
Makoto, what's wrong? You look different.
I want to do my best and be independent.
You look like you're getting used to it.
I'll do my best to help you.
I'm counting on you today.
I'm counting on you.
Good luck, Makoto.
Wait a minute.
I got an e-mail.
It's from the president.
I'm going to the president's office first.
I'll be there soon.
Get in the car and go to the construction site.
Yes, sir.
I'll leave it to you.
See you.
Good luck, Makoto.
This is your lunch box.
I'll be there later.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's delicious.
Stop it.
It's hot.
Makoto.
What's wrong?
I stepped on my wife's butt.
No way.
You're a good father.
I'm sorry to kill you.
You've grown up so much.
You've grown up so much since this morning.
I'm sorry.
I'll make you feel better so that you can do your best at work.
Are you sure?
Do you feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Your mouth is the best.
You're going to the construction site today, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
I'll lick you a lot so that you can do your best at work.
I'll do my best.
It's hot.
You're grumbling a lot.
You've grown up so much.
It's hot.
Do you like this?
Yes.
It's hot.
You've grown up so much.
It feels good.
You're grumbling a lot.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You've grown up so much.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
It's hot.
You're so energetic in the morning.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I've been curious about you for a while.
I've heard that you have a mole on your neck.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You've grown up so much.
Don't do that.
It's hot.
You've grown up so much.
I'm sorry.
I was too nervous.
Do you think you can do your best at work?
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
You did a good job today.
You did a good job.
Did I?
I want to see you again.
I'll do my best.
You don't have to be independent.
I think I need your guidance.
Please.
Do you think so?
Here you are.
Don't drink too much tonight.
I don't think so.
In the first place, you've grown up so much.
I want to see you.
So, I'll drink with you.
Thank you.
You've done a good job.
It's all thanks to your guidance.
You're right.
You shouldn't drink too much.
I know.
Here you are.
Drink more.
Thank you.
I'll drink with you.
Makoto, you're great.
You've grown up so much.
It's all thanks to your guidance.
I'm grateful to hear that.
I'm envious of you because you have such a beautiful wife.
I think so, too.
She cooks well, too.
I hope you'll find a wife soon.
There aren't many people who can cook well like you.
I don't think so.
What do you think?
I'm proud of you.
It's delicious.
I'm glad you like it.
What kind of fish is this?
Mackerel?
Yes, it's mackerel.
It's delicious.
Honey.
Yes?
I'm sorry, Makoto.
My husband has been a weak drinker for a long time.
No.
That's why I told you not to drink too much.
You've grown up a lot.
I used to drink at a good pace.
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid my husband will find out.
But my husband doesn't get up at all when he drinks.
I'm sorry.
You like me, don't you?
Show me your throat.
Touch my throat.
I'm sorry.
It's too early for you to look at me.
I'm excited.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Are you hot?
It's hot, isn't it?
My husband doesn't get up when he drinks.
He doesn't get up.
Are you going to quit drinking?
I don't want to.
You have a weak neck, don't you?
I'm good at drinking.
I want you to touch me a lot.
What do you want me to do?
If you hide your back, my husband can't see it.
Is that so?
I like being touched by you.
Touch me a lot.
It's very soft.
It's hard.
I'll touch you like this.
I'll touch you a lot.
Let me touch your buttocks, too.
My buttocks?
Why?
I see.
Touch me a lot.
I'll touch your buttocks.
I'll touch you a lot.
It's getting hotter and hotter here.
It's very tight.
I think I'm soaked.
It's very hot.
Don't look at me like that.
Look at my buttocks, too.
You like my buttocks, don't you?
My buttocks are cold.
Can I smell your buttocks?
Yes, you can.
My husband doesn't wake up at all when he sleeps.
I can feel my body.
Hey, don't lick me.
I'm surprised.
It feels good.
Stretch your panties.
It's very hot.
I'm soaked that I'm about to vomit.
It feels good.
I don't want you to lick me.
Stretch your panties.
It feels good.
It's very hot.
Stretch your panties.
It feels good.
I want to feel good, too.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You like this, don't you?
It's hot.
It's soft and it feels good.
It's amazing.
It's very hot, isn't it?
Your waist and legs are shaking.
Can you stand up?
It's okay.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
If I lick your neck, you'll get bigger.
It's hot.
You're very energetic.
It's not a loud voice.
It's okay.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's okay.
Does it feel good?
More.
It's hot.
You're very energetic.
It feels good.
Do you want to put it in?
I don't want to put it in anymore.
I want to put it in.
Do you want to put it in?
Yes.
Let's put it in.
I'll put it in right away.
Do you want to put it in?
It's hot.
Let me take a deep breath.
What?
Do you want to take a bath?
Can I take a bath?
Yes, take a bath.
It feels good.
Let's go.
It's hot.
It feels good.
My cheeks are burning.
It's getting hot.
It feels good.
Let's go.
Look.
I'll put it in.
Can I?
I'll put it in right away.
It feels good.
Let's go.
It's in my stomach.
It feels good.
Let's drink a lot.
I'm standing in a comfortable place because it's big inside.
It feels good.
Turn around.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
It feels good.
More.
You want more, don't you?
It feels good.
I like it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Let's go.
Stretch your legs.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Does it hurt?
It's hot.
It hurts a lot.
Do more.
It feels good.
Let's go.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can't stand it.
It's hot.
Let me help you.