That's it.
I'm sorry.
What's this?
Yes.
Good morning.
I'm Nakajima.
I'm sorry.
I came too early.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I brought a tool set and a seat.
What is this?
This is a seat for children.
You have this when you go to school.
Get a grip.
I'm sorry.
I'm an apprentice.
I went to school until last year.
I can't help it.
It's hard for you too.
I'm sorry.
Hurry up.
I'm going to school.
I'm sorry.
Please.
Please be careful.
Okay.
There are nails and screws.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Here are the documents.
Osara.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Here you are.
Osara.
I'm sorry.
How is your husband?
How is your job?
I'm on a business trip.
I see.
I'm going on a business trip the day after tomorrow.
You are very busy.
You are a president.
Please continue.
I'm sorry.
I can't move my hands.
What's wrong?
Kotaro.
Can't you get a job?
You're in trouble.
Then, I'll make you feel good.
You want me to do that, don't you?
Then,
I'll touch you.
You've grown up.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Were you thinking about something strange?
It's warm.
It feels good here, doesn't it?
What's wrong?
It's moving.
Where does it feel good?
I'll touch you a lot.
I'll make sure of it.
You're cute.
Kotaro,
Do you feel your nipples?
I'm sorry.
You saw it.
What's wrong?
Do you feel it?
Your nipples are moving.
Look.
It feels good.
Are you happy?
What's wrong?
Your body is moving.
You want me to lick you, don't you?
I'll lick you.
What's wrong?
I licked you.
You're sensitive.
What's wrong?
I knew it.
It's getting harder and harder.
What should I do?
What's wrong?
You don't have enough on your pants, do you?
I'll touch you directly.
I'll put it in here.
What's wrong?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Your pants are in the way, aren't they?
I'll take it off.
Look.
What's wrong?
I saw it.
That's what it looked like.
Show me.
You're cute, too.
What's wrong?
Does it feel good?
What do you like to do?
What do you think?
What's wrong?
It's hard, isn't it?
Kotaro.
Come to think of it,
You were looking at my butt earlier, weren't you?
I noticed.
If you want to see it so much,
I'll show you a lot.
Look at me.
Can you see it?
That's right.
I'll show it to you.
If you like it,
Let me know, too.
Look at my foot.
What do you think of it, too?
What's wrong?
I was surprised to hear you saying,
And now I'm going to adhesive it.
I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to throw up.
I'm going to throw up.
Can you see this side better?
How is it?
You can see it well, right?
Kotaro.
I'm going to stroke your neck.
I'm going to throw up.
Are you going to throw up?
It's okay.
I'm going to throw up.
Look at this.
I'm glad you threw up a lot.
It felt good, didn't it?
This is a gift from a dango dealer.
It's delicious, so please eat it.
Is this cheese?
This is very delicious, isn't it?
I'm glad you gave me this.
Thank you for coming to my busy place.
I'm glad you came to my busy place.
I got a call from my husband.
He told me to tell you about the Nakajima police station.
I'm glad you came to my busy place.
By the way, KOTARO...
I'm KOTARO.
I'm sorry.
When did you start working?
I started working this spring.
You're a newbie, aren't you?
I'm a newbie, aren't I?
He hasn't done anything since he left school.
I'm taking care of him.
I don't know if he's going to be something.
Are you a quick drinker?
I'm talking about you.
Me?
Are you a quick drinker?
I haven't learned how to drink yet.
Good luck with your work.
Thank you.
Please eat a lot.
How do you drink?
Thank you.
Do you drink a lot?
I've been trying to control myself lately.
You have a lot of work, don't you?
That's right.
If you drink this much, you'll have a lot of work tomorrow.
Thank you.
I have one more favor to ask you.
I'd like you to take a look at the bathroom.
Is that so?
Are you going to renovate it?
It's a little old.
I was talking to my husband about buying a new one.
That's right.
Where were you looking at?
I was thinking about something.
You should be careful in front of customers.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
You should be careful.
It's a good combination.
It's a big deal.
You made me look at the bathroom.
I'm sorry.
I'm always sorry.
Are you getting drunk?
No, I'm not.
I'm not drunk at all.
You're a strong drinker.
You drink a lot, don't you?
I'm not drunk.
You're listening to me, aren't you?
How is golf going these days?
I'm free when I have a break.
You like it, don't you?
I'm often told about golf.
I don't know.
You bought a new club.
You were boasted about it.
I knew it.
You play golf outside, don't you?
Thank you.
I'll leave it to you.
My husband came home by taxi.
I'm glad you got a taxi.
I was worried that you were drunk.
I'm glad.
I have a meeting tomorrow, so I'll leave it to you.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
I wanted to do something in the bedroom for lunch.
In the bedroom?
Well...
Give me what's in your pocket.
I knew it.
It's not my underwear.
I'm sorry.
I have to wash it.
Don't worry. I'm not angry.
I'm really sorry.
Don't worry.
Look up.
You said you didn't have a girlfriend.
I thought you wanted to have a girlfriend.
I'm sorry.
Stand up.
I can't remember my work.
I'm always scolded by my boss.
Don't cry.
I can't remember my work.
Don't worry.
Kotaro, you did a good job.
Did I?
You did a good job.
Don't cry.
Yes.
Are you calm?
I'm glad.
You think a lot.
Maybe.
Have you ever seen a woman's body?
Yes.
I've never seen a woman's body.
I see.
I'll help you.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
I'll show you.
Can you work from tomorrow?
Well...
You have to let go of your worries.
Do I?
Do you have something to worry about?
Well...
When I saw your wife...
I felt your posture.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
When I looked at you, you were wearing panties.
I thought you were wearing panties.
Yes.
You've never touched your boobs, have you?
No.
Do you want to touch your boobs?
Can I?
Yes.
Touch your boobs gently.
How is it?
How do your boobs feel?
It's very soft.
It feels like this.
Is it different from what you thought?
I thought it would be soft.
You've seen your mother's boobs, haven't you?
Yes.
But it was a long time ago.
I see.
So you've only seen your mother's boobs when she was sucking her boobs?
Yes.
I'll remind you.
Look.
Touch your boobs.
It's amazing.
It's a cute underwear, isn't it?
Yes, it's very cute.
It's my favorite underwear.
Is it?
This yellow color is cute, isn't it?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Let me touch your boobs.
It's warm, isn't it?
It's very warm.
Look.
These are your boobs.
Yes.
It's amazing.
Look.
Your boobs are so soft.
You have to work hard tomorrow.
Yes.
It's amazing.
Can I touch your boobs from now on?
What do you mean?
You want to touch my boobs, don't you?
No, I don't.
I said yes.
I want to touch your boobs.
Good boy.
Can you take off your bra?
Do you know where it is?
Here?
Yes.
Can you take it off?
Like this?
Do your best.
I did it.
Good boy.
If you're good at it, you can do it with one hand.
With one hand?
It's amazing.
I don't think I can do it.
Can you take it off?
Yes.
Like this?
No.
Be gentle.
Do you remember your boobs?
Yes.
It's getting...
It's very soft and smooth.
My boobs are like this, aren't they?
Yes.
Let me see your face.
How do you feel?
It's very soft.
You can lick it.
Can I?
Yes, here.
Don't bite it.
You can lick it gently.
Like this?
Yes, like that.
You're good.
Yes.
Your nipples are getting harder.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
This side, too.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Yes, it does.
This side, too.
I feel like I'm getting used to it.
Are you getting used to it?
You've never looked this way, have you?
No.
Let me see.
Your underwear is cute, too.
Like this?
It's called a tea bag.
Can you see it?
Like this.
Touch it.
Okay.
I feel like I'm getting used to it.
Do you?
It's amazing.
I think it's the first time I've touched a woman's butt.
I've learned a lot today.
Yes.
It's okay if you kick me a little harder.
Is that so?
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good when I touch your butt?
I can't stand it anymore.
Can you look this way?
Your underwear.
You want to look here, don't you?
Can't you see it well?
I'll put this on you.
No way.
Look at this.
Can you see it well?
It's amazing.
I've been shaking for a while.
Does it feel good to touch a woman's butt?
I think so.
It's amazing.
I've never seen a real woman's butt.
Can you see my fingers?
Look at this.
Look at me.
Can you help me?
Help you?
What's wrong?
First of all, I'll touch you gently.
It's very hot.
It feels good.
Look at me.
Here.
Here?
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
It's very hot.
Put your fingers in here.
First, lick your fingers.
If you don't, it won't go in here.
Slowly.
Here.
Put your fingers in gently.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good to touch a woman's butt?
Like this?
Yes.
Do it hard.
Do it slowly.
It's amazing.
Do you feel like a woman?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
It feels better than doing it myself.
Do it harder.
It's amazing.
I was too nervous.
Is that so?
I'm very sweaty.
It's amazing.
This is the inside of a woman.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Show me what's going on here.
Here?
It's been tight here for a while.
Well...
Take it off.
I'll take it off, too.
I've been worried about this for a while.
Well...
I'm sorry.
Do you want to take it off?
Well...
It's okay, isn't it?
Take it off.
It's so big.
You're young, so you can't help it.
I'm sorry.
Well...
It smells good.
Does it smell good?
Yes.
Well...
It's after work.
Do you want me to lick it?
Yes.
You're energetic.
It's like this.
You're dirty.
It's hot.
My wife's saliva is slimy.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
It's hot.
It's very hard.
It hits the back of my throat.
Can you stand this?
My wife is so energetic.
I can't stand it.
You're going to hurt yourself.
Let's go over there.
Come here.
I'll do something better for you.
Something better?
You want to do it, don't you?
Yes.
Let's go over here.
Sit here.
Like this?
Relax.
It's hot.
It's so hard.
You've never done it, have you?
No.
I thought so.
I have a condom.
Do you want to try it?
Can I?
I'll put it on you.
Okay.
Do you know how to put it on?
I've never done it before.
Let's do it together.
Okay.
I'll go get it.
I brought it.
It's hot.
You're nervous for the first time, aren't you?
Yes.
I'll put it on you.
Okay.
Does it hurt?
No, I put it on like this.
Okay.
I've never done it before.
I'll put it on you.
Okay.
Does it hurt?
No.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'll do it slowly.
Okay.
How do you feel?
It's so good.
It's so warm.
Is it your first time?
Yes, it is.
Let me see your tongue.
Look up.
It's so good.
It feels so good when I kiss you.
Are you getting used to it?
Yes.
I'll do it harder.
It's so good.
Are you getting used to it?
Yes.
It's so good.
It feels so good again.
Yes.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
I'll take it off.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Yes, it felt so good.
Next, I'll move you.
Me?
I'll lie down here.
Move.
Can you see it?
Yes.
It's here.
It hurts.
It feels so good.
It's different, isn't it?
It's so good.
Do you remember it?
Do you want to try other exercises?
Yes.
Next, I'll move you from behind.
Okay.
It's hard to see, but it's here.
Is it here?
Yes.
It's here.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
I want more.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
I feel like I'm going to die.
Are you sure?
Yes.
It's so good.
Look.
It's a little hard.
Does it hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Didn't you exercise recently?
I was busy with work.
I see.
You can work well from tomorrow.
Yes.
Don't tell your boss about this.
Okay.
It's a secret between us.
Tatarou.
Yes.
Where is your boss?
He's on a business trip.
I see.
Hey.
Do you remember your work?
A little.
I see.
How do you like my bath?
I was looking at it.
I was wondering where to put the TV.
I see.
It's a little old.
So, I'm going to buy a new one.
I see.
It doesn't have mold.
I'm sorry.
What are you going to do?
What's wrong?
You should take off your clothes.
My clothes?
I see.
How do you like it?
It's transparent, isn't it?
You're wearing a lot of clothes.
I can see your underwear.
Really?
It's transparent.
What color is it?
It's pink.
That's right.
You want to touch it, don't you?
It's hot.
This is mine.
You feel better than before, don't you?
Yes.
It's hot.
I'll touch it directly.
This side is better.
Your skin feels good.
It's moist.
It's going to be a habit.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Your nipples are hard.
Do you understand?
I can feel it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
How do you feel?
Your nipples are soft.
It's hot.
How do you feel?
It's the best.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I'll wash your hair.
How do you feel?
Thank you.
It's amazing.
How do you feel?
It's getting wet.
It's hot.
I haven't touched it yet.
I'll lick it.
It's hot.
Your mouth feels good.
I'm glad.
It's hot.
I'm going to go.
I'm going to put it in your mouth.
It's hot.
Did you feel good?
I'm glad.
I'm going to put it in your mouth.
I'm sorry.
Can you explain to your wife?
I'm going to put it in your mouth.
Is this okay?
I'm done.
Thank you.
Wife.
I'll do it again.
It's hot.
I can't forget what my wife did for me.
Was it that good?
Yes.
It's hot.
You like my chest, don't you?
I can't be satisfied with my clothes.
It's hot.
Your underwear is sexy.
Thank you.
Can I touch you directly?
Your underwear is so sexy.
Thank you.
Ah, ah, ah...
It feels good...
Your wife's part is getting really stiff.
Happy New Year
Touch mine too
Feel good?
Yes
Wow, it's getting harder and harder
I think so
It's getting harder and harder
It's getting like this
Because you feel good when I touch you
Feel good?
It feels good
I want to sleep more
You're getting bigger
Can I make you feel good?
Feel good?
It feels good
I'll lick your mouth
Your mouth feels good
It's warm and I feel good
Feel good?
Please lick my head
Okay
I'll lick your head
You're good
I'll lick this side
Feel good?
It's not just me
I'll make you feel good
How do you feel?
It feels good
I'm glad
I feel you're getting wet
Really?
Here?
Yes
Good
You're a good girl
Let me see
I want to see your important part
I'm sorry
You're amazing
You're wet
How do you feel?
I feel good
I want to see your important part
Do you feel good?
Please sit on me
I'll lick you
Really?
Let's lick each other
Well
Here?
I feel good
Breathe
Open your lungs
Wow, it's so soft and feels so good.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it's the best.
It's so good.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm at the important place of my wife.
I was looking forward to being with you, Kotaro.
I couldn't wait any longer.
It's so good.
I'm going to move.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
How about you?
It feels so good.
It's the best.
It's so good.
I love you, Kotaro.
I love having sex with my wife.
It's so good.
Like this?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
Next time, I want you to move.
Okay.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
Do you want me to massage your back?
It's so good.
I love this posture.
It feels so good.
How about this?
It's so good.
It's different, isn't it?
I can feel you.
I'm so happy.
It's so good.
More.
Did you know that I have a neck pain?
Is that so?
Okay.
It's so good.
I can't do it.
Yes give it all to me
I won't give it back
I win
I'd like to win
Stop it!
I'm sorry.
Harder! More!
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
You're good at licking now.
Thanks to you.
I'm sorry.
More.
With my wife.
Hold my legs.
Wow.
I'm sorry.
It's the best.
My wife.
I'm going to leave here.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
It was very pleasant.
Can I have sex with you again?
Yes.
I want to do it again.