The next day
I'm worried about something.
What's wrong, Yosuke? Are you worried about something?
No, it's nothing.
Well, I'm a good man, so don't worry about me.
The next day
Hey, it's about time for Susumu and the others to come, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Oh, it's already this time.
Oh, here it is, here it is, here it is.
You're so energetic.
The next day
Hey, it's here.
Oh, it's here.
Oh, Minami, it's been a long time.
It's been a long time.
It's sudden again, Susumu.
I'm sorry, I'll take care of you.
Hey, Yosuke, come here.
Hello, Yosuke.
Hello.
Yosuke, you've grown up.
I met you when you were a baby.
You don't know about them, do you?
That's right, I don't know them at all.
Hey, what are you talking about? Get up.
Oh, well, let's get up a little bit.
Okay, get up.
Oh, what's that?
Get up, get up.
But you've really grown up, Yosuke.
That's right.
Well, this kind of growth is fast.
Will you come back from the mayor next week?
Well, in the meantime, please take care of Yosuke.
What are you talking about?
That's right.
I like children, so I'm happy that my family has increased.
Well, if you say so, it's really helpful.
Yosuke, I'm sorry.
I'm a man, so I might be a little annoying.
No, no, please be careful on your way out.
Thank you very much.
It's really helpful.
I'm sorry.
Can I eat this?
Sure, eat a lot.
It's delicious.
It's really delicious.
You can have it.
Yosuke, you're a good boy.
Well, thank you.
Thank you.
And so, I was able to see Yosuke's face.
Yes, that was the beginning of everything.
Yosuke, the bath is ready.
Please come in.
I'll come in a little later.
But I don't want to be late.
I want to play a little longer.
Then I'll go in first.
I'm sorry.
Yosuke, what's wrong?
I want to take a bath.
You want to take a bath?
I'm going to go to bed now.
I want to go in together.
Together?
Then you want to go in together?
Yes.
It feels good.
Does Yosuke go in with his father?
No.
Then today is a special day.
Yes.
I'll wash your body.
Please stand still.
Yes.
Are you nervous?
You don't have to be nervous.
Yes.
When you're in this house,
you can think of me as your mother.
Yes.
Please stand still.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
This is the first time I've washed your body.
The first time?
Yes.
Hey, Ma-chan.
I'll wash your body next time.
Yosuke?
Okay.
Then I'll wash your body.
This is the first time I've washed your body.
The first time?
Yes.
You're different from me.
The shape of your body.
Your body is so soft.
Amazing.
You're bigger than me.
I see.
That's okay.
Why?
You said you had to wash your body.
That's okay.
Really?
I'll wash your body a little more.
Okay.
I'll wash your bottom body next time.
Wow.
You don't have any dandruff.
I want to see more.
No.
Why?
Because I can't wash your body without seeing it.
That's okay.
Okay, I'll wash your body.
It's okay.
It's okay?
You're like this.
Wow.
Amazing.
Ryosuke.
It's better to wash here, right?
It's okay.
My father told me to wash this part.
I'll wash it myself.
Really?
I'll wash it for you.
Okay.
I'll wash your back.
Back?
Look back.
Amazing.
I'll wash your back.
It's beautiful.
Really?
Thank you.
It's soft.
Ryosuke.
You don't have to wash your bottom.
Why?
It's better to wash it properly.
Because I can wash it myself.
Because you washed it for me.
I have to return it.
Wow.
Amazing.
I can't wash it properly.
So, I'll wash your bottom.
More.
I'll wash it properly.
I'll wash it for you.
It's enough.
I have to wash it more.
The body of a woman is amazing.
It's really soft.
Ryosuke.
What?
It's enough.
Stop it.
What?
It's enough.
Let's go upstairs.
Your penis is swollen.
What is this?
It's a good sign.
It's a good sign?
Yes.
I see.
It's enough. Let's go upstairs.
I'll wash it for you.
I was having a fight with my husband.
He was angry with me.
But I didn't think he was going to be so very angry with me.
I didn't think he was going to be so very angry with me.
I'm going to go now.
Take care of Ryosuke.
Leave it to me.
I'm going to go now.
Take care of Ryosuke.
Leave it to me.
Let's get started.
First, let's make the dough.
Boom boom.
It's cold!
Don't scare Yosuke!
Hey, grandma, let's play.
No, you can't do this.
I'm cleaning.
No, it's cold.
I'll play with you later.
No, let's play.
It's cold.
No, Yosuke.
I want to play.
I'll play with you later.
No, no.
No.
Let go of me.
You're mean.
I'll play with you later.
No, no.
It's cold.
Yosuke.
No, no.
I'll play with you.
It's cold.
No, no.
I'm sorry.
No, Yosuke.
You won't play with me.
I'll play with you later.
No.
I want to play now.
No, Yosuke.
No.
Yosuke.
Let go of me.
No.
I'll play with you later.
It's cold.
No, Yosuke.
Please stop.
It's fun.
I'll play with you later.
What are you doing, Yosuke?
No.
You can't do that.
I like it.
No, Yosuke.
It's cold.
Yosuke, you can't play with me.
No, Yosuke.
I'll play with you later.
What?
I'm cleaning up.
I'm playing with you.
It's cold.
I'll play with you later.
No.
I want to play now.
Where are you hanging?
Where?
Is it your butt?
No, it's not.
Where are you touching?
You can't touch it.
Why not?
Whatever.
Yosuke.
You can't touch it.
Did you get hurt, Yosuke?
I don't know.
No.
You can't touch it.
It's interesting.
No, it's not.
Don't move.
What color is it?
Yosuke.
No.
Yosuke, stop it.
Is it blue?
I'll play with you later.
Don't move.
Don't get in my way.
What?
I'm just playing.
I'll play with you later.
It's interesting.
Don't wet it.
Why?
Whatever.
I don't know.
Yosuke.
This side too.
No.
You can't touch it.
I don't want to.
You don't want to.
Don't get in my way.
No.
Where are you touching?
What?
Where am I?
No.
Don't get in my way.
I'll play with you later.
No.
It's cold.
This side too.
It's getting wet.
If you get wet,
you just have to change clothes.
That's not the problem.
Wow.
What color is this?
What color?
Yosuke.
It's interesting.
No.
This is interesting.
It's not interesting.
I'm interesting.
It's getting wet.
What are you doing?
I'll take this off.
Don't take it off.
You don't want to get wet.
I'll change clothes later.
Okay.
I'll do it for you.
It came off.
It didn't come off.
It's no good, Yosuke.
Wow.
It's really dry.
It's cold.
Stop it, Yosuke.
Wow.
It's no good.
Why?
Do you hate me?
I don't hate you.
Then,
you don't care about me, do you?
After cleaning,
No.
Yosuke.
Is it cold?
It's cold. I'll play with you later.
You don't want to be cold, do you?
No.
Then,
What are you doing?
I feel sorry for you
if you stay cold.
No.
Don't do that.
Wow.
It's no good.
It's cold.
Stop it, Yosuke.
What?
You don't want to play with me.
I'll play with you later.
No.
No. You'll get wet.
You'll get wet?
You don't want to get wet, do you?
No.
Stop it.
Yosuke, what are you doing?
You don't want to get wet.
Don't do that.
No.
It's no good.
Stop it, Yosuke.
It's cold.
No, Yosuke.
Stop it.
Hey.
I'll play with you later.
Stop it.
You shouldn't play with me like this.
What?
What do you mean?
I don't know.
It's no good.
Don't do that.
Yosuke.
Stop it.
Okay.
Okay?
Let's continue.
What?
You were cleaning, right?
You can continue cleaning.
I'll play alone.
What are you doing?
Don't worry.
Stop it.
Yosuke.
What are you doing, Yosuke?
Stop it.
Yosuke.
Hey.
Are these pants?
Are these pants for girls?
Yosuke.
Don't play with water.
What do you mean?
Don't look at people.
Tell me more.
Are these pants for girls?
This is amazing.
Stop it.
Stop it, Yosuke.
What?
Where are you touching?
I'm not touching anything.
Stop it.
I see.
You said that men shouldn't look at women.
I shouldn't look at women.
I see.
I should do this.
I shouldn't do this.
Yosuke.
I don't know.
You know.
This is the wrong way to use it, isn't it?
You're wrong.
Is that so?
It's not working.
What should I do?
I see.
This is also not working.
What should I do?
I have an idea.
What is it?
This is good, isn't it?
You have a lot of moisture on your butt.
I'll clean it up.
Clean it up?
What are you doing?
I'm just cleaning it up.
It's not that kind of thing.
What?
Your butt...
It smells funny.
You shouldn't do that.
What is this?
Can I lick it more?
No.
No?
It's amazing.
There's more and more moisture on your butt.
What is this?
It's not working.
There's more and more moisture on your butt.
It's amazing.
It's not working.
Are you okay?
Your body is shaking.
It's nothing.
I'm okay.
Hey.
It's hot again.
It's like this again.
Hey.
You're fine, aren't you?
No, don't touch it.
What?
Should I tell my father that it's like this?
Hey, hey.
It's amazing.
Hey.
No.
Don't touch it.
Touch it with your hands.
It's amazing if you touch it yourself.
I think it's better if you touch it with your hands.
Stop it.
It's amazing.
You shouldn't do this.
Why?
It feels good.
It's too early to say that.
What?
What do you mean?
It feels good.
Touch it with your hands.
You shouldn't do this.
Close your eyes.
No.
Do this.
Stop it.
Give me your other hand.
No.
Hey.
It's amazing.
Yosuke.
Stop it.
I'm a genius.
Close your eyes.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
If you touch it with your hands,
it feels like it's getting hotter.
Stop it, Yosuke.
It's too early to say that.
What?
When does it get hot?
Not yet.
I don't know.
Can I say this to my father?
You don't have to.
I want you to touch it with your hands.
You shouldn't say that.
I'll keep quiet.
Listen to me.
It's amazing.
Hey.
What?
I came up with a better idea.
A better idea?
Maybe
you should
put it in your mouth
instead of your hands.
It'll feel better.
No.
Give me your other hand.
Please.
I'll say it to my father.
You shouldn't say that.
Give me your other hand.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It feels better
than I thought.
It's amazing.
Give me your other hand.
Please.
It's amazing.
It feels good
to touch it with your mouth.
Did you know that?
Touch it more.
Give me your other hand.
Hey.
You can see
my butt well.
You don't have to see it.
No.
Wow.
It's amazing.
When you touch it
with your butt,
you'll feel
more strange.
It feels good.
Give me your other hand.
I think it's enough.
No.
Give me more.
It's hot.
It won't cool down.
It feels good.
Give me your other hand.
It feels weird.
It's amazing.
It's coming out.
Don't take it out.
Why did you take it out?
Because
it's coming out
suddenly.
It hurts.
Don't do this.
I'm angry.
Run away.
tight
It's that kind of logic.
It's OK.
It's nothing.
Good night.
What's wrong, Iwasuke-kun?
Did you fall?
Hey, just a little bit.
Hey, it's okay, right?
Iwasuke-kun, stop it.
What's wrong?
No, I can't do this.
What do you mean?
I'll fall.
It's okay.
I can't do this.
I can't sleep at night if I remember my aunt's body.
Stop it.
No, I can't do this.
I can't do this.
Stop it.
Do you like it?
You have a lot of dandruff.
Stop it.
No.
I can't sleep at all when I get up.
I don't know what to do.
You have a lot of dandruff.
Give me this.
Please.
Can I make a loud voice here?
No.
You're going to wake up, aren't you?
So do it.
You have a lot of dandruff.
I came up with a good idea.
I wanted to try it.
Let's see.
I think this hole in your mouth,
I think this hole will get into your mouth.
No.
You put it in your mouth,
so I think it will feel good if you put it in this hole.
Please, I want to put it in.
I'll put it in.
Can I wake you up?
You don't want me to wake you up, right?
Then, you should be quiet.
Can I put it in?
Wow!
What is this?
Can I put it in?
Wow! What is this?
Wow!
It feels so good.
You are hugging me.
No!
Wow!
Hurry up!
No!
It feels so good.
Wow!
No!
You are strong.
Your hips are moving.
Wow!
Stop it!
What kind of game is this?
Wow!
You can't move like this.
Why?
I can't sleep.
I want to do more.
It feels so good.
I can't sleep.
Wow!
You are snoring again.
What's wrong?
Wow!
Stop it!
I want to do more.
Wow!
I'll do this next time.
I'll do like this.
You can move like this.
Try it.
It feels so good.
I'll stop doing this.
I don't want to stop doing this.
I'll sleep.
Wow!
It's okay if you don't wake up.
You are snoring again.
It feels good.
I love your butt.
I'll do this more.
You look happy.
Really?
I can't believe it.
I want to do it in a different way.
I'm so glad I came to this house.
Thank you.
I met your butt.
You're always boring.
Thank you, auntie.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
It looks like you didn't wake up.
You're sleeping.
It's okay.
It looks like an old woman's butt.
It's fun.
That's right.
It's okay.
You don't wake up at all.
Isn't this play fun?
It's okay.
Hey.
I feel a little strange.
What is this?
It looks like it's going to come out again.
It's not good.
Why?
Even if you say this?
It's not good.
It's going to come out again.
I can't stand it.
It's not good.
Oh, no.
It's coming out.
What happened?
Hurry up and wipe it.
It's coming out.
When the white one came out,
I suddenly became sleepy.
I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
It's gone.
It's coming out.
Oh, no.
I was with my husband
and I got along with such a child.
I couldn't sleep on that day.
What's wrong, Miyami?
Are you not sleepy?
Your face looks tired.
Really?
I've been fine recently.
You did it a long time ago.
You have to sleep well when you sleep.
Yes.
Good night.
It's gone.
This is...
Amazing.
I knew it, Yoshiki.
You shouldn't take laundry by yourself.
I found an interesting clothes.
What's this?
It's not a problem.
It's not a toy.
What?
It's about yesterday.
You shouldn't do that again.
But...
But what?
I don't have a mother.
So I want to take care of you.
So...
Irohsuke.
I'm sorry.
I said too much.
Do you hate me?
I don't hate you.
Really?
Will you play with me again?
Yes, I will.
Then,
wear this.
This is
not a toy.
I wear this when I exercise.
What?
You don't play with me.
Let's play another time.
Okay?
You don't like me.
You really want me to disappear.
No.
Okay.
Let's play with this.
Really?
I did it.
I change clothes.
Look at me.
I want to see you transform.
No.
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
Koora, look at me.
Look at me.
Please look at me.
No.
I did it.
You just changed clothes.
What did you do?
Wow.
You are cool.
This is cool.
Wow.
It's cool.
You are slimy.
You look like you're in a transformation.
This part is hard.
Yosuke, don't do that.
Why?
Yosuke.
Yosuke, think about playing.
What do I do with this?
This is for exercise.
Exercise?
What kind of exercise?
Not this kind of exercise, but stretching.
What is stretching?
What do you want to do?
What do I want to do?
Amazing.
What do you want to do?
I want to see what stretching is.
What else?
You want to see that?
Please.
I did it.
Stretching is...
Like this.
Where does this stretch?
Your back stretches.
Your back is around here?
Yosuke, don't go down.
Why?
I'm checking where it's stretching.
Is this enough?
No, no.
I want to see more.
Yosuke, let's try it.
I'm fine with it.
Let's play together.
It's more fun to watch.
It's more fun to do it together.
It looks difficult.
I can't do it because I'm not wearing this.
No, stop it.
Yosuke, stop it.
Why?
Do it more.
Stretching is like this.
Yosuke, let's do it together.
I'll help you with the stretching.
If you do it like this, you can stretch more.
Yosuke, stop it.
No, I'm just helping you.
Stretching is not like that.
If you do it like this, you can stretch more.
Adults know how to have fun.
It's amazing.
This is stretching.
It's fun.
A lot.
It's cold.
I'm sorry.
Did you enjoy the stretching?
Yosuke, stop it.
I can feel your bottom again.
You always feel this when you are tired.
I'm sweating.
I'm getting wet.
I'm getting wet again.
Hey, auntie.
If you put your finger in this hole, you can put your finger in it.
I shouldn't do that.
Can I put my finger in it?
No.
But you can put your finger in it right away.
You can put your finger in it right away.
Amazing.
You did it.
It's warm.
Your finger is very soft.
I shouldn't put my finger in it.
It's easy to put your finger in it.
What will happen if I put my finger in it faster?
I'm sorry.
Why?
It's okay now, right?
More, more.
When I looked at your back, I felt your bottom again.
It's okay now.
I shouldn't rub it.
Why?
Amazing.
This is amazing.
Do adults do this kind of thing?
Close your eyes.
No, no.
Amazing.
When I put my finger in your bottom,
I feel like I'm going to put my finger in your bottom again.
You shouldn't put your finger in it.
What?
But I don't know.
Close your eyes.
It's okay.
It's interesting to put your finger in it.
Amazing.
Hey, auntie.
You're getting bigger and bigger.
This game is really fun, auntie.
Close your eyes.
Close your eyes, Osuke.
I don't like it.
It feels good to rub your bottom.
Close your eyes.
What?
Oh, auntie.
It went in.
I'm sorry.
Your bottom is wet.
It went in.
Amazing.
It feels good.
It feels good to rub your bottom.
Adults do this kind of thing.
It's not fair.
I'm sorry.
It feels good to rub your bottom.
I'm going.
I want to put something on your butt today.
Can I put something on your butt?
No, you can't.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's amazing.
It's about to come out.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's coming out.
I put something on your butt.
I told you not to put something on my butt.
It was a fun game.
It was nice...
and my body started to get into your butt.
my body started to get into your butt.
My body started to get into your butt.
Although the
This is the first time I've done this, so I'm not sure if I'll be able to do it this time, but I'm sure I'll be able to do it this time, so I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to make a new one this time.
.
This is my kids' favorite powder.
I did them yesterday in the morning, so I'll use double-sided tape as well.
I'm going to do it this time, so I'm using double-sided tape.
This time I'm going to use double-sided tape.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
Let's play
It's getting really warm
Yosuke-kun's chin
Hey, you've changed
It's delicious
Let's play a lot
It feels so good
Tell me more
Yosuke-kun
How about this?
The tongue is soft
It feels good
It's amazing
It's amazing, right?
It feels good
You can stop drinking
It's good
Chin-chin, do you like it?
I like it
Yosuke-kun, it's special
It's because you've grown up
It feels good
It's amazing
Hey, grandma
I want to see more of your body
Do you want to see it?
Yosuke-kun, you've grown up
It's amazing
What are those clothes?
What do you think?
It's amazing
Do adults wear such clothes?
Adults wear such clothes
It's amazing
What do you want me to do?
Lick it
I want you to lick it
Like this?
You're good
It's thanks to you
Yosuke-kun, you're good
It's good
Why is your wrist so stiff?
Because you're good
I see
You're good at licking my boobs
I'm happy
Will you be happy?
Yosuke-kun
There's something I like more than boobs
Where?
Here
Your butt
I like your butt
Show me more of your butt
Okay?
Okay
Show me more
Your butt smells good
Does it feel good to touch your butt?
Yes
Your butt is so beautiful
I'm happy
I like your butt
I want to lick your butt more
Lick it more
Do you want me to lick it more?
You're eating into my belly
Do you like to eat into my belly like this?
Do you want me to lick your butt more?
Lick it
Wow
Your butt is so soft
You're good
Do you want me to lick your butt more?
Yes
Lick it more
Do you want me to lick your butt more?
Put your fingers in
Lick it more
Your butt is so soft
Put your fingers in
Do you want me to lick your butt more?
Is this enough?
Yes
You put two fingers in
Do you want me to lick your butt more?
Lick it more
Yosuke
I want a massage
You want a massage?
What do you mean?
I want to put it in
You want to put it in?
Where do you want to put it?
In my belly
Sleep there
I want to put it in
Okay
Your butt is so soft
It feels good
How is my butt?
It's the best
This butt
It feels good
Aiki
You said it
You can say whatever you want
It feels good
Let's go
What is this?
There is something like this
How does it feel?
It feels good
It's amazing
Let's go
It feels good
I'm sorry
You fell in love with me
What's wrong?
Hello
I'm late today
I see
This way?
This way is okay
It's okay
I see
See you
Who did you fall in love with?
My husband
I see
Let's go
It's okay
It feels good
Let's go!
No!
I don't want to do this!
It's okay. You can do it.
That's amazing.
You're doing it while looking at your mom's butt.
I'm sorry.
That's amazing.
You're good at acting.
You love my chinchin, don't you?
I love it.
Say it more.
You love my chinchin more than your chinchin, don't you?
I love it more.
That's no good.
That hurts.
That's amazing.
You can see your aunt's beautiful butt very well.
That's no good.
That hurts.
That's amazing.
My aunt feels great, too.
When you look at your aunt's butt,
your chinchin gets bigger and bigger.
That's amazing.
You're going to come out again.
Let me out.
I'm going to let you out.
You're going to come out.
Your spirit is beating in my chinchin.
I'm going to let you out.
That was fun.
I don't need a toy with this.
Was it fun?
I'll see you later.
We couldn't go back to the past.
We overlapped our bodies like we did every day.
And then...
I'm sorry for bothering you.
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
Where's Yosuke?
I think he's getting ready to go home.
I'm going home.
Maybe he's feeling better.
Maybe.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to go home either.
I want to stay like this forever.
I'm going to be a part of this family.
Mom...
Thank you for watching.