Applause
Hi to
The week of Miss Yori.
today is
Where do you think you are?
See you see?
today is
Come to Taiwan, I say.
Going to Taiwan.
This is my second high school trip in my life.
I usually go to high school, so I don’t come here.
I remember it was like this, long ago.
Today I have a date with the actress.
I don’t know how they will come,
I am very nervous, but
I think you want to have fun.
Please be kind today.
Come to me.
Oh I have come.
Thank you, I am pleased.
I am pleased.
It is Southern.
Thank you, I am a wanderer.
Please please.
Did you photograph something?
I was photographing.
Was it early?
No, it is just good.
Oh well was.
It has already begun.
Please be kind today.
Please be kind.
Can I have it?
Okay okay? Thanks to.
It is nice.
It is still white.
Maybe it is white.
It is very white.
Well, but it was a fire.
Do not burn white.
Should I go somewhere?
Yes to.
Good morning.
For example today.
Yes is
How many photographs?
Oh yeah
The fourth eye.
The fourth eye?
What have I photographed so far?
So far
Oh yeah
The last time.
The first time
A little
You will go.
This is the case, expectations are high today, pressure is high.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
So far, many have been alone.
How many are you.
It changes the gym.
This is the first time I have done so with one person.
Yes is it.
I am nervous.
I try to not disappoint you a little.
Oh, I pulled it back again.
It was very cloudy!
Yes is.
Why is she a woman.
Okay okay.
Where do you normally play?
I am in Fukuoka, so I am in Fukuoka.
Yes, it is Fukuoka.
Going home to photograph?
Yes is
It is hard.
Have you ever been on a plane?
I ride a lot.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
What trip did you go on?
I went to Korea and the Crown.
Oh, and so on.
But it got a little sluggish again.
in the world.
Yes is.
Yes, well okay
Have you been many times?
You went pretty much.
So much?
At least once I go.
It is awesome!
It is very close to here, so it is easy to get there.
Oh, and so, of course.
I can photograph this very quickly.
I took a picture, tell me.
Riding from the shore?
I need to close it a little earlier.
Okay okay is.
It pushes happiness.
I missed very much.
by
I say to be.
I liked this kind of thing, when I was a kid.
I missed it.
Like that pack nearby.
Oh, I understand.
You have a patchwork, right?
Yes
Do you like sweets?
You may want to eat something candy sometimes.
Yes, of course it is.
He is the one I just talked about.
Yes yes yes.
Didn’t you have any of these tastes?
How about.
Oh, this is something.
Probably not.
He is only a moment.
I missed
50 yen? and the price is higher.
higher than before.
So much movie?
Not even 50 yen.
You did not do it, right?
No, it is true.
It was about 30 yen or more.
Oh, in this place.
impact of the impact.
It smells like popcorn.
Because there is a movie feeling.
Oh, and so on.
Do you like movies?
I like the movie.
What do you see?
Or a horror system.
Do you like horror?
I am happy with the recent horror, is there anything?
Something has been cracked out at this time.
No, I understand, I understand.
I told him to give out something specifically.
Suddenly, it will be.
I will write it later, remember.
Yes, it should have been then.
There is a.
Is it still moving?
It is still moving.
Can you hear the sound?
It is hard to fall.
I photographed it.
I have only photographed it a few times in my life.
Have fun.
Do not write.
I have written my book, and it is okay.
How was the feeling, by the way?
Feel good
Have you heard?
Do you usually use toys?
No, if not router.
Where do you guess now?
You told me to be.
You are a very cute kid, you are wonderful.
You have a fucking pizza.
Okay okay.
Are you interested?
There is really a lot of hassle now.
Do you have any purpose?
Was there?
sweetly
New products
Is there any?
I want to do.
What is China aiming for?
The artist.
1 in 5 is.
Yes, this is the face.
I will have a seat.
Oh, Seal, are you okay?
Let the actors get filled.
That is not chips.
Chipper, of course.
It is chips.
Strengthens
Until I hit.
I thought I would let him do it several times.
No, I didn’t think I would shoot at you.
Luckily is
Bring the capsule.
What happened?
Oh well!
Oh is?
Bring the capsule.
Go to.
There was.
The Bocobots.
Very pleased.
It is pulling.
by one shot.
I did it.
power is
power power.
A lot of meat.
Oh, it is true.
You can buy just a small piece.
Please use it.
sweetly
The smell of man.
I was ready to fly for thousands.
It is amazing, surprising yourself.
Thanks to Mr. Irene.
Not sure if you can take a photo on a booking.
It was fun to hide at all.
I mean, you are not in.
What here?
It looks like acrylic.
A very round.
It is fine, the circle.
Clothes and looks good.
The goldfish are long.
Yes, I think so, very much.
Why is the hole open?
No one dances.
There are many kinds of goldfish.
Yes, totally differently
and large too.
by
Really this size?
You look something big.
I do not know anything.
But so is.
The best friend.
I love you, my best friend.
Mr the Frog.
beautifully
Anything is doc.
by Doc
And the color.
Expectations will be great.
I think very adult.
Oh yeah, yeah yeah.
Then you will think, right?
What happened?
Yes, what happened to me?
See also Mr.
Are you sick?
No is?
Are you okay at all?
Is it okay?
Let’s look around.
Suddenly appeared
Suddenly I realized.
I knew it.
The back turned.
You see fish.
Craig is beautiful.
I said something, is it okay?
I like it, the excitement is great.
It feels good.
Would you rather fly?
Is it okay?
It feels like you’re not in the middle?
I have a polish face.
It feels good, but I care about it.
Are you okay? have you not seen?
Everyone is fascinated by fish.
Maybe not anymore.
No more can?
Maybe not
I flew.
I was surprised.
Oh... oh... oh...
Suddenly, the snow was growing, suddenly.
Oh, it was fun.
No, it was very beautiful.
Yes to.
Did you watch it on the way?
I have not seen.
It was not in my hands for a long time.
It was a lot of flying, but not hard.
This is the first time I’ve used it to jump outside.
The first time.
Not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not
You like it.
Or something.
Fuck you fuck you.
Is it because it is big?
Why is it.
What is it?
Are you doing it intentionally?
I did not do it intentionally.
There are lots of people.
There is also a weak spot.
Yes, where is it?
Very weak too.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
There is a nose outside.
I like both.
Okay is.
Tired of you.
Are you used to photographing?
some
than the first.
If you can say.
Is there anything you thought you would start?
to the head.
and Damn.
So, make it a little stronger.
As to the head.
I went from Fukuoka to Tokyo.
Are you not filming?
Isn’t it hard enough?
I feel stronger.
I am not strong now.
Buy it?
Try to buy?
Try to buy.
The sensitivity is very high.
Do you like what I say?
A beautiful reason.
Is your body resting?
Are you not resting?
Once I have stopped, I will stop.
Next is it not that you are being shaken?
Do you like to be struck?
It feels like shooting quickly.
So much
Was it good now?
Did you want to talk about the previous?
Or do you want to get in quickly?
Oh yeah
I like it very much.
Or I don’t like it.
As surprising as well.
Yes is
You really like it.
Yes
Thanks to.
Eat it.
Ice tea from lemonade.
Thanks to.
I will use it here.
Is it okay?
What is it?
It is delicious.
Is it too tasty?
It is so delicious.
I got in my right hand. sorry. sorry. sorry.
It is getting strong.
I will stop.
I am going to stop, I am going to leave.
Can not stop?
I do not stop.
It’s too stimulating to drink.
What are you drinking?
Has the stimulant Tara ever drank lemonade?
No is
Is it not?
First inspection is.
It must be delicious.
Is the lemonade okay?
Will you come for a few hours to drink?
Absolutely impossible.
Yes, members are coming, so come.
It is best to drink after you are tired.
When we go, we will go out on the beach.
Going out on the coast.
Go to go?
Let us go.
I came here.
I will see Toro soon.
In such a free space.
Not able to see.
Maybe, maybe, when you look at this, you’re going to see the eyes open.
Are you okay?
Oh shit, you are beautiful.
He is walking, he is walking.
Okay okay okay.
Great, I am hitting it.
Is it hit?
Is the staircase okay?
Can I go.
Can I? is it okay?
You are okay.
No, I am walking hard.
I walk well.
It also has vibrations when you get down.
It is fun.
Okay okay okay okay.
A little more.
Night has arrived.
Yes, I was tired.
Feel badly
Okay there.
Going to there.
What happened?
Nothing is troublesome.
is okay.
It is OK.
What happened?
Take a little.
Is it okay?
Very bad feeling.
No No No No No No
It doesn’t hurt, right?
Feel good
You say it is bad and you feel bad.
Can not be?
What can’t I endure?
Can I tell you again?
I want to come.
I stood up with one word.
I understand
You understand?
Yes
Oh, I came here, I came here.
Oh, well I walked.
Have you been a little too much?
No more can?
cannot
A little, oh
I think you put the switch in your pocket.
Have you stopped?
stopped it.
I can’t stand it, I’ve finished.
No longer stopped.
at all.
Have you already burned?
Okay is.
Maybe it burned.
This is a beautiful view, it will burn.
It is strange how you can’t wash it.
Is it better not to wash?
Edu is
I want to rest somewhere.
by
I will try to photograph the room.
I wonder if this happens.
I don’t like it, I don’t like it.
I had a lot of drunk.
5 January 1950
I want to go.
Go to?
Can you go?
If you let me go so far.
lightly
Let us go.
If you let me go so far.
I will take you out.
I understand.
Let us go slowly.
Let us go.
by
I followed it.
I think it was going to make a lot of skinny.
They both finally disappeared.
You were last bad.
Maybe was pretty bad.
She had a very cute face.
Really?
What happened?
Why Why?
I thought what you want.
Does it not hurt?
The Chew?
hurtly
Where are you standing?
It is fast.
Because I cannot endure.
Can you endure?
Can I try it?
What can’t I endure?
Oh yeah yeah yeah
A little bit.
Stand up and stand up.
What what what?
What did you try down to?
Why should I spill.
What happened.
Oh Oh Oh
You took it.
A little
Why Why Why
Get up properly.
Go to sleep?
Can I drop it?
Sleep up in a real.
You are sleeping down.
Sleep by
I will let it down.
It is fast.
Why is it getting so hard?
Why is it.
Maybe so good.
A little bit.
Oh well fuck.
It feels good.
Why it always feels like that.
Is it different?
It feels good.
Yes
Feels good?
Feel good
Oh well fuck.
Oh is
Yes
Do you hear the sound?
Oh yeah
Laughing
Wasn’t it so?
Too much chill?
Because it is the most ruinous.
Because I really liked it.
A fast pace?
Show me your breasts.
I said a little nothing.
Feel good
Oh awesome.
Feels good chick?
Feel good
greatly
Mr Chick
Yes
Stand up and let me stand up.
Okay is?
Feels good?
Stay still
OK is.
Dust to Dust.
Yes
Oh yeah
Feels good?
Very good feeling.
Oh yeah
It is very fucking.
Your breasts are very good.
Is it really good?
very beautifully
Yes
Oh oh oh
two
2nd
Three
The language of Ost?
This is
Laughing
Sleep to
and AR
very painful
Oh yeah
Yes
No to
Oh yeah
Feel a bit good.
Feel good
Oh yeah
What are you doing?
Always doing it by myself.
Can you stand up a little?
OK is.
here here?
No to
Feel good
Feels good?
No to
Feel good
Oh yeah
Toys in this.
Stay with this.
Fuck you fuck you.
How can it be bad.
See also
I take toys.
A little more this.
Feels good?
I like it, my flyer.
Yes
Oh well fuck.
They make you feel good together.
Yes
together with
No to
Stop it.
This man came.
Do not seem to be able?
It will seem to be.
Will it seem to be possible?
Talk again.
2nd
Oh yeah
Make up it.
A little hurry.
Use it if you touch.
Very bad feeling.
is good.
Be a little harder.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Oh yeah
Oh, and a little.
Oh, it was
Why did you leave me here?
Oh yeah
No, because I felt good.
It was inside.
Oh yes so much.
Did you want to get in?
I was sorry, I didn’t tell you.
Let’s go there.
Let us go.
Tish is here.
Sorry, I felt so good.
Very nervous.
Go well.
Why give it out.
Sit and sit.
How do you feel?
Oh well well well.
Feel good
Did you notice?
Yes
Feel good
Didn’t this go too?
Yes
Would you stop?
Oh is?
I want more.
What what what?
It is heavy.
Was it heavy?
Oh is?
Oh...
Do you want so much?
Yes
Oh...
I cannot try.
Yes
Oh...
Press it all the time.
Yes
Oh...
I went in.
Why do you vomit?
Maybe we should take a break.
by
Do not be.
Do you vomit?
standing up again.
Why tell me before I hear?
Do not be.
It is growing.
touch more.
More of?
Oh yeah
Oh yeah yeah yeah
WEB
Feel good
Oh yeah, then then
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Touch it directly.
and straight?
Yes to.
Is it part?
and
Turn it?
Yes to.
Show me a little.
I am ashamed.
So see it?
I am ashamed today.
It is beautiful.
difficulty
More of
More of?
How many more do you want?
It feels good.
Oh well fuck.
Oh Oh Oh
No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No
I will soon breathe.
No to No.
Go to?
Oh Oh Oh
No to no.
No No No No No No No No
Oh Oh Oh
No to no.
No to No.
Go to go.
Why be hit.
If you go, tell me.
I think now.
I am troubled.
It seemed to go?
yet another time.
stretch your hand a little.
Oh well bad.
Feel good
It feels good.
Oh, and so badly.
No to No.
No longer
Do not stop.
Tired of breathing.
No, no no no
Did you put in?
Not yet entered.
Are you not in?
Feel good
You will buy it.
Heads to head.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
I do not know.
No No No No
Go to
I am scared I am scared I am scared
not stop
Let me go.
I thought it was pretty good.
Feels good?
Feel good
It feels good.
No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
Oh, something badly
Too bad intention.
cannot go.
Could not go?
I have not gone.
My ass hurts.
This underwear is bad.
I think this is good.
Is it good today?
I understand
W is
Zero is
I made me.
Suffering is?
coldly
Cold and cold.
Come, come and come
Why do you cry.
I went away without intention.
Snow is
Sorry to
It feels good.
not yet
The tension is delayed.
Oh is
No to
Feel good
It hurts, it hurts.
Play it.
Feel good
Give me, give me
A great feeling.
No to no.
Feel good
Very good feeling.
Oh is
by
Come to me.
No to
by INTRO
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Yes
Going, Going and Going
Oh yeah
No to
Stand up.
Oh is
Take the hand.
Okay okay.
It feels good.
Feel good
Going, Going and Going
Boo, Boo and Boo, it feels good.
by
No to
Oh yeah
Oh well
by
It feels good.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
and angular
Me is
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah yeah
Oh yeah
Yes
You are full.
It is awesome.
pleased
Have you skined?
Yes
It felt good.
You have fallen asleep.
Shower here.
Yes, we are on.
Can wear it?
Yes
Be careful.
greatly
It is awesome.
Yes, be careful of it.
Let wait.
I will take a bath too.
Let us go in together?
Yes, let’s go in together.
Oh, it is warm.
It may have been a long time since I took a bath.
Always taking a shower?
There may be a lot of shower.
I also always take a shower.
Yes is.
Feel good
Very small.
sweetly
It is very small for both of you.
No to
Can I ride on my feet?
On the feet?
Yes
Oh yeah
What do you do? like it?
What are you doing?
Drink it
Drink to?
I want to drink normally.
No mention of Mark.
by Kilomellaw
was
Oh, so, can you bother me again?
Yes yes
In the bathroom?
Yes, in the bathroom.
Oh yeah
This is the first time I have tried a bath.
Do not go to the chicken, what?
Feel good
Feels good?
Yes yes
Next →
Oh Oh
No to no.
Tell it to Tyler.
Oh is?
Yes Yes
Feel good
Feels good?
............
He is moving very much.
It became a dumb.
Okay, I have gone.
AsmR
cannot be used.
Yes, it is okay
Go to bed?
Yes
I only entered a little.
Actually is
I have prepared a gift.
A gift?
When did I buy it, so?
Because they are ready for the bed.
If you want, look at it.
I want to see.
So let’s go out.
Yes
Oh is?
This is awesome.
What happened?
There is no strange thing.
No strange place?
Yes
But this is, right?
No, I am ashamed
This is
Oh yeah
You are a cute Bee.
Yippidy yi yippity yay.
Can you go out.
You will not come out at all.
by
He has a lot of ass.
I am very ashamed.
well is.
Why can you hide it there?
The hole is open, so I write.
Is it open?
Confirmed a little.
Yippidy yi yippity yay.
Just one second.
fastly
You know this in a second.
Just one second.
It is difficult.
by
No, it is nice. – You are cute.
I get a lot of ass.
Show me the back.
Oh, I am very embarrassed.
It is cute.
I am sorry a little.
And then, back, a little hand.
My back is healing, no.
No, no, that is all that.
Can not?
No to no.
Maybe you stand up.
Can I sit?
So what cosplay is this?
See this, do you not understand?
The cat?
The maid?
The Cat Ears Maid.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Do you know what the maid is?
It is like serving your master.
is right.
When you want to do something.
Please please is.
When I want to do it.
Do I have to be cuddly?
Just cheated on today.
No to
He was independent.
Looks like it is?
Sit down now.
to here?
No need to hide.
I will doc.
You mean cosplay, right?
Oh no, not too much.
No to no?
It seems to be seen.
I am pickling my feet.
Everything you have to hide is hidden.
Yes
Okay, this is fine.
Oh yeah?
What do you mean?
Can I just do so with Sosa?
No no no
Not just this.
Is it not enough?
I have to tell you that nothing is enough.
Yes
I want you to touch it.
Want to touch?
Yes
I want to do more ugly.
How to say?
Yes
Oh is?
How to say?
Do you have to be a woman?
Why Meghan?
Go to the camera.
Oh is?
What do you want to do?
Shamefully
I want to do more.
With the master.
I want to touch a lot.
I have to say that right.
Licking or touching.
Please please
Oh he is sleeping.
Go to sleep?
here here?
Do you like the sound?
Yes I like it.
Oh oh oh
The scratch has failed.
by
Touch the bottom again.
The below.
Yes, the below.
Do not see?
Thee to?
You know.
I have to say right.
I want you to touch it.
So where?
It hurt?
I want you to touch it.
here here?
It is awesome.
Feel good
Oh oh oh
No to
Oh well feel good.
No to no.
No to
Oh oh oh
Not to no.
Feel good
No to no.
It is spike.
Please wipe it.
Please stop it.
Feels good?
Feel good
I am scared.
Oh yeah
by
Feels good.
Oh is
Oh awesome.
Feels good.
No to no.
Because they are sensitive there.
No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No
Stay a little.
Oh, I am going
I will go soon again.
No to No.
Oh, I am going to go.
No, because it wasn’t possible.
Oh no no.
I had to have power.
Take a hat.
Feels good?
I used it head.
Do you feel good?
Yes
Oh yeah
Do you feel good for a little?
Feel good
Yes
Oh yeah
No to
Are you feeling good now?
Feel good
The master’s food is delicious.
Oh yeah
Oh is
Can I sit a little?
by
Open the feet.
Yes
No is
by
Own
Yes
Are you tired?
The feet.
Yes
Just extend here.
And turn your feet.
Turn your feet.
Yes
Wait a little.
Feel good
Stop it.
Oh, it is so empty.
It feels good.
Very good feeling.
Feel good
I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go I go
Sorry to
Are you tired?
still is
Is it okay?
Feel good
The sadness came out many times.
The stomach hurts.
Oh go go!
Go, go, go and go!
It is not crazy!
Oh well.
Tired
I have gone.
So I gave time.
Sleep today.
to sleep?
I went into the bath and sweated.
It is a good time.
I want to.
Oh is?
Want to here?
How long do you do?
Until the morning.
Until the morning?
well to
Seriously
Also well, my daughter.
Let us try hard.
Yes
It became a lot of bed.
Yes, you went in.
Yes
......
A week later.
Eating while Nam
Was it awake?
What are you doing?
He was hungry, so I touched him.
Didn’t he grow up?
Which of them?
Is it purple?
It is removed.
Feel good
Are you still sleeping?
still sleeping
Feels good?
Why are you touching?
Why Why?
Because I am in the room.
So many people?
Yesterday is
Okay, still sleeping
Oh is?
Feels good?
How do you look?
It feels like.
Yes is
Is it good here?
It feels good there.
What do you like?
Yes to?
I like it next door.
What here?
It is getting very hard.
It became a huge smoke.
It is becoming.
It became
No to
Oh yeah
by
No to
Oh yeah
Oh yeah yeah
So stay on.
Oh well fucking.
Oh, shit, that is good too.
Feels good?
It is moving very much.
A little bit of trouble.
Do you feel good?
It is becoming a great shit.
It won’t end in your mouth.
Oh is?
What do you mean?
Do you mean Mascara?
Oh is?
Do not do?
No to?
Be calm.
Take out the hand.
What? what to do?
What is?
Why? what?
What is suddenly.
Does not hurt?
No, it does not hurt.
What is done?
was arrested.
Totally
Wait a little.
cannot photograph.
No such thing.
No to
I am changing again, definitely.
Really?
by
No to
No, no no longer, no longer
It is okay, I am not sweating.
Okay, okay, I’m going home.
It feels good.
Oh...
Yes
Oh, and there
It feels good.
Oh, oh, you feel good.
Is it good? here.
No is no.
by
Oh yeah
Activity
Oh well
Oh oh oh
Oh yeah
Boe
Oh is
who
by
Lick it again.
A is
No to
Yes
The correspondent
No to
here
already feel
Oh yeah yeah yeah
It feels good.
Feels small.
This is no.
What to say.
Come to.
This eye
Feel good
Add a lot.
Oh yeah
Can I take hands?
Turn your feet.
Oh yeah
Feel good
It is awesome, I say.
It feels good.
Tagged,  Tagged  Tagged
Yes
More than.
Oh oh oh
and more...
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Feels good.
No to O.
No more, no more.
Oh, a great feeling.
Oh is
More of
Oh, the feeling
I like this.
Oh is
Oh, the feeling
I feel
Deceased because of.
No to
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Goo is
Oh is
Get it down.
A lot out.
There are trees.
From the early.
I did it.
So something.
It happened in the morning.
Yesterday is
After yesterday’s date.
How was it until now?
The date was fun.
Edge felt great.
well was
Wait a little while, until lunchtime.
Yes
Go to sleep a little slowly.
Go to sleep?
Then take a shower and go to bed, and go to bed tomorrow.
Take a shower once.
Go to sleep?
Maybe you will be fooled again.
If I slept.
If you can’t sleep?
What if I didn’t sleep?
Yes
Do it?
Not even sleeping.
Do it.
Then for now.
Yes
Let us talk at least.
Yes, let’s talk.
Yes
Go to sleep now.
It will only sweat.
Awaken a little.
Wake me up.
Sleep is
You can sleep.
by
to flow?
A little
That is?
Wait and wait.
This is all, this is all.
by Really?
20 minutes of reference
2 days 330
A beautiful custom.
Awesome people like me.