One year later.
I was really happy to be married to this man for a year.
I think that I am now looking to see the house I live in.
My mother brought the laundry.
thanks to.
It is softened.
Their mother had a little bit of a kid.
My parents are married again and suddenly I can make it.
Maybe it was confusing.
They accepted me as a family.
by
No to?
Help my mother while I am not there.
I know you know.
You are too busy, you are too busy, you are too busy, right?
Yes, but if you have any problems, always rely on me.
Thanks, are you ready for the trip?
You’re going out in the evening, right?
Oh, it was still on the way.
No forget anything?
Go home, and at least it will be okay.
I’ve been single for a year, I miss it a little.
It is not so, it is the only one.
Oh you.
There is only one, not now.
A little patience.
But we won’t see you in a year.
Stop it, we are not a couple.
When we come back, we will both travel.
If you are the only one who is unhappy, you are a little bit lazy.
I have not seen you for a year, but I have not done anything.
You will face it properly.
I started to feel like my husband was crazy.
Since we both started living.
It was just one day.
Can I take a bath?
Okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
by Mr.
Are you there, Mr.
Sorry to.
I came to get the sandwiches.
Okay okay.
Sendai is alone.
Oh yeah
Oh, I understand
Sorry for myself.
I went in the disguise.
Yes, it is okay.
Pete is out.
So is.
The Circle of Sandy.
He invited me to a drinking party.
Okay, not okay
When is it?
I have not decided on the day yet.
I was told to do it next week.
But that day may be late.
Oh yes, have fun.
It doesn’t change as usual, Mr. President.
Was it my mistake?
Mom, what is it?
Well, no, we’re not going to be together for a while?
At first I was worried about whether I could live with my college son.
That made me nervous too.
But, mother, no, because she is a gentle and beautiful person.
I am happy to be a family.
Oh my lord.
I have a request.
Please please?
Okay to that?
I dreamed of being heard like this.
The knee is fine.
well was
Oh well Mr Yuri.
Do you miss your father?
Oh is?
Usually, it is married and is a time of lust.
I have such a big son.
My father is not a single lady.
Did you worry so much?
I’m sure you missed your brother a little.
It will be long from now on.
I do not care.
Do you really say?
You really want kids, don’t you?
I want to.
He is not so young either.
You want to be more sweet, right?
Oh yeah
But he is a working man.
Do you want to make a skimmer with your dad?
The look is over.
I have to go buy hot food.
I will go shopping.
No to
Follow me
It hurts. 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂
by Mr.
by
Oh, my dear, what happened?
I mentioned before that, the drinking circles.
It’s now, I don’t want to eat dinner.
Yes I understand.
I’m going to go to the last train, but go back.
I understand
So I will go.
Go to go.
University students today.
Such a skinship.
Is it normal?
Or is
Also Mr.
You are missing it somewhere.
and
This night.
Finally
What I was afraid of happened.
Yoshiko, go home now.
Sorry, I was asleep.
Mr Yoshin?
What happened?
Yoshiko, what is it?
Oh stop it.
What happened?
No to no.
Mr Yoshin.
But it is parents, right?
A little...
A little, a little...
You were a girl yesterday, right?
Is it different?
I know...
I saw it.
No is...
Oh, my dear, I drank too much.
You are very dissatisfied, right?
That’s why I made her a woman, right?
No to.
Oh, because I drank too much.
I will bring water.
Wait a little.
I will help you.
I stand up, I know.
by
You are dissatisfied, right?
not my
Oh my not.
I will help.
Please let me handle it.
Wait to
He is standing.
Wait a little.
It feels good, right?
Direct radiation is good.
You are down?
Feels good?
Feel good
He sleeps great.
See also
A little
See this.
A little that.
Oh well sir.
touch it.
If Yuri had said.
has grown up.
It is
Because I am a boy.
It will just feel better.
It just gets better.
I hope it’s not a socks.
Sit to
Feel good
He sits straight.
hurtly
Do not forgive.
I want to have.
Oh yeah
Feel good
hurtly
Yuri is beautiful.
Very good feeling.
fall a little.
Oh oh oh
here here
Yes
Oh oh oh
Oh well fuck.
Go out go out.
Oh oh
Because not.
Thanks to Yuli.
It felt good.
Our lives started getting a little crazy.
I said it last time.
I have to touch Yuri.
I could not.
So is
Oh my lord.
Oh yeah yeah
Oh Mike
Thanks to Dutch.
So much so much.
Mr is
If if
If so, was he well?
Good day, what about today?
Today is vacation.
and so.
I am so cruel, sorry I can't get in touch.
Yes, it is okay.
How are you? it doesn’t change?
Are you doing good friendship?
All in all, it looks okay.
I think Yuri is having a hard time.
Yes Mr Ike.
Maybe you can travel a little sooner and come home.
I want to do that, too, in the mountains.
Because the place decides.
by
Oh sorry to.
Yes
Mr Yuri.
Clean up the room.
I want to tell you.
I understand
Let me go.
I will take time again.
I will call again.
I know, do your job well.
thanks to
What happened.
Give me back the room stuff.
A huge dust has gone out.
Really great eg.
Great here around.
How about Mr. Dude?
than it.
Because I understood.
I know, so sit in bed.
How is it? feel good?
Is it nice here?
Very good feeling.
Can I be tough?
Feels better?
Feel good
The scan is ringing.
If you look at your ass.
I was excited.
Slow down or I will leave.
Is it so?
slowly to
Shit slowly?
Feel good
Feels good?
Do you do it yourself?
It is doing.
But when you see the Dutch.
You will not be able to endure.
Oh, my friend, I want to add a mouth.
Because when you are always in your hand, your mouth is always open.
No so is.
Please try it in your mouth.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah.
Such as this?
Continue to
Their brown beard is soft.
It is warm in her mouth.
Oh, there is a lot of saliva.
Great, here too
Oh well great.
I want you to do this backwards.
Oh, so good, it feels like.
Oh well great.
Shit, you will go.
Go up to bed.
I hope that you feel better too.
I am okay.
When I was leaning, she was very excited.
No, but after all.
It’s not just me that I feel better, right?
What of what?
She also had a very striking face.
No so is.
He is already standing.
What is this, Mr. Zhao?
Very standing up.
by Mr.
Stop doing it this way.
Feel more well.
Feels good?
Feel good
It is becoming more and more tough.
He is wet.
No to No.
What is not?
No to Mr.
here here?
You are not excited.
I am I.
Mr Eeee
I am accustomed.
Do it yours.
Why not?
Not even the feet.
His body moved.
Raise more up.
See well
Curry’s hands hurt.
Shit, you are sleeping now.
Oh, I went out.
Oh is
Oh, so great
Feel good
Yuri has licked me a lot.
Oh, so very good feeling.
Feel good
I cannot endure.
Just the child who talked.
You can’t even endure the spell.
Why do that...
You have skin, look at it.
This will only sleep.
Just make it.
You cannot sleep.
No, no
Lisa is fine.
Feel good
Once this happened.
Sorry about the shark.
If you feel good.
Feels good though.
Feel good
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Have you ever had such sex with your father?
It does not exist.
I think he’ll go already.
Do not give it to your stomach.
Good luck and I didn’t come.
Good luck, I’ll get you out.
Your sister is fine, right?
Feels good though.
My sister
I do not want to fly.
and sister too.
You want to fly.
Feel good
My sister
I will already go out.
I can no longer endure.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh
Oh well already.
Oh Oh Oh
Oh no more.
I told him to go out.
Sorry to
But
You also felt good.
Yes
Oh Oh Oh
I learned sex.
It is that we fall.
It was quick.
One of them.
How many times you have been with the Dutch is great.
No so does.
I prefer the younger high school students.
Sex with Yuri is the best.
I can only have sex with Yuri.
Mr Yuri.
Sleeping in the bedroom of the couple is no longer a matter of course.
But this relationship.
Did you wake up again, Mr. Dudley?
Have you thought a little?
I know, this relationship is...
Mr. Dwight...
I know what not to do.
But our relationship remained unchanged, one and another.
Feel the voice.
It feels good.
You are sleeping well, it feels good.
You look so wild, you feel good, right?
Would you prefer to be strong?
From my dad.
Have you gone out?
Now is?
If if
Oh my dear.
What happened?
Was he okay?
Yes, you are well.
Yuri, what are you doing now?
Today is a vacation.
A resting day?
Do you shop today?
I think I’ll go soon.
It is so.
So, I want to come and buy something.
Can I buy it?
Yes
Go to the light bulb.
I want to buy an earpiece.
I use it a little, it’s broken.
Yes
Next time I go home.
I will buy it until then.
Can I go shopping today?
Yes, I can go.
Do you know what my earplugs are?
Yes
I know, if you find.
Is it okay?
Yes, it is okay
I am, I am
Going to shopping, right?
Yes yes yes
You probably haven’t eaten much sweetness lately, right?
Eat something sweet when you are not there.
Yes, thank you
What do you want to eat now?
The Princ?
Yes, Princeton
The restaurant in front of the station is delicious.
Come buy it.
You can eat it yourself.
I also like Princeton.
Yes
When I go home, I buy it.
Because there are many types.
Yes
Eat it today and buy the best.
Yes, well done
Yes
I have recently.
I am a little busy.
Yes
Maybe you can get a promotion at work.
Maybe he could be the boss, though.
I’ll be very busy again.
I am busy, I want to eat sweet.
I want to eat a princess when I get home.
I love Yuri, so I will buy it when I go home.
Yes, it was good.
I will probably be back next month, so I will call you again when the date is set.
Please remove the printer.
Yes I understand.
I’m working, but when I get home, I’ll be very busy.
It might be quite difficult.
I’ll go back next month and get some rest.
Let’s go somewhere together.
Do you want to go somewhere?
A playground.
No to?
The expression?
Go to Expression?
Do you want to ride something?
The viewing car.
Where is the car show?
You got to the car near your house.
Oh well okay.
Yes, I don’t drink either.
Yes yes yes.
Could you go to Karasjok?
You can go near us.
Oh yeah.
Not to be here and here.
Yes, yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
So you went to Karina, right?
Yes to.
What is this boy.
What you like is your swallow.
So, there is a way to go, so let’s go there.
What happened?
Yes to.
well is?
Is it okay?
Yes to.
So, what about music? what about music?
Is it bad?
Are you playing something?
Oh well, I am going.
Is it okay?
by Dudley?
You look bad.
Is it okay?
Do not force too much.
Yes
Do not worry a little.
Do you have a cold or something?
And if so, Dad?
Oh, Yuri what happened?
My mother is cold.
A cold?
Yes
Is it okay?
I’ll show you it, it’s okay.
Please help me with the bill.
Oh, you know it.
Then again later.
Oh, I understand
Then is.
Yes, I will cut it.
I felt a lot while calling.
Feel good
Have you been anal?
Yes
Oh is
Oh yeah
cry to
Yes
I want you to be so.
Come to
by Aha
by
No to
It feels good with a full stomach.
Feel good
1, 2, 3
by
You were still breathing while you were calling.
I want to put it in your mouth.
Oh well fuck.
Oh yeah
Oh fuck it.
Take out the tongue.
Was it good?
Yes
Next time, feel good about me.
Yes, I understand
Yes, the Yucca cuisine is great.
After a year of marriage, Yuki has returned.
Yuki, I’m not going to talk about you anymore.
If I could go back to a normal family, I would be happy.
That is all.
Next time, let’s eat something together.
Yes well well.
What do you want to eat?
Do you say.
Yes to.
You have grown up a little.
Oh, sorry, I’ll go to the toilet.
Lack of attention in the back.
Come to.
I can only touch it, it’s wet.
I can’t go back to my dad now.
No so does.
If you blame my father today.
Reject it.
No to?
Sex with Garmin.
If you can refuse, you can return to your normal family.
My relationship with the man will end.
It really.
There was not a day we didn’t have sex.
Can you bear such a man?
And then the night came.
Were you still awake?
by Dudley,
Sorry to miss me.
Yes to.
A year of fatigue.
I’ll have to go to the mayor again in a week.
Is it so?
But next is only one month.
No longer want to live away for a year.
well was
Yes
by Dud
But not now.
Maybe because the man is waking up.
It is OK.
No to
You are tired of travel agency.
You can never do it again.
by
Go to sleep today.
I will go to the toilet.
Good night.
by Mr.
I was still awake.
I thought he was sleeping long ago.
I thought I was in the middle of sex with my dad.
I refused his invitation.
Oh well, it is great.
Did you come here to tell me about it?
I don’t want to end my relationship with you.
I want sex.
Yes
Creole is tight.
You have given me.
Soon I entered.
I too
He sleeps great.
Feel good
Are you too busy here?
I am in trouble.
Oh is
Yes
Oh yeah
No to
Oh oh oh...
Oh oh...
Oh...
Oh, and it feels good.
Oh well awesome.
So feel good.
Oh no no no.
Oh it hurts.
Oh Oh Oh
Kia is over too.
It is getting bigger.
Feel good
You like it, right?
It is all I feel.
Feel good
It feels good.
Oh yeah
Oh yeah yeah yeah
had had it.
No to
Oh, very good feeling.
Can not regret?
Follow it from below.
It feels good.
Do this so.
Oh yeah...
Oh well...
It will hit.
Go to sleep something.
Oh, and so on.
Oh yeah yeah
Oh...
Oh yeah...
Oh is
still standing up.
Full of stomach.
It feels good.
Oh too serious.
Can not do?
My feet hurt.
Oh is
Foot is shaken.
More of
Oh is
Feel good
Good for the back of the feet.
Oh that?
It is just me, right?
It is too fast, it is common.
I think he is that.
Culture is about love, destruction.
A little indicated.
The universe is an adult broadcasting.
Yes
It is delicious.
I want a bedroom.
Yes
Get out more.
Oh is
I want a bedroom.
Yes
Get out.
Oh is
Death is in.
Oh yeah yeah
Oh yeah yeah yeah
well well
Full of water paper.
You can think you are pregnant.
No, you don’t even have to go on a job trip.
The three family lives are back.
From now on, we will be four people.