During that time?
It's going to overlap with Tatsuo's business trip.
Oh, the room?
The room is fine.
I want to see Kazu-kun, too.
I know, I know.
It's my sister's request.
Well, it's fine.
It's fine. I'll tell him.
See you.
What's up?
My sister wants me to take care of Kazu-kun.
Kazu-kun?
It's been a while. He's grown up, right?
Yeah, he's in the middle of his entrance exam.
Entrance exam?
That's going to cost a lot of money.
I told him that he could study for the exam better if he got a hotel room.
But it seems like my sister is having a hard time, too.
That's true.
What should I do? Aren't you angry?
Of course not.
When is he coming?
On Sunday.
Then I can come, too.
I'm sorry.
We've been talking about going shopping together for a long time.
It's fine.
It's more important to take care of relatives, right?
Well, he said he was going to this university.
Let's go.
Okay.
I'm home.
Welcome.
It's been a while.
You've grown up.
Come in.
Thank you.
You can use this room.
Study hard.
I'll call you when dinner is ready.
Okay.
Thank you.
I see.
You're great.
You don't want to worry your parents.
But I think it's a good thing to use your parents' money to study hard.
Right, Maki?
You have a girlfriend, don't you?
That's good.
You're young.
You can go out with her.
Hey, you.
Why are you drunk?
It's early in the morning tomorrow.
I'm sorry to say that.
No.
We've been dating for a long time.
It's my first time dating a girl.
I want you to teach me a lot.
Of course.
No, no.
At least until the exam is over.
And she's not popular.
I can't take care of a girl.
No.
It's amazing that you like a beautiful woman like me.
You're a good boy, Kaz.
I'm sorry.
I just didn't like you.
No, it's amazing.
The alcohol is delicious today.
Let's eat.
You drank too much.
I'm sorry.
Kazuya, I'll put a towel here.
Thank you.
Thank you for the bath.
It's good to have a bath.
Where's Kazuya?
He fell asleep.
He doesn't want to take a bath.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
He's always like that.
If you want to study, you can open the refrigerator and take a drink.
Thank you.
Good night.
I'm sorry.
I don't know if it's a good idea, but I don't think it's a good idea to do that.
I don't know if it's a good idea to do that, but I don't think it's a good idea to do that.
I have a lot to say, sir!
Bye.
See you later.
Good luck with your studies, Kaguya.
I don't want you to take anything else too seriously.
It's at your disposal.
See you later.
See you.
I made some snacks. Do you want some?
Here you are.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
It's good.
I'm glad you like it.
Don't you miss your girlfriend?
Yes.
But she said she would have sex with me if I did well in the exam.
What?
I see.
I'm looking forward to it.
But it's our first time.
I'm worried if I can do well.
It's our first time.
I'm sure I can do well.
How did you feel when you had your first sex?
What?
When I had my first sex?
It hurt at first.
Did it hurt?
Yes.
It hurt at first.
How do you use this?
It's important.
Can you tell me how to use this?
Me?
Please.
I don't know how to use this.
Please tell me.
I don't want to fail.
I understand.
Take it out of the bag.
Okay.
Take out your finger.
This is important for you.
Important?
I mean...
Change.
Okay.
Put this on your finger.
Can I try it?
Try it.
Wait.
What are you doing?
I want you to put this on my finger.
What?
Put this on my finger.
Okay.
How do you use this?
How do I use this?
Like this?
Please tell me.
Me?
This is the back side.
This is the front side.
Okay.
Like this.
Try it.
Slide it down.
I'm scared.
Are you scared?
I'm scared, too.
Try it.
Like this.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Slide it down.
Please try it.
Like this.
What?
I want you to put this on my finger.
No.
I have a girlfriend.
I have to wait until I have a girlfriend.
I put this on your finger, too.
My girlfriend asked me to go out with her.
I've always wanted to go out with you.
What are you talking about?
Calm down.
No.
Please.
I've always wanted to go out with you.
I didn't mean that.
I know.
I'm Zenki.
Zenki?
Yes.
Where did you learn that name?
I met her on the way.
On the way?
Wait.
Don't be so rough.
Calm down.
I'm wearing a rubber band.
I can't wear it.
Wait.
You're so big.
I can't wear it.
I'll make you feel better.
Don't say that.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
My girlfriend said you were too big.
No.
Wait.
You're so beautiful.
Are you sure?
Wait.
No.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
You're so beautiful.
Don't be so rough.
My girlfriend said you were too big.
Wait.
Don't be so rough.
No.
Wait.
Don't be so rough.
I'll make you feel better.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
No.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
You're so stiff.
No.
Wait.
My girlfriend said you felt good.
No.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
Wait.
It's wet.
You don't have to do that.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
It's wet.
Don't put it in.
Wait.
It's wet.
No.
Don't put it in.
Wait.
No.
Don't put it in.
Wait.
I'll lick you.
What?
I'm sorry.
Wait.
I want to feel better.
I'm sorry.
No.
Don't lick me.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's huge!
My stomach aches all over.
Oh, my gosh!
Lie down and rest for a minute.
Give me a break!
It's disgusting.
Yeah.
It feels good to be your older brother.
Hi Buddy!
Buddy...
I'm sorry.
It feels so good.
You shouldn't lick it so much.
What if it comes out?
It hurts.
You shouldn't put it in your mouth.
I can't stand it anymore.
You just licked it.
Wait a minute.
You were feeling good.
You don't have to lick it.
Wait a minute.
I'll make you feel better.
It's okay.
It feels so good.
I understand.
Rubber.
Do you have it?
You can do it.
Wait a minute.
Like this?
It's rough.
Are you okay?
It's not good.
I put this on you, so it's okay.
Wait a minute.
It's too thick.
Don't go that far.
It's not good.
It feels so good.
Wait a minute.
Don't move it.
Don't push it.
It feels so good.
Wait a minute.
It's not good.
It's coming out.
Don't do it.
It's good.
It's amazing.
Are you still doing it?
It's coming out a lot.
What should I do?
Take this off, too.
Be careful not to leak.
How do I take this off?
Be careful not to spill it.
Don't spill it.
It's leaking.
It's leaking a lot.
What?
I have to throw it away.
I'll throw it away later.
I still want to do it.
Where are you going to leave it?
On the sofa?
I can still do it.
I just took it out.
Kazuya, are you kidding me?
I'll throw it away.
I want to do it again.
Do it again?
But it's coming out a lot.
You can put a rubber band on it.
Wait a minute.
It's still hard.
Don't push it so hard.
It's coming out a lot.
Wait a minute.
I can't do it anymore.
My knees are shaking.
Wait a minute.
It's still hard.
I can't do it anymore.
It's hard.
It's no good.
It's disgusting.
This is horrible.
Oh!
Oh, my God!
What?
Oh!
Where are you?
My child!
I'm so sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
Why did you just take it out?
Can I take it out again?
You're so sweet.
You can take it out like this.
I'm so sorry.
I'm thirsty.
Can I drink this?
You're amazing.
You, too.
Thank you.
I'm so sorry.
Can I do it again?
Again?
I still have a lot.
What?
You still have a lot?
I still have a lot.
Are you kidding me?
I took it out twice.
I still have a lot.
What should I do?
Let's take a break.
You're amazing.
I want to do it again.
Let's do it again.
You don't have to do this.
No, no.
Here, here.
Look!
Oh, my boy!
Amazing…
Great work.
Straighten your back.
Can you do it?
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
I'm hungry.
I have to cook.
I just ate.
I'm so excited.
Kazuya, you have to study.
I want to see your face.
I know how to do it.
You don't have to do it anymore.
You have to study for the entrance exam.
You can't.
You're so cute.
Don't say that.
You're married.
It's hard here.
Don't say that.
I'm happy.
Wait, wait.
Wait.
I can't stand it anymore.
I promised her.
I don't want you to say that.
But I can't.
I promised her.
I like you more.
Don't say that.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Don't say that.
I know.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
Don't say that.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
Don't say that.
What should I do?
Hello.
What's wrong?
I heard your voice.
And I was wondering if you were doing well with Kazuya.
I was wondering if I was doing well.
I'm studying Kazuya.
I see.
Are you doing your best?
I remember my case.
I was nervous.
I'm doing well.
My work is going well.
I'm going to eat local food alone.
I see.
I'm looking forward to it.
I heard that fish is delicious.
I'm going to have lunch with a good cook tomorrow.
See you later.
Good night.
Wait.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
I don't know.
Hey.
It's wet here.
Don't touch me while I'm on the phone.
It's wet.
It's amazing.
Don't do that.
What are you doing?
Don't touch me.
Don't do that.
Are you kidding me?
Hey.
Don't do that.
Why are you licking me?
No.
It's amazing.
I've never been licked.
It's wetter than before.
Don't touch me.
Don't do that.
Wait.
No.
It's amazing.
Don't do that.
It's embarrassing.
No.
Don't do that.
It's dangerous.
It's amazing.
No.
Don't do that.
I've never been licked.
It's embarrassing.
No.
It's dangerous.
Don't do that.
I've never been licked.
You were beautiful.
I want to lick you.
Don't do that.
I can't bear it.
Wait.
Let me lick you.
Don't do that.
Why?
I can't bear it.
You can study if you feel better.
I feel better.
Stand up.
You can't concentrate on studying because you're shaking.
That's right.
You should feel better.
I want to put it in your mouth.
I'll put it in your mouth.
In my mouth?
Really?
Yes.
In my mouth.
I'll put it in your mouth.
I want to touch your butt.
What?
Wait.
Sit down.
I feel good.
I'll put it in your mouth.
I want to touch your butt.
I feel good.
What?
Stand up.
I feel good.
I want to touch your butt.
You have a lot of it.
I have to study for the entrance exam.
I feel good.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it feels good.
Ma'am, I want you to do it.
Oh, it's hot.
It's so good.
I want to pee.
It hurts.
What?
Your tail?
I want to pee.
No, no, no.
It's embarrassing.
Wait a minute.
It hurts.
If you crouch down, it'll get stuck.
It's too close.
It hurts.
Wait a minute.
It'll get stuck.
I want to pee.
Please let me pee.
Don't do that.
It'll get stuck.
I want to pee.
No.
Let me pee here.
What?
It's embarrassing.
I want to pee.
Please.
No, no, no.
Don't say that.
It hurts.
Please.
No.
It's embarrassing.
I want to pee.
Don't do that.
It's embarrassing.
Wait a minute.
Why are you licking my tail?
No.
Wait a minute.
You're touching my tail.
It feels good.
You're licking my tail.
Wait a minute.
Hey.
It feels good.
Thank you.
Don't lick my tail.
No.
It got stuck.
It got stuck on your face.
It's embarrassing.
You've been standing for a long time.
I was excited when I saw you.
It's embarrassing.
It feels good.
My mouth feels good.
I want to pee.
Let's go.
Okay.
Is this the bed you always sleep on?
That's right.
But it doesn't stick together.
But...
It's like this.
But you won't notice.
I won't.
I didn't do it at all.
You're a bad uncle.
Why?
You're a bad uncle who doesn't have sex.
You're so beautiful.
Ma'am.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I want to have a lot of sex.
That's right.
It feels good.
You have a lot of pimples.
You have a lot of pimples on your thighs.
Why?
I wanted to have a lot of sex.
It's hot.
It's cold.
Get on my back.
I feel like I'm doing something wrong.
I'm scared.
It feels good in my mouth.
Do you like having a lot of sex?
It's hot.
It's delicious.
You have a lot of pimples on your mouth.
Don't pinch me.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm excited.
Your boobs are warm and exciting.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I want to have a lot of sex.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Be patient.
It's hot.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I want to have a lot of sex.
As a woman.
You want to have a lot of sex, don't you?
Yes.
Are you tired?
It feels good.
It's hot.
You're lying.
No, it's not hot yet.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Your tongue is soft and it feels good.
It's hot.
You have a cute tongue.
It feels good.
You're amazing.
You can eat so much.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You're amazing.
It's hot.
You're licking everywhere.
You're amazing.
It's hot.
I can't stand it.
You don't have that, do you?
I don't.
You can't stand it.
You're sweating a lot.
It's okay.
It's hot.
Take your time.
I will.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Let me move it.
It feels good.
I can't move it.
You're amazing.
I can't.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
I can't move it.
I want to take a break.
Did you notice that I was gone?
It's completely different.
I remembered such a pleasant thing.
Do you want me to help you?
I can feel it from the tip of my toes.
I can feel the entrance.
It's amazing.
I can feel it from the tip of my toes.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Don't cry.
More.
Let's go together.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It feels really good.
It's amazing.
I want to do more.
Do you want to do more?
There's a lot in there.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's amazing.
Push it in with one foot.
It's overflowing.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Do more.
It's amazing.
Push it in with one foot.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Let's go.
Don't stop.
Push it in.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
There's a lot in there.
It's amazing.
You pushed it in with one foot.
You slept again.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
You're still standing.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
There's a lot in there.
I see.
You're still standing.
I want to push it in more.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
You pushed it in all the time.
You're still standing.
There's a lot in there.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Which do you like, slow or fast?
I like slow.
I like fast.
It's amazing.
It tickles.
Are you tickling yourself?
I can feel the angle.
It tickles.
I'm embarrassed to look at it.
There's a lot in there.
It tickles.
You're good.
You're going to go while I'm holding your neck.
You're going.
You're going again.
I can't stop.
What should I do?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Can I hold your neck?
It's amazing.
I'm going again.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Good morning.
Wait a minute.
You have an exam today, don't you?
You'll be late.
It's okay.
I can't ski today.
That's not important.
You have to do your best.
I lost.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You're so stiff this morning.
You're stiff.
Are you going to take off your clothes?
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
You're sweating a lot.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You're sweating a lot.
It's hot.
Kiyoko, how did it go?
Were you surprised?
Kamui even lived with our father,
but he divorced due to his father's condition.
Why?
Because I'm sick.
What did you hear?
I'm sick from raising my voice.
Really?
But you love him so much.
I'm sorry.
I left right away.
I felt sick.
Let's do it again.
I feel sick.
You did a good job.
I want to do it again.
Let's do it again.
You did a good job.
I'm sorry.
Let's do it again.
I feel sick.
I'm back.
I bought a souvenir.
Welcome back.
I'm back.
Wait a minute.
It was fast.
It was going well.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
I bought a souvenir.
Thank you.
I'm going to take a shower.
Thank you for watching.