Sorry, but there is.
Oh, is it here?
Yes to.
Thank you very much for using today.
Then the bus starts.
It is OK.
Sorry to.
I like to shoot.
Oh sorry to.
Sorry, but I’m concerned about the smell.
Oh yeah, it is okay.
Sorry to.
You are very well.
A little hungry.
Sorry to
Eating early is not good.
You will eat too early.
Eat it okay.
Eat slowly.
I am hungry, though.
Only this.
They eat a lot.
You are probably hungry.
I haven’t eaten anything since morning.
I think I will manage.
Oh yes yes
If it were good.
I eat the cooking of the strawberries.
Cooking of cakes?
Do you hate the cabbage?
It is a great favorite.
Okay okay?
You are following me, right?
I don’t know your mouth.
I like it.
Good to you.
Okay okay?
Thanks to.
It is delicious.
pleased
My husband, a great favorite.
Is it yes?
But my husband eats.
Okay, okay, there are other things.
Sorry to
Okay, I won’t bother you.
I am waiting a little.
Tastefully
Can you tell me this a little bit more?
I want to take it here...
I bring it to the solo.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Men are nourished, right?
Oh, but I too.
Yes is it.
I am also going to a job interview.
Is it so?
So we have to feed.
Sorry to
Have a good luck.
Thanks to.
I don’t know if I’m light either.
If you can get a job safely.
Maybe live in town.
Make it noisy.
I will definitely nourish you.
Oh, it is awesome.
Sorry to sorry.
Oh yes yes
Okay okay.
This bus is just over time.
I will wait for the upgrade.
Please rest well.
I was tired.
It is up.
Maybe tomorrow.
Can I get it in the Tintin?
Thanks to.
So glad, was it so delicious?
was the best.
Take it home.
I am sitting.
Maybe there is under.
Please rest.
I am sitting.
There is also a seat.
Can I try to close my eyes?
I am sitting.
Then take a rest.
Sorry to
Is it okay?
I cannot sleep.
You will try hard tomorrow.
well
I have to sleep.
Are you moving yourself?
I am doing it.
I will forget too.
Just tell me the name, please.
It is Lily.
Interview and good luck.
Thanks to.
by Adieu
Today, nuNu live is gathered up to the same time as an hour.
In some ways, it makes automatic sounds.
Then I am,
Oh yes yes
Oh thank you.
What about Leica?
Oh no no
The waterfall that moved next door.
If you want, please do this.
Thanks for your politeness.
thanks to
Please read, please please.
Yes, so is
Mr Riley
Not too shift?
Oh no, but
Shamefully
is beautiful.
But why?
I can’t forget about Riley.
But it was a hassle, right?
I was a little surprised.
But maybe glad.
Is it really?
It is beautiful.
Again and again.
Yes is
has come
Mr Milicia
It is the rest, but will it be eaten?
I want to eat.
So please go up.
Okay okay?
Yes is
I will bother you a little.
Sorry, but I haven’t moved a little.
Oh, Harper, you are eating all of this.
Oh yeah yeah
You have to get proper nutrition.
Yes is
Are you hungry?
Yes, it is very empty.
Do not eat.
Oh thank you.
Please go.
I will hinder you.
Yes, I will hinder you.
Your shoulder hurt.
Yes, but not yet
still completely
Please go
Is it really good?
I will eat.
Hand made is delicious.
Oh is?
Yes
Were you so hungry?
Oh yeah yeah
Must eat properly.
Can you eat meat?
Yes
It is meat.
Oh well okay.
Good was
Very delicious.
Yes is.
Yes, it is delicious.
I am pleased.
Very delicious, this
You are good at cooking, boy.
Will you tell me that?
It tastes so good, this.
I have to eat slowly.
The throat will be squeezed.
Best of this.
I am worried, I will make it sometimes.
Oh well okay?
Are you with the shelf now?
Yes, he is sleeping.
I need to go home immediately.
Are you going home now?
Come to the shelf.
See you?
Oh my dear, a little.
Let me tell you.
calm a little.
I struck
Oh yeah yeah.
I will wash you.
Oh is?
was injured.
Oh yeah then
No to No.
I have all.
is okay.
I don’t know if I sleep.
I will follow.
Do not carry.
say something.
I did not understand.
But see it.
Mr. Eric, I can’t stand it anymore.
I have to go home.
No, but I cannot endure.
Oh well awesome.
See also, no.
Just a little bit.
immediately
It is black already.
Just a little.
Yes is
Oh yeah
Sorry very much.
Feels good?
Very good hand.
No change in direction.
Suezwa is moving.
The stomach hurt.
strongly
Tastefully
The stomach hurt.
No to
2nd
She is finally helping the audience.
TM is
Oh is
by DIT
Close your mouth and go.
Show me your mouth.
Did I drink it?
No, a little bit
I am glad.
So is.
I am coming gradually.
Are you going home now?
Maybe go home.
Yes is
Oh is
by DON
by DOKON
Oh yes yes
Good night.
You eat cappuccino.
No, it looks good.
and yeah
Eat the right meal.
Thanks to.
Wait a little.
strongly
It was not enough to pick up.
Oh yeah yeah
Oh yeah
A little
Yes to.
Oh yeah
Oh yeah if.
Yes to.
I went to the store, but it was sold out.
Oh yeah yeah.
Because it is near home.
Yes, yes thanks
Yes, then then
I told him that he was near home.
I understand.
So go home today and open the window.
I chose to go.
He was locked outside the house.
I did.
A good boy.
I want to be a good boy.
already done it.
I will cry.
I am very tired.
Stand up
is beautiful.
by Jia
did it
I can get better in my body.
I also like the thinking of Caroline.
Only one can wash his own heart down.
I moved his fingers.
I will protect his body.
You can put your power in this hand.
If I split his body,
My eyes are small,
Your body is used correctly.
I cut my hair and Christina’s face.
The grandmother’s head.
float well.
Sit in the country and rhythmical.
by
Oh yeah
and more
by
Not okay.
Glad to be.
I am glad you have been with Tito in this way.
The first time I saw him, I thought.
It was so.
I was surprised.
Maybe then I would have put myself somewhere.
No longer do you do that.
But I wanted to do it at that time.
Absolutely
Always be praised.
Okay okay well.
Tell me near.
Yes is.
So here too.
You can sit next to me.
No, not to predict.
Is it so?
So, so too much.
I haven’t started getting in.
Is it so?
It is high, a little.
So to embrace.
I will let the bus light off.
Please rest slowly.
Then rest.
rest to
Ricky, that was it.
Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes
OK is OK.
I say okay.
It was crazy.