Epilogues
Aoyama Suzuki
Yes, thank you for your hard work.
Yes.
Tomorrow, I have to go to the factory to inspect some APOs.
Yes, I think I can get some contracts by the time I get back to Tokyo.
Yes, I'll mail the details to the manager.
Yes, excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Sheesh, she's so annoying.
She's so annoying.
Oh, it's 6pm.
I'll check in at the hotel.
Excuse me.
Thank you for waiting.
This way, please.
May I ask your name?
I'm Sugiura.
I'm Sugiura Takashi.
Mr. Sugiura, thank you for waiting.
This way, please.
Yes.
Thank you.
Welcome back to your room.
The elevator is over there.
Please use it.
Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Your room is on the 7th floor.
Yes.
The elevator is over there.
Please use it.
Yes.
Please let me know if you need anything.
This way, please.
Thank you.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
About this case, I got the client's statement.
Yes.
But I got it confirmed by the manager.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
I'll contact you later.
It's always my fault.
It's annoying.
Yes.
Yes, this is the front desk.
I'm sorry.
I have a favor to ask you.
Can you bring me the sewing tools?
Sewing tools?
Yes, I got it.
I'll bring it to you.
Yes, please.
Yes.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Here are the sewing tools.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
I have a favor to ask you.
Yes.
Just a moment.
Please.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it myself.
No, it's okay.
Did you scratch your back?
I have a computer.
Give me your hand.
I'm sorry.
Here you are.
I came here for a business trip.
But I quarreled with my boss.
He is a very powerful person.
He is responsible for me.
But he forced me to work for him.
When I said back to him, he grabbed my chest.
He was hiding it with his tie.
I'm sorry.
But you are great.
You are young, but you are patient.
You are a good person.
Thank you.
Are you married?
Yes.
Do you have children?
Yes, I have one.
Is he big?
He is a high school student.
High school student?
You look so young.
I didn't think you were so big.
Thank you.
Are you a year old today?
Year old?
Do you work until midnight?
Yes, I do.
But I shouldn't say that.
I'm glad to see a beautiful woman like you again tomorrow morning.
Thank you.
Hello.
I made a snack and put it in the refrigerator.
Please eat it.
My father will make breakfast.
And you shouldn't play games until late at night.
Do you understand?
See you.
I'm sorry.
Is she your daughter?
Yes, she is.
She always plays games without studying.
She is not a child of that age.
My son is playing games on his smartphone all year round.
Sata, can I talk to you for a moment?
Yes.
This is the product of the Asian test you proposed.
I heard that it is popular in the head office.
Really?
The head office will hold a game on the 5th of next month.
I'll put you in the shift.
I'm nervous.
Don't worry, Sata.
We'll be together until the morning.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Yes, this is the head office.
Yes.
Yes, understood.
Yes, I'll bring it right away.
What's the matter?
It seems that your bed is dirty.
I'll bring the bed sheets.
The staff is leaving at this time.
I can't ask you to change the bed sheets.
No, I'll do it.
Don't worry.
Yes.
It's a little early, but you can take a rest in the hair salon.
No, I'm fine.
That's good.
Most of the customers are back today.
Take a rest early sometimes.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry for talking to you.
Yes.
I'll go.
Yes, see you.
I'll go home soon.
I see.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll do my best.
See you.
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
Can I open the front door?
Don't worry.
There is another person.
I'm sorry.
I spilled alcohol.
I was worried about my boss.
If I didn't drink alcohol, I would have exploded.
Don't worry.
Don't rely on alcohol.
I'm sorry.
When I spilled alcohol on the bed, the person in front of me did it.
The staff who made the bed has already left.
I'm lucky to meet you again.
I was frustrated.
My heart was about to explode.
Don't worry.
You can't drink anymore.
You're drunk.
I'll drink a little more.
No.
I'm sorry.
I spilled alcohol.
I'm lonely.
Please stay with me tonight.
If you stay with me, I won't be broken.
I'm sorry.
I can't drink anymore.
Please stop.
I'm lonely.
You can't drink anymore.
Please stop.
I can't drink anymore.
I'm sorry.
Do you know Wakante?
Look at this.
It's Wakante.
Wakante.
We're doing this on purpose.
What are you doing?
You seduced me.
Hey.
You showed me your butt.
If you show me this video, no one will know.
Please stop.
Hey.
That video...
No.
And...
A hotel manager came to my room at this time.
Please stop.
What are you talking about?
You knew I was drinking and practicing.
No.
Please stop.
I was drunk.
If other people see this video, what will you do?
What are you talking about? I didn't do that.
You saw the video.
You seduced me.
No.
Please stop.
What are you doing?
I'm here.
Please stop.
If you were a high school student, you would be in puberty.
What are you talking about?
Are you a boy or a girl?
Please stop.
I'm a girl.
You're a girl.
If you were a high school student...
Please stop.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
What are you doing?
I can't move.
No.
Please stop.
Sir.
Hey.
If you make a loud voice, it will be heard by other people.
Can't you hold your voice?
What are you doing?
No.
Please stop.
Why are you here?
Can't you sleep?
What are you talking about?
That's not true.
No.
You have a good posture.
Please stop.
You're crying.
Suta-san.
Don't cry.
You're crying.
What are you doing?
I didn't think you hated it so much.
Please stop.
Please.
I can't.
I can't hold it anymore.
No.
No. Stop.
Stop.
No.
Suta-san.
Stop.
No.
Suta-san.
You're alone.
That's right.
Stop.
I don't know because I didn't give you a birth yet.
Did you really give birth?
Stop.
No.
Suta-san.
Every time a woman gives birth, she loses her place.
Suta-san's place.
Suta-san's place is not like that at all.
You seem to feel very good.
No.
Stop it.
Please.
No.
What are you doing?
Stop.
No.
Sir.
Please.
Please forgive me.
How can I say this?
Suta-san who seduced you is wrong, isn't he?
What are you saying?
Are you going to blame me?
Stop.
It's impossible.
Please stop.
No.
Stop.
Sir.
What are you doing?
Why are you so wet?
No.
Do you think it's okay for a woman to be wet?
What are you talking about?
Stop.
Let me go.
Women are like that, aren't they?
No.
Stop.
The woman who seduced you looked very happy.
What are you talking about?
My Chimpo is popular with the women in the hotel.
Suta-san, please try it.
No.
Stop.
Open your mouth wider.
You can tell what it's like once you bite it, right?
That image will remain for a long time.
Have you ever heard of a digital tattoo?
I'll cut your tail.
It feels good.
Open your mouth wider.
Suta-san, I won't hurt you if you do as I say.
Listen to me.
No.
Suta-san, open your mouth wider.
It feels good.
Open your mouth wider.
Stop.
Where are you going?
I can't see you.
Suta-san.
I thought I could see you.
Stop.
Please.
You can't move because it's too painful, right?
What are you going to do?
Do you want me to erase the image in front of you?
Please erase it.
What are you going to do?
Look.
No.
You look so happy.
Stop.
Please stop.
I want you to say it.
Suta-san.
Why don't you say it honestly?
Why are you running away?
No.
You're a boy.
You know what I mean, right?
Stop.
Don't you know how to open this properly?
You know how to open this, right?
I told you.
No.
Stop.
Please take it off.
Suta-san.
Stop.
You're really a boy, right?
No.
What are you doing?
Suta-san.
Do you think it's okay to do this?
At this point,
I'm more nervous than ever.
Stop.
No.
How do you feel?
Do you want me to pat you?
No.
How do you feel?
It feels good, right?
No.
Stop.
Please.
No.
Stop.
Suta-san.
You're a boy, right?
Why are you doing this to me?
You know how to do it, right?
No.
Suta-san, you know how to do it, right?
Stop.
No.
Why did you do that?
Stop.
How many times did you do that?
You did it many times, right?
No, I didn't.
No.
Stop.
You know how to do it, right?
No.
Stop.
What are you doing?
Is there something wrong with you?
No.
Stop.
Suta-san.
Suta-san's senpai is here.
No.
Does it feel good enough to make you cry?
Stop.
Suta-san, I don't think you're a child.
And you're moving so much.
I can't stop.
Why are you doing this to me?
Stop.
If you can't get your tongue out, I'll tear it off.
You don't need this, do you?
But I want to kiss you more.
Stop.
No.
What's wrong?
Stop.
I know.
You can do it.
That's right, Suta-san.
You can do it, so stop.
No.
Stop.
You're moving so much.
I'm happy.
Please stop.
You're crying because you can't blame me, right?
Stop.
No.
No?
It feels good.
It's good.
Did you think you could stop now?
I don't want to stop because it feels good, Suta-san.
Stop.
It's good.
You can't go on like this.
Stop.
No.
You can't.
Stop.
Please stop.
It's good.
Stop.
Suta-san, please stop.
Suta-san, come here.
What are you going to do?
What am I going to do?
You know what I'm going to do.
Look.
What are you going to do?
Stop.
Look.
Look at this.
Stop.
Now we're even.
Maybe.
Look.
It's a two-shot.
Actually, Sata-san seduced me, so I'm sorry.
As a hotel manager, I'm disqualified.
Drinking in a guest room and having sex.
Suta-san.
You took a good picture.
Sutan.
Have you eaten yet?
Yes, I have.
What's wrong?
You always say you're hungry.
Yes, I'll leave it to you.
I see.
Then, let's have pasta after changing.
No, let's go to a family restaurant.
Momo said there's a pizza toast.
Let's go there.
I love the coffee there.
Excuse me.
I left my work, so I'll go back.
You can leave it to someone else.
Excuse me.
Yes, that's right.
It's the same as the e-mail I sent yesterday.
Yes.
It's okay.
Excuse me.
I'm at the company now.
I'll call you later.
Excuse me.
It's the same as always.
Please come in.
What are you doing?
You really came in a uniform.
You look like you haven't told anyone about me.
That's right.
I can't tell anyone about that.
Because...
I can't make excuses with this.
I was told to upload this picture on the Internet.
I really believed it.
I don't want to show my mother to my child.
I'm going to ask my daughter to be my friend.
Please don't.
Digital tattoos will last a lifetime.
I just want to touch your body.
That's enough to erase this picture.
Please give it back to me.
Let's stop doing that.
Put your tongue out.
Hurry up.
You have a long tongue.
I don't want to.
Did you forget the picture?
Put your tongue out.
Come on.
I can't.
Please stop.
Don't resist.
I told you before.
I just want to touch your body.
I don't want to.
Let me see.
Open your legs.
I can't.
Please stop.
It's wet.
No, it's not.
Please stop.
What is this?
It's not wet.
Let me see.
It's wet.
I can't.
Let me see your face.
Please stop.
How do you feel?
It's getting wet.
Please stop.
It's wet.
Sit down.
What are you looking at?
I don't want you to feel bad.
You should have fun with me.
It feels good.
Please stop.
You are always honest.
I don't want you to get excited.
Please stop.
I can't.
You can't?
Look at your face.
What's wrong with you?
I can't.
You look lonely.
It's not true.
You are wearing a mask.
I can't.
Look at me.
I don't want you to do this.
Don't make my room dirty.
It's getting wet.
Please stop.
I don't want you to feel bad.
I can't.
Don't move.
Please stop.
I can't.
Don't move.
You can see your face in the mirror.
I can't.
Please stop.
Are you mad?
I can't.
Please stop.
You look happy.
I can't.
Please stop.
Are you mad?
I can't.
Please stop.
Let's be happy together.
I can't.
Please stop.
You look happy.
I can't.
Please stop.
You look happy.
I can't.
Please stop.
I wonder if you were raised freely in this big world.
Let me be free, too.
Please stop.
You look happy.
I can't.
Please stop.
You are weak.
I can't.
Please sit on me.
Can't you move?
I can't.
If you can't move, I will.
Please stop.
Please.
I can't.
Please don't push me.
Even if you feel good.
I can't.
Please stop.
I've been doing this all the time.
I can't.
Please stop.
Are you going to work tomorrow?
You don't have to say it.
You are going to work.
Please tell me your phone number.
I can't.
Please stop.
Give it back.
I can't.
Please stop.
I can contact you anytime with this.
For example.
Such a photo.
I can give you such a photo anytime.
What do you think if your daughter sees it?
Please stop.
One day, I got such a photo on my daughter's phone.
I can't.
Please delete it.
Mr.Sugiura.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I have something to tell you.
What's up?
What can I do for you?
Excuse me.
You will be found out.
I don't mind being found out.
Please stop.
I can't.
Sir.
What should I do?
Please stop.
I can't.
You will be found out.
Please stop.
I can't.
Sir.
Please stop.
I can't.
Try to taste it.
How does it taste?
I know you are wet.
Be honest.
I can't.
Please stop.
Please.
I can't.
Please stop.
Is that so?
I didn't know that.
Please.
I can't.
Please stop.
Sir.
I can't.
Please stop.
Tokyu-sensei?
Tokyu-sensei.
Okay, let's do it.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Haruka, are you listening to me?
No, I'm not.
Tokyu-sensei.
No.
Please stop.
Tokyu-sensei.
No.
Please stop.
Are you staying the night?
Yes, I am.
Okay.
Thank you.
What's your name?
I'm Takahashi.
Oh, Mr. Takahashi.
This way, please.
Just your name.
Oh, this way, please.
Okay.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Okay.
A customer in room 406 moved to room 502 because she didn't like the kitchen.
I see.
Oh, what did you do the day before yesterday?
Oh, the day before yesterday?
You know, when I invited you to my house in the morning.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't a big job.
I was a little worried.
I see.
Yes.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Well, I got a call from my daughter.
At this time?
Yes.
She said she had a stomachache.
Oh, really?
Maybe that's why.
Oh, my. Are you okay?
Yes.
I'll call you back.
What?
Tomita-san.
Yes.
I put the accommodation fee and the current accommodation fee together.
Oh, okay.
Okay, I got it.
Room 502
Oh, my.
Please don't do this.
What if it hurts?
Sato-san.
You were wetting here on the front.
Oh, my.
I can't believe you're wetting there.
You're like Sasuke.
Please don't do this.
What if someone comes?
What?
Please don't do this.
What are you talking about, Sato-san?
No.
On the contrary, what would you do if your children saw that video?
Please don't do this.
I just kissed you.
Don't get used to it.
I'm sleepy.
No.
You're so wet.
Please don't do this.
No.
Oh, my.
Are you okay?
No.
Please don't do this.
I just kissed you.
No.
Please don't do this.
What are you doing?
I've always wanted to touch you.
Sato-san.
What are you doing?
No.
Please don't do this.
I'm tired.
No.
Let's do something more pleasant.
Please don't do this.
I'm sleepy.
I'm just watching you.
Please don't do this.
No.
Sato-san.
Why do you always try to make yourself feel better?
Please don't do this.
What's the matter?
Who do you think you are?
I'm sorry.
Please make yourself feel better before anyone else does.
That's what you should do.
I'm sleepy.
Come on.
You...
Please make yourself feel better before anyone else does.
Sato-san.
You're a proper motel man.
You know how to make yourself feel better, don't you?
You're so stubborn.
Sato-san.
Please make yourself feel better before anyone else does.
I can't do this anymore.
Please don't do this.
Come on in.
You're just in time.
It's cold.
Sato-san.
Let's do a lot of nice things together.
I'm done with this.
Stop it.
Sato-san.
You've grown this big.
What are you talking about?
Stop it.
Please stop it.
Huh?
Sato-san.
No.
You're wetter than before.
Stop it.
Where are you going?
Sato-san.
Stop it.
I said stop it.
Sato-san.
Let's do a lot of nice things together.
I still have a video.
Give it back.
I can't erase it.
Please.
It's in my cell phone forever.
Stop it.
Where are you running away?
There's no place to run away.
If you go out, there are customers.
Let's stay here together.
Look, Sato-san.
This face of a dog.
You feel it, don't you?
I don't feel.
Look in the mirror more.
I want to make sure everyone's inside.
Stop it.
Sato-san.
Look in the mirror.
Don't you feel it?
This.
Stop it.
Sato-san.
If you go out like this,
it's the worst.
Your daughter will see the video.
Stop it.
Then listen to me.
Sato-san.
You'll feel better.
Stop it.
I feel good.
You feel it, don't you?
Look in the mirror.
I feel good.
Sato-san.
I can't take it anymore.
I want you to hit me here.
I feel good.
Look at your face.
Can you see your face?
I feel good.
You look like you want to hit me.
I can't.
Stop it.
Look at your face.
I can't.
Stop it.
Sato-san.
You can't take it anymore, can you?
I can't.
Stop it.
Be honest.
Feel it.
I can't.
You're doing something amazing.
You're overreacting.
I can't.
Try to move in a comfortable way.
How do you feel?
I can't.
You're getting better, Sato-san.
How do you feel?
I can't.
Sato-san, how do you feel?
How do you feel?
I can't.
Look at me.
I can't anymore.
Listen to me.
What are you going to do now?
I can't.
How do you feel?
How do you feel, Sato-san?
I can't.
I can't move.
Move more.
I can't.
Let's have more fun.
Let's.
I can't.
You can't die like that.
Let's go.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't hold it in.
Sato-san was too emotional.
I'm sorry.
I can't.