When you develop your skills, your connection with people changes.
You came in a little late yesterday though.
Yeah.
Did you have a proper dinner?
I had dinner with the employees.
It was either beef bowl or pizza.
Well, it can't be helped if you work overtime.
I wish you could take a little more time.
Yeah.
I'm busy now.
I can't take care of my diet.
I see.
I wish you could take a little more time.
Do you want to go somewhere?
Yeah.
Hot spring.
Let's go when you calm down.
Yeah.
Please let me sleep here.
I'm sorry, Egawa-kun.
It's okay.
You drink too much.
Well, it can't be helped because I'm a company employee.
What? You're a company employee?
Don't you know that?
What do you mean?
Our company is in trouble now.
Our software is full of bugs.
We were refused to sign a contract.
And we spent a lot of money on the development team.
What do you mean?
Is that true?
If it goes on like this, our company will go bankrupt.
Was our company in such a situation?
We were refused to sign a contract with a bank.
And we have to rely on Mr. Yamane.
Who is Mr. Yamane?
He's an individual investor and the owner of our company.
But the president seems to hate Mr. Yamane very much.
It's not the time to say whether I like him or not.
The president is very proud.
So, he won't go to Mr. Yamane.
Oh, right.
If it's okay with you,
your wife can ask Mr. Yamane.
Me?
Yes.
Welcome.
Come in.
Yes.
So,
what does the wife of Mr. Yamane want from me?
Well,
I'm here to ask you for a favor.
Oh,
do you have an order?
Yes.
Oh, I see.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Did you tell the president of Mishima that you would come here?
No.
I see.
Then, show me your attitude.
My attitude?
Yes.
Hurry up.
I see.
You're here to ask me for a favor, aren't you?
Yes.
I'll do my best.
Your wife...
Shh!
I see.
You should kneel down.
No, I don't want to.
You're here to ask me for a favor, aren't you?
Yes.
I'll do my best.
Well,
you don't have to think about it.
It's up to you.
Oh, no.
Please don't.
You don't have to be prepared.
I'm prepared.
Then, show me.
I can't understand.
I'll do my best.
You can't do anything with words.
Even if you say so,
here you are.
I said it's up to you.
If you do your best,
Mr. Mihama will help you.
Yes.
That's all.
No, it's not.
I feel sorry for your wife.
I'll do my best.
No, you can't.
I'll pay you back someday.
Someday?
You have to pay me first.
Now?
Yes, now.
Well...
Just say it.
What?
I'm sorry.
Mr. Mihama
Hello.
Miki, where is the president?
What?
Is he all right?
I don't know.
Do you want something to drink?
No, thank you.
President.
Honey.
When I tried to go to the deal,
he collapsed suddenly.
What?
Don't exaggerate.
I told you to take care of your health.
I'm fine.
I'll take a rest today.
Mr. Mihama collapsed.
What?
Did your wife eat something strange?
No, she didn't.
You know what to do, don't you?
I'll do my best.
Please go home.
Thank you.
Do it from the beginning.
Take off your clothes.
What?
Are you going to be late again?
No, I'm not.
You're here to tell your wife, aren't you?
Yes, I understand.
Take off your clothes.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
You're flustered, aren't you?
You're nervous because you want to see him again, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Your wife is big.
What are you embarrassed about?
Hurry up.
Okay.
You're wearing a cute shirt.
What are you doing?
Don't take it off.
You're here to get your money back, aren't you?
That's right.
Please don't.
That's enough.
Go home.
Please go home.
I took it off.
I need money.
You have no choice but to listen to me.
I understand.
Put your hands behind your back.
Look at me.
Hurry up.
Like this?
Of course.
Come closer.
Hurry up.
Look at me.
Like this?
You're wearing a nice shirt.
Sit down.
What are you doing?
Hurry up.
Spread your legs.
Okay.
Why are you embarrassed?
Look at me.
You're still hiding.
I have to tell you twice.
I'm sorry.
Look at me.
Your hands are in the way.
You're wearing a nice shirt.
Spread your legs.
Look at me.
I want to take a picture of your face.
Okay.
Look at me and make an excuse.
Make me feel bad.
That's how you become brave.
Okay.
Touch me.
Look at me.
You have to make me feel bad.
I can't get excited.
Okay.
You have to make me laugh.
Look at me.
You don't have to do that.
Your legs are closing.
Think about yourself.
Okay.
Do you always do that alone?
No.
You want to feel better, don't you?
Keep doing it.
Okay.
I can't tell if you look at me or not.
You're boring.
Be brave.
Okay.
That's how you become brave.
Are you underestimating me?
No, I'm not.
You can't even say it.
I'm doing it.
You're pretending to do it.
You're an adult.
Show me.
Don't be a pervert.
Okay.
Show me.
You're getting better.
Your legs are closing.
You're trying to get excited.
No, I'm not.
No, you're not.
Your voice is getting better.
Do you want me to help you?
What?
Keep doing it.
Okay.
Don't expect too much.
Look at me.
Okay.
Do you feel better?
No, I don't.
Don't lie to me.
Okay.
It's better to lie to someone.
That's right.
Do you feel better?
Yes, I do.
You're brave.
Okay.
Show me more.
It's close.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Look at me.
I'm helping you.
Thank you.
You don't feel anything.
You're boring.
Is that all?
No, it's not.
I see.
Show me your action.
Hurry up.
You know what I mean, right?
Yes, I do.
Why did you touch me?
What?
I told you.
I didn't say anything.
I just said I know.
Did you want to touch me?
No.
Say you want to touch me.
Hurry up.
I want to touch you.
Please.
You're clumsy.
Hurry up.
Please.
I want to touch you.
You're clumsy.
Hurry up.
I want to touch you.
Please.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Rub it well.
I can't feel your hand.
Okay.
I can't do it.
It's not enough.
What?
I did my best.
It's not enough.
I'll do my best.
Okay.
Please.
I can't feel your hand.
Do you want to touch me?
Yes.
If you say so,
I can't feel your hand.
I'll do my best.
Please.
Rub it well.
Okay.
Don't be shy.
Hurry up.
Okay.
It's been a long time.
Thank you.
You're so desperate.
Yes, I am.
I can't feel your hand.
What should I do?
Well...
Do you want me to show you how to do it?
Try it.
Okay.
Hurry up.
You're weak.
I'll give you a snack.
Okay.
It's good, isn't it?
Yes.
You're so weak.
I'll give you a snack.
Okay.
You're so weak.
I'll give you a snack.
Okay.
You're so weak.
I'll give you a snack.
Okay.
Do you want me to do it?
Do it yourself.
I didn't ask you to stop.
I'll give you a snack if you get angry.
I'm sorry.
I told you to stand up.
You're in a bad condition.
Hurry up.
Say, please.
Please.
What should I do?
If you say so,
I have no choice but to think about it.
Do you lick your face?
No, I don't.
You have a lot of hair on your hands.
You have to use it.
Yes.
I want you to lick my hand.
Do you know that?
Yes.
You have to rest your hands and wash your mouth.
Where are you going?
Look at me.
You are trembling.
Let's do it now.
Come here.
Show me there.
Again?
Again.
Come on.
Like this?
Yes, hurry up.
Okay.
Do it like this.
Touch me.
Show me your private part.
Trust is important.
You have to be careful.
Okay.
It's a little close.
Keep doing it.
Okay.
Let's do it again.
Keep doing it.
Touch me.
Touch your private part.
Okay.
Look at me.
It's a little big.
You like big things, don't you?
My stomach hurts.
You are trembling.
Your hands are not stopped.
My stomach hurts.
Let's do it again.
Okay.
What?
I'm helping you.
Are you happy?
Thank you very much.
It's getting a little cold, isn't it?
Touch your private part.
I think one is not enough.
What?
Hold your feet.
This part, too.
Hold your feet firmly.
It's very tight.
It's not like that.
Don't lick such a dirty thing.
It can't be helped.
It feels good to be licked by yourself, doesn't it?
Yes, it feels good.
You are very honest.
If you are so honest, as a man, you should be quiet.
Do you want me to make you feel good?
Say something.
Yes, please.
Do you want me to make you feel good?
Yes.
Then, roll over.
Here?
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Wait a minute.
Please.
Please let me in.
Let me in.
I can't do anything but licking you.
Is that so?
Let's go to bed.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Your mouth is lonely.
What are you going to do?
What are you doing?
Good night.
Don't move because it's easy for me to move.
Don't move.
You move too much.
That's why you like me.
You surprised me.
You didn't do anything with me.
I don't do anything private.
You don't do anything private.
You've been saying that for a while.
I didn't say that.
You didn't say that for a while.
Don't lie.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'll be nice to you.
Please.
You're getting older.
I'm sorry.
Do you do this to Miyama?
No.
What do you do to Miyama?
I don't do it recently.
You don't do it recently.
You're lucky.
Did you come here for this?
I'll do it myself.
Oh, I see.
Come on.
Move your wrist too.
Let me see your face.
It hurts.
Let me see.
Show me how serious you are.
I don't want to.
Do it.
It feels good.
I'll speed up.
Look at me.
Don't make a noise.
Okay.
It hurts.
I have underwear.
Give me your underwear.
You can do it if you want.
It hurts.
Don't make a noise.
You can do it if you want.
It feels good.
Don't make a noise.
You can do it if you want.
It hurts.
I'll speed up.
I can't stop.
It hurts.
Let me go.
You're so funny.
Wait a minute.
Please go home.
Is this a bath?
It's small.
Don't open the door.
It's okay.
I'll speed up.
What are you doing?
I'm frying.
You can wear shoes.
I can't.
It's okay.
Where is it?
Don't go into the bedroom.
Are you sleeping with Mihama here?
Which one are you using?
It smells.
Don't do that.
Why are you in the bed?
You like sex, don't you?
No.
Why are you inviting me?
I'm not inviting you.
Don't get me wrong.
What do you want me to do?
It's not like that.
Do you want me to shut up?
I've been waiting for you.
It's a little close.
I don't know if it's close.
You're getting excited.
You're opening your mouth.
I'm sorry.
You look like a woman.
I'm scared.
Why?
Do you want me to be cute?
I don't know.
I want you to be cute.
Do you want me to be cute?
I don't know.
If you want me to be cute,
Don't you want me to touch you?
Please touch me.
Where?
I want you to touch me on my skin.
On your skin?
Here?
Yes.
Good.
You're getting excited.
What's this?
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
It's too late.
I'll take it off myself.
Put it on me.
Yes.
I'll put it on you.
What do you want me to do?
Please lick my neck.
Why are you so cute?
Are you the only one who feels good?
I feel good.
You like sex so much.
I'll put it on you.
You know what I mean, right?
Hurry up.
Move forward.
Look at me.
You can't be so slow.
You don't understand unless I do this.
Open your mouth.
Open your eyes.
Take off your top.
You have beautiful teeth.
It's a waste if you don't use them.
Yes.
You know what I mean, right?
You can't do it well.
You are so excited.
You told me to do it.
What are you biting?
You are trembling.
That's right.
Are you doing it for Mihama-kun?
Then just me?
What? Do you like me?
I do.
What?
It's for Hiroshi.
I wonder if you'll say that at a time like this.
To be honest with your body.
You're always sandwiched.
It's on your nipples.
Huh?
Feels good.
It's soft, isn't it?
That's the way to do it.
Licking.
Do you want me to take care of you that much?
Okay, okay.
Why are you resisting?
That's not the way to do it.
It's soft, isn't it?
Okay, okay.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's soft, isn't it?
That's the way to do it.
You're resisting.
You're happy, aren't you?
The other side.
Hold on tight.
It's soft, isn't it?
It's wet, isn't it?
Look at me.
Touch me.
It's soft, isn't it?
Touch my nipple.
I'll put my finger in it.
It's not enough.
What are you feeling?
It's hard, isn't it?
It's hot.
What?
It's hard, isn't it?
Turn around.
What do you want me to do?
From behind.
What?
Please step forward.
You can't be in that position.
From behind.
Please.
You don't have to be in that position.
Get down.
It feels good.
Do you like me?
You're very honest.
I have to be honest.
You can do whatever you want.
It feels good.
I'll help you.
Don't get up.
I'm tired.
It's your turn.
Move.
Don't move your boobs too much.
Does it hurt?
Are you happy now?
No, I'm not.
You're happy, aren't you?
Don't move your boobs too much.
You're already awake, aren't you?
You look like you're in a bad mood.
Look at me.
Don't look away.
Don't move your boobs too much.
Don't hit me.
Look at me.
Don't look away.
Don't move your boobs too much.
Look at me.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're almost there.
It's not over yet.
Lean on me.
It's time to eat.
Incredible.
It looks delicious.
You're a great cook, Megwin.
Can I have it?
Thank you.
That's great.
Do you prepare a dinner?
I don't think so.
That's great.
Mr. Yamane.
Good morning.
What's wrong, Mr. Yamane?
Mr. Nihama.
It seems that the company is strict.
Let's talk in the back.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't leave him alone as an investor.
Yes.
Let the employees talk within 10 minutes.
What?
I can't.
You can, Baishun.
Are you okay?
Are you from the company?
Yes.
I've been working here since spring.
Who are you?
I'm Nihama's wife.
Are you the president?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Tuno.
Don't tell anyone.
Come with me.
Wait a minute.
Where are you going?
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
I'll do it for you.
No.
I can't do it.
It's okay.
Don't tell anyone.
My chest hurts.
Do you like me?
I like you.
But I can't.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Does it hurt?
If I touch you, I'll get a bruise.
Are you okay?
I don't know if anyone is listening.
Look at me.
I can't touch you.
I don't want to touch you.
Wait a minute.
Why are you doing this?
I have to do this.
The president is here.
What's wrong?
I can't do this.
Wait a minute.
Please forgive me.
It's okay.
I can't do this.
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
I can't do this.
Why?
Let's stop this.
I can't do this.
It's okay.
What do you want to do?
I have a lot of things.
What do you have?
I can't do this.
Do you like bamboo?
Yes.
I can't do this.
Come here.
Here.
Good girl.
It's time to go home for dinner.
Are you ready?
Stop it!
What happened to your elbow?
Where is the camera?
I don't have it.
See what?
OK, I got it.
Take your phone and put it in your bag.
My phone?
Yes.
Give me your bag.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Yes.
Has it been 10 minutes?
I don't know.
Please don't tell the president.
This is a secret.
Yes.
Are you tired?
No.
Is it because it's dark?
Everyone was happy with the lunch box.
I'm sorry.
Can you make it again today?
Yes.
Come a little later.
I want to feed the people who are working overtime.
Okay.
Can I really do it?
You don't have a company, do you?
Yes.
I got a commission from the bank.
I see.
Why don't you make me your wife?
What?
Do you feel better?
Tell me clearly.
I was very tired and went home.
When I got home,
the room was clean.
The room was clean.
What are you doing?
There is ah information on the table.
There is aosh information on the table.
You can leave it.
I'm already working hard.
There was a lot of family pranks.
I was furious at my wife.
Why are you trying to be happy by yourself?
She couldn't forgive me.
So, do you want to get back at her?
No.
I just want to break her heart.
You're crazy.
I'm sorry.
I'm so tired.
I left my chocolate here.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
No, I'm fine.
Good evening.
Hey, Reniki.
Come on in.
I thought you might be hungry.
Really?
Thank you.
Here you are.
I'm so happy.
I love you, Miki.
Me, too.
You mean the lunch box, right?
No, I love you, Miki.
Stop it.
I love you.
I love you, Miki.
Stop it.
By the way, did your wife say anything strange to you?
My wife?
I don't know.
Did she?
Which one?
I don't know.
Stop it.
Where are you touching?
I'm scared.
Please be quiet.
Are you doing this?
No, I'm not.
I've always wanted to make you happy.
I was happy when I saw you at the wedding.
I'm glad to see you all.
Stop it.
Don't touch me.
Don't move.
Put your tongue out.
Stop it.
You're disgusting.
Open your mouth.
Put your tongue out.
Disgusting.
That's right.
Give me a kiss.
I'm glad to see you all.
Stop it.
You're dirty.
I'll show you.
You're disgusting.
You're the best.
You're beautiful.
You're getting a little chubby.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Wow,
it's coming out soon.
It's good
.
I've always wanted to see it.
Look over here.
No, please stop.
I don't think he's licking it.
It's not a manga.
He's licking it.
Keep going.
I can't stand it.
Wow, it's getting hot in here.
His legs are open.
It's hot.
I can't stand it.
His butt is also open.
How is it?
It's really hot.
I can't stand it.
It's hot.
Is that so?
Wow,
it's hot.
I don't like it.
It's really beautiful.
I'll put it here.
Please let me go.
Where do you want me to lick?
He's crazy.
The hair's also turned blue.
What do you like?
I love that.
It smells good.
Hey, are you stupid?
Come on, get on this side
Put your back on it
You are great
Hold your legs
Good
You are so wet
Don't hide it
Are you excited?
You are lying
Tell me the truth
Are you excited?
A little bit
You are the best
Let's have fun
Does it feel good?
You can't touch the blanket
I want you to do this
Let me see
Show me
Come on
One, two
You are such a good boy
Let me see you
You are so beautiful
Open your mouth
You are such a good boy
Can I touch you?
Good for you
I didn't say I like you
Can I touch you?
You are such a good boy
Keep doing it
Do you want to show me?
Show me
You are such a good boy
You should tell me when you are going
I brought something interesting
What is it?
You put it in your bag?
What's wrong?
You are not the first time, right?
Does it feels good?
It feels great, right?
It feels great
Come on, come on
You are such a good boy.
Look at this side, too.
I will put it on your belly.
Do you want me to put it on your belly?
Please.
I will put it on your belly.
I will put it on your belly, too.
You are such a good boy.
Do you feel good?
Do you feel good, Miki-san?
Both of them.
Both of them?
Do you think I will go crazy if I have both of them?
Please say it clearly.
I will go crazy if I have both of them.
You are the best.
Do you feel good?
Are you going to go crazy?
Please say it clearly.
You are such a good boy.
You fell down.
Let's go to bed.
Good boy.
You seem to want something in your mouth.
You want something in your mouth.
No?
You feel good, don't you?
You are such a good boy.
That's why I think you are cute.
Do you think it's okay for me to do this?
You can't be satisfied with this.
You feel good, don't you?
What are you talking about?
But...
What will happen if you put this in your mouth?
You can't say such a thing.
You can open your mouth by yourself.
Okay.
You put it in your mouth.
When you put it in your mouth, show it to me.
It's good.
You feel good.
You can see it, right?
You have to say it feels good
It feels good
Let's move this
How is it?
Does it feel good?
Wow, you are full of energy
You are full of energy
I'm glad you are full of energy
You remember it feels good, right?
Yeah, I do
You can do it
Hold it
Hold it, Chiku
Here you go.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
You should let out all the blood!
Greeeeat!
I know you love us, our pretty savords.
Still going toferthe sacrifice of son.
We're all gonna be one body and I'm gonna make it secondary for you.
You are a good boy.
He is going to sleep.
Open your mouth.
Do you want me to wipe your face?
Good boy.
You are a good boy.
Do you want me to wipe your face?
You like a hard work, don't you?
You move too much.
Do you feel good?
Thank you.
Do you want me to wipe your face?
Open your mouth.
You have a good face.
Do you feel good?
What's wrong?
You can do it yourself.
You have a bad mouth.
But you feel good, don't you?
You feel good.
Look at me.
You are so cute
Don't come close to my face
How do you feel?
You are trembling
You are so cute
Don't come close to my face
Miki-san, come here
Sit here
Open your mouth
I'll give you a foot massage
How do you feel?
You still have some hair left.
There is smoke now.
Let's do it again.
You want to eat two?
You want to be extravagant?
You look good
You have a big belly
Your mom is here
Your mom left you
Are you enjoying?
Here we go
This is a lot
Aren't you watching me I-chan?
Wow, you are very strong.
You are a very good girl.
Miki-chan, how do you feel?
It's big.
It's big, isn't it?
Yes.
You have a lot of hair.
Good.
You are very good.
You are the best.
Do you want me to brush your teeth?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It hurts.
You have a lot of hair in your mouth.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You don't have any hair, so you should enjoy it.
Do what you want to do.
You have a lot of hair in your mouth.
You look happy.
I'll brush your teeth.
Do what you want to do.
You have a lot of hair in your mouth.
We're off to Dora's house
Don't pull me
Let's go over here
Are you tired?
No, I'm not
It looks like you'll get it eventually.
Thanks for helping me!
Go, go, go!
If you don't say, go, go...
I'm so tired!
Look, he's smiling!
He's smiling!
Good morning.
Ready?
You really want to stir him, don't you?
You're opening your  right now
You like it?
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
You're the only one who feels good.
I know.
You like me the most, don't you?
That's right.
It's time to get up.
Does it feel good?
You're the only one who feels good.
That's right.
It's time to get up.
I'm really tired.
I can do it.
Come on, get up.
You're very energetic.
Do you like it?
Yes.
You're having fun, aren't you?
It's time to have sex.
Come on, get up.
You're very energetic.
It's time to have sex.
Does it feel good?
Do you want to have sex?
Yes.
Do you like me?
Say it again.
I like you.
It's time to have sex.
Do you like me?
Ah!
Say it again.
Let me live again.
What?
I want to sing.
You want to live?
Ah!
Let me put you on the floor.
Tell me what you want me to do.
I want you to do it for me.
What? Tell me.
Where? Tell me.
I want you to do it for me.
I'll do it for you tomorrow.
Spread your butt.
I'll do it for you.
Do you feel the pain?
Yes.
Give me your hand.
You're strong.
I'll do it for you.
Do it.
Do you feel the pain?
No.
I'll do it for you.
I'm scared.
Come here.
You're weak.
I'll do it for you.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad you love me.
I'm tired.
Why?
I don't have a place to go home.
I can't live without working.
I'll do my best to work.
Are you desperate?
I'll think about it.
I'll go first.
Thank you for your hard work.
You made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
You always make a mistake.
Would you like some tea?
Yes, please.
Be careful.
I'm sorry.