I'm going to get married to a husband who's a year older than me, and live a life where nothing changes.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
I'm with Daichi today.
Hello.
Welcome.
Let's go to the room.
Give me some tea.
Okay.
I wanted to feel the meaning of life.
Daichi, have a seat.
Thank you.
Daichi, how's it going with your girlfriend?
She's doing well.
How about you?
Have you talked to her yet?
It's hard to fall in love.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Okay.
I told you I'm going to a party tonight.
I'll be waiting for you.
She's not coming tonight.
Come back before someone sees us.
Please.
I want to hug you just once.
Daichi.
That was the meaning of life for my son's friend.
It was winter five years ago.
We lived in the same apartment.
Okay.
You can eat later.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Your mom is having a hard time.
She has to make a living on her own.
We have to help each other.
At that time, my husband's cheating was found.
It was the worst thing for the couple.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Bye.
Hey.
What I'm going to say is just a word.
So...
Let me say it.
I...
I like you.
What?
I learned how much I loved him.
Mom.
You're late.
Yes.
Mom.
Can you keep it a secret?
Yes.
Mom.
I didn't care who he was if I could make him feel lonely.
I...
I've never done this before.
I won't say anything.
Let me see.
I...
Have you ever taken off your bra?
I don't know.
I'll teach you.
Pull the hook.
Like this.
I did it.
Can I touch you?
Yes.
Touch me gently.
It feels good.
I want to lick you.
Will you lick me?
Yes.
Do you want to put it in?
Do you have a rubber band?
No.
Put it on.
Can I?
Yes.
Put it on.
It feels good.
It's warm.
Can I move?
Yes.
It feels good.
Riku!
Your nose is amazing.
It's amazing.
And...
Does it feel good?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It feels really good.
It's okay. Make it feel even better.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'm going to die.
No, no. Hang in there.
You can do it.
I'll do my best.
Hang in there.
This is amazing.
How is it?
It's amazing.
I can still see it.
Look closely.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
This butt is amazing.
I'm going crazy.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Let's go.
It's important.
Do it from behind.
From behind?
It feels good.
You're going to move.
I want to move a lot, but I can't go yet.
It feels good.
This butt is amazing.
I can't do it.
It's amazing.
I'm tired.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Not yet.
You can't do it yet.
You can do it.
Hang in there.
It's amazing.
It's tingling.
Do you feel tingling?
It's amazing.
I want to go out.
You can't go inside.
Inside?
Okay.
If you don't want to go inside, you can do whatever you want.
It's amazing.
It's okay.
It was my first time.
Yes.
I love you.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Marina.
Aichi.
I love you.
I'm sorry. It's my husband.
Hello.
Do you know where that jacket is?
It's in the closet on the right.
Is that all?
Yes.
I have to go back to work.
Are you going back as usual?
I have a meeting today.
I might be an hour late.
Okay.
See you.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'll do it.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
It's the best.
It's delicious.
Drink a lot.
Did you do it?
I can't do it.
Really?
Don't say that.
It's just Aichi.
Marina.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
It's disgusting.
Touch me.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
It's disgusting.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Don't do that.
It's hot.
Wait.
Let's go.
It's hot.
It's wet.
Did you do it?
It's amazing.
It's hot.
Your waist is moving.
It's disgusting.
Show me more.
Wait.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
Let's go.
It's hot.
It's disgusting.
I want to die.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It's disgusting.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
It's amazing.
It's disgusting.
Why are you making a face?
I want to sleep.
Why?
I want you to do that.
It feels good.
Hold me tight.
It's hot.
It's delicious.
I want you to do that more.
It feels good.
Is that good?
That's good.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Let's feel good together.
It's raining.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I want you to do that more.
Like this?
It's amazing.
Wait.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's delicious.
I want you to do that more.
Let me do it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I want you to do that more.
It's amazing.
Wait.
I'll do it.
It's hot.
I want you to do that more.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I want you to do that more.
Not yet.
I can't do it.
Wait.
It's hot.
I want you to do that more.
Wait.
It's hot.
What is it?
I can't do it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I want you to do that more.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I want you to do that more.
It's hot.
I'll do it.
It's amazing.
It's more amazing than before.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I'll do it.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
It's hot.
I want you to do that more.
Do you like her?
No, I don't.
You're lying.
I'll do it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Do you want to see a movie?
It hurts.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'll do it.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I'll do it.
I can't do it yet.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I'll do it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It hurts.
I'll do it.
I can't do it.
It hurts.
Tell me you like him more than me.
Tell me.
I like him more than you.
I like you.
I can't do it.
Show me your face.
I want to see it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
It's hot.
Can I take it out?
Take it out.
It's hot.
Give it to me.
It feels good.
I'll clean it up.
It's hot.
Recently,
I haven't been able to buy powder.
The number of shifts has increased.
It's because it's a semiconductor.
What's wrong with that?
No.
I'm a little worried.
If something happens,
it'll be bad.
We...
I don't know.
What do you mean?
Well,
I can't help it.
Why can't I see you today?
I'm sorry.
I got a call from my part-time job.
I told you I was free today.
I took a day off, too.
I'm sorry.
I'll pay you back.
Bye.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
You can go to her place.
I'm fine.
You're more important to me.
It feels good.
She's my girlfriend.
I can't help it.
I'm glad.
Are you really okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
That's bad.
Please do more.
It's hot.
I can't help it.
Thank you.
You're the best.
It's hot.
I'm glad you told me that.
Can I kiss you?
Yes.
Put your tongue out.
Put it out again.
You're the best.
It's hard.
Do you want me to lick you?
I want you to lick me.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You're cute.
It's hot.
I love you.
Thank you.
It's hot.
Are you excited?
I'm excited.
I want you to lick me more.
Do you want me to kiss you?
You like it.
I like it.
What do you want me to do with your boobs?
I want you to pinch me with your boobs.
What should I do?
Do you want me to pinch you that much?
I want you to pinch me.
Do you want me to make you feel better?
Of course.
Okay.
It's hot.
You're amazing.
Is it hot?
Your boobs are amazing.
Look at me.
You have a lot of boobs.
It feels good.
Can I stand up?
Come here.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You like it.
I'm so lucky to have sex with you.
You're cute.
It feels good.
Don't you have sex with her?
I don't.
I don't want to have sex with her.
You're getting harder.
It feels good.
You're going to have sex with her.
I'm sorry.
You can't have sex with her yet.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Your boobs are soft.
It feels good.
You can pinch your boobs.
I'm going to pinch your boobs harder.
Feel it.
It feels good.
You're cute.
You have a good face.
I'm sleepy.
I want you to kiss me.
Okay.
It feels good.
You're sniffling.
You're not holding back.
It feels good.
I want you to put a lot of Marina's drool on me.
Go ahead.
It feels good.
Marina.
Can I put your drool on me?
Okay.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can't hold back.
You're getting bigger.
Sit down.
Look at me.
It feels good.
It's hot.
You like me, don't you?
Yes, I do.
You're shivering.
You're cute.
Feel it.
You have a good face.
You're getting bigger.
It's hot.
Let me know if you want to go.
Okay.
Marina.
Do you want me to do this?
Yes.
Do it with your mouth.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
I can't do this.
I'm going to fall.
It hurts.
Ouch!
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
Can you do it again?
Of course.
I can do it.
It's hot.
I'm back.
Let's go.
It's hot.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
You're early.
I was free today.
So, I came early.
I'm going to bed.
I'm going to the pharmacy.
Okay.
Daichi.
Why are you here?
I forgot to tell you.
I skipped a class today.
Really?
So, I came here.
Do you want to eat something?
No.
Really?
Thank you.
It's good, isn't it?
It's good.
It's Miki.
Hello?
I'm fine.
I was free today.
Okay.
I'll be there soon.
Wait for me.
Daichi.
I'm sorry.
Go home.
I can make up with Miki.
I'm sorry.
I'm going home.
Wait for me.
What about you?
Don't worry about me.
I'm sorry.
I can't stand it anymore.
More.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I wanted to kiss you.
Thank you.
It feels good.
I wanted to kiss you.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I'm going to lick you.
I can feel it.
I'll do it harder.
I'm going to lick you.
Don't do that.
It feels good.
I'm going to lick you.
I love you.
I'm being licked a lot.
Are you happy?
I'm happy.
It feels good.
I'm going to lick you.
I want to lick you.
Don't lick me.
I want you to lick me.
You licked me a lot.
So do I.
It's ticklish.
Next is my turn.
I'm going to kill you.
Look at me.
It's ticklish.
It feels good.
Next.
I'm happy.
I'm happy to be killed by you.
You're trembling.
It feels good.
You're standing up.
You're cute.
Do you want to go home?
It feels good.
It's ticklish.
I can't stand it anymore.
I want to sleep.
It feels good.
It's ticklish.
I want to sleep.
You can't speak.
You can only speak to me.
I know.
Do you really know?
I know, but it feels good.
You're getting bigger.
I want to drool.
Please do it again.
You're getting bigger.
It feels good.
It's coming out.
No.
You can't speak.
Let's touch.
I want to touch.
Do you feel ticklish?
It's ticklish.
It feels good.
Maybe...
It's ticklish.
Let's go.
It feels good.
It's ticklish.
I want to lick your butt.
Do it more.
It's ticklish.
I want to lick your butt more.
I want to lick more.
It's ticklish.
It feels good.
I want to lick everything.
It's ticklish.
It feels good.
Let's go.
It's ticklish.
Wait.
It feels good.
I can see your shape.
I want you to feel more.
It tickles.
Wait.
Let's go.
It feels good.
It tickles.
I like this.
This is amazing.
Let's go.
It tickles.
This is amazing.
Let's go again.
It tickles.
This is amazing.
Let's go again.
Let's go.
It tickles.
This is amazing.
Marino is shivering.
I can't stop.
It tickles.
I'm sorry.
I can't stop.
We shouldn't stop.
This is amazing.
Let's go.
It feels so good.
I want to go there again.
I'll get angry if you don't do it because it's the second time.
OK.
Let me go there again.
You've got a fat tummy!
You able to get out.
Marina-san...
If you weren't here...
I'd be...
dead right now.
Marina-san...
When I was alone, I felt guilt in my heart.
But I still needed him.
Because the time I spent with him made me forget everything.
Please, Marina.