It's been a long time.
Hello, Junya.
Thank you for coming.
Rie is taking a walk now.
Is that so?
Pregnancy exercise is important.
Then I will go up first.
Yes.
A little bit more without the box.
Well, you had to close the box.
In that case, use a crowbar.
Thank you for coming all the way here.
No, it's fine.
We were both busy anyway.
It's hard to be a mother.
There's a lot of things I can't do on my own.
Besides, Junya is going to have a baby soon.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
You have to make a lot of money from now on.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to the bathroom.
I'm sorry.
Mom, I'm home.
I'm home.
Did you exercise?
It must have been hot.
That's right.
Exercise is important.
You've grown up a lot.
That's right.
That's great.
You have to have a healthy baby.
That's right.
I can't wait to see you soon.
Can you sit down?
You can sit down.
I'm fine now.
Is that so?
I was worried about you because you asked me to help you.
What's wrong?
I can sit down now and then.
The problem is Junya.
Junya?
What do you usually do?
What are you doing?
Hey.
You stink.
You did it alone, didn't you?
I didn't do it.
I can tell by the smell.
You stink.
The doctor said that pregnancy is sensitive to smell.
Why do you do that?
I can't sit down.
I'm sorry.
You're not having sex, are you?
I can't help you.
Can I sit down?
No, you can't.
You can't.
What are you doing?
I'm begging you.
I don't want you to beg me.
Please be patient.
Oh, my God.
You can't do that.
I'll do it somewhere.
Don't do that in your house.
It may affect your baby.
By the way.
I'll divorce you if I have a baby.
Divorce?
I can't do that.
I'll never forgive you.
Do you understand?
I promise you.
I see.
But when I have a chance, I feel like I'm going to give up.
He didn't care about my body at all.
I was so angry when I thought so.
If I had a mother, I would have calmed down.
I see.
But I was surprised to see you.
I'm not surprised.
Before I got pregnant, I had a hard time every day.
I thought you were thinking about me.
I see.
Mom, let's make dinner.
I got a little hot when I heard about the sex problem of my daughters.
I don't care about that.
I was envious of my youth.
One day.
I wonder if you're getting smaller every day.
I think I'm growing up.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Mom.
Thank you.
Rie.
I overslept today.
I see.
Do you want to eat first?
Yes, please.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong with you?
Sorry?
I'm tired from work.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Do you want touch?
What?
Rie told me a lot of things.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to see my underwear?
Yes, I do.
It's a cucumber.
You can touch it.
Okay.
It's a cucumber.
It's really beautiful.
I'm scared.
Mom.
Can I touch it directly?
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Does it feel good here?
It feels good.
I'm scared.
Do you want me to hold your hand?
Is it okay?
It's hard, isn't it?
I'm scared.
Can I kiss you?
I want you to feel better.
You've grown up a lot.
I feel good.
It's hard not to be able to do it yourself.
I hope you feel better.
Thank you very much.
This is hard.
I'll do it.
That's great.
You slept a lot.
You're always doing your best at work.
Sometimes you want to be spoiled.
I'm sorry.
No.
I'll keep it a secret to you.
Eat this.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
You feel better, don't you?
It's a secret between us.
That's great.
I can still smell it.
Let me wear it.
I'm pregnant.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm going to go.
It won't take long.
Be careful.
Let's clean up.
You're early.
Are you alone?
He'll be back soon.
What's wrong?
Can you go out with me again?
I can't.
Please.
That's enough, isn't it?
This is painful.
That's not true.
You really wanted to be a mother, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
I'm sure you'll get stronger as you get older.
Please, just one more time.
That's all I can do.
Do you feel anything?
No, I don't.
You do, don't you?
Wait a minute.
Don't look at me.
No, don't.
Is it cold?
No, it's not.
Really?
Then, let me hold your hand.
What's going on?
It's cold.
Are you feeling sick?
No, I'm not.
Don't look at me.
Can I hold your hand?
No, I can't.
Please, just one more time.
It's cold.
No, I can't.
I'm so happy to hear your voice.
It's almost over.
Look at my face.
Please, just one more time.
Do you feel anything?
Yes, I do.
I'm so happy to hear your voice.
Do you feel anything?
He came to me many times.
What's wrong with you?
I want you to love me.
I can't.
What time do you think it is?
I can't eat rice.
I can't.
I can't have six.
I can't eat chicken.
I can't eat meat.
I can't do it.
I can't eat meat anymore.
I don't know what to do.
She looks much better.
He has just recovered.
I can't help but cry when I think about how much I've missed you.
...China, give Me your gum?
You've been asking to give me your gum ever since.
You gave me your gum when we got married for the first time.
Give me your gum....
Mom, I'm going to be the last one to go.
Please take care of Kintaro.
I can't.
I'm so happy.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
bうわぁ
It's so hot
it's so hot
We just ate warm chocolate
we just ate warm chocolat
I don't know what to say
But I don't know what to say
So take care and be patient
Let's put it in.
Do you want to put it in?
Put it on properly.
I understand.
Please turn your hips this way.
It's hot.
It's burning.
Please spread your hips.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
Don't you feel better if I take this off?
It's hot.
Do you feel better?
Of course.
That's what it means to take this off.
Don't you feel better if I take this off?
It's hot.
It feels good.
No, no, no.
Hurry up.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Hello, dad.
How are you?
I'm fine.
I'm so hungry.
By the way, are you eating alone?
Only bento?
You can't do that.
You have to live long.
You're going to be an old man.
Mom is here.
Do you want to go home?
I'll call you later.
I'm going to clean the bathroom.
Mom will call you later.
I'll tell your mom.
I'm going for a walk.
It's better to take a break.
That's right.
Humans fall in no time.
It's hot.
Lie down on your back.
I'm dead
Oh, dad, dad, dad, dad, dad
Someone is coming
Ah! Ah! Ah!
The miso soup is delicious.
Yeah.
The soup stock is good.
It's delicious.
Yeah.
Mom, it's really good.
It's delicious.
Was it good?
Thanks to you,
I'm saved a lot.
Junya's sexual desire
seems to have calmed down.
Yeah.
Is that so?
It was good.
Well,
it's a little early,
but I'm thinking of
having a baby
tomorrow.
Is it okay?
But isn't it still quite early?
That's right,
but if it goes on like this,
it will cost my living expenses,
and Junya said it was okay.
Eh?
Junya too?
Yes.
I can do housework on my own,
and I think
Rino's family
can live in peace.
By the way,
my friend is having a farewell party tomorrow,
so I'll go out a little around noon.
Yeah.
I'm looking forward to it.
Oh,
the baby is finally born.
but while I'm at home,
I can eat a lot of mom's food,
so it's nice.
Right, mom?
Mom?
Oh, yeah.
You should make it once in a while.
Of course.
Well, please make it until the baby is born.
Yeah.
If the baby is born,
I have to make dinner,
so mom, please teach me a lot.
Yeah.
It makes me feel nostalgic.
That's right.
You're going to be a mother.
Yeah.
I'm looking forward to it.
Well, I'm going.
Yeah.
Have fun.
What will you do when you pick her up?
Well, I'll call her.
Maybe around 15 o'clock.
Okay.
Take care.
Yeah.
I'm going.
Junya,
this kind of relationship
is not good.
When I and Rie
go back to our parents' house,
let's stop this kind of relationship.
Do you want that?
Yes.
Go back to your parents' house,
go back to a life without sex,
can you stand it?
I can't stand it.
Yeah.
Junya,
it's okay.
I'm going to sleep.
If you pull her strategy, she explains it appropriately.
When she is in a rut, it should not take long before she mom comes back.
But the discrimination from mom makes the baby's mouth openopedia.
The baby remembers mom as I mom.
You're so cute.
It's so hard.
It's so hot.
I love you so much.
It feels good.
I'm going.
I'm going again.
It hurts.
It's so hot.
I can't breathe.
Please put on an umbrella.
I want to go to the bathroom.
Does it have anything to do with you?
I want to be a mom.
I love you, too.
Please show me your belly.
It's so hot.
I want to go to the bathroom.
I feel sick.
I feel sick, too.
It's so hot.
Please take a deep breath.
I can't breathe.
It's so hot.
I'm going to the bathroom.
I want to go to the bathroom.
It's so hot.
I feel sick.
Please tell me you love me.
I love you.
It's so hot.
Please take a deep breath.
I'm dying.
It's so hot.
I can't take it anymore.
I can't take it anymore, no way.
I can't take it anymore, I can't take it anymore.
Num, num!
Oh, wow.
The sweet potato is really turning brown.
This is terrible.
Why did you do that?
This is disgusting.
I'm sorry.
Ouch!
I want it back.
I'm sorry.
I was worried.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I feel good.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I feel good.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I want to do it again.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
I'll do my best to make you feel better.
I'll do my best to live alone.
Thank you for everything.
Mom.
Why don't you go to see Junya?
It's not easy to live alone.
That's right.
Let's do that.
Let's go.
See you.
Mom.
I love you.