This is the first time I've seen such a thing, and I'm not sure if it's a good thing or a bad thing.
I'm not sure if it's a good thing or a bad thing.
It's a difficult topic.
It's difficult.
I'm not sure if it's a good thing or a bad thing.
It's a difficult topic.
It was a good money for me who didn't even record a part-time job for about 8 hours on one way for 7,000 yen per person.
But if I could meet that person, if I could have sex with that person, I didn't want it at all.
However, I was a little worried if that person would really come.
It's been 6 months since I met her and became friends in an online game.
By the way, her name in the game was Aoi.
I did it.
It's too strong.
You've improved too much.
You've gotten so much better lately.
You've done too much without going to college.
You've been playing the game for a long time.
I'm a full-time boss, so I have time.
You just served because you're great.
That's not true.
Don't make fun of me.
My husband is back.
I did it.
I'm sorry.
I had a hobby of playing games with her, and it was easier and more fun to talk than anything else.
A few days later, we sent each other a picture of our faces in a message.
We sent each other a picture of our faces in a message.
I lost.
Is this Ao?
She's so cute.
She's too cute.
I'm sorry.
Did you get through?
Hello, I'm Ao.
My real name is Aoi.
What's yours?
Are you really my husband?
You're so young.
I'm so happy.
This is my third marriage.
Where do you live?
I live in Aichi.
I see.
Aichi is a nice place, isn't it?
By the way, I went to see your concert last year.
By the way, are you a student now?
Do you have a girlfriend?
What?
You don't have a girlfriend?
I don't have one.
You have a cute face.
People who are popular are born popular.
Because I'm not popular.
That's why I'm a virgin for the rest of my life.
What?
Are you a precious person?
Yes.
That's great.
That's not true.
People around me make fun of me.
I didn't know that.
By the way,
Do you want me to be a virgin?
What?
If you can come to Tokyo,
I can steal your virginity.
She said something like an erotic manga to me.
At this time, I thought it was a light joke.
It wasn't a joke.
Masato.
Aoi?
I'm glad to meet you.
Nice to meet you. I'm Aoi.
You're great.
I'm glad you came.
We made a promise.
I'm glad.
Then,
Let's go to the hotel.
What?
You came here to steal my virginity, didn't you?
I wanted to have a meal with you.
I didn't know that.
Love hotels are delicious.
We have everything.
Let's go.
Wait.
Do you have any other plans?
Well...
Let's go.
I'm going to have sex with her.
Are you nervous?
It's my first time to stay in a hotel.
It's cute.
Don't look at me.
The elevator is small.
Maybe the hotel is small.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
This is my room.
This is your room.
Yes.
Why are you looking at me?
I'm not.
I'm wondering if I can stay here.
Yes.
I'm embarrassed.
Ouch!
Your heart is beating.
I'm nervous.
It's cute.
I'm nervous, too.
Touch me.
Ouch!
It's true.
Your heart is beating.
Yes.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
What?
Can I take a shower?
I'll go in first.
Okay.
Leave it to me.
You washed your underwear in the bathroom yesterday, didn't you?
That's...
HBO
able
Let me see your tongue.
Can you feel this part?
Can I really kiss you?
Yes, you can.
I haven't touched you yet.
I didn't know you could feel this much just by touching your body.
It's a little uncomfortable.
You have a lot of pimples.
You are very sensitive.
Let me see your mouth.
Let me see your tongue.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
I'll cool it down.
It's still hot.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Leave it to me.
Thank you very much.
It's strange, isn't it?
Are you getting bigger?
Yes, I am.
You are cute.
You can be cuter.
Boys are cuter when they speak.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's embarrassing.
You can stay like this.
You are more sexy when you stay like this.
It's hot, isn't it?
Don't hide it.
It's embarrassing.
Why do you hide it?
Show me more.
It's hot.
Don't hide it.
Show me more.
You are cute.
Don't hide it.
Please turn off the light.
It's okay.
It's easier to see when it's bright.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Do you want me to lick you?
You've never been licked.
I'll lick you.
Can I lick you?
I love you.
You are very sensitive.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It's warm.
It's your first time, isn't it?
It's my first time.
You are very sensitive.
Is this part sensitive?
It's very hot.
You are very sensitive.
It's cold.
It's delicious.
It's getting harder and harder.
It feels good.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
Are you about to leave?
I'm sorry.
I'm about to leave.
You can't leave yet.
It's hot.
It's very hot.
You can't leave yet.
You are sensitive.
You are cute.
It's hot.
Do you want to touch my body?
Touch my body.
It's very soft.
Is this your first time touching my body?
It's my first time.
Look at me a lot.
Look at me and touch me a lot.
Good job.
Do you want to touch my body?
How is it?
Is it good?
It's my first time.
Does it feel good?
Do you want to touch me a lot?
Good job.
Does it feel good?
Look at me a lot.
I can feel it.
Do you want to touch my body?
It's here.
It's wet even if you wear pants.
Do you understand?
It's hot.
I'm excited.
Do you want to wear pants?
Touch me.
It's wet.
Do you understand?
More.
Look at me.
You're used to it, aren't you?
I'm happy.
You're good at kissing.
Do you want to lick me?
Don't look at me like that.
Look at me.
Take your time.
There.
It feels good.
Lick me.
It's a pleasant spot.
You're good at it.
It feels good.
Do it harder.
There.
Lick me more.
You're good at it.
There.
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
It feels good.
You're good at it.
Really?
Do you want to lie down?
I want to lie down.
Lie down.
Can I?
It feels good.
There.
Open your mouth.
Let's put it in your mouth.
Rubber.
It's okay.
I think it's there.
It's raw.
It's okay.
It's in.
How is it?
It feels good.
How do I look?
It's hot.
I'm going to move my waist.
It feels good.
You can't open it yet.
There's a lot in there.
It feels good.
Touch it.
You can't.
It's hot.
You can see it well, right?
Yes, I can see it.
It feels good.
There.
Look closely.
I'm going to go.
You can't.
You can't go.
It feels good.
I'm going to go again.
You can't.
I'm going.
You can't go yet.
It feels good.
Look closely at my butt.
You can see it well, right?
It feels good.
You can't.
There's a lot in there.
It feels good.
We might be a good match.
I'm going to give you a lot.
You can't.
I'm going to go.
You can't go.
It feels good.
I'm going to cry.
Touch me.
That's right.
I can feel it, too.
I'll do my best.
You're cute.
It feels good.
It's hot.
You can't.
It feels good.
Give me more.
You can't.
There's a lot in there.
I'm going to go.
You can't.
I've been used by a virgin many times.
I'm glad.
It feels good.
I'm going to do it a little harder.
You can't.
I'm sorry.
Did you go?
You went inside.
Look, there's a lot.
I'm sorry.
Did you go?
There's still a lot.
I didn't cut it all.
I'll squeeze it for you.
You can't.
It's good.
Next.
You can't.
Look up.
It feels good.
Move as you like.
Today.
When you like it.
I want you to let it out.
Let it out a lot.
It feels good.
You can't.
Come on.
It feels good.
Move your waist.
You can't.
It feels good.
Move it a lot.
You can let it out a lot.
It feels good.
Help me.
You can't.
It feels good.
Congratulations on your enlistment.
Come here.
You can't.
You're still energetic.
It feels good.
We still have time today.
Let's do it again after a break.
It feels good.
Aoi thoroughly explored my weaknesses until the end.
She taught me a lot of pleasant things.
It feels good.
You can't.
It's already this time.
Time flies.
But I had a lot of fun.
I was with Aoi.
Actually, if I had more time,
I would have taken you to Tokyo.
What time is the bus?
It was pretty early, wasn't it?
I'll give you a ride home.
Well...
I...
I want to go home.
I don't want you to go home yet.
Let's...
Let's stay together.
What?
Let's go.
Where are we going?
She knew everything I wanted to say and do.
And she went instead of me.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Sit down.
Excuse me.
Where's your husband?
He went out yesterday.
So don't worry about him.
You haven't eaten anything, have you?
Do you want to eat something?
Can I?
Of course.
What do you want to eat?
Eggs, onions and minced meat.
Hamburger.
I'm glad.
You're a good husband, aren't you?
Of course.
I'm not just playing games.
I'm hungry.
I'll make it quickly.
Of course, sex was the best.
But the time with Aoi made me feel warm and happy.
It's good.
I thought I should spend more time like this.
Thank you.
Is it good?
It's really good.
I'm glad.
I'll give you a secret ingredient.
Is it a tomato?
I think it goes well with the sauce.
I think so, too.
I'll put a lot of it.
You're good at it.
Let's eat.
I want to eat.
I'll bring it.
Let's eat.
I'll let you eat.
Is that okay?
Is it good?
It's soft.
I'm glad.
The fire inside is just right.
Isn't it?
It's good.
You can eat it.
I'll eat.
It has a lot of meat flavor.
It's good to mix.
It's hot.
You can eat it.
You have an appetite and a desire for sex.
I have a desire for sex.
It's hot.
You can eat it.
Don't eat your hands.
Is it good?
It's good.
I'm fine, too.
I'll sit down.
It reminds me of the hotel.
It's hot.
I can't eat it.
You can eat it.
You're not a virgin anymore.
Is that so?
What do you mean?
Am I not allowed to be a virgin?
Who graduated you from the hotel?
It's you.
That's right.
You can eat it.
I'll eat this.
It's hot.
You don't have to stop your hands.
I want to eat it.
I can't help it.
It looks delicious.
It's hot.
I can't help it.
I just gave you a lot.
It's hard.
It's hot.
I knew it.
You're a virgin.
I can't help it.
It's hot.
It's delicious.
I love you.
Is that so?
It's hot.
I love you.
I can't help it.
Don't eat it.
It's hot.
You want to eat my mango, don't you?
I remembered what happened at the hotel.
It's hot.
I can't help it.
I'll eat it, too.
Why me?
Let's eat.
It's delicious.
It's hot.
I'll eat it, too.
Please.
Shall we take a bath together?
Yes.
I'm embarrassed.
It's warm.
I'm very happy.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm sorry about earlier.
No, it's okay.
I bullied you, didn't I?
It's okay.
What?
I told you earlier.
Are you already out of your mind?
It's okay.
I told you earlier.
You can do whatever you want to do today.
Yes.
It's hot.
It's your first time taking a bath with a woman, isn't it?
Of course.
It's warm.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Yes.
Touch me.
I just touched your boobs.
You're so wet.
I'm wet.
I'll wash your body.
My body?
I'll wash your mouth.
No, I'll wash your mouth.
I'm embarrassed.
It's okay.
Sit here.
Yes.
Don't hide it.
It's too bright.
It's hot.
You've been standing for a long time.
No.
It's hot.
How do you feel?
It's good, isn't it?
Yes.
It's your first time doing this, isn't it?
It's hot.
Wash my boobs, too.
I'm just washing your body.
But I feel good.
I feel good, too.
I'll wash your back with these boobs.
My back?
Is this your first time doing this?
Yes, it is.
How do you feel?
It's good.
I don't do this to my husband.
I'm happy.
My back feels good.
It's hot.
You've been standing for a long time.
I feel good.
It's hot.
It's hot over there, too.
Over there?
It's hot.
I can't do this.
I'll take a shower.
It's hot.
I can't do this yet.
Let me do it, too.
It's hot.
I'll take a shower.
Thank you.
Can I stand up?
Yes.
Put your hands on me.
You've been doing well.
I can't do this.
I'm sorry to bully you.
It's hot.
Something came out.
Are you going to do it again?
Are you going to do it?
You can't.
It's hot.
Look at me.
Yes.
It's hot.
You can't.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
It's hot.
I'll squeeze your boobs.
My boobs?
It feels good.
It's called a pie-slit.
Pie-slit?
Yes.
It feels good.
I feel like I'm going to jump out of my body.
Hold on a little longer.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Are you going to do it again?
It's hot.
Are you going to do it?
You can't.
You're moving a lot.
It's hot.
It feels good.
If you keep doing it, you'll reach your limit.
I'll do it forever.
It's hot.
I can't stop sweating.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I can't stop sweating.
It feels good.
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
I've been holding it in.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm sorry I kept looking at you like that.
It's okay.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm glad.
I'll do a lot more.
Okay.
It's hot.
That's dangerous.
Wait a minute.
Are you ready?
You're too good.
I'm better at having sex.
You're better at playing games.
I'm getting better at having sex.
I'm like a sponge.
You're cheeky.
I'll pay you back for what you taught me.
You're a good boy.
I'll turn off the TV.
Come here.
Do you want to have sex with me?
Of course I do.
I'm having a hard time, too.
Really?
Yeah.
Let me hear more.
Okay.
Yeah.
It's hot.
It's too hot.
I can't do it.
Do you want me to lick you?
It's hot.
It feels good.
You've never licked here, have you?
I've never licked here.
It feels good.
How do you feel?
Does it feel good here?
You can feel it, right?
It's hot.
Something's coming out.
It's too hot.
It's hot.
I love talking in your house.
Me, too.
It's hot.
I'm sleepy.
No.
I know when you're going to go.
It's hot.
No.
Do you want me to lick you?
Let's lick together.
Together?
Can we lick together?
Let's lick together.
It feels good.
Really?
I'm glad.
Lick me more.
That's great.
It feels good.
Let's feel good together.
Do it more.
No.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
I haven't put it in yet.
It feels good.
I'll put it in.
Doesn't it feel good?
Don't do that.
I'll put it in.
It feels better than going to the bathroom today.
Really?
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's not good.
Don't do that.
Can you feel it even if I put it in?
I can feel it.
I can feel you.
You don't have to touch me.
You can move your hips a little more.
Don't do that.
bah
If I'm with sex, I can do it in any time
Ayu-san, if I'm with you, I can do it again and again for hours.
Hey, follow me from behind.
Yes.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
I'll move first.
Yes.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
It feels good.
More.
You can move as you like.
Ayu-san.
More.
Ah!
That's right.
You're moving too much.
More.
Ah!
You can't go.
Yes.
Ah!
It feels good.
You're amazing.
You can do things I didn't teach you.
Ayu-san, I want to make you feel good.
Ah!
You're amazing.
I want to do more.
Let's do a lot.
Ah!
You didn't teach me that, did you?
I'll make you feel good.
Ah!
It feels good.
No, I can't!
Ai-chan!
Ai-kun!
Ah!
Ai-kun, no!
Mmm!
Why is it?
Why don't you hurry up?
It will be best if you come earlier.
It hurts so much, I can't take it no more!
Ouch, so painful!
Really, so painful!
Ouch! Go away, go away!
Don't you want more space?
Let's go to the bedroom
Come here.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Let's do it again.
Really? Let's do it a lot.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Do you know the owner of this bed?
Yes, I do.
You must be excited.
No, I'm a little scared.
It's okay.
Let's do it more.
We're on a business trip.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
It's weird.
Let's go together.
I can't do it.
Can I help you?
You can do it, right?
I can't do it.
It feels good.
I haven't put it in yet.
I'll put it in.
I just put it in, but it's still hard.
It feels good.
I'm doing this with you.
Forget about me.
Just forget about me now.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I feel like I'm going to go again.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Do you want me to put it in more?
You can put a lot in.
Tell me when you're going.
It feels good.
I'll get sick.
trembling
It's out again
It was a Good feeling
Then
Do you want to shovel the third time?
What?
I see.
That's gross.
That's amazing.
You can still do it.
It's still hard.
It's just hard.
It feels good.
I see.
It's still hard even though you just said it.
You can do it.
I don't know if I can do it.
It's still hard.
That's what I like.
You can do it.
It's hard.
I'm sorry.
You're going to do it again?
I'm going to do it again.
That's amazing.
You did it again.
I'm going to squeeze it out until the end.
It's not over yet.
You can do it.
It feels good.
More.
You can do it.
It feels good.
More.
You can do it.
I like you.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to be popular.
I came here to make a good girlfriend.
I like you.
Can I see you again?
I'm sorry.
No.
I can't keep
distance from you.
Enjoy your
enjoy your
I'm sure
you'll have a wonderful girlfriend.
Hey.
Don't forget
I'm sure
you'll have a wonderful girlfriend.
Since then
I've been
playing games
Since then
I haven't been able to get in touch with Aoi.
Now
I don't think it's real
I'm sure