You always say you clean up, right?
So if you calm down, do it.
Sorry, but don’t make such a puzzle.
I am pregnant, I am always angry, I am never angry.
I always say I clean up, but I don’t clean up anything.
Do not spread it.
Do not spread, so clean it up.
I will take the washing machine later.
Now is
Two rooms, this is.
The socks, and take them off.
You can put this in the washing machine.
I always wonder who is spreading.
I say too much for girls.
Next time, it is always.
A baby is born.
To be two babies.
No, but also for the baby.
I think it’s better not to be so philanthropic.
Also for the baby.
Take your own lead, go ahead.
Do it now, do it immediately.
Clean it up, now.
My wife is 3 months pregnant and her hormone balance is disrupted.
It was hard to be angry at little things.
Oh and.
How is it?
Is there any trouble?
My stomach is fine.
But it is our man.
Anyway, I was not angry, I was angry.
I cannot do anything about the house.
Okay, so badly
thanks to
No, do not care about anything.
If your mother comes, it will help you.
Do you have something to eat?
Oh, what can I do.
I would like to ask for a hamburger.
I loved hamburger, I loved it.
And then the hamburger and your favorite juice.
You know, add to the tofu.
of course.
It was a great fun for your mother.
I am also happy to meet the Tucson.
Yes, I have to tell anyone else.
I will do anything, so don’t fight with her.
Try as hard as possible.
Yes, it is better for the body.
Yes, for the baby.
Yes is.
So my wife’s mother came home.
Please rest slowly, thank you.
My mother is very helpful.
Tell your mother anything, because it is difficult to give birth.
Good morning, my mom, good morning.
It is hot, yes.
Sorry to sorry.
It is hot, so you need to get plenty of water.
Yes is
Soon I will be Dad.
My mother is here, don’t make it all.
Help me too.
No, I am now working.
Okay, I came here to do the house.
Don’t be afraid, I’m teaching this man.
If you get to be a gentleman here, you will become a bad guy who doesn’t do anything, or you’ll be a little too harsh.
Well, this guy is not enough to know that he is a father, so that’s just enough.
Since her mother arrived, her life has not changed.
No one, I do not know at all.
I don’t say that much anymore.
It is okay, it is cool.
Hey, go to work.
Yes, then please later.
Have a good luck.
Yes, come to me.
Just look at this man’s face, come.
No longer so much trouble.
Oh, you guys, you are busy with work.
Not to say too much.
What happened?
What did I do now.
Yes, yes is
Nothing, show me it quickly.
Have you done something now?
No to
You know something.
What this
I say goodbye to humans.
Do not be alone.
It is good rubbish.
It is not rubbish.
You are good guys, just get it out.
I am hungry in Sunny.
It means there is no fire.
What are you doing there alone?
I feel better alone.
It is a good rubbish, really.
Oh, do not do it.
Banned for women.
Oh is?
What is?
You can endure that.
No, because
I did not do either.
As much as a woman.
You are determined not.
You are Dad.
If a child is crying, you’ll make a woman cry.
That is the time and case.
In case of time, now and now.
Do you know?
Not having children now.
The couple are sharing together.
We share pain, we share joy, you know?
Not sharing the suffering.
What is?
One will end up feeling good.
You know you.
Because you really don’t know anymore.
I understand. I understand.
to prohibit.
and poor.
I really don’t know next.
Because it is marriage.
If you can’t really stand it, just take a little hand.
What do you say? I feel awkward.
Why do you say I feel bad?
Because it is a physical phenomenon.
A physical phenomenon?
I have to be patient, but I must meet the limit.
Noise is noise! wait!
You know? answered me?
Yes is
He was ordered to go hungry and seemed mad.
What a shameless face, this.
A little, seriously
Painful pain pain.
Do not stop?
Not really, but DV.
Not the DV.
I understand.
Really good for men.
Think about the feelings of women.
If you have a baby, you will live with three of them.
So, we do not fight.
Eat it here.
I will eat.
Eat the eggs too.
When is the next exam?
Was it next week?
How is it?
I think it is growing well.
well was
I want heavy.
So is it.
Is it time to start moving?
Yes, it sometimes moves.
You are going to be a bit puzzled here.
It is fun.
He was a very moving child.
Is it so?
The back of his legs looked a little bit shaped.
Then an active child comes out.
It looks like a high school.
So let’s climb the tree.
It is fun.
really is.
What can I call?
A little grandma.
You will also become a father.
Be well aware.
Yes
Coolly cool
Do not say that?
mother
Oh yes!
Ashley, I am going to the hospital now.
Oh... oh...
What happened to Tohoku?
Is it okay?
You know, I am pregnant, so you said it was terrible, right?
Yes, but I think there is no other way.
Do not force it.
You don’t have to listen to everything that the child says.
You are tired of her, right?
I will massage you.
Oh no, I am sorry.
Okay is.
Oh yeah
Sorry for the trouble with my child.
Oh well well
You are tired.
Oh yeah
Sorry, but this is
You can make it a woman.
What do you do.
You are talking by chance, I listen.
I am afraid to break my wife’s words.
I know, but then, Akira will go crazy.
Shay, you smelled my underwear.
Sorry, but that
I am not angry.
It will be crazy today.
Because I cannot see.
Lie down.
Oh yeah
From home
Just about this.
Sorry for the hard work.
mother
by Khatta
I said something terrible.
I was scared.
Yes, you have worked hard.
well well well
You have to do well, you have to reward.
Is it a reward?
If you can’t do it alone, I should do it, right?
I will give you hand.
Oh no, oh no, oh no, my mother
Is your mother okay?
Okay, you did it well, it is hard.
Yes is
You do not have to endure.
Mom, you don’t have to help me.
Yes is
Mom, it smells so bad.
Yes to?
Yes is
Can you show me your breasts?
I will show you.
Do you feel good?
Oh my mother.
Can I lick my breasts?
Do you feel good?
It feels good.
Feel your power easily.
Sorry to
I am glad you feel it.
Feels good?
You tried hard.
well well well
Sorry to
Please ride.
How is?
What is good?
It feels good.
Good morning please.
It is strange.
Feels good?
Yes to.
Congratulations to Mr.
Stand up.
Feels good?
It feels good.
How is?
not bear it.
Yes is
Feel better.
How is?
No to no.
Okay is.
Was it good?
Yes is
It came out.
Sorry to sorry.
Oh yeah yeah
Sorry to
This is about only two of you.
Secret is.
Oh yeah, of course.
Sorry, this too
Is it okay?
Oh, you were stuck.
A lot of hardship came out.
Sorry to
Okay is.
Same as that.
Welcome to.
Yes is
How was the examination?
Yes, my baby was very heavy, but I was waiting and I was really tired.
I am so happy that I have an appetite.
Yes, I cannot do without eating.
But you are fat.
When my mother was there, she could not eat at all.
Was it terrible?
And then it smells, I ate it.
But my mother’s food is delicious.
Yes it is delicious.
I wish someone would listen to me when I am suffering.
No more asshole.
So, I’m eating, I’m not saying that.
My mother’s hand was still in my mind and I felt crazy when I remembered it.
I will clean up in a moment.
What happened, Mr. Heck?
I will strike you.
I wake up now, it’s okay.
by
No to girls.
No to
Tastefully
Oh, I will get back.
What do we do, make us feel better.
No to Texas?
You’ve been in Texas last week.
No and no.
Entering in.
No to no.
No to
Very strongly
Come to me.
I can care about him or her.
My head has become better.
Do not do this?
You did not do it, right?
No to
No to No.
Let us kill.
It falls.
I want to see if I go.
What happened.
Sorry, but my mother is so good.
Sorry, really sorry for leaving.
Get out properly.
I will help, I will help.
Which one...
Okay okay? is okay?
Take it out and get it out.
And Andrew...
Take the big rose.
is honest.
Thank you mother.
Do not give out anything.
Sorry to sorry.
What is?
I am going to the station tomorrow at Telecaster.
How about?
The Tucson is at 4am tomorrow.
No tobacco either.
Oh, before the station, buy a reputable GTA store again, and you get the money, and go and try it tomorrow.
What happened suddenly?
I think you want to change your mind, I mean you are lying.
Thanks now.
Not rare though?
Oh no, that, after recognizing that, I didn’t care about the tacos at all, again, I’m really sorry if I remember something like that.
Sorry for saying too much too.
Tomorrow, I’ll be doing something with my mom and I, so slowly.
Yes thank you.
Sorry to
No to no.
I can no longer eat.
Please please.
Do you do this last time?
No to
Can I swear?
Oh yeah
No to
here here
mother
You know it is back?
Not really crazy.
No to
My stomach hurts and suffers.
How do I feel good?
Stay as now.
It feels good.
It hurts!
What are you doing?
Oh yeah
I really can’t say this last.
because I choose.
forgive me.
Please please
I want to calm.
Can I enter?
I entered.
Feel good
I want to kiss your mother.
It feels good.
Please keep it home.
I can pin.
Let me get used to it.
2nd
No is
Oh yeah yeah yeah
had it.
Casually
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah
The channel guests.
Sorry to
It felt so much, I was gone.
by Nayla
Feel it.
I want to go.
It feels good.
Oh is
Feel good
The sperm inside is coming out.
What is?
I will go.
Really the last.
Yes is
promise to me.
I understand.
Sorry now.
I cannot read back.
Write the face.
Please please.
I will go.
No to Akihito.
No to
Mr Akihito
Sorry to
Last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time last time.
I want my grandfather, I don’t want.
Let me do.
Oh my mother.
I want to do it again, too much.
Mom, is it okay?
The stomach is full.
The last one.
First to run away.
Wait to
Please make me hungry.
Yes
More strong power.
Ride the liver.
Yes
Oh, it hurts
Can you get me in?
Feel good
Yes is
Hungry is hungry.
Spread the leg again.
Very beautiful.
Show me where your mother is.
Please can please.
Come to your mom’s favorite room.
Feel good
Can I come now?
It feels good.
Yes
Feel good
What I want.
I will get a lot out.
Put out a lot.
Yes is
Oh, oh
Okay, get it out a lot.
Yes is
Oh yeah yeah
Mother, I will leave.
Get out, dog
Oh is
Mom, I am hungry.
It hurts and hurts.
Please show me that you are sitting on your own.
Feel good
I like it, I like it.
Well, I don’t check anything, Sandra has, yes, he’s borrowing this version, the bluebleish Jim, the long-lost, and also theitar, the biuch, telling me a lot, again,
Is it okay?
Sorry, thank you
Do you really need to follow me?
Hospital
Yes, it is okay.
You will be alone and shy.
Then I will go.
Be careful.
I will go.
Come to me.
I want to fail.
I want to fail in the water.
I will not betray you here.
Because all of that is wrong with her.
Or can it stop now?
I don’t want to, I’m also my mother.
I had been letting my wife secretly go with her mother several times.