I think we'll be there soon.
Hikaru...
I don't think you're wrong.
It's okay. I'm not a kid.
Where's Hikaru?
Yeah.
He said he'd make us dinner.
It's okay. It doesn't matter.
It's okay.
Oh, come on.
Hikaru and I have been childhood friends since we were kids, and we always spent time together.
When I was a college student, I went to a university in the city.
Hikaru and I left the local university and decided to find a job in the city.
When I heard they were getting married, I was really surprised.
But both of them are important to me, so I kept my feelings for Hikaru in my heart and comforted them.
I'm not lying about this feeling.
Oh, it's been a while.
Yeah, it's been a while.
Thank you for waiting.
I've been waiting.
I'm sorry I got here a little early.
We just got back from the store.
By the way, you didn't have any luggage, did you?
No, I didn't.
Me, neither.
I'm sorry.
By the way, is it really okay?
Of course.
I'm sure you'll find a place to stay here.
Don't worry about anything.
Thank you.
That's right.
Why are you hesitating?
Come on, get in.
What?
Yuto is tired, so be nice to him.
Okay.
But it's been a while, so I really wanted to see you.
Come on, let's go.
I can't help it.
This way, this way.
Isn't the house really big?
You've never been here since you moved in?
Yeah.
You've worked hard.
No, no, no.
It's a loan.
And Kaguya is working part-time.
You two work hard and pay it back.
That's right.
Then I'll show you your room.
You can use it freely.
Yeah.
Then I'll prepare dinner.
I'm sorry.
I'll leave you two alone.
It's okay.
And I'm glad that the three of us can spend time together even when we grow up.
That's right.
Think of it as your own house and move in.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Is there anything you don't like?
No, it's okay as usual.
Okay.
Then I'll make it.
Yeah.
The light hasn't changed at all, has it?
It hasn't changed.
It's the same as before.
The next day
Good morning.
Ouch!
What are you wearing?
What's wrong?
No, I don't know what's wrong.
That dress...
Is it strange?
You always dress like this.
Do I always dress like this?
You've been like this for a long time.
Why are you embarrassed?
Good morning.
What are you wearing?
Hikaru's clothes.
Oh, that's right.
Hikaru, put on some clothes.
What?
You always dress like this.
That's right, but Jiro is here.
Put on something for the time being.
What?
You don't have to look at Jiro.
I'm sure you're worried about Jiro, not you.
I don't care.
We're childhood friends.
Right, Jiro?
Well...
Right?
Go back to your room and put on something.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
He's a little sloppy at home.
I see.
What are you going to do today?
I made a reservation at a real estate agency today.
I'm going to look at a lot of real estate.
I see.
He seems to be preparing a feast at night.
Don't be too late.
Okay.
I'm counting on you.
I'm hungry.
Cheers.
Today's meal looks delicious.
Really?
Can I eat it?
Yes, please.
Itadakimasu.
Can I eat it, too?
It's a fried chicken noodle.
Is that so?
It's delicious.
Really?
You like fried chicken, don't you?
Yes, I do.
It's really delicious.
Hikaru is getting better at cooking.
Right?
I'm surprised.
What's wrong with you?
You used to be a dark mother.
Don't say that.
I've grown up, too.
You're amazing.
There's no such thing as a bad meal.
I can make it many times.
You're a fool.
I can make a delicious meal.
It's the best.
What's wrong?
What?
I told you.
I can make a delicious meal.
You don't care about it.
I care about it.
Really?
Do you care about it?
You don't care about it, do you?
I care about it.
I can make a delicious meal.
That's not true.
I usually walk around in my underwear.
I don't care about it.
I'm sorry.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
This is delicious, too.
Are you wearing clothes today?
Yes, I am.
You're right.
You should be careful.
I'm used to it.
It's easy.
Are you okay?
Do you need a towel?
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
I'm wet.
Thank you.
You're wet.
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
You're always like this when you drink water.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Do you want to drink more?
Thank you.
Where is it?
It's in the back.
Is it in the back?
Yes, it is.
Did you find it?
Is this it?
Yes, it is.
Thank you.
Do you want to eat this?
Yes, please.
Do you want to eat this first?
I'm sorry.
It's fun to eat together like this.
Isn't it?
It's a lot of fun.
Yes, it is.
I'm glad to be able to eat together like this.
Me, too.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
The hamburger steak is delicious.
Really?
Yes.
There was also cheese in it.
Please make it again.
Okay.
Jiro.
I'm sorry.
By the way, are you alone in your hometown?
I'm going to live alone.
Is that so?
I was talking to Ichiro.
I was wondering if you were going to get married.
Actually, I broke up with my girlfriend recently.
Is that so?
She is your colleague at work, isn't she?
Yes.
I lost my job at work.
I wanted to go back to my hometown.
I thought it was just right.
I'm glad you came back to your hometown.
I'm sorry.
Let's drink together today.
Thank you.
Go out with Ichiro.
I can't go out with him tomorrow.
Let's drink.
You'll be able to go out with him soon.
Thank you.
Cheer up.
Let's drink.
Thank you.
More.
You make me drink a lot.
What kind of girl is Jiro?
I don't know because I broke up with her.
I'm drunk.
It's time to get up.
I agree.
I remember the old days when the three of us could talk happily.
It's good to do this once in a while.
Let's hang out sometime.
Are you sure?
Come here.
Thank you.
You're not good at this.
Why?
I'm good at this.
You're not good at this.
It's easy.
Hey.
I'm glad you're having fun.
I agree.
What's wrong?
Hey.
What?
Jiro is next to me.
Don't do that.
I'll ask him.
No.
It's too early.
Let's go to bed.
Come on.
I'm going to bed.
Do you want to keep having sex while Jiro is here?
I want you to keep having sex.
I can't do that.
You can.
I'm going to bed.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Okay.
Good night.
What?
You don't have to do that.
You don't do that these days.
I can't leave such a cute wife.
I can't wait for a week.
I can't.
Ah...
this is so tough.
Ah, I feel good...
Ah...
ouch
ah
oh
This is the first time I've done this, so I'm not sure if I'll be able to do it well.
I'm not sure if I'll be able to do it well, so I'm not sure if I'll be able to do it well.
I got used to practicing this method.
I want to have sex.
I can't believe Hikaru is going to do that.
I can't believe it.
Good luck with your work today.
Thank you.
You found a nice house.
Yes.
I want you to wear a skirt.
I don't mind.
That's good.
I'm going.
See you.
You don't mind, do you?
No.
I'm going to clean up.
Am I in the way?
Don't worry about it.
I'm going.
Thank you.
Is Hikaru your partner today?
Yes, from this evening.
What are you doing today?
I'm going to look at some things online.
Hikaru.
I can see your underwear.
What?
Were you peeping at me?
No, I wasn't.
You just didn't care about me.
It's okay.
We've known each other since we were kids.
You don't care about my underwear, do you?
I'm going to clean up.
Hey.
Yes?
You're not wearing your usual skirt.
Yes, I am.
I see.
But my girlfriend just dumped me.
I'm not happy about it.
I'm going home.
I'm going to bed.
It's scary to have animals at home.
Ichiro might attack me.
Ichiro?
What?
I was just kidding.
You're not the one who dumped me.
What?
I felt it here last night.
That's...
What?
Don't do that.
Wait, Ichiro.
Hey.
Don't do that.
Wait.
Ichiro, I'm married.
Don't pretend to be innocent.
Don't say that.
No, I don't mean that.
No.
Wait.
Don't do that.
Ichiro.
No.
Ichiro, don't do that.
I know.
No.
Don't do that.
I know.
Ichiro.
Don't do that.
No.
Ichiro, don't do that.
Don't do that.
Wait.
Ichiro.
Don't do that.
No.
Why? Ichiro.
Don't do that.
Wait.
You have a beautiful butt.
Don't do that.
Ouch.
I was looking at Hikaru in a bad way.
What did you do to Hikaru?
Do you hate Hikaru?
Well...
Tell me.
I want to be an amateur.
Please kiss me.
No.
Ouch.
Please kiss me.
No.
I love you.
I feel good.
I'll kiss you more.
Thank you for your hard work.
I see.
I think you can get ready for tomorrow.
Let's go to drink.
It was hard for me to release him.
I see.
From that day, we started our secret relationship.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Thank you.
He seems to be busy.
He has a lot of complaints.
I see.
I'm worried about him.
Hikaru.
Did you wake up?
Where is my brother?
He went to bed.
I see.
Aren't you sleepy?
I can't stand it anymore.
I want to play with you.
Okay.
Are you afraid of me?
You are cute.
I'm getting bigger.
I'm happy.
Why are you laughing?
I want to see your boobs.
Do you want to see my boobs?
How is it?
Do you like my boobs?
Can I see more?
You are beautiful.
Can I lick your boobs?
You are cute.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
You are amazing.
Wait a minute.
I want to see your face.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'll be more careful.
What is this?
I want to see your butt.
Do you want to see my butt?
Please move your butt a little.
Okay.
You are beautiful.
Your butt is beautiful.
It's hot.
I don't feel good.
What are you saying?
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
I'll clean your face.
It's hot.
I want to kiss you.
I want to feel good.
Okay.
It's hot.
Please touch me more.
I want to feel good.
It's hot.
Hold my legs.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I want to feel good.
It feels good.
It's hot.
When I do this, I remember the old days.
The old days?
Yes.
You stayed with me until the morning.
Yes, I did.
Ichiro fell asleep at that time.
But you talked to me.
You held my hands.
I was happy.
Just kidding.
Are you talking about Hikaru and me?
Let's stop talking about it.
Don't sleep.
You'll catch a cold.
Bye.
Hikaru?
Hikaru still cares about me.
But if I steal Hikaru from him, everyone will be unhappy.
Welcome back.
Did you run?
Yes.
How about you?
I'm fine.
If you don't exercise, you'll get fat.
I've been fat since I married Hikaru.
By the way, Hikaru also got fat after marriage.
Really?
That's not true.
Hikaru is always beautiful.
You're the only one who says that.
I'm glad.
I'm going to stretch.
You can take a shower.
Jiro?
I can't.
Wait.
I can't do it now.
I can't...
If you eat it, can you poop properly??
It smells so disgusting.
I can't do it.
Hang in there.
Jiro.
Do you have any good friends in your hometown?
I don't have any good friends.
I'm sure you have one.
I was wondering.
Do you mean you like her?
Yes.
I don't know.
Hikaru, do you have one?
Yes.
I'm sure you have one.
Think about it.
Did you like her when you were a student?
I don't know.
By the way,
Did you find a good place?
Well,
I found a good place about 3 kilometers from here.
That's good.
I thought I couldn't find a good place.
But I found a good place.
I think I can escape from here.
It's a wild place.
I can live in a wild place.
I'll find a good place and live there.
You always say that.
I want you to move to another place.
It's hard to find a good place.
Jiro will be here soon.
You're right.
I'll clean up.
Do you need help?
No, I'm fine.
I'll clean up.
Do you need help?
No, I'm fine.
I'll clean up.
Thank you.
Do you need help?
Yes.
Jiro.
Yes?
Do you want me to introduce you to a girl at my company?
No, I don't need it.
I go out with her once in a while.
I don't need it.
I think that's enough.
I'm fine now.
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Thank you.
Have you packed your things?
Yes.
I've finished what I can do here.
I don't want to stay here for a long time.
I see.
Let's have a farewell party tonight.
I don't want to be late.
I don't mind.
I'm sorry about the bath.
I'm sorry.
It's strange to say that to a married man.
It's not strange.
I've always liked you.
Hikaru.
Your phone is ringing.
Ichiro.
Hello, Ichiro?
Yes.
Are you free today?
I had a problem at work.
I see.
Yes.
I'm fine.
Good luck at work.
Bye.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
I've been holding it in all this time.
Don't say that.
Ichiro.
I like you.
I've always liked you.
I'm glad.
I don't know what to do.
I love you.
I love you too.
...
Uh-oh.
It feels so good.
Ahh.
Ah...
Ouch!
Ouch...
I don't know why but I feel like I'm going to have a hard time with my deafness
I'm going...
Chiyo, I can't take it anymore, you can lie down
I can do it.
Oh, my God.
I feel sick.
I love you, too.
I'm going.
Give me a kiss.
I love you, too.
I feel sick.
I'm going.
I love you, too.
I feel sick.
I'm going.
I love you.
I want to be with you forever.
It's hot, so be careful.
Thank you.
Are you going?
Yes.
It's shining.
It's good.
Did you forget something?
It's okay.
Thank you.
You can come anytime.
I'll go get the car.
Wait a minute.
I'm going.
Chihiro.
Hikaru.
I'll pick you up.
I'm waiting for you.
I'm going.
Then I'm going out.
Translated by Releska