I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to die if I don't do this.
Hello.
I'm here.
I'm sorry I dropped by all of a sudden.
OK.
My husband hasn't been away on business for a while, so I thought I'd practice traveling now.
I can't help you if you don't know what's going on anywhere since your baby's born.
Thank you very much.
Oh, please have a seat.
I'll bring you some tea.
Where's Nomi?
He's going to the hospital for a check-up.
I was going to go with him, but I don't want him to be stuck all the time.
During the check-up, your mind and body become unstable.
Oh, is that so?
I see.
Can you tell me how to use the kitchen?
Sure.
Well...
This is the big plate.
And that's a colander.
These are cooking utensils.
And this is a knife.
I'm home!
Welcome home!
Oh, it's you, mom!
Long time no see!
Are you okay?
How was the check-up?
It went well.
That's good.
You must be tired.
Yes, I am.
I'm exhausted.
Me, too.
It's been a while.
You've grown up.
It's this month.
I'm looking forward to it.
Me, too.
Here's your tea.
Thank you.
It stinks!
You smoked, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
I'm sorry.
I told you many times not to smoke because it's bad for the baby!
I told you I'd quit if I were born.
You can't quit when you're pregnant!
I don't smoke when you're around.
Why are you yelling?
Because you're yelling!
Apologize.
What's with that attitude?
I'm sorry.
Mom.
Can you quit smoking?
I don't want to.
Please use this room.
It's a work room now, but I'm going to make it a children's room.
I see.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I want to be of help to Nami, so I'm helping her with the housework.
But I'm so tired from all the work.
I'll take care of the housework, so don't worry.
Mifu is doing a good job.
I'm sure he'll be a good dad.
Thank you.
Is this it?
Yes, please.
Thank you.
Is your mom at work?
Yes.
She just took a day off.
Really?
Will you come every day when you're born?
I don't think I can come every day.
I feel better when my mom is there.
I'll try to be there as much as I can.
Hey!
Shut up!
What are you doing?
Nami.
I'm sorry.
I'm so irritated that I can't stand it.
Water.
Nami.
I'm so tired.
I know.
Get along with her.
Okay.
Apologize to her.
Can I talk to you?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
I'm so irritated that I can't stand it.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
What?
Wait.
Did you do it alone?
Why?
You promised you wouldn't do it.
It's okay to do it alone.
No!
I'm doing what I want to do for her.
Why do you do whatever you want?
Believe me!
I can't.
I might cheat on her.
Then you should get a divorce.
I'll sleep in the living room tonight.
Do whatever you want!
I'm sorry.
Yoshi.
I overheard your fight.
You can't do it alone.
It's weird that you can't stand it.
I know how you feel.
I was frustrated during my pregnancy.
I was stressed out by my husband.
He cheated on me before Nami was born.
I was sad.
But I didn't realize it.
Babies need a father.
But I still have a thorn in my heart.
My heart aches when I think about it.
I don't want Nami to feel that way.
I'll take care of Yoshi.
Don't cheat on him.
It's okay.
It's just a hand.
It's not cheating.
Yoshi.
Yes?
Get well soon.
Okay.
Is there anything you want me to do?
Is there?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
You don't have to hold it in.
I'll hold it.
It's in the way, isn't it?
Yes.
It feels good.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to lick me.
It feels good.
It feels good on my head, too.
It's very hard.
It feels good.
Mom.
Can I kiss you?
It's hot.
Mom.
If it's okay with you,
I want you to let me suck your boobs.
Can I?
Hurry up.
It's hot.
On my knees.
Let me suck your boobs.
It's hot.
Mom.
I want you to lick me again.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Mom.
I want you to lick me again.
It's hot.
You puked a lot.
Yes.
Did it feel good?
That's good.
It's hot.
You puked a lot.
Did it feel good?
Yes.
That's good.
It's hot.
Can I have this back?
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
My back hurts.
Massage me.
Later.
Why don't you be nice to me?
It's hot.
My legs hurt.
Your legs?
They're swollen.
I see.
Not there.
Massage me.
Doesn't it hurt?
Massage me harder.
Harder?
I don't feel good.
Massage me.
Nami.
Don't you think this salon is nice?
It's nice.
There's a massage shop nearby.
Why don't you go there?
It's nice.
Is it okay?
Can I go there?
Of course.
Really?
Thank you.
I'll go get ready.
I made a reservation.
I didn't know that.
Are you okay?
I didn't know.
It's nice.
Thank you.
Good luck with your work.
Okay.
I made a reservation.
I still have some housework to do.
I'll be back.
You can't.
You were fine yesterday.
You'll be fine for a while.
I'll be back.
What's wrong with you?
I can't.
I can't stand it.
You can't.
You're working.
I'm worried about my mom.
I can't concentrate.
Mom.
You can't.
I can't stand it.
Please.
You can't.
I can't.
Mom.
Please.
Do you understand?
Mom.
I can't help it.
This is the last time.
Okay.
Mom.
Don't be angry.
Tomorrow.
At 9 o'clock.
Take off your clothes.
9 o'clock.
Mom.
Mom, it feels good.
Yes.
It feels good.
Well.
I'm going to bed.
Okay.
Good night.
I want you to kiss me again.
It feels good.
Let me kiss you.
I have a cold.
Get well soon.
It's hot.
Just a little.
Mom.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't bear it.
It's hot.
Mom.
Look at me.
It's hot.
I couldn't bear it.
Look at me.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
Calm down.
I'll do it with my hands.
It's hot.
Mom.
Mother...
You're crying, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
You're not, are you?
Don't cry.
Mother...
Please don't cry.
I can't take it anymore.
Get me out of here.
Mother...
You're so wet.
You want me, don't you?
No, I'm not wet.
You are.
No, I'm not.
That's...
That's no good.
You can't do that.
I can't do that.
I can't.
Mother...
It feels so good.
It's no good.
It feels so good here.
I can't take it anymore.
Mother...
It's no good.
Get me out of here.
Mother, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Mother...
Did you like it?
It feels so good.
Mother...
Please take this off.
Take it off.
It's no good.
Take this off.
One more time.
It's no good.
I can't take it anymore.
One more time.
Can I?
Can I take it off?
Take it off.
It feels so good.
Mother...
I haven't been able to have sex in a long time.
I haven't been able to do anything.
It's been a long time.
It feels so good.
Mother...
Can I do more?
Can I?
Mother...
It feels good, doesn't it?
Can I cry?
Can I?
Mother...
Can I cry?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Mother...
I'm home.
Welcome home.
How was it?
The curry was so good.
I want to buy sushi again.
It's good, isn't it?
I bought a ticket.
Really?
It's a good deal.
Why don't you go there, too?
I'll go there.
I heard that there's a bone marrow competition.
I want to go there when I'm born.
It's good, isn't it?
Don't you want to have a big butt?
Mother...
Thank you for cleaning the bath.
I'll do it.
Leave it to me.
Thank you.
Can you help me, too?
Okay.
What's wrong with Miyuki?
She told me to help her.
I'll help you.
Are you okay?
I'm going to get wet.
I told you to forget about yesterday.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
It's my fault.
I'm going to get wet.
I'm going to take a bath.
I'm going home tomorrow morning.
Stay a little longer.
I want to stay with my mom.
But my dad will come home.
I can't do anything without my dad and mom.
Instead, I'll make you something you like today.
Really?
Then I'll have an omelet.
Okay.
I see.
I'm going to lend it to my mom.
Are you done with your work?
Yes, I'm done.
Mom, I'll help you.
Thank you.
Thanks to my mom, I'm in a good mood.
Please stay a little longer.
I can't.
But I can't live without my mom.
I can't live without my mom.
Stop looking at me.
Don't look at me.
Mom.
I can't live without you.
I can't.
But you don't hate me, do you?
I don't hate you.
I can't.
Mom.
How are you?
I'm fine.
How about you?
Are you on a diet?
I haven't been on a diet recently.
I see.
You only eat soil.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
But you have a strong back.
No, I don't.
I'm sorry.
Mom.
You're wet.
I'm not wet.
What should I do with the laundry?
Did you do the laundry?
I'll do it later.
Please do it.
It's slippery.
Don't worry.
I'll do it.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
Are you off until tomorrow?
That's right.
I see.
I feel lonely.
That's right.
I can't help it.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for supporting me in the short time I have
please don't cry
That should be fine.
Now that's okay.
Black
A
one
I thought
It's hard
It's a
mother
Is itウ
good?
Hmmm
Wow
Hmm
Look
What's the matter with you?
You've done your homework.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Can you give me your car?
I understand.
Where is your mother?
She is in the bathroom.
Is that so.
Please close your eyes.
It's a very good feeling.
I'm going to bed.
Good night.
You're going to bed tomorrow, right?
Is that so?
Can you leave me alone?
I got it.
I don't want to be found out.
Then,
Do it more.
Good night.
I'm going to be found out.
What's wrong?
My stomach is moving.
Wait a minute.
It's moving.
It's amazing.
My stomach is moving.
Hurry up.
I'm sorry.
Look at this.
My stomach is moving.
It's true.
It's amazing.
It's like this.
You're a man.
Is that so?
You're so energetic.
I'm sorry.
One last time.
Please do it again.
No.
If I do it again,
I'll be serious.
It's okay.
I'll forget it.
I'll be serious.
I'm jealous of you and Nami.
I'm Nami's mother.
Let's be patient with each other.
Mother.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Yeah,
my
friend
Yep, it's nastyきれい
I'm going to puke
I feel sick.
My goodness!
Damn!
Let's drink together.
Come here.
It's hot.
Can I put it in?
I want to put it in, too.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'm glad.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
Mom.
Can I do more?
I'll do it a lot today.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Mom.
It's a waste.
Get up.
Please move.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, mom.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
You've become more like your father.
Is that so?
Actually, I'm pregnant.
What?
Don't worry. I'll take care of you.
Keep up the good work, Dad.