Let me explain it, Keiichi.
Akabane himself has split up in Gakuignosuke's party.
For now, they are helping each other.
Hiroshi-kun!
Oh, Mom!
Oh, hello.
Are you going out?
No.
If I smoke at home, I'll get scolded by Yui.
Oh, I see.
Oh, I'll carry your luggage.
Oh, that's fine.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Excuse me.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Your face is getting kinder.
Is that so?
Is it because the baby is a girl?
Hmm.
Until Dad comes back, Mom will help you, so please tell me anything.
Thank you.
You're getting bigger.
Ah, another cigarette?
Eh?
I told you to quit it, but you didn't quit at all.
I helped with the housework, but now I have more work to do.
I'm in trouble.
Oh, well, well.
I bought a souvenir, so I'll give it to you.
You like this, don't you?
Thank you.
You like this, don't you, Hiroshi?
Eat up.
Oh, and this.
I thought it would look good on you, so I bought it.
I'm glad.
It does look good on you.
Mom.
It's cool.
You're going to be a dad soon, so don't treat me like a kid.
I'm sorry.
You know, I've always wanted a son and a daughter,
so I want to be like a real son and do everything for them.
If you want a son so badly, why don't you work with me?
I mean, you're still young.
You can have another son, right?
No way.
I'm not like that with you anymore.
I'm looking forward to it.
Come in, mom.
Thank you.
Please use this room.
It's a work room now, but I'm going to turn it into a children's room.
Oh, I see.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, it's a mess.
I'll clean it up.
No, it's okay.
I'll do it, so you can work.
But...
It's okay.
I'll do it.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Please come in.
Thank you.
Did you work?
Yes.
This looks difficult.
No, it's not.
Do you do this every day?
Yes.
Wow.
Men who can work are cool.
By the way, I'm in the way, aren't I?
I'm sorry.
Thank you for coming.
Yes.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
I can't stand it anymore.
Stop it.
What?
You said you wouldn't do that until the baby was born.
Why?
It's strange to forbid women to have sex.
I'm doing my best with this body, but you're the only one who wants to be clean.
Is that what you mean?
You watch pornography, don't you?
You're cheating on other women.
Do you understand?
I understand.
If you do it, it's not cheating.
What?
You're disgusting.
Aren't you ashamed of having a baby?
Get out of here.
Sleep in the living room tonight.
What?
Good night.
Can I sleep here?
I can't believe it's forbidden to have sex.
What should I do?
If I don't have sex every day, I'll go crazy.
Hiroshi.
Mom.
Did you hear the result?
It's forbidden to have sex alone.
You're overdoing it.
If you don't mind, can I help you?
Why?
I'm just doing it with my hands.
It's not cheating.
It's okay.
It's not cheating?
I'll touch you.
Can I touch you?
Take it off.
Okay.
It's hard, isn't it?
Yes.
It was hard, wasn't it?
It's getting harder and harder.
Since when have you been patient?
It was hard, wasn't it?
It's better to be a little wet, isn't it?
Mom.
Please be patient.
More.
Please.
Okay, more.
More.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You're a strong girl.
No.
You're kind.
You're kind, too.
Mom.
Can I kiss you?
You can't kiss me.
Why?
If you kiss me, you'll cheat on me.
Then...
Can I be patient?
Patience?
Yes.
I can't help it.
Just a little.
Just a little?
Can I have a little more?
Just a little.
Just a little?
I want to kiss you.
Kiss?
Yes.
I want to kiss you.
Then...
Just a little kiss.
Yes.
Wow.
It's amazing.
It's so soft.
It's getting bigger than before.
I'm curious about your big chest.
Do you want to see it?
I do.
Just a little.
Come here.
Yes.
Wow.
Don't look at me.
Just look at me.
Just look at me?
Yes.
It's so big.
Wow.
How is it?
Can't I look at you?
No.
Then...
Just a little.
Yes.
I want to be an adult.
You look like a baby.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Don't hold back.
Just relax.
Yes.
Wow.
It's amazing.
It's getting harder.
Wow.
Mom.
Yes?
I want you to lick me.
Do you want me to lick you?
Yes.
I can't help it.
Can I?
Yes.
I can't help it.
You don't tell Yui, do you?
No.
Yes.
I'm going to put a lot of anesthesia.
It's amazing.
It's intense.
Wow.
Mom is about to sleep.
Really?
Wake up.
Mom is about to sleep.
Wow.
I put a lot of anesthesia.
It's refreshing.
Make up with Yui.
Yes.
Don't cheat on her.
It hurts.
I don't know why you quarreled.
But it's not good to make him sleep on the sofa.
You should sleep with him from today.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I'm sorry, too.
I'm sorry.
Let's shake hands.
Shake hands.
Yes.
Make up with her.
I'm going.
Do you want to go with me?
It's a simple test, so you can go alone.
Take care of the house.
I'm going.
See you.
It was refreshing yesterday, so you'll be fine for a while, right?
Yes.
I'm going.
It was refreshing yesterday, so you'll be fine for a while, right?
Mom.
I can't stand it anymore.
Do you have a job?
I can't work because I'm worried about you.
Please.
I want to work.
But...
If you feel better, you can work.
Yes.
I'm going.
Please touch me a lot.
You can do whatever you want.
I'm going.
It feels so good.
I want you to be a strong woman.
I can't.
It feels so good.
It hurts when I touch you, right?
It's amazing.
Your body is very attractive.
It hurts.
Let me see.
I'll make you feel better with my hands and hands.
I'm going.
Be careful.
I can't.
If I do this, I'll cheat on you.
Can I cheat on you with someone other than your mother?
I can't do that.
Can I?
I'll make you feel better.
Wait for me.
I can't.
I can't do this.
Let me see.
I can't.
Hiroshi, you can't do this.
Let me see.
I can't.
It's so big.
It's amazing.
I can't.
I can't do that.
It's so wet here.
It's so wet.
I can't.
I can't do that.
It's amazing.
It's so wet.
I can't.
Let me see.
It's so wet.
I can't.
It's so wet here.
It's amazing.
I can't.
Can I smell you?
Does it feel good?
I can't.
Why can't you?
How about this?
I can't.
Let me see.
It's so wet.
I can't.
Can you see?
I can't go any further.
Calm down.
It's so wet.
Stay still.
Don't look at me.
I can't.
What should I do?
Mom.
Don't look at me.
It's okay, mom.
I can't.
You're getting used to it.
Look.
Are you okay?
Calm down.
What's wrong?
I can't stand up.
I can't.
Why?
It's okay.
I can't.
Can you see me?
I'll get you up.
Get me up.
I can't.
I ca n't eat
I'm sorry.
Please don't do this.
I can't stand it anymore.
Wait a minute.
Don't do that.
I'm serious.
Wait a minute.
Please don't do that.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
Don't do that.
Please don't do that.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
That's amazing.
You're still crying.
I still want to do it.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
That's amazing.
Please don't do that.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
Mom.
I'm still standing.
That's amazing.
It's only until you get here.
You can't cheat on me with anyone else.
I won't do it.
Don't lie to me.
It's okay.
No way.
The bear is wet.
It's all wet.
Okay, okay.
Oh, it smells good.
Welcome back.
How was it?
It was fine.
I'm glad.
You helped me with dinner.
Oh, yes.
Thank you.
I'll go to the sofa.
Take a rest.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's amazing.
It's clean.
It's still there.
Is it still there?
Yes.
I'm hungry.
Really?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It's bubbling.
You look fine.
You're hungry.
It's amazing.
You look fine.
Thank you.
It's amazing.
Mom.
Yes.
I'll go for a walk.
Okay.
A walk?
Yes.
Be careful.
Okay.
I'll go for a walk.
Have a good day.
You look fine.
Mom.
It feels good.
I'll go for a walk.
It's amazing.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much
Thank you.
The way she looks after the baby is trembling.
I can't take it anymore.
It feels good.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Did you go shopping?
Yes.
Where's Hiroshi?
Maybe he's at work.
He's not here.
Is he smoking again?
I'll look for him.
Have a good day.
I can't take it anymore.
What if he finds you?
Please, mom.
I can't take it anymore.
Can you play with me?
With you?
I can't take it anymore.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
I can't take it anymore.
It feels good.
Mom, I can't take it anymore.
Please, eat it.
Please, lick it.
I can't take it anymore.
Mom, I can't take it anymore.
I just said it.
I can't take it anymore.
Here you go.
You're going home tomorrow, right?
Stay a little longer.
I want to stay with you, but dad will come back.
I see.
You don't have to stay with mom.
You have me.
I'm fine.
I'll take care of the rest.
Take a rest on the sofa.
Are you sure?
Thank you.
Mom, I'll help you.
Mom, please stay a little longer.
Please.
It's embarrassing because dad will come back.
I know.
Please.
It's embarrassing.
Thank you.
I'm fine.
Hey.
What's up?
Come here.
Look at this.
I bought this book.
Let's write our names on it.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's spring.
Please.
One last time.
I can't.
I've always wanted a boy.
I couldn't give up.
I wanted to be like my son.
If I do more than this, I'll fall in love.
Honey.
Let's go to bed.
I'm going home tomorrow.
The baby is doing fine.
I think the baby will be happy.
Hey, honey, we're...
Why don't we...
Why don't we make a baby again?
I know, but...
I've seen two of them looking happy, and...
That's what I thought.
Well...
Let's talk tomorrow.
See you.
Yeah.
I don't know what to do.
How you doing, dude?
bless you, buddy.
Can I kiss you?
Can I, Georgie?
Thank you so much!
I love you.
This is the first time I've done this.
Don't do that.
I'm going to throw up.
I want to drink a lot.
I want to drink more.
I feel sick.
I'm going to throw up.
I want to drink a lot.
I want to lick you.
I'm going to throw up.
...
..
....
...
.....?
.....
...
....
Your ears are yellow...
What's wrong?
Ah, it feels so good.
It feels so good.
Give me your hand.
Ah, it feels so good.
More.
I want to do more.
Give me a lot.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah.
Ahh.
Did you spit it out?
It feels so good.
Ouch!
You're so cute!
You're laughing so much!
I'm your grandma.
I'm your mom.
You're so cute!
You're a good girl.
Are you sleeping?
Yes.
Let me see.
I'm your dad.
Are you used to it?
Yes, but it was hard at first.
Because my mom didn't come at all.
I'm sorry.
Were you busy?
A little.
I couldn't sleep.
You couldn't sleep?
Congratulations!
What's wrong?
Are you hungry?
Watch your head.
Come here.
Are you hungry?
I'll make you milk.
He was a boy.
What's your name?
Dad.
Congratulations!