Two weeks after failing to focus on practice
Happy to play for new Team
and striving for new days
You are getting better recently
You think so?
The knot
You guys got better
I'm a bit tipsy
You're drinking too much.
Next time, please don't drink so much.
You've been drinking a lot lately.
It's hard to make money.
But it's good.
It's good.
Have you been playing golf lately?
No, I haven't been able to go at all.
I don't drink at all.
That's right.
It's hard to go to work.
I haven't been able to go to work at all, so I'm proud of my golf club.
I bought this.
Please show me.
Really?
I got married.
It's a secret to him.
Is it a secret?
I got married.
That's right.
But thanks to that, I'm very happy.
You guys are just playing.
That's right.
Let us make it.
We're the ones who clean up.
But I'm always busy at work.
Isn't it about today?
Kyoka is too kind.
Really?
This is the same as when I'm at home.
That's right.
Women are good at making sweets.
Women are good at cooking.
I don't want you to think that way.
Women don't always carry small sewing sets.
Really?
I'm carrying it.
Really.
Look.
It's true.
That's amazing.
There are kind people like Kyoka.
Men shouldn't date.
That's right.
Hey, Miki.
Did you say something?
I didn't say anything.
Bring me a canapé.
Okay.
I'll bring it.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Here it is.
Here you go.
Satoshi, you're a kind husband.
Really?
Isn't it normal?
It's not normal.
Hey.
You're saying bad things about me again.
I'm not.
You're so mean.
We're good friends, aren't we?
No, we're not.
We always fight.
Really?
Let's drink wine while we eat.
Sounds good.
Let's keep it a secret.
Here's the canapé.
It looks delicious.
Thank you.
You should practice more.
It's difficult.
I'll teach you.
Please.
Thank you.
Kanda and Tachibana live in the same apartment.
They visit each other's apartment once a month.
Kanda's wife, Kyouka, and Miki,
have decided to tell each other about their husbands.
Today, Kanda's wife invited me to her house.
Kanda and I practiced putting until the food was ready.
Thank you.
Tachibana.
I'm going to buy a title list.
What?
I was thinking about which one to buy,
but I think the title list suits me better.
So, I bought it.
Is it that expensive?
Are you sure?
It's not that expensive.
Oh, and this is a secret.
I'm going to buy a golf car.
Are you serious?
I don't think I can go golf with this car.
So, I bought it.
Are you sure?
Of course, it's a secret from Miki.
So, please don't tell her.
If I were you, I'd be angry.
Tachibana, let's buy it.
No, no, no.
Kyouka will be angry.
Is it okay to buy a golf club?
No, no, no.
The other day, he bought a golf club.
Really?
It's a club called Taito something.
He only has one hand, right?
I wonder how many he's going to buy.
Hey, Miki.
You're making fun of me again.
Really?
Stop it.
In front of Tachibana's wife.
My wife has a lot of complaints.
What are they?
Even if it's a golf club,
It doesn't make sense if the inside is lame.
Lame?
Do you still have that?
Yes.
It's okay to have a golf club.
It's not okay.
I'm making money, so it's okay.
So, you don't have to buy it.
You don't know how good it is.
It's really good.
Let's not fight.
That's right.
We're all having fun.
Let's cheers.
I'll bring it.
Ryoji, take this.
Thank you.
Take it.
I got it.
Here you go.
I'll make it.
Miki, you're good at this.
I can do whatever I want.
Does it look delicious?
It looks delicious.
Doesn't it look delicious?
Cheers.
Let's cheers.
It's delicious.
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's really good.
Miki, you don't like what I did.
Well, well, well.
That's right.
It's about the same.
I was doing it a while ago, but I couldn't do it at all.
You failed.
I failed.
Kanako.
I want to get married to Satoshi.
Wait, wait, wait.
What are you talking about?
I was surprised.
I want to get married to Kyoka.
You can't.
You can't get married to Satoshi.
No, no, no.
You can't, can you?
You're always nagging me.
It's the first day of our marriage.
That's right.
Let's drink.
Let's have fun.
Cheers.
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
It's really good.
Let's eat.
Thank you.
It's a good meal.
It's good.
It goes well with wine.
It's delicious.
Mr. Kanda's wife was very angry.
I wonder if it's okay.
Actually, KENTA.
There's another big explosion.
What is it?
You bought a car, didn't you?
Are you kidding me?
It's really bad.
It's a big deal.
I wonder if it's okay.
I don't know.
I'm scared.
I think the fight will get worse.
I don't know what to do.
What should we do with the bath?
Do you want to take a bath first?
Let's take a bath.
Okay.
What is it?
Isn't it Miki and KENTA?
They're having a big fight.
I don't know what's going on.
Mr. Kanda.
Listen to me.
What's wrong?
Why did you bring such a big luggage?
Listen to me.
He bought a car without telling me.
It's okay.
You're going to use it, too.
I don't need a car.
You need it.
I don't need it.
That's why I bought it.
I'm really going out.
Really?
Then go out.
I'm going out.
Hurry up and go out.
It's okay.
I'm going out.
Go out.
Hurry up.
Please stop fighting.
Let's go back to the room.
I can't live with him.
I don't want to live with a narrow-minded person like him.
Don't say that.
What are you doing?
I'm going home.
I can't live with him.
Go home.
Don't say that.
Please stop.
Your home is Kyushu, isn't it?
I'll do as you say.
I'm going home.
Wait a minute.
Please calm down.
I understand.
But I can't live with him.
I can't live with him, either.
I don't want to sleep under the same roof as him.
Then let's calm down in our house.
That's right.
Let's drink some hot tea and calm down.
Okay.
Let's go.
I'll listen to you.
Have you calmed down?
Yes.
I don't think you can sleep with him when you go back to Kyushu.
I think so, too.
But I don't want to be with him now.
Miki.
Why don't you stay at my house?
What?
I think it's better.
But...
No, but.
I think it's impossible to fix it when you go back to Kyushu.
I think so, too.
Can I?
Yes, you can.
Right?
Yes.
Thank you.
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
Have you eaten?
Not yet.
I see.
Then we have to get ready.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
It's delicious.
I'm glad.
This is really good, too.
Miki made it.
Really?
Yes.
It's really good.
I'm glad.
It's really fresh.
I think so, too.
Three of us.
Yes.
I'm happy to have a variety of accessories.
I'm good at this kind of thing.
It's good.
It's good, isn't it?
Isn't this my house?
Yes.
Kenta, did you break the plate?
I wonder if Kenta is okay.
He's fine on his own.
You say that.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Kenta can't eat.
I'll make it.
I'll do it.
Don't.
You'll fight again.
I'll make it.
Today?
You're Miki's partner.
I'll be right back.
Don't worry about it.
Let's eat.
I'm sorry.
Good evening.
Kyoka.
What's wrong?
I'm here to help you.
I'm fine.
Excuse me.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Leave it to me.
What?
You're bald.
I was going to make ramen.
The egg is broken.
I was going to put an egg on it.
Didn't you have hair?
I'm sorry.
I'll do it later.
Please sit down.
I'm sorry.
What are you going to do?
I'll do it alone.
Alone?
You can't cook well.
I'll do it.
I wish I was as kind as you.
What are you talking about?
You're kind, too.
Let's eat.
Okay.
It's delicious.
Kyoka did it on her own.
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
Let's eat.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
The chopsticks are stuck.
Let's eat and cheer up.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
How are you?
Do you want to make up?
No.
I see.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm going to see Kenta.
What?
You can't do anything alone.
I'm sorry.
You can't do anything alone, either.
I'll do it.
You'll fight again when you get back.
I'll listen to Kenta.
You listen to Miki.
Okay.
It's a good opportunity to see each other again.
Miki.
Can you help me collect the leaves?
Okay.
Thank you.
It's hot.
This was the beginning of everything.
Kyoka.
What's wrong?
You've changed.
What?
You haven't changed much, have you?
Let me do it.
Can I do it?
Of course.
Thank you.
I'll bring a plate and chopsticks.
It's over there.
Okay.
I see.
You look like a married couple.
Yes.
Here you are.
Thank you.
It's amazing.
It's not a big deal.
Can I eat it?
Of course.
It's really good.
Really?
Yes.
I'm glad.
Actually, Miki made it.
What?
Is that so?
It's okay.
Please eat it today.
Okay.
I'll listen to you today.
Really?
Can you drink wine with me?
What?
We can't live without alcohol.
Okay?
I can't help it.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Don't tell her that you drank with me.
Of course.
Let's drink a lot and have a party.
Okay.
Please drink a lot.
You're a fast drinker.
Especially today.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I made you suffer.
If you're worried about me,
you don't have to live like this.
I can't apologize to you.
Really?
Yes.
I sleep on the floor.
No.
Please sleep well.
The bedroom is over there.
I'm sorry.
Please sleep well.
Good night.
I want to apologize to you.
You can apologize to me.
I want you to understand.
If I have a child,
I can't live like this.
I can't go out.
Did you tell her?
No.
That's not good.
Men are clumsy.
I drank too much.
It's 1.30 a.m.
You're right.
I drank too much.
Do you want to drink more?
I'm fine.
I have to get up tomorrow.
I don't know what she'll say.
I see.
Do you want to take a bath tomorrow?
Yes.
You drank too much.
I'll sleep here tonight.
You can sleep in the bedroom.
No.
Miki will be angry.
I don't care.
Really?
Yes.
I'll sleep here.
You can sleep in the bedroom.
I can't.
I'll sleep here.
You can sleep in the bedroom.
Okay.
You can wash the dishes tomorrow.
I'll drink this.
Okay.
Miki.
What's wrong?
I wish I could be an adult like you.
You're an adult.
Thank you.
Satoshi.
Yes?
Can I hug your back?
No.
When I'm lonely, I want to lean on something.
But you're the one who can lean on my back.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Good night.
I almost made a mistake.
I can't believe I'm sleeping with my neighbor's wife in my own house.
But I can tell Kyoka that.
I'm sorry.
Kenta.
Wake up.
Good morning.
Please.
Wake up.
Good morning.
When did you become like this?
I don't know.
Can you get away from me?
You're hitting me.
I'm sorry.
Can you get away from me?
Let's keep this a secret.
Kenta.
Are you listening to me?
No.
I'm sorry.
I said no.
Calm down.
I'm sorry.
I said no.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm sorry.
I said no.
Calm down.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what I'm doing.
I said no.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
I said no.
I'm sorry.
I told you I was going to talk to you, didn't I?
You did? That's wonderful.
Please, calm down.
If you look at me like that, I can't calm down.
No, no, no.
You're going to talk to me, aren't you?
I'll talk to you.
I'm going to talk to you.
No, no, no.
Please, stop it.
Calm down.
No, no, no.
Please.
Calm down.
No, no, no.
I can't breathe.
Please.
Can you hear me?
No, no, no.
Wait.
Please.
I can't breathe.
Calm down.
I don't know what I'm doing.
I know.
No, no, no.
I can't do this.
Please, calm down.
I don't know.
I can't do this.
Please, calm down.
Calm down.
I can't do this.
Do you know how beautiful you are?
I don't know what I'm doing.
I can't do this.
It's your fault.
You're in a coma.
I can't do this.
Oh no, not again.
No, stop it.
It doesn't feel good at all.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
She's gone.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
She's gone.
I can't!
I'm gonna be quick!
Please, no!
I can't, I can't!
Please!
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
I can't do it anymore.
Wait.
No, no, no.
I'll give you a massage.
No.
I can't do it anymore.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
I hate it.
No, no.
Touch me.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
I'll do it again.
Are you enough?
I can't do it anymore.
I couldn't hear you talking like this.
It's okay.
It's all right.
Please, hang in there.
It will pass.
It's okay.
Ah...
Does it feel good?
It's okay.
It's a real man.
There there.
There, there.
Long time no see!
Have you eaten?
Open your mouth.
Don't cry...
Let it out more
It's all right, it's all right.
It doesn't work.
It's all right.
It's all right, it's all right.
Can I hurry up?
A.
This way.
No.
Don't, Oku.
Look at the inside of her body.
Oh, dear.
Don't, Oku.
Look at the inside of her body.
Oku, don't.
Don't, Oku.
Let's get up.
What have you done?
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to do.
What are you looking at?
I'm sorry. I just looked at it.
I'm sorry.
Are you worried about Satoshi?
It's already 10 o'clock, but the curtains aren't open.
I think he's sleeping.
At this time?
I told him too much.
I think he'll be able to breathe.
I'm going to talk to him.
That's good.
Let's have some tea.
Okay.
I'm going to talk to him.
It's more like lunch than breakfast.
Please say something.
Don't you think it's Miki's fault?
It's a betrayal.
That's right.
We just talked about wanting a child.
I remember that.
Please cherish Miki more.
I'm sorry.
You're betraying your wife.
I'm not betraying her.
If you feel that way, you're betraying her.
I'm sorry.
I've been worried about my wife.
I don't know what to say.
I've been waiting for her to come here once a month.
Please don't say such a confusing thing.
I'm not going to say it lightly.
But I fell in love with my wife.
It's over. I'm going home.
Wait a minute.
I'm in trouble.
I can't do this.
I don't want to go home.
I can't.
I'm going home.
I'm in trouble.
I'm sorry.
What are you going to do?
I'm going home.
I can't.
I can't forget my wife.
Miki is here.
I like my wife more than Miki.
What are you talking about?
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Miki is here.
I don't want to talk to her.
I'm in trouble.
My husband is here.
Please.
Calm down.
I'm in trouble.
I can't.
I can't forget my wife.
I'm in trouble.
I like my wife more than Miki.
Do you feel your body?
Take a deep breath.
I can't.
I can't do this.
Take a deep breath.
What should I do?
You should feel better now.
I can't do this.
You are injured.
Please lick me.
I can't do this.
You should feel better now.
Wife.
What's wrong?
I forgot something.
That's good.
I'll go shopping.
Did you stay at home the other day?
What?
My husband was worried about you.
I'm sorry this happened to you because of me.
I'll buy some food for you.
I'll go home tomorrow.
I don't want to bother you.
I want to talk to him.
I see.
Come in.
Thank you.
Be careful.
I'll go.
I'm sorry.
You...
How's it going?
I went to buy food for you.
I saw you there.
Are you going home tomorrow?
Yes.
I heard that too.
What's wrong?
I forgot something.
I see.
Where did you sleep?
In the bedroom.
I slept on the sofa.
I see.
You slept separately, right?
Of course.
I see.
It's strange.
I'm sorry.
You're not married.
You're living under the same roof.
You're right.
Wait.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
You're not married.
I can't.
You can't.
Miki is back.
It's okay.
Wait.
Please.
I can't.
Miki is back.
Wait.
I can't.
I'll wait for you tomorrow.
I should have noticed my wife earlier.
Excuse me.
Can we sleep in the bedroom tonight?
I can't.
We're husband and wife.
We're just neighbors from now on.
How do you know that?
Miki told me.
She'll be back tomorrow.
So...
Just for today.
We're just neighbors...
from now on.
If we stay like this,
we'll be in trouble.
So,
let's sleep together tonight.
Okay.
That's all for today.
Yes.
Can I talk to her tomorrow?
You'll be fine.
Thank you.
I thought...
I could make a mistake with you.
What?
But...
I can't marry you.
Miki...
I'm just kidding.
Good night.
Can we do this?
We're just neighbors from now on.
But we're close.
We'll be back soon.
Good night.
That way.
I can't do it.
That was close.
I'm sorry.
Good morning.
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Can I do this in the morning?
I want to do this in the morning.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to go to the bathroom.
I will do everything
just to go to the bathroom.
Just to go to the bathroom.
Just to do
Just let me do
just let me do
right now
would get home
I'm sorry.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
Do you cheat in this way?
No, I don't.
It's so difficult.
It's okay, it's okay.
Wait.
No, I don't.
I'm sweating.
Wait.
No, I don't.
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm sweating.
I feel good.
No, I don't.
I'm sweating.
It's okay, it's okay.
No, I don't.
Wait, wait.
It's okay, it's okay.
No, I don't.
I'm sweating.
I feel good.
No, I don't.
I'm sweating.
I feel good.
Wait, wait.
I'm sweating.
Aaah!!!
I can't stand it anymore.
The other way!
No more!
I can't stand it.
OH,NO!
Ouch!
Oh, my God!
It's so thick and big.
I know you're hitting me.
I'll do my best if I have to.
Oh, my God!
No, no, no.
No, no.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
Swearing
What the hell are you doing, Ryoko?
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no.
No, don't do that.
It hurts.
No, no, no.
I'm fine.
I'm fine!
How do you feel?
I feel great.
I'm fine.
How do you feel?
No! No!
Is everything okay?
Shunsuke, please.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no!
Oh, no.
How are you feeling?
Go to bed.
Come here.
You moved by yourself, so your voice is dying.
My back hurts so bad.
Let me help you.
If you make too much noise, your husband will hear you.
Be patient.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
Let me help you.
No, no, no.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
Here's your lunch.
What's wrong?
Are you that happy about your lunch?
Sir, you're acting strange.
Sir, are you sure you're okay?
What's wrong?
Since then, my wife has been hiding from me...
...along with my husband.