Thank you for watching.
Oh, you're here.
Welcome back.
Here.
Yoshino, it's been a while.
It's been a while.
I've been drinking all the time.
This is a senior from another station.
My name is Yoshino.
Good evening.
Please come in.
Thank you for coming.
Are you a gynecologist?
Yes.
They say gynecologists are rare these days.
That's right.
Skin care and eye care are popular.
I see.
Where's the bathroom?
It's in the hallway.
Yoshino
How's my brother doing?
He's a little misunderstood by his looks.
But he's the best in the station.
Right?
You've seen through me.
He's a year younger than me, so he's like a parent to me.
I understand.
Thank you.
Yoshino
You don't look good.
What?
I see.
Do you have any trauma in the past?
Like you hate sex.
What?
When I was drinking, I asked my brother.
I can't do much, but I'm doing what I have to do.
My brother said he was hurt when he joined.
No, I don't think so.
I'm a doctor's egg, so I'm fine.
In medical terms, it's called genitalia.
Genitalia
It's called genitalia in the world.
It's a urban legend that he couldn't get out of the penis.
In fact, most genitalia occur before they are inserted.
I see.
It's just that the muscles around the penis are stiff.
It hurts, but you insert it without loosening it, so you hate sex.
You know a lot.
I'll introduce you to a good doctor next time.
Would you like a female doctor?
Yes, please.
Please like sex.
What?
It's a genitalia, so genitalia are enemies.
I see.
You don't have to be nervous about alcohol.
Would you like to drink with me?
Then
I'm going to the last stop, so I'll leave you alone.
Please go ahead.
It's early in the morning tomorrow.
I see.
Thank you for the delicious sake and time.
See you again.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
See you again.
Yes.
Excuse me.
It's a gift.
Yes.
Thank you for your time.
Please come again.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Sister.
Would you like to come to the Japanese-style room when my brother wakes up?
Yes.
I've forgotten the continuation of the story.
I see.
I'm going.
Please take off your underwear and lie down there.
What?
I'll take a look at your genitalia.
Are you sure?
I'm embarrassed because I think you're my brother.
I don't feel anything when I look at your genitalia.
You're right.
I don't feel anything.
While you're relaxing with sake,
Come on.
Yes.
Thank you.
Please put your hand there.
Yes.
Thank you.
If it hurts, please raise your right hand.
Yes.
Please sit on your knees.
Thank you.
I'm going to examine your genitalia.
Yes.
As I thought, your genitalia are very small.
Don't get me wrong.
This is your genitalia.
Yes.
Please relax.
Thank you.
Does it hurt?
No.
I'm relaxing your muscles.
Yes.
Thank you.
Are you all right?
I'm an egg of the Sanfujinkai.
This is my job.
Please relax and leave it to me.
Thank you.
Take a deep breath.
It seems to have loosened up.
Thank you.
That's...
I have to loosen up here.
That's not good.
Does it hurt?
No.
Are you all right?
It's not painful.
Please relax.
Slowly.
Please look at this.
I'm sorry.
I have to loosen up here.
How is it?
It's not good.
It's very tight.
You're sweating a lot.
Let's...
Let's have sex.
I don't think that's a good idea.
I'm just kidding.
I'm your brother's wife.
This is the limit of what my brother can do.
Even medical treatment.
By the way, your sister's body is very erotic.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm a man before I'm a doctor.
I can't help but look at you.
I envy my brother.
I'm going.
See you later.
I betrayed my husband.
No, that was medical treatment.
And it's my brother's fault.
I just got swept away.
Did you forget something?
What are you doing?
I'm going to give you a kiss.
What are you talking about?
Relax.
Leave it to me.
Let me kiss you.
If it wasn't for medical treatment, I wouldn't do this for free.
It's just a finger, isn't it?
That's right.
It's just a finger, so it's not cheating.
But...
If you don't drink, you'll be more alert.
Do you want to drink?
Wait a minute.
I'm going.
Stop.
Give me the alcohol in your mouth.
If I don't drink, I'll feel guilty about my brother.
Come on, show me your face.
It's okay.
It's because of the alcohol.
I just got swept away.
Sister, come here.
It's okay.
It's not your fault.
It's my fault.
Leave it to me.
It's okay.
It's not good.
What are you talking about?
It's my fault.
You have a beautiful face.
I love you, Kiyoko.
...
Don't come in.
Hi.
You?
Your face is beautiful.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
Open your legs.
I'm sorry.
Please lick my foot.
It's going well.
What are you doing?
You don't want to be with me?
I'm going home.
You want me to stay, don't you?
I'm going to sleep.
It's different from your brother's.
It's big.
My jaw is going to come off.
That's better.
I'm going to sleep.
You want me, don't you?
Let's not do that.
I can't do that.
You can't?
It's my fault.
It's not your fault.
But...
I'm going to sleep.
It's sucking.
You like to sleep.
I like it.
I can't.
I'm going to sleep.
It's sucking.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's sucking.
Does it feel good?
Do you like the desert?
I like it.
I'm going to sleep.
Do you want me to put you in my arms?
I want you to put me in your arms.
Please put me in your arms.
It's sucking.
Oh my goodness.
Did something happen?
Don't cry.
Mums.
Oh, dear.
Don't cry.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha manicure
What can I do for you?
It seems you are in pain.
Well, I'm going to bed.
What?
I don't want to see her naked.
I want to burn something beautiful in her eyes.
I betrayed my husband.
But it's my brother's fault.
I was just swept away.
I have something to tell you.
I got a call from Yuji in the evening.
I heard a lot.
I don't know what to say.
I'm sorry I always want to get in right away.
What?
No.
I told my brother because I was drunk.
I told him not to come in because Aya was in pain.
It seems to come from time to time even if it's a foreign visit.
A married couple who are in pain due to sexual intercourse.
I heard a lot from him.
How about tonight?
What?
It's been a while.
If you go against the flow, you can still pull it back.
What?
Can I be swept away?
I'm sorry.
Treatment room.
I can't.
What did you do with your brother?
Why don't you do it?
I told him I would do it, but he didn't do it.
Then it's okay to do it with me.
The bad thing is that my brother doesn't have sex.
But...
Leave it to the flow.
Can I be swept away?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm sorry sorry
Oh
Hmm
What?
You said you don't want it, but you're so hungry.
You want it, don't you?
You're hungry.
What?
You're hungry, aren't you?
Hey, bro.
Don't sleep.
It's almost night.
Hey.
Bro.
Don't sleep here.
Wake up.
I'm glad you're awake.
You were a little dizzy, weren't you?
What?
Let's talk here.
What are you talking about?
If you don't talk to me, I'll tell my brother everything.
No, you can't.
Hey, bro.
You know what?
You can't.
Then...
I'll tell him.
Okay.
I'm not a bad guy.
Don't worry.
Hmm.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm wet.
Hmm.
Hm.
I made a mistake.
Don't cry.
What's wrong?
You're crying too much.
Don't cry.
I made a mistake.
Talk to me.
It feels good.
I made a mistake.
Don't cry.
I'm sorry.
It's the best.
Don't cry.
I'm sorry.
It's the best.
I'll leave it to you.
Pregnant?
Yes.
He's the son of the third wife.
What is he doing?
He said he didn't want to have a baby.
I wonder if he's getting married.
I told him before I joined the medical school.
Be careful with women.
I wonder if he's caught by a bad woman.
I want him to be a great third wife.
I want him to raise our children.
Hey.
How about tonight?
What?
Make-up.
I'll do my best not to hurt you.
I'm sorry.
Pregnant?
Yes.
A day later.
He said too many things.
He's back now.
I don't know what to do with myself.
I don't know what to do.
I don't need a man.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting, sister.
I didn't wait for anything.
No, even I, the third wife, was deceived.
I wasn't pregnant.
If you were, you wouldn't come back here.
Giyose
Sister
I'll do something good for you today.
What is it?
If you can't see it, you'll be excited.
Yes, I understand.
Giyose
What is it?
Good girl.
Ouch!
Pinch me.
Did you feel pain?
Ouch!
Open your mouth.
Good girl.
Did you feel pain?
Open your mouth.
Good girl.
Did you feel pain?
Ouch!
Hey, talk to me.
I'm not sure if it's a good thing or a bad thing.
She's getting all warm in Senpai's arms.
It's a relationship that's...
That boy is a starting point.
You say that.
Say it quickly.
You like dried potatoes.
That sucks!
Great job!
You ate a lot!
Just look at this.
Here you are!
Here's your favorite.
I'm still want to sleep, but I can't help it.
I still want to sleep for a while, but I can't help it
Sir, you choked you and made it jelly.
Oh, no.
Look.
I'll put a lot of this in your throat.
Oh, no.
Hey, miss.
Don't go too far.
I'll put this in your throat.
Oh, no.
You're trying so hard.
You're happy to have two gums, aren't you?
I'll put this in your throat.
You're trying so hard.
You like small things, don't you?
I don't care if it's small.
Oh, no.
I'll put this in your throat.
You're excited, aren't you?
You've been eating a lot of good-smelling mangoes.
Because...
You want me to touch your mangoes, don't you?
I'll try small things.
Sit down.
Oh, no.
You want it, don't you?
Here we go.
You have such a big and strong body.
You're so skinny.
I can't do it.
It's okay.
Let me show you.
It's okay, isn't it?
You want to taste it, don't you?
Let me show you.
Here we go.
You're bleeding again, aren't you?
You like me, don't you?
I like you.
I can't do it.
What's wrong?
You're amazing.
You want it, don't you?
Here we go.
Taste it.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
You're so strong.
You're amazing.
Here we go.
How do you feel?
You have a lot of blood on your tongue.
Here we go.
You're amazing.
I love you.
I can't do it.
You're amazing.
You're so strong.
I can't do it.
You're amazing.
You're so strong.
It feels good.
You're amazing.
You're so strong.
Senpai.
You should have done it inside.
Was it good?
You're always drinking after pills.
You're my family.
I'm about to cry.
Do you want me to hold you?
Why do I have to be loved by such a terrible man?
Don't cry.
You're amazing.
I'll give you a shot.
You want more, don't you?
You're amazing.
That's right.
You were inside, weren't you?
You're amazing.
I'll give you a shot.
You're sweating, aren't you?
You're not hungry yet, are you?
You're amazing.
That's enough.
I was just swept away.