A few days later
Haya, I'm leaving
Take care
I know
Good luck
Thank you
There's a lot of fried chicken today
Yeah!
Here you are
Thank you
I'm leaving
My wife Aya is from the same hometown
We've been dating since we were students
She knows everything about me
She's my precious person
A few days later
I'm back
Good job
I didn't have much lunch
I'll give you lunch
No, thanks
This again
Ueno-san's bento always looks good
Does your wife make it?
Yeah
She's good at cooking
She's from the same hometown
I see
Don't you have a girlfriend who cooks for you?
I meet her often on the app
There was a girl who was good at cooking
She was so pretty
She cooked for me all day
It's time for you to graduate
What?
Isn't it amazing to get married to a local student?
It was a long-distance relationship when you were in college
Yeah
Haya came here after he got married
What?
According to my statistics
90% of long-distance couples cheat on their wives
Maybe your wife cheated on you
What?
No way
I don't know
It's not just Haya
She said she didn't like men
She's quiet
It's easy to get along with women like her
Then, I'll flirt with her
What?
Are you sure?
I can do it
I don't know what you're talking about
Let's eat
Ueno-san, your bento looks good
Really?
Thank you
It's so good
I'm so happy that I can cook
I'm so jealous of Ueno-san
It's so good
I'm so happy that I can cook
It looks so good
Wait a minute
It'll be ready soon
Haya
Yeah?
Can I bring my juniors over after work?
They said they want to eat your food
Sure
It's rare for you to bring your juniors over
Well, thank you
They're my cute juniors
I see
I'm looking forward to seeing you
It looks so good
Did you wash your hands?
You have to wash your hands
Okay
Be careful
I'm home
Excuse me
Taichi
I'm looking forward to seeing you
It's easy
Haya
Welcome back
I'm home
This is my junior, Shimada
Nice to meet you, I'm Taichi Shimada
I'm sorry for coming all of a sudden
It's okay
I'm Aya, the wife of Kazuto
My husband always takes care of me
Please come in
Okay
I'm looking forward to seeing you
I'm going to prepare the meal
Please take your time
Your wife is so beautiful
I know
Is she messing with you?
Isn't it too soft?
You drank too much
It's fun and delicious
We have to drink more
You should drink more
You
I know
It's not my drink
You're the type of person who drinks a lot
Of course
You can drink a lot today
Shut up
I'm going to drink by myself
Cheers
You're the best
You're good at cooking
You're really good at cooking
Did you work as a cook?
No, I didn't
I thought you were in a restaurant
You're exaggerating
I'm just praising you
You're good at cooking
Aya-san, what do you like about Ueha-san?
You
Ueha-san, don't you want to hear it?
I don't
I want to hear it
It's embarrassing
Ueha-san, please be nice to me
I won't be nice to you
Why?
You're scary
I'm kind
You're really good at cooking
Taichi is popular
Stop it
I'm not popular
I'm lonely
You're really good at cooking
I always want someone to comfort me
I want to be nice to a beautiful person like Aya-san
You're really nice
I'm spoiled
I want to be spoiled by an older woman
That's true
I'm surprised
You're not spoiled
That's true
Aya-san, what do you think about younger women?
I don't think they're cute
What are you talking about?
I'm not talking about myself
Don't get me wrong
That's weird
Are you older than me?
I'll follow you
Let's go
Hello
Yes
Now?
Okay, I'll be right there
What's wrong?
I have to check something today
I have to go to work
Now?
It won't take long
I'll be right back
Taichi
Be Aya's partner
Okay
Aya, I'm leaving
Take care
I'll be back in 3 hours
3 hours?
I'll see you off
Okay
As promised
I'll see you off in 3 hours
Uehara-san
You can spend your time at a bar
I can't
I'll spend my time
See you
I'm looking forward to it
Sigh
I'm home
Uehara-san, you left
I'm working hard
Uehara-san, you have a lot of work
Do you hear about the company?
He doesn't tell me much
I don't think he does
But he really likes you
I like you a lot
I'm serious
You'll be promoted
Wow
Aya-san, you'll have a good life
What?
Do you wanna drink?
Let's drink
Cheers
I'll drink
Sigh
It's gone
It's good
Cheers
Thank you
I feel like I'm the host
Me?
Don't worry about it
You're kind
Thank you
Sigh
Shimada-san, you drink a lot
No, I don't
Aya-san, you drink a lot
I had a lot of fun
You drink a lot when you have fun
Let's drink more
Cheers
Aya-san, seriously
You're so stylish
I'm sorry
Thank you
I'm happy
You're amazing
Uehara-san, you're a proud wife
No, I'm not
I want to walk with a beautiful woman like you
Me too
But, Okabu-kun doesn't say that
I can't say that
Is that so?
I'll say it
You're so beautiful
I've been thinking about it
Really?
I'm honestly happy
You're beautiful
You're stylish
It's effective
She's angry
She's definitely angry
It's because you have someone to support you
You?
I can see it from here
Can you see it?
I can see it
Let's do this
It feels good
You're good at it
Really?
I'll drink more
You're good
Really?
It feels good
Aya-san, it smells good
It smells good
It smells like Aya-san
It smells like me?
I wonder what it smells like
It smells good
Really?
It feels good
Can you ask me about my selfishness?
Selfishness?
Can I be spoiled?
Are you spoiled?
I'm spoiled
You're cute
Can I have a lap pillow?
A lap pillow?
I like it
You can have it here
If you want
Can I?
Like this
Can I sit down?
It's relaxing
It's really relaxing
You're really spoiled
Ueha-san, don't you do this?
I don't do this to my family
Like this
It feels good
Do you like to touch each other?
Touch each other?
I wonder
Sometimes I miss someone
I understand
I miss you too
Really?
Yes
It feels good
You're cute
Can I hug you?
Hug?
I want to hug you from behind
You can hug me from behind
Not from the front?
It feels good
Yes
I feel excited
Why do you feel excited?
Because it's new
Don't you do this?
No, I don't
I don't do this to my family
You're too drunk
Really?
When I get drunk, I kiss you
Do you like to kiss?
I wonder
Do you have weak ears?
Taichi
Don't do this
What do you mean?
You're shy
You're so cute
I'm shy
Don't you like to kiss on the cheek?
Or
Do you like a normal kiss?
No
I'm married
But you said
When I saw you
I thought you were beautiful
I'm happy
I want to see your face
Your face is so cute
Your lips are so soft
Really?
Can I try?
No
You can't
Just a little
Your lips are so soft
I want to see more
Do you like to kiss?
You like it, right?
I like it
Do you like my kiss?
You're good
Where is your genitalia?
It's a secret
Can I find it?
I'll find it
I'm sorry
You're not only big
You're also sensitive
I'm shy
Can I touch you more?
I'm sorry
You're so sensitive
I'm shy
I can't
What can't you do?
I can't do anything
What if I do more than that?
Are you going to do it with your nipples?
You're too sexy
What's wrong?
I'm shy
I want to see you being shy
You're so beautiful
You're still sensitive
I can't
You're so cute
Do you want me to pet you more?
Take it off
Where do you want me to pet you?
You're so wet
I want you to pet me here
Wait
Should I wait?
You want me to pet you more, right?
What's wrong?
I want you to pet me more
You're so cute
Please pet me
You're so stubborn
Is it good?
I like it
You can taste it
You're so mean
You can pet me more
You're mouth is so wet
You're so mean
You can't let go
You're so stubborn
It's your fault
It's my fault
Wait a minute
Please
H Ball
He is trying to eat up
He already finished
You see
She's purring so much that it feels good.
You're going to go there again, aren't you?
I'm scared.
Didn't you do it with Ueha-san?
No, I didn't.
Then, can you just scream?
Is that so?
Do you like me?
You're going to hit me, aren't you?
No, I can't.
That feels good.
That feels good, doesn't it?
No, I can't.
No, no, no, no.
No? You're going to go, so no?
No, no, no.
No, I can't.
Aya-san, you can't pull it out.
You have to be a good girl and keep putting it in.
Do you understand?
I understand.
I'm scared.
You're going to go, aren't you?
I'm going to go.
I'm going to go, too.
Oh, my God.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'm going to go.
I'm still going, so don't pull it out.
Aya-san, you're a good girl, aren't you?
I'm going to go.
You have to move.
Don't rest, Aya-san.
I'm still going, so don't pull it out.
I'm going.
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
Did you eat it?
Do you know you're throbbing inside?
Yes.
You like nakadashi, don't you?
I don't like it.
You really like it.
You want more, don't you?
I'm going.
I'm going to push you up from below.
Don't do that.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm going.
I'm going, too.
Don't sleep.
Look over there.
Don't move.
You're so energetic.
I'm sleepy.
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
Look over there.
Don't do that.
I'm going.
I'm going, too.
Don't do that.
Oh, my God.
Your face is melting.
It's not over yet.
That's amazing.
I'm going.
Don't sleep.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing.
I did it five times.
Can you do it five times without sleeping?
That's amazing.
Did you like it?
Oh, my God.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
How was your work?
There was no problem.
I'm going to go now.
I can't stay too long.
Please come again.
You must be tired.
I'll prepare a bath.
How was it?
I did my best.
But it didn't work.
I told you.
I'm sorry.
But it was good.
The food was delicious.
You look beautiful today.
You look like a model.
I know.
I envy you.
I'm sorry.
I was talking to Taichi while I was away.
It's normal.
It's about work and cooking.
You said you wanted me to teach you the cook.
So I asked you to come next time.
It was nice to talk about it.
Good night.
What?
I'm so sad because you're out.
You're not going to do it?
You're here for dinner, right?
I wanted to make sure the love between husband and wife, so I got on the back seat of my junior.
It was just that, but I didn't expect it to be like this behind my back.
What?
It hurts.
I'll do it, too.
You're beautiful today, too.
I'm happy.
Touch me.
What?
Where do you want me to touch?
Here.
You don't have to touch here.
You're mean.
What?
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
What?
You have a very erotic face.
That's not true.
What?
I want to see your erotic face more.
That's not true.
What?
I'm sorry.
You have a very erotic face.
You're not the only one who has an erotic face.
That's not true.
What?
Why are you sleeping like this?
Because it feels good.
Is it because it feels good?
I'm sorry.
What?
You have a very erotic face.
Because it feels good.
I'm sorry.
You have a very erotic face.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
You have a very erotic face.
I want you to kiss me.
I love you.
I want you to feel good about this.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I want you to lick me.
I want you to lick me, too.
Can I lick you?
Yes.
I want you to lick me.
You are very good at licking.
Your penis is very big.
It's totally different from my family's penis.
Your mouth feels good, too.
I'm glad.
I want you to lick me forever.
I'll lick you a lot.
We only have three hours today.
If you don't come back, I'll be angry.
We have three hours.
Do you want me to lick you until the last minute?
Until the last minute.
Your penis is very big.
Can I lie on your side?
Your bed style is very good.
I feel good.
Are you okay?
I love you.
I love you, too.
You are very good at licking.
I want you to lick me, too.
Can I lick you?
I want you to lick me.
Don't run away.
I want you to lick me again.
I love you.
I want you to lick me.
I feel good.
I can't stand it anymore.
I want you to lick me.
I feel good.
I can't stand it anymore.
I want you to lick me more.
I want you to lick me.
I love you.
Leave me alone.
Do you love me?
I feel good.
Let's go together.
Don't pull it out yet.
Don't you want to pull it out?
No.
You have to pull it out.
Don't pull it out.
Do you want more?
I'm going to cry.
I can't do it anymore.
That's great.
I'm holding you tight.
Do you want to go somewhere?
I can't do it anymore.
I can't do this anymore.
You can't do this anymore, can you?
That's too much.
I can't do it anymore.
I'll put it in front of you.
I'm sorry.
It's too hard.
It's too big.
I can't do it anymore.
Can I do it?
I'll do it, too.
Let's do it together.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels good.
I'm sweating a lot.
I can't do it anymore.
Look at me.
Can I hold your hand?
I can't do it anymore.
That's amazing.
It feels good.
It's cold, isn't it?
I'm sweating a lot.
I can't do it anymore.
That's amazing.
I'm sweating a lot.
It feels good.
That's amazing.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm going to start.
I'm sweating.
Ah!
Ahhhh!
AHHHHHHH!!
tears
AHHHHHHHHHH!!!
AHHHHHHHH!!)
One more
Where?
Somebody, please help me.
D bow to the Buddha
This video is commercially available in Japanese.
Are you sleeping?
Oh!
How many times did you pee?
About five times?
Five times?
Yes.
I peed about five times.
Oh!
I'm going to be addicted.
Me too.
Oh!
Taichi can't work at all.
But he's always cute.
Really?
Yes.
He's always smiling even when he makes a mistake.
He's so cute.
I can't hate him.
He looks at me a lot.
He's cute even when he makes a mistake.
He's so cute.
Yes.
I can feel it.
I'm a little annoyed.
But he's cute.
I see.
Thank you.
Taichi said he wanted to come again.
Can I call him?
Yes.
Of course.
Anytime.
Thank you.
He should find a girlfriend soon.
I think so.
He's always in a daze.
Really?
I'm a little worried about him.
Don't worry.
I'm worried about him.
It's good.
It's really good.
Aya's cooking is really good.
I see.
Everything is good.
You eat too much.
It's true.
You should find a girlfriend soon.
What?
If I eat Aya's cooking, it's too expensive.
What should I do?
Don't worry.
It's good for your marriage.
I don't think so.
I think so.
It's good.
It's really good.
Thank you.
It's good.
What do you usually eat?
I only eat convenience store bento.
If I eat Aya's cooking, I'll cry.
You talk too much.
What kind of woman is Taichi's type?
Type?
I see.
I like a woman with a small body.
But I don't like a woman with a small body because her style is not good.
I see.
I like a woman who can do housework.
Are you talking about Aya?
You look like an ideal woman.
I'm good at cooking.
But I can't break up with Aya.
Of course.
It was delicious.
I'm full and happy.
I can eat as much as I want.
You don't have to eat again.
I'm looking forward to it every day.
That's a miracle.
That's how delicious it is.
Aya's cooking is really delicious.
Thank you.
I'm happy.
Ueha-san.
It's not good to eat only lunch.
I have a bento every day.
There is a delicious ramen near here.
This is more delicious.
That may be so.
It's not good to eat ramen every day.
I'm fat because I eat ramen.
I'm healthy.
Ueha-san has a healthy body.
Because she eats a lot.
You are slacking off again.
I'll help you wash the dishes.
Are you okay?
I had a delicious meal.
I have to work.
It's okay.
I'll help you wash the dishes.
Thank you.
Can I do it here?
You can only do that.
You are a good man.
You said it yourself.
I'll wash the dishes.
Taichi, do you do housework at home?
I have to do it at least.
If I don't do it, I'll lose my shirt.
If you don't do it, your shirt will smell.
I want to keep my shirt clean.
Taichi is popular.
He is washing the dishes.
Have you met a good woman recently?
Recently, I have.
I have a favorite woman.
You haven't heard of her?
I haven't heard of her.
I can't play with her all the time.
Is that so?
I don't think so.
Taichi is playing with me all the time.
It's fun to play with you.
You are a good man.
Is it easier to work if you have a good woman?
I think so.
I'm having fun now.
You are young.
You don't have to worry about it.
You will have a good wife someday.
Yes.
He is washing the dishes.
Taichi only talks about ramen and women.
I don't care about ramen and women.
I'm looking forward to a single man.
You are too single.
You have to work hard.
You are doing your best.
I'm not done yet.
You will have juniors.
You have to teach them.
It's okay.
I'm good at teaching.
Don't talk nonsense.
You have to be responsible.
It's okay.
I have a lot of responsibility.
You only talk.
You are good at that.
I'm counting on you.
Leave it to me.
Aya.
I ran out of alcohol.
It's the last day of drinking.
I see.
I'm going to the convenience store.
You should go shopping.
I will go shopping.
Take your time.
Be careful.
I will go shopping.
Don't do that.
You will be exposed.
You are patient.
You are excited.
I'm embarrassed.
You are excited because you are embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
I was nervous.
Please talk to me.
I'm sorry.
I have to hurry up.
You will be back.
I'm sorry.
I will be back.
Please hurry up.
Please drink a lot of alcohol.
Please use your hands.
I'm sorry.
You are too gentle.
You are amazing.
I'm sorry.
You are begging me.
You are begging me, aren't you?
You are mean.
Uggh...
Oh, so good...
Oh my...
I think I'm gonna die.
Ughhhhhhh
How long are you going to be like this, Aya-san?
What's wrong?
You have to tell me the truth.
You can't do that.
I'm going to come back.
You have to be patient today.
Let's do it again next time.
Can you bear it?
I can't.
You're so cute.
I'm going to come back.
I didn't notice their relationship at all.
He's on a business trip again.
That's how much the company expects you.
Have you been playing lately?
It's not bad.
Stop playing and focus on your work.
You can't do it.
I see.
I wish I had someone like Aya-san.
Aya will be happy.
Aya-san is good at cooking.
I can't leave her if she catches my stomach.
That's right.
You can come to eat when you're on a business trip.
Aya likes it, too.
Really?
If Aya can't do it,
This is the bond of love.
Aya-san and Senpai are great.
When I saw you together the other day,
I thought you didn't like us.
That's right.
Our bond of love is iron.
I can't break it.
You're very strong.
I'm glad I came here.
I can't do it.
You're beautiful and good at cooking.
It's an ideal dream.
That's right.
I'm leaving.
Did you forget anything?
No, I'm fine.
I'll call you when I get there.
I'm waiting for you.
I'm sorry for today.
I really want to eat Aya's cooking.
I'll do my best to prepare the meal.
It's hard for you to live alone.
Thank you.
Take care.
I'm leaving.
What are they talking about?
Recording.
It's amazing.
It's big.
The camera is beautiful.
Thank you for the meal.
Reia is on a business trip.
Let's talk a lot.
I agree.
I can't do it until the end.
I'm angry.
I want to have a good time today.
Please show me your face.
You're a coward.
How many men have you been talking to?
You can tell me now.
I knew it.
A-kun!!
You're one to talk, Takahashi.
Huh?
I can't believe it's been a year since I last saw you.
I'm so happy to see you.
It's so good.
I can't help but kiss you.
I want you so much.
It's so good.
Can I lick you?
You want to lick me, right?
I want to lick you.
It's so good.
It's a mess.
You want me to touch you more, right?
It's so good.
Put more in my fingers.
Do you want me to put it all the way in?
There are three fingers in it.
It's so good.
How many times have you been licked?
I can't do it anymore.
I want to sleep.
I'll drink the next one.
Put your butt out.
You're pulling a string.
Which one is it?
Put your butt out.
I can't do it anymore.
Is it gone?
That's amazing.
The butt is spread out.
What are you going to do?
It's hot.
It's funny.
You're already funny.
You're funny.
It's hot.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm going to break.
You're going to break, aren't you?
I really can't.
Oh, it's broken.
I want to break it.
Do you want to break it?
Oh, it's hard.
Oh, it's amazing.
Look at me more.
Look at my body more.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's hard.
Oh, it's overflowing.
Do you want more?
I love you.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's hard.
Oh, it's overflung.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it's hard.
Oh, our oh.
oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
I'm so chilly!
Oh, no!
It's not coming off!
It's not coming!
I can't stop gasping
You cry too loud.
oh,my bad
culpable
My old man!
My dear old man!
Help me!
I can't move!
I can't laugh anymore.
Help me!
I can't make it.
I want to kiss you
while your mama is not here.
Maybe Ichigo saw it?
How often do you shoot?
What are you doing?
What?
Taichi?
Hey
Call me right now
What are you doing?
Ouch
To be continued