We've known each other for more than 20 years but this person isn't close enough to help us be happy.
When I face my gonds Yukinoshita Bridge, I look back on the past.
Good morning!
It's amazing that you start working at this time.
Do you want to eat later?
Well...
What? What's wrong?
Aya is fine, isn't she?
She's fine.
Don't worry about work at the age of 34.
We often stay at each other's house remotely.
I want you to be careful.
Well...
Your part-time job history is...
Oh, it's been a long time since you were in high school.
I'm sorry.
I got married right after I graduated from college.
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
It's a simple job, so it doesn't matter much.
I understand.
I'll hire you.
Really?
Thank you very much.
It's only been a week, but thank you.
You're welcome.
This is the locker room and the break room.
Okay.
There's no women's locker room, so men and women can share it.
Please change your clothes when you change.
I understand.
How many times do you make the same mistake?
I'm sorry.
You're over 30 years old and you're doing such a job.
Takeda-kun.
Please take care of Uehane-san.
Okay.
Sasaki-kun.
I'm Uehane.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Takeda.
Well...
Yes?
Are you going to do it in that outfit?
Yes.
What?
It must be hot.
I think so.
Takeda-san.
I'm sorry.
Can you close the zipper for me?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Okay.
It's amazing that you can do it by yourself.
I'm used to it.
I can do it by myself.
Thank you.
It's hot.
I told you.
I'll put you down.
Thank you.
It's hot.
Are you going to eat with that?
Well...
It's hot.
Thank you for your hard work.
The zipper is...
Let's do it.
I'm sorry.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I took it off.
Thank you.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't bear to see your body.
It's okay.
Calm down.
I'm sorry.
I've been looking at you for a long time.
It's painful.
I wanted to touch you.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
What should I do if someone comes?
It's okay.
I'm not okay.
What should I do if someone comes?
It's wonderful.
It's painful.
I'm sorry.
I have to do more.
It's wonderful.
It's beautiful.
You're sweating.
It's wonderful.
I'm sweating.
That's not true.
You're not sweating.
You smell good.
That's not true.
I'm excited.
It's okay.
I couldn't bear to see your body.
That's not true.
It's hot.
You're sweating.
It's wonderful.
It's not good.
It's hot.
I'm embarrassed.
Why are you embarrassed?
It's beautiful.
It's wonderful.
Don't look at me.
Please look at me.
It's not good.
I couldn't bear to see your body.
It's hot.
Wait.
I'm a married woman.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't bear to see your body.
Please stand up.
Don't look at me.
You're sweating a lot.
I couldn't bear to see your body.
It's wonderful.
It's hot.
Calm down.
It's delicious.
I couldn't bear to see your body.
Look at your butt.
Do you usually wear this?
No.
You're sweating a lot.
I couldn't bear to see your body.
You're not satisfied with your body.
You don't usually wear this.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't bear to see your body.
You're thin.
Your husband is funny.
No.
I couldn't bear to see your body.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't wear a T-shirt.
No.
You're wearing a T-shirt that you like.
Do you usually wear a T-shirt?
No.
Don't be embarrassed.
You're sweating a lot.
You shouldn't wear a T-shirt.
I didn't wear a T-shirt.
You look good in a T-shirt.
No.
You're sweating a lot.
What's wrong with you?
You started to speak in a low voice.
You're sweating a lot.
I'll give you a massage.
Don't be embarrassed.
No.
Wait.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm really embarrassed.
No.
What?
Is it here?
No.
Wait.
You're sweating a lot.
Don't hide it.
I'm cold.
No.
You're sweating a lot.
You started to speak in a low voice.
It's been a long time, hasn't it?
You're sweating a lot.
Don't say that.
You're not sweating at all.
You're sweating a lot.
You're so cute.
Please lick me.
It's been a long time, hasn't it?
You're sweating a lot.
Please lick me.
You're licking me.
Don't do that.
You're sweating a lot.
It feels good.
It's been a long time, hasn't it?
You're sweating a lot.
It feels good.
It's been a long time, hasn't it?
Why is it so hard?
Look at this.
I'm sorry.
Don't you want to lick me?
Open your mouth.
You like this, don't you?
I'll give you more.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
I can't help it.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels really good.
I can't help it.
Does it feel good?
Look at this.
Wait a minute.
I can't help it.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll give you more.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
I can't help it.
I'm sweating so much.
I'll lick you.
I can't help it.
It's hot.
It's painful.
It's painful, isn't it?
It's hot.
It feels good.
Your lower back is moving.
It's hot.
My back hurts.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
Good morning.
The rabbit is cute.
It's so cute.
It's amazing.
Mr. Rabbit.
It's so cute.
It's cute.
See you.
Let's go.
I can't relax at all.
Well.
Takeda-san, I made some bento for you, would you like to have some?
Oh, thank you very much!
Is it okay if I have some?
I don't know if you like it or not.
Oh, okay.
Wow, that's amazing.
It looks so good.
Thank you very much.
Wow, that's amazing.
It looks so good.
Would you like to have some?
Is it okay if I have some?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Enjoy your meal.
It looks so good.
Thank you very much.
It's so good.
Takeda-san, you seem to enjoy your meal.
Oh, do I?
When I see such a delicious bento, I become like this.
It's so good.
I was walking with a woman you don't know.
Oh, really?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
I'll have some, too.
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
I'll have some, too.
It's so good.
I'm sorry.
I'll prepare your meal.
It's okay.
I ate outside.
Don't sleep on the sofa in that clothes.
What?
You sweat a lot.
Go to the bathroom.
Wait.
Do you love me?
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
Takeda-san, don't do that.
Why?
Don't do that.
Don't kiss me.
I'll be serious.
Be serious to me.
Don't do that.
Please.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize to me.
I'm smelly and dirty, aren't I?
No, you're not.
Takeda-kun, stand up.
What?
I can't have sex with you.
But I'm happy that you're excited about me.
Can I touch you?
What?
Okay.
Thank you.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's hard, isn't it?
That's great.
Can I touch you?
Yes.
That's great.
Here.
Thank you.
That's great.
Takeda-san.
Can I lick you?
What?
No, you can't.
That's great.
Here.
Can I touch you?
That's great.
Here.
You feel so good.
It feels good.
It's hard all the time, isn't it?
Yes, it feels good.
That's great.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
That's great.
You've had a lot.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't help it.
Did you feel good?
Yes, I did.
That's great.
I can't help it.
You can't help it, can you?
Why does your body hurt so much?
I can't help it.
You're sweating so much.
You really can't help it?
I can't help it.
You have a great body.
Look at this.
Do you see this?
My body is like this.
Look at my body.
I can't help it.
Don't kiss me.
I'm standing here.
You want to see me, don't you?
I can't help it.
I've grown so big.
It's your fault.
I can't help it.
Does it feel good here?
You're the best.
My body is like this.
I can't help it.
Look at this.
My body is like this.
You're the best.
You've grown up.
I can't help it.
Does it feel good here?
Does it feel good?
You're the best.
Do you see this?
My body is like this.
Sit down.
I'll give you a bath.
You're very nervous.
You're very sensitive.
Wait a minute.
You'll feel better in the morning.
I'll give you a massage.
I'll give you a massage in the morning.
You like to eat.
You've grown up.
I'll give you a massage in the morning.
I can't help it.
You've grown up.
I'll give you a massage in the morning.
Does it feel good?
You're good at it.
It feels good.
Please continue.
I'll give you a massage in the morning.
I can't help it.
I'm home.
We'll go up first.
Please lock the back door.
Thank you for your hard work.
What's wrong?
Good morning.
Give me a kiss.
That's great.
Don't I sweat?
You smell good.
Really?
That's great.
Can I look at you?
You're beautiful.
Are you weak?
That's great.
Are you here?
Are you feeling hot?
Here, too.
Are you that excited?
I'm so happy.
Ah,
You're here somewhere?
You're startled...
You're cute when you move.
I can't.
What's wrong with you?
Did you fall asleep?
That's great.
Are you all right?
Look at me.
Come here.
Sit here.
That's great.
Come here.
Stop it.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
I'm glad you're so wet.
That's great.
Are you ashamed of me?
I'm ashamed.
Please don't be ashamed of me.
I'm ashamed of you.
Why?
You have such a beautiful body.
No.
You're beautiful.
I'm sweating.
I can't see anything.
It's so heavy.
It's sensitive here.
I can't move.
It's so wet here.
My fingers are so wet.
I want you to wipe it off.
It's so wet here.
I can't see anything.
I couldn't have sex with you.
But you're so wet.
I'm so happy.
It's so wet here.
I want you to get wet.
That's...
What is it?
I'm going to get wet.
Did you get wet?
Please get wet.
It's so wet here.
You're so cute.
I'll give you more.
Look at me.
I'm so pretty.
You're sweating here.
I'm sweating a lot, so I can't do it.
I'll lower it.
I'm sweating.
Did you get wet?
Does it feel good?
Let's go to bed.
I'm sorry.
It's cold.
It feels good.
It smells bad.
It doesn't smell bad.
It's cold.
It feels good.
You're good.
It's the best.
It feels good.
You're good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's the best.
I can't stand it anymore.
It hurts in the morning, doesn't it?
It hurts in the morning.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's the best.
It feels good in the morning.
It feels good.
It's the best.
It's amazing.
It's here.
It's the best.
It's so hot!
It feels so good.
It's the best.
It's so good.
It's so hot.
I can't stop it.
Don't do that.
Hold me tight.
I can't help it.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
Are you okay?
It's hot.
I want to warm you up.
Are you okay?
It's hot.
Hold me tight.
I can't help it.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
I can't help it.
Help me.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
Are you going home today?
Yes.
I see.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Thank you.
I know it's hard for you.
I'm rooting for you.
Bye.
Takeda-san, is it good?
Yes, your food is really good.
It's good.
I'm glad.
Takeda-san.
Aya-san.
I'm sorry.
Takeda-san.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
Takeda-san.
Does it feel good?
I'm glad.
I'm sorry.