I'm sorry.
Why?
Why did this happen?
I'm Okaho Tadashiro. Nice to meet you.
You look well.
Yes, I'm fine.
I have a question.
Why are you looking for a job when you're already married?
Actually, I met my husband at a restaurant the other day.
I applied for this job because I wanted to support my family as much as possible.
I see. I understand.
I'll hire you for the time being.
Thank you very much.
When can you start working?
Anytime is fine.
Then, please come here at 10 a.m. tomorrow.
Thank you.
You had an interview today, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
I don't think I can do it today.
I see.
You know, I went to the part-time job interview today.
I'm sorry for what I did to you.
Don't worry about it.
I have to pay off the loan of this house.
I'm sorry for what I did to you.
Thank you for waiting.
Here's your coffee.
Thank you.
Ms. Tanashiro.
Yes?
How's your work?
Is there anything you don't know?
No.
I'm fine now.
Really?
Yes.
Then, keep up the good work.
See you later.
I have no choice.
I have to put up with it.
Thank you.
How was the part-time job interview today?
How was it?
The manager and other part-timers were all kind.
I see.
I have to do my best, too.
Don't worry.
You don't have to rush.
Thank you.
Ms. Tanashiro.
Hello.
Yes.
I'm changing now.
I'm fine.
I'm going shopping.
Okay.
See you later.
Ms. Tanashiro.
Yes?
Can you stay here tonight?
Okay.
First, I'll show you how to clean this coffee machine.
There's a lot of water stains here.
Yes.
If you don't clean it every day, it'll be hard to clean.
Can you wipe it for me?
Okay.
Put more effort into it.
If you don't wipe it well, it won't come off.
Okay.
Yes.
Put your weight on it.
Put more effort into it.
Like this.
What's wrong?
Concentrate on it.
Okay.
If you don't concentrate on it, it won't come off.
Yes.
It's good.
It's clean now.
Yes.
Do it like this.
There's a lot of dust and water stains here.
Yes.
You have to clean it.
Okay.
Put more effort into it.
If you don't clean it well, it won't come off.
I'll support you.
Okay.
Concentrate on it.
Yes.
It's clean now.
From now on, you have to do it by yourself.
Okay.
Can I go home now?
Yes.
Excuse me.
That's enough.
Ms. Tamashiro.
It must be hard for you to work in a restaurant.
You have to put up with it.
No.
Don't do that.
Kaho.
Why are you here?
I had an interview today.
I see.
How's work?
It's fine.
Let's go home.
Okay.
Iced cafe latte, L.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Please have a seat.
Ms. Tamashiro.
Take a break.
Okay.
Excuse me.
I'm tired.
Hello.
Can I talk to you?
Yes.
To be honest,
you don't have a lot of work, do you?
What do you mean?
You have a lot of customers,
but you don't have a lot of tools.
What do you mean?
For example,
like this.
Don't do that.
You'll remember soon.
That's what you're bad at.
This is sexual harassment.
It's not good to make a fuss.
What?
And
your husband is unemployed,
and he wants to make money.
You have to listen to the manager.
Please don't.
What?
I can fire you anytime.
You'll be in trouble if you get fired.
Your husband must be sad.
You'll be fired soon.
You don't want your husband to be sad, do you?
What do you think?
I'm not sad.
That's right.
Then listen to me.
That's enough.
What?
Are you sure you don't want to be fired?
I don't mind.
But...
You'll be in trouble.
Yes.
Your husband must be sad.
You'll be in trouble if you get fired.
Yes.
You don't hate this, do you?
What?
Look.
It's getting hot.
Please don't.
It's hot.
Your husband won't be satisfied with your body.
What do you think?
Look.
You look so sad.
Show me your face.
Why are you crying?
What?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
You don't want to be fired, do you?
You look so sad.
What's wrong?
You don't want to be fired, do you?
It's hot.
It's a back injury, isn't it?
Look.
Let me touch you.
You're sweating a lot.
Does it feel good?
You don't want to be fired, do you?
It's a back injury, isn't it?
Show me your face.
You look so sad.
You're sweating a lot.
You don't want to be fired, do you?
Please stop it...
Does it feel good?
You should be honest.
It feels good...
Please stop it...
Are you okay?
I'm sorry...
Please stop it...
What is this?
I'm sorry...
Please stop it...
It's not a big deal, isn't it?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's not a big deal, is it?
I hate it, I hate it
Please stop it
I hate it
The agency has been wet
I want you to feel better.
Look at me.
Do you know what to do?
You like it, don't you?
Look at me.
It smells bad.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to make you wait.
What's wrong?
I'll give you more.
That's right.
It feels good.
You're drooling.
Your husband won't do this to you.
I'm sorry.
I want to put it in your mouth.
Can I put it in your mouth?
I'll put it in your mouth.
That's right.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
What's wrong?
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It felt so good.
It's okay.
It's okay, isn't it?
Look at me.
I can't do it.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
It was terrible, Taro.
It's terrible.
I'm sorry.
I took a good picture.
I took a bath first.
I see.
I'll take a bath, too.
Thank you.
Please wait in your seat.
Tamashiro.
Yes?
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Yes.
You look a little gloomy.
You should smile more.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Anyway,
why don't you take off your panties?
What?
If you can't take it off by yourself, I'll do it for you.
Wait a minute.
Please don't.
You'll be fine.
What?
Wait a minute.
There are customers.
You can't see them, so you'll be fine.
Please don't.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Americano.
Americano?
Hot.
Hot?
Yes.
Thank you.
And...
Yes?
Sandwich.
Sandwich?
Yes.
Thank you.
That's all.
Okay.
How much is it?
It's 1,100 yen.
1,100 yen?
Yes.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Okay.
Please wait a moment.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'll take care of this.
What?
Be nice.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Can you make a napolitan?
Yes, I can.
How long will it take?
Well...
About 5 to 6 minutes.
I see.
Yes.
I'll take that.
Okay.
I'll use my smartphone.
It'll be 680 yen.
Here you are.
Okay.
Thank you.
Please don't do that.
Concentrate.
You're doing good.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Wait a moment.
Okay.
I have something to tell you today.
What?
But my husband is waiting for me.
Can't I tell him tomorrow?
You can tell him tomorrow.
But...
I'll send this to your husband.
What?
He's not here.
And...
He left without paying.
Hello?
Well...
I was suddenly asked to work.
I'll be late today.
I'm sorry.
See you.
What's wrong?
Don't put your tongue out.
I can't.
Can't you do it yourself?
I'll do it for you.
I'm sorry.
I'm doing it for you.
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
Let's have fun.
I can't.
Let's make up.
My husband...
What are you talking about?
Why are you here?
That's what you were going to do, right?
I'm sorry.
You're not wearing underwear, are you?
You're not, are you?
I'm sorry.
Who are you wearing this underwear for?
Tell me.
My husband.
Don't lie to me.
I'm sorry.
That's nice.
I like this kind of underwear.
I'm sorry.
You have a lot of wrinkles.
You can feel it.
I'm sorry.
This way.
You're beautiful.
I'm sorry.
I'll kiss you here, too.
I'll put it on your tongue.
I'm sorry.
You've got a lot on your tongue.
How does your tongue taste?
Is it good?
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
I'll kiss you.
Why?
I'm sorry.
It's stressful, isn't it?
It's so stressful.
It's so stressful, isn't it?
Don't cry.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
It's okay, it's okay.
Don't cry.
It's okay.
Please calm down.
Please lick my feet.
It feels good.
Don't cry.
Please lick my feet.
It's okay.
Don't cry.
It's cold.
This is the last one.
Please lick my feet.
It's okay.
It's just a pain.
Don't cry.
It's okay.
I don't want you to cry.
Don't cry.
It's just a pain.
Let me hug you.
Do you feel good?
Don't cry.
Let me hug you.
Do you feel good?
Don't cry.
This is not the end.
Hello?
Don't cry.
Welcome home.
I'm sorry I woke you up.
What happened yesterday?
I was at a drinking party.
My co-worker fell down.
I was free.
I see.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
Did you have fun?
Yes.
I'm sorry I woke you up.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
You're finally honest.
Do you like me?
I'm sorry.
Are you excited?
Yes.
Do you feel good?
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
The staffs came to visit us!
Mother who has just returned from work
Mom who is being pampered
What's wrong?
Do you feel sick?
I feel sick.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I understand
I will understand
Last more
I'll show you.
Excuse me.
I'll arrest you.
Hurry up.
Yes.
Are you sure?
Wait a minute.
Kaho.
Honey.
I had an interview today.
I see.
Is he the manager?
Yes.
I'm Odagiri, the manager.
I'm always grateful to you.
Thank you for hiring me.
See you.
Kaho, do you remember what day it is next week?
Of course.
It's a wedding anniversary.
Yes.
I'm unemployed now, so I can't celebrate it.
Let's spend the anniversary together.
Okay.
I won't shift on that day.
Thank you.
Okay.
Hello.
Are you okay?
I can't today.
Why?
I have an appointment with my husband.
I need you.
But...
You need me, too.
I'm sorry.
You wanted to kiss me, didn't you?
You're lying.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'll make you feel better.
Do you want to cry?
Yes.
I'll make you feel better.
Come on.
You're getting better.
Can you hear me?
I'm embarrassed.
Do you want to sleep?
I don't want to.
Why?
Please continue.
I don't want to.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
I feel good.
I can't.
I'm going to sleep.
That's good.
You want to feel good, don't you?
Don't you?
I feel good.
I'm going to sleep.
I can't.
I don't want to.
Your panties are wet.
You can't wear panties anymore.
I can't.
What do you want me to do?
Please continue.
Please make me feel better.
Where?
Do you want me to make you feel better?
Yes.
I can't.
Open your butt.
I can't breathe.
It hurts.
I can't.
I can see you.
I can't breathe.
Do you want me to do it?
I can't.
It feels good.
Please breathe a lot.
It's crazy.
Don't use your hands.
I'm sweating.
What do you want to do?
I want to lick you.
What do you want to lick?
Do you want to lick me?
Please open your mouth.
It feels good.
Look at me.
Is it delicious?
It's delicious.
I'll let you speak more.
Do you want to speak more?
I want to speak more.
It's crazy.
Do you want to speak more?
I want to speak more.
Is it delicious?
It's delicious.
Do you want to speak more?
I want to speak more.
Look at me.
It feels good.
I'm going.
I'll kick your ass.
Do you want me to kick you from behind?
Please kick me.
Please move slowly.
It feels good.
It's hard.
Please follow me.
It feels good.
There you go.
Do you want more?
Please give me more.
There you go.
It feels so good.
It hurts.
Please stop here.
It's okay.
It's okay?
To feel good, right?
It feels good...
See, you swooned on your own.
C  hlee.
Such a great feeling...
Ouch...
There might be people who love me And there might be people who don't even want me
It's a farce
What was that just now?!
What was that?!
I've never been touched like that
I'm scared.
Koko had beenOREGAI for over two hours.
Koko, are you charging Kuro too much?
After exercising, she has a hug error in her back.
It's hard to play with Koko when she's crying.
I'm coming!
What's wrong?
No, no, no!
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
Do you want more?
I want more.
Yes, I do.
Come here.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
Let's clean up.
Look down.
Clean up.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I want more.
Do you want more?
You're going to be four times bigger.
I want more.
Please.
Please give me more.
More?
Where?
Please put the stuff in my bag.
Where is it?
I feel sick.
Please put the stuff in my bag.
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
Please put the stuff in my bag.
Where?
I feel sick.
Please be careful.
Please put the stuff in my bag.
I feel sick.
Please be careful.
Whoosh!
Ouch!
That's so cold.
His back is shaking.
He is very frightened
he is doing his best.
She's mild, but stuffy.
If this is a mask,
they feel uncomfortable around their eyes.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to take you to the doctor?
Yes, I do.
I want you to take me to the doctor.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Help me.
I'm not sure if this is a good idea or a bad idea, but I'm going to try it anyway.
What's wrong?
I love you.
How about you?
I love you more.
I see.
What are you doing?
I love you.
How about you?
I love you more.
I love you.
Thank you for watching!