I've been married to my husband for 20 years, and I've been thinking about the same thing every day since one day.
Oh, welcome.
Let's go to the room.
I wanted to feel the meaning of being alive.
Mirei.
Yes.
I'd like a cup of tea, please.
I've been married to my husband for 20 years, and I've been thinking about the same thing every day since one day.
Yuzuru, how's your girlfriend lately?
Huh?
Oh, she's still doing it.
What about Riku?
Oh, you're after Mika, aren't you?
No, I want to go out with her.
I've been married to my husband for 20 years, and I've been thinking about the same thing every day since one day.
Yuzuru, what's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Oh, okay.
I told you I was going to the party tonight.
I'm waiting at home as usual.
My girlfriend won't come today.
Hurry back before someone comes.
Please.
Let me hug you just once.
He, my son's friend, was the meaning of my life.
He was everything to me now.
I'm sorry.
Really?
Hello?
Hey, I ran out of coffee.
Then there's a new one in the kitchen on the right.
I'm sorry. I have to get back to work.
Are you coming home late?
I have a meeting, so I might be an hour late.
Okay.
Yeah, bye.
Are you okay, uncle?
Yeah, I'm fine. Let's hurry.
I'm sorry.
Are you thirsty?
Give it all out.
I'll be waiting.
Here.
I'm sorry.
You're not with him, are you?
Of course not.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Don't look at me.
It feels good.
Give me more.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
She's not coming, is she?
She's not coming.
It's okay.
I love you.
I've been putting up with it since I decided to be with you.
I'm glad.
I love you.
Everything you have is mine.
It feels good.
I love you.
Do you want me to hold you?
Yes.
It's hot.
You are very gentle.
You are very erotic.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I love you.
I learned it from you.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Ah...
It feels very sort of comfortable.
Do you feel great?
Knees, too...
Ah...
I'm so surprised.
Does it feel good here?
It's getting really hard.
I'm so surprised.
Rin-chan, I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to sleep behind you.
This suits you.
You like this, don't you, Yuzuru-kun?
I'm going to sleep.
I can't stand it anymore.
Give me some, too.
I'm going to sleep.
Yuzuru-kun, I'm so happy.
This suits you.
I'm going to sleep.
This feels good.
This is amazing.
I'm going to sleep.
This feels good.
I'm sorry.
Do you want more?
I want more.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to throw up.
It's okay.
Give me everything you have.
Are you out of your mind?
I'm out of my mind.
It all started five years ago in the summer.
At that time, we lived in the same apartment building.
Izura, you can eat this later.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
It's hard to live in the same apartment building.
We have to help each other.
I'm going home.
At that time, my husband cheated on me.
We were in a bad relationship.
I've been suffering for a long time without cheating.
I was miserable.
What's wrong with you?
Don't worry about me.
I'm going home.
What I'm going to say from now on is just a word.
So...
Just listen to me.
I...
I like you.
I'm sorry.
Please forget it.
Ma'am.
Mom.
It's late at night, isn't it?
Yes.
What I'm going to do now...
Can you keep it a secret?
What?
Um...
Ma'am.
Wait a minute.
Wait...
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Ah...
It hurts.
I hurt...
Um...
It's hot.
You're good at kissing.
It's getting really hard.
It's hot.
Your face is very beautiful.
It's very sexy.
It's hot.
I'm happy.
Let me do it, too.
It's hot.
It's very beautiful.
I'm sweating.
I'm sorry.
Let's have a drink.
It's hot.
Drink as much as you like.
Yes.
It's hot.
I want to drink more.
May I drink directly?
Yes.
It's hot.
You're good.
Did you feel good?
Yes.
It's hot.
I'm sweating.
I want to go out.
It's okay.
Just wear it.
Is it okay?
Yes.
It's hot.
Please do it slowly.
Slowly?
Yes.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
It's hot.
Please do it slowly.
Yes.
Do you feel good?
It's hot.
Please do it slowly.
Is it okay?
It's beautiful.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
Please do it slowly.
Yes.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
Please don't tell anyone.
I won't.
Please do it slowly.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
Please do it slowly.
I'll do it from behind.
It feels good.
You can move as you like.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's okay.
You can do it.
But you can't do it inside.
I want to wipe my face.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Did you do it again?
He has been drowning in his youthful body and overflowing sexual desire since that day.
It seems that you are late to go to the party recently.
It seems that you have more shifts.
I hope something will happen.
What do you mean?
You can't do that.
Of course.
We are a couple.
I have been drowning.
I can't see you anymore.
Why can't I see you?
I'm sorry.
I was called to work suddenly.
I took a day off, too.
I'm really sorry.
I'll make up for it.
See you.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
You don't have to go to her.
I'm okay.
You are more important to me.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm sorry.
You are too erotic.
Do you hate it?
I love it.
I'm sorry.
Do you really hate me?
It's okay.
Don't worry.
I'm sorry.
You are too erotic.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Please wake up.
I love you.
I love you, too.
It's soft and feels good.
I'm sorry.
Please let me do it.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
You didn't forget to do it, did you?
Of course.
But...
I can do it again.
Can I do it now?
It's okay.
But you have to do it.
I know.
Please talk to me.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I can do it.
You slept a lot.
I'm sorry.
You have to do it again.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
You came back early.
I was bored at the store.
So I came back early.
I'll take a break and go to work at night.
I see.
Yuzuru?
Why are you here?
I forgot something.
I skipped a class today.
So I came to pick it up.
Let's eat together.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
I'm sorry.
Who is it?
Mika?
Hello?
Karaoke?
I'm free now.
Now?
Okay.
Yuzuru.
Can you come back today?
I think I can do it with Mika.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm in a hurry.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
By the way, promise me.
Promise me again.
I'm sorry.
I'm hot.
I feel good.
I was surprised.
Did you feel good here?
Yes.
I feel my knees.
Do you like my feet?
I love it.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
I'm hot.
Do you feel good here?
Yes.
Please hold me.
I'm surprised.
It's very tight.
It's very soft.
Please rub it more.
It hurts.
I love you.
You are very cute.
I'm hot.
Please rub it more.
It's very soft.
I'm hot.
I feel good.
Please rub it more.
I'm hot.
Please come out of me.
I know.
I feel good.
I'm hot.
I want to lick here.
Let's lick together.
Please come out of me.
I'm hot.
You are very strong.
Let's go.
You can't do that.
Did you feel good?
I feel good.
You are cute.
I can't stand it anymore.
I want to puke.
I feel good.
You are very strong.
Let's go.
I feel good.
Did you feel good?
Let's go.
I feel good.
I want to puke.
Please get down.
I feel good.
You are very strong.
You are cute.
I feel good.
Please get down.
You are amazing.
I feel good.
You are strong.
You are amazing.
Let's go.
I feel good.
You are amazing.
You are better than an old man.
Really?
Let's go.
I feel good.
You are the best.
Let's go.
I feel good.
Let me out.
Let me out of your body.
I feel good.
You are amazing.
Let me out.
Let me out of your body.
I feel good.
You are amazing.
I know.
I have to end it someday.
But,
it's not now.
I needed him.
Only the time with him
makes me forget everything.
Thank you for watching.