I understand.
Mom, don't worry.
I'll study properly.
I'll call you later.
I'm a first-year adult.
I'm going to a school in the city.
I'm going to visit my aunt this year.
But I don't like my aunt.
It's been a long time.
How are you?
You've grown up.
Thank you.
It's your first time in Tokyo, isn't it?
Yes.
Didn't you get lost?
I'm fine.
Please come in.
Excuse me.
It's very spacious.
You brought a lot of luggage.
I have a lot.
My mother told me to give this to you.
Really? Thank you.
This is...
Please take care of it.
You don't have to worry about it.
Where is your uncle?
Wait a minute.
Your daughter is here.
Hiro.
It's been a long time.
You've become a man.
You were still an elementary school student.
That's right.
I was surprised.
Look at this.
I got this.
I love this.
I'm looking forward to working with you for a year.
I don't want to bother you.
Let's get along.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you.
I don't want to bother you.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Don't call me aunt.
Call me Aika-chan.
I don't want to call you aunt.
Wait a minute.
Let's take a picture.
Please take this.
It's been a long time.
Cheese.
It's good.
As I said earlier, I'm not good at old women.
I'm not good at old women.
I'm doing my best.
When I lived with my aunt for a month, I found out that she had a social media account.
What?
And it was a popular account with many followers.
Are you a pilot?
No, I'm not.
I'm not a pilot.
Last week, I went to Dubai.
What is this?
It's all a lie.
Thank you, Midorimushi.
Thank you so much.
You're so cool.
Thank you.
You talk a lot.
Really?
That's right.
That's why you're so cool.
Thank you.
I think it's a good idea to do a live stream.
What do you enjoy recently?
Do you have a favorite food?
Do you want to hear your self-introduction?
Do you like sweet food?
I know.
I like it, too.
I like sweet food, too.
Do you want to see it?
I'm going to eat it here.
Ta-da!
Mont Blanc.
Do you know where this is from?
That's right.
I can't make a reservation there.
I can't buy it even if I line up.
How did you get it?
You're curious, aren't you?
My beloved husband bought it for me.
I'm jealous.
He loves me.
Right?
I don't want to be lonely.
When I'm busy on a flight, he always buys me souvenirs and comes back.
That's what I bought this time.
Isn't it great?
I'm so happy.
I'll eat it.
I'll take a bite.
It's delicious.
It's really delicious.
I love Mont Blanc, especially among sweets.
So, I'm happy to eat extra coconut.
Thank you, Aki-san.
Thank you for buying it for me.
You bought me a lot.
Do you like manju?
I don't like it at all.
You like manju, don't you?
On days when my husband is not around, I earn money by doing a live broadcast every day.
I feel sorry for my husband.
Thank you for your Friday, Saturday, and holiday.
Thank you for purchasing three badges.
I'll go over there.
I'm sorry. It's nothing.
There is no one here.
Don't say scary things.
I'll give this to everyone.
I'll eat it.
It's delicious.
Cheers, everyone.
You scared me.
It's in my mouth.
Tell me that it's in your mouth.
Why are you naked?
I gave you a bath in the past.
That's a long time ago.
I'll do something amazing for you.
I'm the one who peels the face of a newcomer.
Don't say such an embarrassing thing.
Show me.
I don't want to.
Are you using it?
What's that reaction?
Please come in.
I don't think so.
Don't look at me.
What are you talking about?
Are you a virgin?
Don't ask me such a question.
Really?
Are you serious?
At that age?
That's not what I want to talk about.
You're lame.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
I don't want to talk about it with you.
It's true that virgins are lame and embarrassing.
That's not true.
You live in the countryside, don't you?
No.
If you're a virgin in the countryside at that age, you're the only one who's not super cool.
Hurry up.
That's not true.
I just don't want to talk about it with you.
I don't want to talk about it with you.
I don't care.
Take your time.
I'm sorry.
I was angry at my aunt who said I was a virgin.
And at that time, I thought I'd take advantage of her weakness and threaten her.
After that, I started investigating my aunt.
I decided to find out the secret of my aunt.
Hello.
You're so beautiful.
I was surprised.
Let's go.
I made a reservation for dinner.
I'm glad.
Let's go.
Is this the right place?
Yes.
I'm glad.
I was looking forward to it.
I made a reservation at a very nice place.
Really?
I'm glad.
Hello.
Today, my beloved husband came with me on a trip.
Look at this.
Can you see it?
He took me to a very beautiful place.
I'm glad.
It's cool, isn't it?
He planned such a wonderful trip to make me happy with a surprise.
It's the same clothes.
Yes.
Out.
He's pretending to be perfect.
I pretended to be a rich man and sent a message to my aunt.
If my aunt is stupid, I'm sure she'll fall for it.
1 million yen?
10 million?
As expected.
My aunt's in a trap.
A kind old man opens his eyes to a rich man.
Women need to be punished.
Yes?
Look at this.
Isn't it cute?
Well, it's flashy.
Flashy?
Yes.
But it doesn't look like a person, does it?
Well, yes.
I think it's cute, though.
I wonder if the picture will look good.
I like the light around here.
What?
Really?
But I can't reach it.
I can't take a good picture.
Hey, can you take a picture of this for me?
Oh, sure.
Thank you.
Take a good picture.
Okay.
I'll take a picture.
How is it?
Like this?
Does it look good?
Yes.
Where are you going in such a flashy outfit?
Hmm, I wonder.
Well, I don't know where I'm going.
Well, I'm going. Study hard.
Okay.
Bye.
Be careful.
Aika really came to the hotel.
I don't know who's coming.
She's really stupid.
I'm going.
Today's hotel is like this.
I'm glad that I was able to take you to various places.
Yeah.
What?
I was surprised.
Why?
What are you talking about?
I'm the DM guy that you were flirting with.
What?
What are you talking about?
You're a rich man.
You were the worst woman.
No, no.
Did you go out with me?
The other day.
I took a picture like this.
What?
What do you mean?
I don't understand.
It's a flashy account like an influencer.
It's just a lie.
It doesn't matter.
If you know this, you'll be a rich man.
Don't tell that person.
What should I do?
I have a suggestion.
What is it?
Let's have sex here.
What are you talking about?
You're crazy.
If we have sex, I won't tell anyone.
I don't understand.
What are you talking about?
Let's go home.
Don't do that.
I know what will happen if I show you the picture.
I'll do it with money.
You're dirty.
Why don't you do it with me?
Don't do that.
I'll tell you.
I'll show you my account.
Why?
I don't want to.
I know what I'm doing.
I'm excited to think that I'm kissing an old man.
I don't want to.
Why don't you do it with money?
Do it with me.
I don't want to.
I have a flashy account.
I'm so excited.
Intestines are soft.
I'll have sex.
You'll be in front of the uncle.
Listen to me.
I was able to put on perfume for the man of the day
What kind of sex do you always get money for?
Tell me
Do you kiss?
I don't
That's right
Kiss like you always do
Hey
If you're too rough
I'll end your life
Okay?
Don't look at your neighbor's account
I think it's fun
I can't play
I like this kind of thing
It feels good
It doesn't feel good at all
The virgin
You have a big mouth
Hey, old lady
Do you know your position?
You have a big mouth
I don't know what pain is
It's your finger
Don't
Does your finger feel good?
No
It's already wet
It's not wet
It's wet
I can't move it if I put so much effort
Ah
The worst
You know
If you don't resist, you won't do anything
Wow
You have a big mouth
Don't
Old lady
I'll go in soon
I don't want to
I really don't want to
You look cute when you feel it
I get excited when I see you feel it
I don't feel it
Don't
I don't want to
Old lady
You have a small mouth
Look at me
You always
Made fun of me as a virgin
But I'm a virgin
You're a kid
Now you're being made a virgin
Are you upset?
I'm not a virgin
Why are you looking down on me?
I'll make you angry
Old lady
Stop it
I really don't want to
Open your mouth
No
Hey
You always make fun of me as a virgin
I don't want to
My mouth is full
Don't make fun of me
I'm regretting that I made a mistake
I think I can return it as much as I want
It's the best
It feels good to be honest
Open your mouth
I'm always cheeky, so I'm doing this
I can't stop this
I'm sorry
Not yet
Swallow
I can't stop
I'm lonely
What is this
I'm a virgin who my aunt has been making fun of
Can you still make fun of me
Look at me
I can show this to my uncle
I can send it right away
It's strange to be in love
No
Did you know that your aunt is not actually a virgin?
I love to have sex
I want to do it even if I pay money
I'm going to have an aunt's baby
I want to be honest
I can't stop
Tighten
Hey
I thought it was a virgin
I can't go yet
I can't stop
I don't know if my aunt feels good
I can't see
I don't want to
It's not a question
I'm getting better
Please
I can't stop
I can't see
I don't want to
I don't know if my aunt feels good
I can send it right away
I can't stop
I can't see
I want to do more
I can't stop
I can't move
I don't know if my aunt feels good
I can't stop
I want to do more with my aunt
How do you feel now?
I don't want to
I want to hear sang
Isn't it bad to eat?
It's okay to go, isn't it?
No, what are you talking about?
You have to go seriously.
If you lie, you'll find out inside.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 40, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42, 41, 42
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
ああああああああ
ええええええ th
あああ あぁっ
You're lying.
That's the last of them.
Please let me go...
Ma.
You go easy on her, Ma'am.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 40, 41, 42, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 50, 51, 51, 52, 52, 53, 53, 54, 55, 56, 56, 57, 57, 58, 58, 59, 59, 60, 60, 60, 61, 61, 62, 62, 63, 62, 63, 63, 62, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63
63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63,
63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, 63, Community
You should run away.
Hey, old lady.
You're just a kid. You should run away.
Wait.
I'll go too.
Hurry.
Hey.
You cry with such a cute voice, don't you?
It's up to you what happens next.
That felt good.
I ate faster than I wanted to.
Masa, your butt is beautiful.
It's going to be a good video.
It smells so good.
It looks delicious.
It smells so good, Masa.
Wait a minute.
Can I tell my uncle what we did the other day?
No, you can't.
I have a picture of it.
Can I show it to my uncle?
No, you can't.
Can I lie to my uncle that I was attacked by a ghost?
Let's not play with me anymore.
No, you can't.
I'll be found out.
You looked so comfortable.
Please don't.
Can I show you the picture?
You looked so comfortable.
Why are you a little wet?
Because...
I can't hold my voice when I'm with you.
Don't touch me.
I told you not to touch me.
I love your breasts.
You're too excited.
No, I'm not.
It smells so good, Masa.
Masa.
Are you making fried rice today?
Yes, wait a minute.
I'm hungry.
What did you say?
I said I'd rather be with my uncle.
No, you can't.
I want to keep it a secret from my uncle.
What are you doing?
That photo.
If he finds out,
your uncle's job,
and your aunt's,
will be ruined.
I don't want to.
If everything is ruined,
your aunt will be sad.
I don't want to see that face.
I'm sorry, aunt.
I'm sorry.
More.
You like me, don't you?
I'm sorry.
I want to make you feel better.
Did he find out?
I'm sorry, aunt.
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
I won't stop until I'm satisfied.
Stop it now.
Are you sure?
Stop it, aunt.
No.
Stop it.
I won't let you go if you listen to me.
I won't let you go if you don't shut up.
I'm sorry.
Are you satisfied?
Why are you satisfied?
Stop it.
I want to make you feel better.
Open your mouth.
Stop it.
You licked me when I took that picture.
You like to lick me, don't you?
But I don't want to lick you now.
I feel good when you lick me now.
I feel good.
Are you hungry?
I'm hungry.
I'm sorry.
What are you holding?
Move your thighs.
That's the best.
I feel good.
You have a weak jaw.
You should lick me more comfortably.
I feel good.
Hiro.
Hi.
Did you go to do the laundry?
I'll open the door.
You should lick me more comfortably.
I feel good.
I'll give you a sandwich.
You're not eating it.
Don't spill...
She drank it all,
anyway.
She used it up.
It's good, isn't it?
The seasoning is good.
After that, Aika-san became more and more obedient.
My aunt and I had sex many times.
It's hot.
I'm going to sleep here.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sad?
I don't want you to be tired.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Don't move.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
I'm so happy.
It's cold.
I'm home.
Come in.
Here you are.
Thank you, ma'am.
You're wearing a naked apron.
You're great.
I can learn a lot from you.
You're sleeping next to me.
You're a pervert.
I want to catch my breath.
Lick me now.
Now?
Don't you like it?
But...
I want you to lick me now.
Come on.
Or you don't want to be licked?
I don't think so.
If you were licked in front of me, you'd want to be licked.
Come on.
I want you to lick me now.
You're sleeping next to me.
You listen to everything I say.
But...
You're a pervert.
You like me, don't you?
Does it hurt?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It doesn't hurt.
I'll give you more.
I'll put it in your mouth.
How is it?
It's good.
Look at me.
I'll put it in your mouth.
It's good.
You listen to everything I say.
I'll put it in your mouth.
It's good.
If you talk too much, he'll find out.
Hey.
You move first.
Okay.
You need to tighten your throat.
Do you understand?
Can you do it yourself?
Yes.
I'll put it in your mouth.
It's good.
You like me, don't you?
I'm too excited.
I'll put it in your mouth.
Can I put it in your mouth?
Please.
Please put it in my mouth.
Where do you want me to put it?
In the back.
I'll put it in your mouth.
I was just licking you, but you're wet.
You're a pervert.
I'll put it in your mouth.
You did your best this morning.
You want me to put it in your mouth, right?
I want you to put it in my mouth.
Can you put up with my voice?
I can't.
If you don't put up with my voice, I'll find out.
Do you understand?
Yes.
That's right.
Beg me more.
Please put it in my mouth.
Do you want me to put it in your mouth?
I want you to put it in my mouth.
Can you put it in my mouth?
It feels good.
I'll put it in your mouth.
Please put it in my mouth.
I want you to put it in my mouth.
Do you understand?
I can't put up with your voice.
I want you to put it in my mouth.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good here?
I feel good.
Don't put it in your mouth.
I'm sorry.
I put it in your mouth.
I want you to put it in my mouth.
What are you talking about?
I put it in your mouth.
I'm sorry.
You have to hold your voice this time, or you'll be found out.
It's so cold...
It feels good to massage this here.
You'll be found out if you make a lot of noise.
You don't have to be found out.
You can't be found out.
Why are you still going on your own?
You can't stand it.
You're a weakling, aren't you?
You're a weakling.
You can't stand it.
I'm going.
You said you were going.
You're great.
I'll give you a voice.
You can't stand it?
No.
Close your eyes.
...
Ma-san.
What?
You look tired.
You're still waiting?
It's the first time I've ever seen you like this.
It feels so good.
I can't.