A few days later
Cheers!
Hami, you're late for work.
You're late for work, too.
I see. Then I won't have time to say goodbye.
What do you mean?
It's about the baby.
It's been almost two years since you got married.
I want to see my grandchild as soon as possible.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You don't have to force it.
I know.
But I can't raise a child well.
By the way, when you were pregnant with Hami,
you didn't eat for about a month, did you?
A month?
That's right.
At that time, I was in a good mood and everything went well.
I have a good idea.
What is it?
Let's go on a hot spring trip with my family next month.
Until then, Kyubey will stay in the hospital.
What?
Then, Hami and I will go on a hot spring trip together.
That's a good idea.
Wait a minute.
Please wait a minute.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You're late.
I'm late for work.
What do you want to drink?
I'll have a beer.
Excuse me.
Good luck, Kyubey.
What are you talking about?
Let's make a toast.
It's too early.
What are you talking about?
Let's make a toast.
I want to see the inn.
I'm looking forward to it.
Me, too.
You kept your promise.
Yes, I did.
Oh, no.
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
I'm sure you can do it.
We're finally here.
It looks like a good inn.
I can't wait to get in the hot spring.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Are you sick?
No, I'm fine.
Really?
I'm fine.
Let's take a break in our rooms.
Okay.
See you at dinner.
See you later.
Let's go to the room.
Do you think it'll go well?
It's okay.
I'm sure it'll go well.
Yes.
I'm going to take a bath.
Okay.
I can't stand it.
What?
Ouch!
Wait a minute.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
It's been a long time.
I couldn't get in.
I can't help it.
I'm going to get some fresh air.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
What's wrong with you?
I tried to do that with Ami.
She said it hurt.
She refused.
I didn't know that.
I know.
I tried for a month.
I couldn't live up to her expectations.
I'm sorry.
How should I live?
What should I do?
It was too sudden.
Why don't you calm down and try again at night?
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Thank you.
Good luck.
I'll support you.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't ready.
It was too sudden.
Yes.
It can't be helped.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Really?
It's time for dinner.
Yes.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
It's good, isn't it?
It's good.
What's wrong?
I have a stomachache.
Do you have a stomachache?
You'll get better if you drink sake.
Really?
Thank you.
I'll put it in the cup.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I'll put it in the cup.
Okay.
Let's drink.
It looks delicious.
Thank you.
I drank too much.
I can't drink anymore.
You drank too much.
You told me to drink.
Are you okay?
What are you going to do?
I'll go back to my room and take a rest.
I'll take a bath again.
Really?
I'm going to bed.
I'm going to bed, too.
Are you going to bed?
Yes.
Good night.
What should I do?
I can't stand it.
I want to go, but I can't.
I'm crying.
I feel like I'm going to regret it for the rest of my life.
Just once.
Why?
It's hot.
What's wrong?
I'm scared.
Don't come here.
I can't stand it anymore.
I've been holding it in for a long time.
I've been holding it in for a month.
I tried to do it a while ago.
I was told it hurt.
I can't help it.
I know this.
I know this, but I can't help it.
I can't help it.
I want to go to my mom.
Calm down.
I can't.
If you can help me, I'll do anything.
I know I can't do this.
I can't.
Calm down.
Stop it.
I can't do this anymore.
How can I help you?
How much do you want?
I can't.
I can't do it anymore.
Calm down.
Please, I'm begging you.
I really can't do it anymore.
I can't do it anymore.
You got hurt, didn't you?
Stop it.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm going to have a period for a month.
I can't do it.
I can't do it anymore.
Please let me go.
I can't stand it.
I'm begging you.
No, no, no.
I'm going to put you in the water.
No, no.
It's dirty.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels good.
Please, don't do it.
I can't do what I wanted to do.
Wait a minute.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I want to do something.
Don't do it.
I want to do it.
Really.
I want to take it out.
I really can't.
Wait a minute.
Ramen.
I can't stand it anymore.
I want to drop it.
Ramen.
I can't stand it anymore.
Wait a minute.
Yes
I can't
yes
Yes
Yes, let's go back
No, not that way
Let's go
You should go back
I can't
Can I...?
It's too much
Come back
I can't
Wow, how nice
Does it feel good?
I become a lion
It feels so good.
One, two.
One.
Two.
One, two.
It feels so good.
Ouch!
No, no, no.
No, no.
Ouch!
Do you feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Ouch!
What should I do?
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Watch my face, let me dry my tears.
Feel good?!
I can't take it anymore
What have I done?
I've done it
Don't tell anyone about this
Yes, yes
I can't take it anymore
No, no, no
No
I can't hold it
No, no, no
I can't take it anymore
I beg you
No
I can't take it anymore
No, no, no
Calm down
I can't take it anymore
No, no, no
Stop it
No
Calm down
I can't take it anymore
Stop it
Calm down
I can't take it anymore
Stop it
Here
I'm sorry
Stop it
I can't take it anymore
Calm down
Stop it
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm sorry
What are you doing?
Stop it
I'm sorry
It feels good, doesn't it?
Stop it
I can't take it anymore
Calm down
Look at me
It feels good
Stop it
I can't take it anymore
It feels good
Look at me
I can't take it anymore
It feels good
Are you awake?
I can't take it anymore
I'm home
Are you awake?
Saori
Yes
Good morning
I'm going out
We still have time until the check out
What should we do?
I think I'll take another bath
I think I'll go for a walk
I think I'll relax in my room
I'll take a rest
Let's meet up later
Let's go
I can't take it anymore
Pull my neck
I want to do it more
It feels good
Do it more
No, no
No
It feels good
It hurts
I want to put it in
I'm going to put it in
It feels good
Do it more
It hurts
I can't do it
It feels good
It hurts
I'm going to put it in
It feels good
Do it more
Look at me
It hurts
It feels good
I'm going to put it in
It hurts
It feels good
I'm going to put it in
Do it more
It hurts
Look at me
It feels good
It hurts
I'm going to put it in
Do it more
It hurts
I'm going to put it in
It's okay
It hurts
You can do it
It feels good
Touch my neck
More
It feels good
It hurts
Do it more
It feels good
It hurts
I'm going to put it in
It feels good
It hurts
I want you to look at me
It feels good
It's cold
It hurts
It feels good
Do it more
It hurts
It feels good
I'm sorry
I love you
It feels good
It hurts
I'm sorry
Look at me
It hurts
It feels good
Help me
It hurts
It feels good
It was a good place, dad
The food was good
Did you forget anything?
I'm fine
How was it yesterday?
Yes
I'm looking forward to it
Let's go home
I was surprised that my mom was pregnant
I'm embarrassed to have a child at this age
Thank you
Dad, do you have alcohol?
I forgot to bring it
I'll go buy it
Let's go together
I'm pregnant
Please forgive me
It feels good
Touch me more
It hurts
It feels good
It's a secret between us