I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
My name is Eto, from Ito-Oiki.
Oh, you're Mr. Ito.
Please come in.
Is Mr. Kimura here?
Yes, he is.
Please wait a moment.
You're always so beautiful.
This is Fumi Satsuki from the reception.
This is Kaori Suzuki from the sales department.
These two are like the windows to our company.
Which one do you like?
I like Kaori.
Kaori?
I heard she's really good at it.
Really?
Yes.
She looks clean,
but I heard she has a lot to do with the most handsome men in the company.
I'm shocked.
I think I like Fumino.
But Fumino is married.
Yes.
That's right.
This is the third floor of the planning department.
I'll show you around.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'm going out for a bit.
Why did she marry a guy like Satsuki who can't work?
Did she think she had to marry me?
Oh, no.
I stepped on a ladder.
I thought I could do it.
Satsuki.
What are you doing?
Go get your bag.
I'm going.
Don't come back until you get your bag.
Is there something on your face?
No.
You're not here yet.
Yes.
How about lunch?
I'm sorry.
Dinner is fine.
I know a good restaurant.
I'm sorry.
I'm married.
I know that.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I was waiting for you.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'll show you around.
Excuse me.
Tea, please.
It's good.
You're sweating a lot.
Are you going to be late again today?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
I'll make your favorite food and wait for you.
See you.
Nice to meet you.
Are you going to work overtime today?
Yes.
You've been working hard lately.
I'm getting married soon.
I see.
I'm going to work overtime and give you a present.
Good luck.
Okay.
Thank you.
Let's have lunch.
What do you want to eat?
Meat? Seafood?
Did you go to a new restaurant?
Cold pasta was delicious.
You're persistent.
Let's have lunch together.
Do you want French food?
Do you want to eat at the restaurant?
Okay.
You always smell good.
I'm sexy.
What?
What did I do?
What's wrong?
Hey.
What?
I heard that you passed the exam.
Wait a minute.
I showed this to my friends.
This is not good.
You should be a little more mature.
You're right.
Let's eat.
I'm hungry.
I heard that you passed the exam.
You became the leader of the sales team.
I was told to find a new job in the countryside until next Monday.
Do we have to separate on our wedding anniversary?
What?
Is that so?
Do we have to separate on our wedding anniversary next Sunday?
I'll talk to you about it.
It's a little difficult.
You can get a job offer.
So it's not all bad.
I'll go get my underwear.
Hello.
Are you Kaori?
Thank you.
I'm glad you're with me.
I'm not good at booking hotels.
Let's do our best from tomorrow.
I want to go back to the wedding anniversary and surprise my wife.
See you tomorrow.
Who were you talking to at this time?
I was talking to Kaori.
We were booking a hotel to stay together.
Kaori?
Are you staying at the same hotel?
Yes.
Ozora asked us to go together.
Is the room separate?
The room is separate.
What's wrong?
There's a rumor that Kaori is not good.
There's a rumor that Kaori is good-looking.
So I won't be treated like that.
I won't be invited.
Don't worry.
I see.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Hi, Kaori.
Is Satsuki working?
If you want to go back soon, tell him to give you the number.
Don't let your wife contact you.
See you.
What are you doing?
Hey.
Yes.
Do you want to die?
Of course.
It's a joint responsibility.
Go to the room now.
Now?
Do you want to go to the countryside like Satsuki?
Yes.
Hurry up.
Don't come back until you give me the number.
Yes.
See you.
Welcome.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
I'm sorry for being rude to you.
I didn't realize I was sexual harassment until you told me.
I've changed my mind.
Please forgive me.
Don't worry about it.
Everyone makes mistakes.
Thank you.
You don't look well.
What happened?
I don't know.
I've been acting strange lately.
It's like I'm doing a hidden job.
We often run into each other.
I forgot that it was my wedding anniversary the next Sunday.
I haven't heard from you for a long time.
Maybe you're cheating on me.
What?
Actually, Satsuki said she wanted to go on a business trip.
She said her classmate was Kaori.
I met her.
No way.
I thought something was wrong.
It's hard to cheat on you in the company.
But if you go on a business trip, you can cheat on me in the company.
I chose to cheat on you rather than spending my wedding anniversary with you.
I didn't think you were such a man.
Why didn't you go out?
I got an e-mail from Kaori.
Maybe she's waiting for me at the hotel.
I'm sure you're cheating on me.
No way.
What should I do?
We can't get rid of our memories.
If you want to be with Satsuki, you have to keep it in your heart.
But it's frustrating.
I think we should do the same thing.
Then we can be together.
But I can't do that.
I don't know.
Satsuki is waiting for you at Kaori's hotel.
Aren't you upset?
Well...
Look at me.
I think it's good now.
You feel better.
Don't think about anything now.
I hope you feel better.
Here you are.
But...
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone.
But...
Don't think about anything now.
But if someone sees us...
Don't worry.
Don't think about anything.
Satsuki.
You're sensitive.
I haven't done it for a while.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Satsuki is having fun with Kaori.
You didn't do it for her.
You must be lonely.
So, we should do the same thing.
But...
Imagine what Satsuki is doing now.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of her.
But if someone sees us...
Don't worry.
Do you feel good?
No.
I can't do it.
Why?
Satsuki is with Kaori.
Can't you?
But if someone sees us...
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone.
Wait.
I can't do it.
You have a beautiful body.
But you can't be with her.
You're sleepy.
I wanted to do this.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
Someone might see us.
But you're wet.
But...
Don't worry.
I'll help you.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
You're wet.
I can't do it.
Do you feel good?
What's wrong?
But...
I can't do it.
Look at me.
Open your mouth.
Do you feel good?
I can't do it.
Open your mouth.
I'll help you.
I can't do it.
You're wet.
Do you feel good?
I can't do it.
I'll help you.
Do you feel better?
I can't do it.
What's wrong?
Look at me.
It's better to forget it.
I can't do it.
But...
What's wrong?
I can't do it.
Why?
You can do it.
I can't do it.
What's wrong?
Do you feel good?
I can't do it.
It's very tight.
How do you feel?
Look at me.
Your panties are wet.
I can't do it.
You sweat a lot.
You have a beautiful body.
I can't do it.
Do you feel good?
Come here.
I can't do it.
Move.
It's very tight.
Do you feel good?
Look at me.
Come here.
I can't do it.
Look at me.
I feel sick.
I can't do it.
Please forget this.
Hello.
I came back to the hotel after work.
I was busy.
I'm sorry I couldn't contact you.
Where is Kaori?
I was invited to drink in the room.
I refused because I had to prepare for tomorrow.
I checked the other party's information.
I have a lot of things to do.
I thought it was over in the evening.
If it's over so soon, it won't reach you before you get on.
I'm going to stick to the last minute.
I asked Kaori for the overtime fee.
I got a call from Hosoda.
Hosoda is strict with me.
I'm sorry, but I'm not good at Kaori.
She is my ex-girlfriend.
Is that so?
She used to date me a little.
I see.
I can't contact you on Sunday from tomorrow.
If it goes well, I can go back to Sunday.
Don't expect it.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
Please contact me again.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I have something to tell you.
Is it true that you dated Kaori in the past?
Yes.
It's a long time ago.
Are you using Kaori?
I'm going on a business trip.
I'm going to seduce Satsuki.
If I succeed, I'll give you a lot of money.
Kaori is harder than I thought.
I'm sorry.
Amazing.
I'm not good at dating.
I'm sorry.
I don't want Satsuki to see this.
It's the worst.
You guys were watching.
I'm getting dizzy.
What are you going to do?
I want you to process it.
Come here.
Here.
Can you process it?
It's okay.
You can send the video to Satsuki.
I don't want to.
Wait.
It's boring.
Start with a kiss.
Okay.
Why do I have to do this?
Do you know why?
Yes.
I want you to kiss me more.
That's enough.
Do you understand?
Do you want me to lick you?
Hurry up and do it.
I want you to kiss me more.
I don't want to.
This is what it feels like to have sex.
You fooled me.
Sprite
This feels nice.
Is this good enough?
Next, this way.
Why do I have to go that far?
You don't want to be called like that, do you?
You have to be careful.
I understand.
Hurry up and use your mouth.
Do I have to use my mouth?
I can't do it with my hands.
You can use a bowl like last time.
No.
I can't do it.
Can you inhale more?
It's hard to inhale and exhale.
It doesn't feel good.
Do you understand?
Like this?
Do it.
I can't do it.
I want to use a bowl.
You felt good last time, didn't you?
I can't do it.
I don't think I'm such a terrible person.
That's your opinion.
You're terrible.
What do you think?
Maybe you wanted me to lick you.
I can't do that.
That's too bad.
I can't do it.
Get me out of here.
Then make me feel good.
You want me to get you out of here, don't you?
I want it to end soon.
Hurry up.
I can't do it.
I'll get you out of here.
I don't care.
I can't do it.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
I'm Ishii from Aoki Shouji.
Is Mr. Bushida from the medical department here?
Yes, please wait a moment.
First of all, I'd like to ask you to come in.
Yes.
Excuse me.
I'm going to hang up now.
Okay.
Here you are.
Excuse me.
Yes.
I'll show you to the third floor.
Please go to the third floor.
Thank you.
Welcome.
I'm Sato from the medical department.
Thank you.
Please come in.
Yes.
If you look at the data I gave you, the annual sales performance graph is divided into teams.
The blue team is team A and the red team is team B.
The green team is team C.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Thank you.
The sales performance of team C is better in the second half.
Yes.
Team B is still in a parallel line.
I think it will be difficult if we don't improve it.
Thank you.
Is there anything wrong?
Excuse me.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Be careful not to get injured.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
You look very happy.
I'm not happy.
Are you excited?
No.
Can you hear me?
I'm sorry.
Please stop.
It's dangerous if you push her.
Did you feel so good?
No.
I see.
Let me check your pulse.
Your pulse is very fast.
That's not true.
What's this?
I don't know.
It's very Russian.
Your pulse is very sensitive.
That's not true.
I'm sorry.
I can hear your voice.
Please stop.
I can't stand it.
I think it's better to give you a toy.
I'm sorry.
I can hear your voice very well.
Are you depressed?
That's not true.
Please stop.
I'll give you a toy.
That's not true.
Please stop.
I can hear your voice.
That's not true.
I'll give you a toy.
I'm sorry.
That's not true.
Please stop.
Do you want to do more?
That's not true.
You can't do this.
Please stop.
That's not true.
Do you want to do more?
I'll give you a toy.
That's not true.
You don't look so good.
You've lost weight.
I haven't lost weight.
That's not true.
Don't worry.
No one will come here.
That's not true.
Don't worry.
Please stop.
You have a suspicious face.
I don't have a suspicious face.
You have a crooked neck.
I don't know.
That's not true.
You have a good body.
Please stop.
I'm sorry for you.
That's not true.
You can't stand up.
I'll give you a toy.
That's not true.
Please stop.
You have a good body.
That's not true.
Please stop.
Your voice is echoing.
What should I do if someone comes?
Don't worry.
Please stop.
You're in a bad mood.
That's not true.
Please relax.
Please stop.
That's not true.
You look like you're in a bad mood.
What's wrong with you?
Do you want some water?
Why?
You want some water, don't you?
No, I don't.
You don't have to do this.
Don't do this.
I'll put water in your mouth.
Please bear with it.
You want to put water in my mouth, don't you?
I'll put water in your mouth.
Do you want to lick me so much?
That's not what I mean.
If you say you want to lick me, I'll let you lick me.
Don't you want to lick me?
Then I'll continue.
I want to lick you.
Do you want to lick me?
I don't mind if you ask me to lick you like that.
Then I'll let you lick me.
I want to lick you.
Okay.
Put your hands on the floor.
Spread your legs so that they can be seen clearly.
You can do it, can't you?
Do it like this.
Does it feel good?
You don't like it, do you?
Show me where you're touching.
You're amazing.
Touch me more firmly.
How do you feel?
Do you feel better?
Are you satisfied?
Not at all.
Stand up.
Spread your legs.
I'll put this in your mouth.
You want it, don't you?
I don't want it.
I'll put this in your mouth.
It hurts.
What's wrong?
I can't do this anymore.
It feels good.
Which one do you feel better?
What?
I don't know.
I think you should be more honest.
This way.
You said it.
If you say that, I'll get excited.
I'll put this in your mouth.
Do you want more?
Why?
What do you want?
Give it to me.
I'll put this in your mouth.
Did you say something?
No, I didn't.
I'll put this in your mouth.
I can't do this.
I can't do this anymore.
What's wrong?
Do you really want me to stop?
I can't do this anymore.
I don't know what to do.
I can't do it.
Are you okay?
I achieved my goal.
You did your best.
I wanted to celebrate my wedding anniversary with my wife.
I'm going to surprise her secretly.
I think she will be surprised.
I hope she will be happy.
Anyway, you did your best.
Thank you.
That's all.
Gura.
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
I have a day off tomorrow.
So, I'm going to work until the morning.
She must be happy.
I'm going to write her name.
Oh, no.
Yes.
I still have a long way to go.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
Is it okay for you to do this in your house?
I invited you to my house.
It's all my fault.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
You're rubbing your face.
You're disgusting.
I'm sorry.
What are you going to do?
Can I lick you?
It's okay, isn't it?
Do you want to lick me?
Yes.
Don't you want me to lick you?
I want you to lick me.
I feel good.
Do you want to lick me?
I want to lick you.
I want you to lick me.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to lick you?
I want you to lick me.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
Do you want me to lick you?
I want you to lick me.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
You have a different shape.
Do you think so?
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
You have a bad body.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to put it here?
I don't want it.
I'm sorry.
Can't I put it in?
You want it, don't you?
Yes.
You can't do that.
Why?
It's hard.
It's okay, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
I wanted to do it, too.
What?
What's going on here?
Do you want to put it in yourself?
I want to put it in.
Can't I?
You can.
I'm sorry.
Don't do it.
You're sweating a lot.
Do you like it?
Do it again.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.