WARNING
Huh?
Another of his classmate got married.
Maybe I'm the only one who has a crush on him.
I'm sorry.
I'll read it.
Um, here you go.
Thank you.
I'll be waiting for your reply.
Oh, yeah.
I'm sorry. I'm in a hurry.
I'll read it.
Seigo?
Huh?
How do you know my name?
I knew it was you.
You remember me.
Huh?
Um...
I'm sorry.
You're my classmate, Sunao.
Kokonoi Sunao.
Kokonoi...
Sunao?
I wrote you a letter.
I wrote you a letter,
but you didn't read it.
Huh?
No, I didn't.
I read it.
By the way,
let's go for tea sometime.
I want to talk about the old days.
Okay.
I'll give you my number.
Here you go.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
I'm sorry.
I'm working.
I'll call you later.
Good luck with your work.
Thank you.
Bye.
Seigo, you were as cool as you were then.
I'm home.
You said you'd be home late today.
I have plans all of a sudden.
Will you cook for me?
I'm hungry.
Even if you say that,
I only have green onions.
What should I do?
I can't use them.
Okay.
I'll go eat somewhere nearby.
Wait.
Shut up.
Sunao Kokonoe.
Sunao Kokonoe, my childhood friend.
I see.
I didn't see her that much.
She was plain.
But, she's so cool now.
I'm so angry.
Damn it.
What's wrong with me?
It's Sunao.
Hello?
Hello, Seigo.
I called you right away.
What's wrong?
It's hard to say.
Can I go to your house now?
What?
I had a fight with my husband today.
I have nowhere to go.
So, I want you to stay here tonight.
Of course.
I'll be right there.
Thank you.
I'll go to your house now.
Seriously?
I'm sorry.
I bought this.
Let's drink together.
Okay.
Let's go inside.
Hurry up.
It's a beautiful room.
Yes.
I cleaned it in a hurry.
I see.
Let's drink.
Okay.
Cheers.
Thank you.
I'll pour you a drink.
Today,
let's celebrate our reunion.
Cheers.
It's good.
Let's drink.
Cheers.
By the way,
the teacher at that time was a bad guy.
Yes.
He was a bad guy.
He always made me angry.
Really?
Seigo was good-looking.
At that time,
Seigo was good at sports and studying.
He was popular with girls.
At that time,
he confessed his love to me every day.
I sent a letter to Seigo.
But he didn't remember me at all.
No.
That's not true.
We were childhood friends.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
I remembered you.
It's okay.
After that,
I worked hard to get Seigo back.
Then, Seigo became beautiful.
I see.
Then, Seigo confessed his love to me.
Then, we got married.
But, we fought every day.
I see.
You have a beautiful wife.
What are you thinking about?
If I were you,
I would take good care of her.
Did I choose the wrong person?
What?
Wait.
What are you doing?
Is it bad?
No, it's not bad.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Kiss me more.
It's hot.
Let's go to bed.
You're beautiful.
It's hot.
Kiss me more.
I've never kissed you so hard.
I want to kiss you more.
It's hot.
Kiss me more.
You're beautiful.
It's hot.
You're stupid.
You're deceiving me.
You're the best.
I've never kissed you so hard.
Kiss me more.
It's hot.
You're beautiful.
I've never licked you.
I'll lick you.
Look at me.
It feels good.
It tickles a little, but it feels good.
It's hot.
It's getting hot.
I haven't kissed you so much.
I haven't kissed you for a long time.
It's hot.
A little more.
My legs are moving.
It's sensitive here.
It's hot.
My legs are moving.
You're beautiful.
I'm embarrassed.
I'll make you feel better.
It's hot.
It's sensitive here.
I'll make you feel better.
It's hot.
It hurts.
I'll kiss you.
It's hot.
I'll lick you.
It's difficult.
You're getting bigger.
It's hot.
It's refreshing.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'm excited.
Look at me.
You're cute.
I'll drink a lot.
Look at me.
It's hot.
Raise your hands.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Look at me.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'll make you feel better.
Look at me.
It's hot.
You're beautiful.
I'll make you feel better.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I can see you're embarrassed.
You're beautiful.
It feels good.
I'll make you feel better.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Look at me.
What's wrong?
You're sweating.
You're sweating a lot.
Here.
It feels good.
You're sweating a lot.
Look at me.
Here.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm glad.
Here.
You're sweating a lot.
It's hot.
Here.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Kiku...
Let's kiss more.
Kiss me.
I want to kiss you.
Give me your arm.
Give it to me.
It's hot.
It's hard.
Look at me.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it feels good.
It's a little hot.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it feels good.
It feels really good.
Oh, it's hot.
This is bad.
It's cracking.
It's making a lot of noise.
Yes.
It's so good.
It's so refreshing.
It's refreshing.
It's making a lot of noise.
It's so good.
It feels good.
It's making a lot of noise.
What's wrong?
You're about to go, aren't you?
I'm about to go.
I'll help you.
It's making a lot of noise.
It feels so good.
I'll lend you a lot of money.
Wait a minute.
You like this, don't you?
I like this.
It's making a lot of noise.
It feels good.
I've never felt this way before.
It's making a lot of noise.
It feels good.
My stomach hurts.
My stomach hurts a lot.
I can't.
I'll hold it in.
Where should I put it?
Put it in your stomach.
In my stomach?
Please put it in your stomach.
I can't hold it in.
I can't.
Good morning.
It feels good, right?
I've been feeling sick since this morning.
Let's do a lot of pleasant things.
Kimchi
Do you want to do pleasant things?
Yes.
I'll put it in your stomach.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I want you to lick me a lot.
Kimchi
It feels good.
I'll do something more pleasant.
I'm embarrassed.
It's getting harder.
Look at me.
It feels good.
It's getting harder.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's getting harder.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'll do something more pleasant.
It's hard.
It feels good.
I'll do something more pleasant.
It's hard.
It feels good.
Kimchi.
It's hard.
It feels good.
It's getting bigger.
It's good.
It feels good.
It's getting bigger.
My hands are cold.
It's very good.
It's hot.
I'm sweating.
It's very good.
It's hot.
That's it.
I'll put it out.
It's hot.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'll put it out.
It's hot.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'll put it out.
It's hot.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm sweating.
I'm going to work.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to go home.
Okay.
Call me if you need anything.
Come here.
What's wrong?
I can't stand it anymore.
I don't like it.
I don't like it at all.
I can't stand it anymore.
Tamae and Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother, Riki's mother
They're so cute.
It's so good.
Where did he go?
Did he go home?
Honey.
I'm sorry I left home.
It's my fault.
I'll make breakfast today.
Let's eat together.
He hasn't contacted me at all.
What is he doing?
I'm worried.
I'm sorry.
He didn't even look at me in the past.
Now he's thinking about me so much.
You're still awake.
Why are you smiling?
It's nothing.
Let's go to bed.
I'm going to the convenience store.
Are you really going to the convenience store?
It's not a man's place, is it?
I'm going to bed.
I'm glad you're back.
I left home again.
I'm going to bed.
It's delicious.
You're so wet.
I'm going to bed.
It hurts.
I'm going to sleep.
It's delicious.
It feels good.
It's getting hot.
I can't stand it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I want you to get a lot of heat.
Okay.
It feels good.
I'm getting a lot of heat.
It's hot.
I'll give you a lot of heat.
It's making a lot of noise.
It's hot.
It feels good.