2 days later
I'm home.
Welcome home.
This is Kiyoshi, a junior from the countryside.
We've talked a few times, haven't we?
You're Kiyoshi, right?
Nice to meet you. I'm Kiyoshi.
Actually, I'm going to start my own company.
I haven't decided on the amount yet, but I'm in a situation.
I wonder if I can take care of it for a few days at home.
You're such a pain in the ass.
You came out of nowhere.
Think about it.
I will.
You've become a social person.
I'm going to eat.
Honey, wait a minute.
Is it okay to stop all of a sudden?
It's okay.
I'm sure it's a good guy.
But you'll be gone at noon.
You don't have to worry about anything.
You can worry about a fire or anything.
You look like a violent young man with a strong body.
Even though you're my husband's acquaintance, I'm a little worried.
Thank you.
I'm going to wash the dishes.
It's almost lunchtime.
Is there anything you want to eat?
I want to eat rice balls.
Is that really okay?
Yes.
It's the best.
It's a normal rice ball.
No.
It's the same as my wife's.
It's completely different.
Call your wife Natsuki.
Okay.
It's delicious.
What do you like?
I like everything.
Really?
Yes.
What do you like next?
I like everything.
Everything?
Yes.
What do you not like?
Hello.
The days I spent with my husband, who was straight and kind, were wonderful days that warmed my heart.
I bought you a light bulb.
Thank you.
It's hard to get a light bulb, so it was helpful.
I'm sorry I always eat the same food.
That's not true.
Daisuke is a happy man.
Is that so?
I'm sorry I left my luggage here.
It's okay.
I'm happy to be with you.
I'm happy to be with you, too.
What?
No, I didn't mean that.
I see.
It was just a compliment, but my heart was so disturbed that I was surprised.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Kiyoshi and I were waiting for you.
Who asked you to wait for me?
Sometimes you're late.
I'm sorry.
Give me a bath.
Yatsuki, are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'll get you a bath.
Kiyoshi, you eat first.
Okay.
What are you going to do?
I gave it back to Daisuke.
But you told me to throw it away.
So I threw it away without checking the contents.
That's enough.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I woke you up.
Natsuki, what's wrong?
It's okay. It's my fault.
No, it's not.
There's no ideal wife like you.
I'm sorry.
You're good at cooking and kind.
There's no other beautiful woman like you.
Kiyoshi.
I'm sorry.
Kiyoshi, you can't do this.
I feel sorry for Natsuki.
I'm sorry.
Natsuki, talk to me.
Can I touch you?
I'm sorry.
You're beautiful.
Kiyoshi.
I'm sorry.
I hate you.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Kiyoshi.
You're beautiful.
I'm sorry.
Kiyoshi.
You're beautiful.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Wait a minute.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
No.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Praise be!!!
Oh my heart
Oh my!!!
Oh...
Ahhh, feel regret now wasn't it?
Ahh Too Good
Ahhh
Let's Go Let's Go
AHH
Ahhh
Ahh
I can't breathe...
I felt it
Ah, no, no, no
Sorry, sorry, sorry
It hurts.
So hard.
The popcorn is delicious.
Do you eat this popcorn?
Oh, it feels so good.
It feels so good.
I can't do it.
Let's go!
It feels so good.
We have been in a house with no husband and only two of us.
I remembered the joy of women in my body.
It feels so good.
I have a
It's okay.
Are you okay?
It feels good.
No.
It's okay.
It feels good.
Are you sleepy?
Does it feel good?
It feels good for me, too.
It feels good.
Does it hurt?
Can I rub your head?
Rub your head.
It feels good.
This is for you.
Does it feel good?
Does it hurt?
It doesn't hurt.
It feels good.
It's okay.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Do you want to do more?
It feels good for me, too.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Are you sleepy?
Give me a lot.
It feels good.
Are you going home?
Yes.
Let's take a shower.
Let's go.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Do you feel ticklish?
It feels good.
You've grown up again.
Do you want to take a shower?
It feels good.
Yes.
You've lost a lot of weight.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
I have good news.
What is it?
If you're so motivated, you can come by tomorrow.
They'll give you an early admission fee.
I'm glad.
It's a special offer.
The salary is also a member's treatment.
They'll give you a raise.
Come to the office at 12 o'clock.
Okay.
I'm going.
I have to get ready.
Wait.
One last time.
I'm going.
It feels good.
Get up.
You like my boobs, don't you?
I'll brush your boobs.
It feels good.
I'll make you feel better.
I need a lot of hair.
No, no.
I'm going to be full.
I feel sick.
No, no, no.
No, no.
I'm going to be full.
No, no, no.
I feel good.
No...!
Out!
There you go!
Out.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
More.
I can't do it anymore.
Ah...
Oh...
Oh, it's so good.
Ah...
Oh, oh...
Oh...
Ah...
Ahhh...
So gross...
Gross...
Ahhh...
Ahh...
So gross...
Ahhh...
Ahh...
Oh my god,
Oh my god...
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Ah, it feels so good.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no .
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
ah ah ah
ah
蜂身
変える
삼
竸
蜂身
It feels so good.
I feel so good, too.
It feels so good!
I'm sorry.
It feels so good.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I feel so bad.
Oh my gosh.
Oh! Oh! Oh! Ah!
Do you short of breathe?
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Somehow...
How wonderfuI...
Emm! Oh! Oh!
Can you extend the rope to me?
Come on.
Can you extend it?
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17,18,19,20,21,22,23,24,25,26,27,28,29,30,31,32,33,34,34,35,36,37,38,39,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40
OK
Can you really be alright here?
Do you want me to see you to the station?
It's OK
Thank you so much Natsuki
It's good to see you
I'm glad I met you, Kiyoshi.
See you.
Are you hungry?
Do you want to eat rice balls?
Thank you for watching.