The next day
Here you go.
Thank you.
How about dinner tonight?
No, thanks.
I got a call from my classmate's island.
We're going out for a drink.
Oh, I see.
I got it.
Do you have any plans for this weekend?
I don't think there's anything in particular.
Oh, I see.
Why don't we go on a trip together?
It's almost time for our wedding anniversary.
I'd love to.
Thank you.
Well, if you don't mind,
I'd like you to take me on a trip to a hot spring.
Well, you decide where to go.
Thank you.
Well, I'm off.
Take care.
I wonder which hot spring I should go to.
I'm home.
Oh, you're home.
What's going on?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was drinking with my classmate's island.
We had a problem.
What's the problem?
His job is a loan shark.
You know, we're childhood friends.
I got a loan without a repayment deadline.
That's why I asked him to pay me back today.
I can't do that.
Calm down.
What are you going to do now?
I have no choice but to close the company.
If that's not enough, I'll figure it out.
Damn it.
Hey, don't drink too much.
I'm fine.
Shut up.
Honey.
I'm home.
Honey, what are you doing in the morning?
No.
What?
It's good to drink in the morning.
How about a drink?
What are you talking about?
You can't drink in the morning.
No.
You're drunk.
I did my best.
It must have been hard for you.
I'll take care of it.
Are you Ideo's wife?
Yes.
I'm Ideo.
I'd like to talk to you about my debt.
I don't need your advice.
Just pay me back.
That's all.
I don't have much money.
I'll take care of it.
That's all.
Wait a minute.
Can you give me a discount?
I'll do anything.
Thank you.
Give me a discount.
Do you like him so much?
Can you do anything for him?
Yes.
He's my important husband.
I understand.
I'll give you a discount.
Thank you.
What's the condition?
Oyashida.
Yes.
Tell her.
Be my wife on the weekend.
What do you mean?
If you can't do that, I won't talk to you.
Wait a minute.
I'll do it.
Let me do it.
I understand.
Come here this weekend.
That's all.
Thank you.
Why are you dressed like that?
I told you before.
I'm going to work on the weekend.
Don't you remember?
I see.
I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
Please sit down.
You're here.
Don't tell Hideo.
I can't tell him.
Don't be sad.
This is a business.
I'll pay you back.
Let's get started.
First of all, talk to him.
Yes.
What's wrong?
Can't you do it?
You have to do what I say.
Yes.
I understand.
Do you want to do it?
Make a sound and talk.
I understand.
Look at me.
Show me how to move your tongue.
Show me your tongue.
Talk to me more lovingly.
Show me that you love me.
I love you.
Look at me.
Make a sound.
Talk to me more lovingly.
I understand.
What's wrong?
You can't pay me back.
Talk to me more lovingly.
Does it hurt?
Yes.
Do it more.
It's not over yet.
Yes.
Look at me.
Do it more.
I understand.
Look at me.
Use your hands.
I understand.
Do it more.
Yes.
You want to pay me back, don't you?
Take a walk with her.
Don't let her go.
She's mine.
Listen to me.
Don't let her go.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Don't move.
Show me your love.
Yes.
I like it when people do this to me.
Well...
I'm going to see how much of a slut you are.
Yes.
What are you doing?
Give me your tongue.
Accept it.
Do it more.
Don't do it.
Accept it.
What's that hand?
I don't know.
Look at me.
Do it more.
You have a strong body.
How's your neck?
I'm asking you how your neck is.
Can you feel it?
I can't feel it.
You can't feel it.
You're strong.
Give me your tongue.
You have a nice butt.
Show me your butt.
Don't run away.
What's that hand?
I can't see it.
Give me your tongue.
Open it yourself.
Don't make me angry.
Open it.
Open it yourself.
Don't move.
You have a nice butt.
I like it.
Look at me.
I'll look at you.
Can you feel my butthole?
Can you feel it?
Look at me.
Don't run away.
I'll show you.
You have a nice butt.
Look at me.
Do you want to see me?
Thank you.
You haven't opened it yet.
Open it until you can see it.
Open it more.
You have a nice butt.
You'll feel good if you put it in.
Do you feel good?
I don't think so.
I'll look at you.
Look at me.
Open it more.
You have a nice butt.
Can you feel it?
Open it more.
Look at me.
Do you feel good?
Open it.
You have a nice butt.
Look at me.
Open it more.
Don't look at me.
Look at me.
Do you feel good?
I don't think so.
You feel good, don't you?
Don't go anywhere.
Tell me the truth.
Don't go.
Don't go anywhere.
Tell me the truth.
Do you feel good?
What was that?
You didn't tell me.
Open it more.
How do you feel?
You can put it in your mouth.
It's a big mistake if you think it's over just by talking.
You want to put it in your mouth, don't you?
You're my woman.
Listen to me.
Do you understand?
Don't go anywhere.
Wait.
What is it?
Don't do this to me.
I don't know.
It's a big mistake if you think it's over just by talking.
It's a big mistake.
Go.
Don't do this to me.
Did it come out?
I'm sorry for him once.
He's a man who wants to do it as many times as he wants.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Me too.
Don't run away.
Do you know what we're called?
It's called the Zetsurin family.
Let me do it until I feel like it.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Do you feel it?
Show me your face.
How is it?
Which do you like better?
Don't ask me that.
You like this better, don't you?
Does it feel good?
It's amazing, isn't it?
Do you feel it?
Show me your face.
It's amazing, isn't it?
You're done, aren't you?
You're pretty good.
As promised, I'll pay you back.
It's amazing, isn't it?
What should I do today?
I don't know.
For the time being,
I want you to be Zenra.
Walk in four steps.
That's...
Can't you do it?
If so,
That's the end of the story.
You can go home as it is.
I understand.
What's wrong?
Take it off.
Yes.
Don't be nervous.
I'm sorry.
You're Zenra, right?
Yes.
Take it off.
Don't hide it.
Four steps.
Yes.
Walk around here.
Slowly.
Yes.
Stop there.
Sit down.
You can't sit down.
Raise your butt.
I raised it.
Sit down.
Yes.
You're a good boy.
I'll take care of you today.
Yes.
You can't see.
Sit down.
Yes.
The other day,
You played with me.
I enjoyed it.
I'm so excited.
I'll take care of you.
Go ahead.
Walk in four steps.
Yes.
Stop there.
Raise your mouth.
Don't use your hands.
Use your mouth.
Yes.
I'll take you for a walk.
Come here.
Yes.
Walk in four steps.
Come on.
Don't let go of me.
If you let go of me, I'll start over.
Answer me.
Don't let go of me when I answer you.
I'll start over at home.
Come here.
Stop.
I told you not to let go of me.
I'm sorry.
You can eat by yourself.
You like to eat by yourself.
Don't let go of me.
Walk in four steps.
That's it.
Give me two of those soft ones.
Soft ones.
That's it.
Come here.
Here you are.
Grab it.
Rub it on your nipples.
You know that, right?
Do it.
More.
If you don't do it properly, you'll get sick.
Rub it on your nipples.
More.
Why do you look like an abandoned puppy?
What?
More.
You look good.
That's it.
Give me a kiss.
Here you are.
What's that?
You're not a puppy.
Give me more.
I told you to give me a kiss.
Give me a kiss.
More.
Give me more.
Here you are.
More.
Hey.
Put it in your mouth and let me drink it.
You'll get excited.
Do it.
Don't let me drink it.
Here you are.
Rub it on your nipples.
Don't let me drink it.
Answer me.
Do it.
Let me drink it.
Are you done?
Give me a kiss.
Oto.
I'm taking a break.
Give me a kiss.
Give me more.
I'm taking a break.
More.
Here you are.
Give me a kiss.
Keep doing it.
Give me a kiss, rub it on your nipples and repeat it.
I'm taking a break.
Give me a kiss.
More.
Rub it on your nipples.
Hug me.
Both of you.
I'm going to give you a high-five.
High-five.
Do it.
Do it more.
Left and right.
That's right.
Do it seriously.
You want to pay me back, don't you?
Do it.
Do it seriously.
You want to pay me back, don't you?
Do it.
I'm getting excited.
All right.
I'm going to give you a high-five.
But...
From behind.
From behind?
Come on.
I'm going to give you a high-five from behind.
From behind?
Yes.
Do it.
I'm going to give you a high-five.
That's right.
Come on.
Think of it as a tail and grab it.
That's right.
Do you understand?
More.
Come on.
How's my dick?
Is it standing?
Huh?
It's flat, isn't it?
Make it more flat.
Yes.
All right.
Flatten your butt.
Flatten your butt with your butt.
What's wrong?
If you want to go home, do it quickly.
Flatten your butt.
It's going to be hard.
Come on.
What's wrong?
Do it.
That's right.
You don't look like me.
Do it lower.
That's right.
All right.
Come on.
Be careful.
Look at me.
Come on.
Do it.
All right.
Come on.
Look at me.
Do it.
All right.
Good boy.
Oh, no.
You look like you like me.
I don't think it's a good idea.
You like me, don't you?
You look like you like me.
Do you understand?
I don't think it's a good idea.
Let go of my hand.
What's wrong?
Look at me.
Yes.
Open your eyes.
Look at me.
Don't close your eyes.
Give me your drool.
What's wrong with you?
Get on my face.
What's wrong?
Give me your drool.
Come on.
Give me your waist.
What's wrong?
You like it, don't you?
Give me your waist.
What's wrong?
Don't do that.
Give me your butt.
I'll let go of your hand.
Look at me.
I don't want to look at you.
Stay still.
I'm sick.
I'm sick, too.
What are you doing?
You don't care, do you?
Let me do it.
I can't do it.
Come here.
Get up.
What's wrong?
Look at me.
I'll let go of your hand.
Hurry up.
I want to see your back.
I'll let go of your hand.
Come on.
That's good.
Move slowly.
Move.
What should I do?
I told you not to move.
What's wrong?
I'll let go of your hand.
I let go of your hand.
What should I do?
I'll let go of your hand.
Give me your hand.
That's good.
You're a good girl.
I'll let go of your hand.
I can't do it.
Stay still.
That's good.
I'll let go of your hand.
Come here.
That was just a warm-up.
Stand up.
I can do it.
Stay still.
That's good.
You're a good girl.
I'll show you how good I am.
I'll let go of your hand.
That's good.
You're a good girl.
I'll let go of your hand.
That's good.
Good girl.
I'll let go of your hand.
Stay still.
That's good.
I'll let go of your hand.
Are you still angry?
Here you are.
Take it.
Rub it.
Here you are.
I'll do it.
Are you ready?
Do you want me to do more?
Here you are.
Show me your face.
You look good.
You look like you like sex.
Here you are.
Do you feel good?
Do you want more?
Take it all.
Here you are.
I'm sorry.
You can still do it.
I'll continue.
I'll be out soon.
Do you want me to do more?
Here you are.
Take it all.
You can still do it.
I'll continue.
I told you.
I have a strong desire for sex.
You can still do it.
Here you are.
Take it all.
How do you feel?
I'm sorry.
You look good.
I'll show you.
Turn your head.
You can still do it.
Look at me.
You look good.
Here you are.
Raise your legs.
I'll show you.
Do you like me?
Here you are.
What's wrong with you?
You look like an ostrich.
Did you say that?
You can still do it.
Here you are.
I'll show you.
You can still do it.
That's all for this week.
I still have a debt.
I'll pay you back next weekend.
By the way...
Did you feel something?
No, I didn't.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Really?
I'll call you later.
Did you sleep again?
Who was on the phone?
I talked to Oshima.
He said he would reduce my debt.
I can't pay you back all yet.
But it will be easier.
I see.
That's good.
Are you okay?
Talk to me.
I'll pay you back by tomorrow.
But you have to pay me back by today.
Do it right.
Yes, sir.
Should I explain?
What is that?
Let's make a deal!
Go on, kiss me!
Kiss!
Here.
It's now.
Oh...
Good.
Right...
Good job.
Well done.
What do you think?
It's cold.
That's right. That's a good eye.
Look this way.
That's right.
Move your legs.
Please be comfortable.
That's right.
Let me see.
It's out.
It's not enough yet.
Let me see.
Use your hands.
More.
That's right.
You did a good job.
Your debt is settled.
You don't have to come back next week.
Good job.
Welcome back, Aya.
Didn't you drink alcohol today?
I just got a call from Oshima.
Shakiya is gone.
I don't know why, but I don't have to pay him back.
I see.
I'm sorry for bothering you.
I'll start by taking care of myself.
Good luck.
Oshima
I have to polish my sword before my father comes back.
I don't know when he'll come back.
Oh, it's you.
Did you forget something?
No.
My body is hot.
My body is hot and I can't sleep.
It's because of you.
No.
I don't think it's good for you to do that.
Please.
If my father finds out...
No.
If my father finds out, he'll kill me.
Please.
Can you keep it a secret from my father?
No.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
No.
Scuffle.
Get up.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Ah ah ah ah ah ah Ah ah
Ah ah ah
Hmm
PLEASE!!
More!!
Raiko...
Ai-chan
Ai-kun
Are you okay?
I love you.
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
I'll get you out of there.
I'm going to help you get out of there.
I love you.
I'm scared.
I'm happy.
How do you feel?
I'm scared.
I'm going to laugh.
I'm happy.
Dad!
What's going on?
It's not what you think.
What do you mean?
It's not enough.
I see.
I understand.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Hurry up.
How many shots did you take?
Three shots.
Did you do it without your parents' permission?
Sit down.
Pretend you didn't see it.
I'm sorry.
Is it not enough?
It's not enough.
I see.
Go to bed.
It's the first time I've seen such a beautiful woman.
It's not enough, is it?
Go to bed.
It's not enough.
Get up.
What a beautiful woman.
It's not enough.
Do you want another shot?
Please.
It's not enough.
It's cold.
If you come up, I'll stop you with my tongue.
I'll stop you with my tongue.
Tongue.
More.
Do you feel this?
I don't feel it.
Do you want more?
Please give me more.
Open your nose.
What?
Show me your face.
Please.
Open your nose.
You want me to hit you, don't you?
Please hit me.
Please.
I'll hit you.
You're a good girl.
You're a good girl, too.
That's right.
It's cold.
Do you want me to hit you?
You feel good.
Don't close your eyes.
I'm sorry.
I'll close my eyes.
I'm not done yet.
Please give me more.
How many times do you want me to hit you?
I want to hit you a lot.
It's cold.
I want to hit you more.
I'll hold you.
It's cold.
Don't do that.
Please stay there.
Stay there.
I won't stop.
It's cold.
Don't do that.
Are you still cold?
Do you still want me to hit you?
Please give me more.
I didn't know you liked this.
I'm going to hit you again.
Spread your legs.
Like this.
More.
This is good.
You look good.
It's cold.
It feels good.
I'm going to hit you again.
It's cold.
I won't stop.
Do you still want me to hit you?
How do you feel?
It feels good.
I'm going to hit you again.
It's cold.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.