add 60ml of soy milk
add 20ml of sesame oil
finally add 60ml of wine
turn off the seasoning, and then adjust the flavor
How's the fried egg? Is it done?
Yeah, it's done.
That was quick. I was waiting for this.
Thank you.
Itadakimasu.
Oh, right.
Yeah?
How was your weekend?
It was good.
How about you?
Can you make an appointment to go to a movie on the weekend?
I don't mind, but why?
I have a business trip.
Again?
Sorry.
I don't mind if it's work, but you don't have to worry about it.
Yeah.
Itadakimasu.
Ms. Nakano.
Hello.
What are you doing here?
It started raining suddenly, so I was taking shelter in the rain.
Oh, I see.
I haven't seen you in a suit for a long time.
I couldn't have a remote meeting today, so I came to work.
Oh, I see.
A suit of a man is cool, isn't it?
Is it?
But you're used to seeing me in a suit, aren't you?
Maybe so.
What's for dinner?
Oh, I see.
I was thinking of making meat and potatoes today.
Meat and potatoes? Sounds good.
Why don't you ask your girlfriend to make it for you?
I don't have a girlfriend.
If I did, I wouldn't have bought a convenience store bento.
That's a convenience store criticism.
Maybe so.
Oh, it's starting to rain, so I'll go.
Would you like to take an umbrella with you?
No, it's okay.
You don't have to say that.
We're neighbors, so it's okay.
Then, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Good morning.
I'll text you when I get to the hotel over there.
Okay.
Be careful of the tap water.
If you're going to drink it, buy mineral water.
I know.
I'm going.
Are you on a business trip?
Yes, to Hiroshima.
Oh, I see.
Is it breakfast?
What?
That.
Oh, yes.
I'm sorry.
Hmm.
Did you taste it?
No, it's really good.
That's good.
Um...
Why did you invite me to lunch?
Was it a bother?
Oh, no.
It's boring to eat alone.
And...
And what?
You seemed to eat only convenience store food.
That's...
It's a criticism of convenience stores.
Why isn't she here?
Hmm...
I don't know why.
You're so handsome.
You always look at me from the side, don't you?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry to bother you.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Hmm...
Come in.
Excuse me.
Well...
Do you like...
disgusting women?
I don't know.
Then, why did you come here?
Well...
Huh?
Eh?
Well...
It's so hard.
It's no good.
Ouch!
Let me see your tongue.
But...
Ouch!
It's over.
Your nipples are so stiff.
Well, that's...
Wait, wait, wait.
What?
Let me see.
It's fine, isn't it?
You've been staring at this for a while, haven't you?
Well...
What is it?
Can't you answer me?
It's hot.
Do you know how hot it is here?
I don't think I can do this without you.
Don't tell my husband.
Of course I won't.
It's bad for him, too.
You can keep it a secret.
But that's not the problem.
Then what is it?
Don't tell my husband.
It's hot.
It's so hot.
Ouch!
That's no good.
Hey...
You're sweating so much.
Touch me.
It's hot.
I can't touch you.
Are you sure you don't want me to touch you?
Wait, wait, wait.
What is it?
I threw it away.
What are you hiding?
You're so stiff.
Were you this stiff when you were having sex with your husband?
I love you.
You're sweating so much.
You're so big.
It's hot.
I can't put it in my mouth.
It's the first time I've swallowed such a big penis.
It's hot.
Touch me.
Why?
Do you want to see my boobs?
You want to see them, right?
Yes.
It's hot.
Come on.
Lick me.
It's not enough.
Do more.
It's hot.
Show me your tongue.
I love this.
It's hot.
Your nipples are stiff.
Lick me, too.
It's hot.
No.
Lick me.
It's hot.
Lick me, too.
I can't.
Lick me.
It's been a long time since I had such a big penis.
It's hot.
I'm going to cry.
I'm going to go home.
It's not good.
Can you go home like this?
It's hot.
Don't try to go home.
Can you see it?
It was very humid in here.
Come on.
Come closer.
It's hot.
Use your tongue.
I'm going to cry.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Be quiet.
Shut up.
I can't.
It's hot.
It's hard.
It's amazing.
I've never had such a big penis.
It's hot.
It's hard here and there.
Don't do that.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It's in there.
It's hot.
It's very hard.
Stop it.
It's hot.
This time, from behind.
From behind?
It's hot.
It's hard.
I'm going to close my eyes.
It's hot.
It's moving.
Can I do it one more time?
It's hot.
Come here.
Do it harder.
Harder.
It's hot.
It's hard.
More.
Move your hips.
That's right.
I love this.
It's hot.
It's still hard.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
It's tingling.
It's getting tight in there.
Can you see it?
I can feel it.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
Slowly.
I want to touch you slowly.
I want to feel you.
It's hot.
It's getting hot.
I know you're scared.
I'm sorry.
Don't stop.
It hurts.
It's hot.
I can't stand it.
It's intense.
It's hot.
I've known my husband since high school.
We got married three years after graduation.
I came here with my husband's deposit.
Is that so?
I don't have any experience other than my husband.
It's hot.
So...
I didn't imagine having sex with other people would feel so good.
It's hot.
I always felt your gaze from the other side of the window.
Why don't we do a lot of it until the day my husband comes back?
It's hot.
Hello?
Good morning.
What's wrong?
Come to the window.
The window?
Okay.
It's hot.
Men get up early in the morning, don't they?
Are you getting up now?
Yes.
Just a little.
I don't want to hear that.
It's hot.
Please listen to me.
Can you hear this sound?
Is this a body?
This is what I do when I'm not around.
I'm not a pervert.
Then...
Please come with me.
It's hot.
Are you all right?
I'm really wet here.
It's hot.
I'm...
I'm going to die.
It's hot.
Can you see my butt?
Can you see it?
It's hot.
I'm embarrassed.
Look at this.
It's very hot here.
Please listen to the sound.
It's hot.
Can you hear me?
Can you hear the sound of a cat?
I can hear the sound of a cat.
It's hot.
It's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Can you come here and lick me?
I can't.
What is it?
Did you call me?
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
Please give me a soft kiss.
Wait a minute.
I made a mistake.
Take your time.
I'm sorry.
Do you like it?
Take your time.
I'm sorry.
Did you feel stiff here?
Of course.
You showed me a hole.
How did I look like a pervert?
You were very nice.
I'm sorry.
Don't move your legs.
You've grown so much.
I'm sorry.
Why are you on my pants?
I want you to lick me more.
Please lick me more.
I can't.
I can't stand it.
Please lick me more.
It's stained.
It came out of the middle.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't say that.
It came out of the middle.
I'm embarrassed.
Can't I lick you?
I can't.
You've grown up.
But...
I can't stand it.
You're such a pain in the neck.
You've been working so hard since this morning.
You won't be able to work remotely today, will you?
Today is Saturday.
I don't care about that.
Ouch!
Come on. Let's walk this way.
No, wait. What are you doing?
Come on, come closer to the window.
Ouch!
Can you imagine?
You were looking at me from the other side of the window.
You might be looking at yourself, too.
Come on, imagine it.
Ouch!
If you can't imagine it, let's open it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Why not?
I was looking at you with my eyes closed.
You might have been seen by the other residents.
You should be a pervert like him.
No, I can't be seen.
You're a pervert.
No!
It's not good to be seen in this way.
You're working so hard.
Okay, okay.
Okay, look this way.
Here.
Do you want me to tear this part with my penis?
No, no, no.
You can't do that.
I'm crying.
Look.
I can tear it.
No, no, no.
You really can't do that.
Hey, hey, hey.
You're mean.
I'm not mean.
I'm a pervert.
You didn't even touch my nipples, but they got so hard.
No.
You're mean.
I'm going to puke.
You can't do that.
You're going to puke, aren't you?
Okay.
Do you want me to put this in?
I want to put it in.
Do you really want to put it in?
Yes.
Please.
Do you want to go back to the futon?
Yes.
You want me to put it in, don't you?
You can't take it out here.
Please.
You can't.
I can't?
Lie down quietly.
If you really want to put it in.
You're going to put it in?
You're going to put it in.
You can't yet.
How is it?
My nipples are hard, aren't they?
If you rub it like that...
Rubbing feels good, too.
If you rub it like that, it'll come out.
You can't.
You want to put it in, don't you?
You can't. It'll really come out.
You can't.
It'll come out like this.
It's coming out.
You can't yet.
You want to put it in, don't you?
You want to put it in me again, don't you?
I want to.
Then hold on.
Hold on.
Not yet.
I can't.
You can't.
You can do it.
You couldn't do it.
You can't.
Please put it in.
If you can hold on, you can put it in.
I don't want to just rub it.
Hold on.
I can't hold on.
I can't do this.
You can put it in.
You can't.
You can't do this.
You're becoming more and more of a pervert.
I can't do this.
I can't.
You can't.
You can't do this.
You want to put it in me, don't you?
You want to put it in, don't you?
It's hot.
Please lick me more.
Please lick me properly.
You're becoming more and more of a pervert.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's hard to get up.
The taste of the Manjiru I made is amazing.
You're becoming more and more of a pervert.
I'm a pervert, aren't I?
You're a pervert.
You're becoming more and more of a pervert.
Hold on.
Please make me a little harder.
It feels good.
Please stick to me more than yesterday.
It's hot.
Please make me a little harder.
It's about to come out.
Please stick to me more than yesterday.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't help it.
I haven't put it in yet.
I'm sorry.
You can still do it, can't you?
I want to be more of a pervert.
It's hot.
You...
Yes.
I see.
Okay.
Call me when you have time to go home.
Yes.
Bye.
What's wrong?
Are you up late today?
I was going to stay one more night.
But I finished work earlier than I thought.
I was told that the expenses were reduced.
So I came back without staying at the hotel.
If the expenses were reduced, wouldn't the cancellation fee be charged on the same day?
I was told that the expenses were reduced.
So I stayed at the hotel for one night.
I'm a pervert.
I see.
I've eaten.
Is the bath open?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Are you sure you can stay here?
I'm fine.
I told you that I want to be more of a pervert.
But...
And I couldn't stay at the hotel earlier.
I'm fine.
My husband...
I left a letter at home saying that I'm going shopping.
I see.
Won't he be worried if I'm late?
I don't think he'll be worried.
I don't think he'll think that I'm doing this.
I'm sorry.
Touch me more.
I want you to lick me.
I'm sorry.
I want you to lick me more.
Don't do this to me.
I'm sorry.
I want you to lick me more.
Don't do this to me.
I'm sorry.
I want you to lick me more.
I want you to feel better.
I'm sorry.
I want you to lick me more.
Stand up.
I'm sorry.
I want you to lick me more.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
I want you to lick me more.
Can you open the curtain?
That's not good.
It's okay.
Wait a minute.
Can't you see?
I'm nervous.
Are you okay?
Keep an eye on me.
I can see you.
I don't think he knows I'm here.
I'm nervous.
I want you to lick me more.
He's over there.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
I'm so nervous.
I'm nervous.
That's not enough.
He doesn't know I'm here.
I'm nervous.
I want you to lick me more.
That's not enough.
I can't believe you're licking me.
I'm sorry.
You made me a pervert.
I can't speak because of your hands.
I'm nervous.
Do you feel like this?
That's not enough.
I want you to lick me more.
I'm sorry.
That's not enough.
You made me a pervert.
I can't believe you're licking me.
That's not enough.
I'm nervous.
You made me a pervert.
I can't speak because of your hands.
I'm nervous.
I want you to lick me more.
How do you want me to lick you?
Come on.
I want you to lick me more.
I can't stand it anymore.
I couldn't do it earlier.
That's not it.
I don't want you to rub me like that.
I want you to put it in.
Please put it in your belly.
Say it out loud.
I can hear you.
You want to put it in, right?
I want to put it in.
I can hear you.
Don't you have to put it in?
I want to put it in your belly.
I've been wanting to do this for a long time.
I'll put it in your belly.
I didn't know it would go this far.
It's not over yet.
What are you talking about?
If you're going to say it, say it out loud.
Put it in your belly.
I want to put it in your belly.
Look at this.
Look at me putting it in my belly.
More.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'll put it in your belly.
Maiko, you can't do this.
I didn't notice it at all.
Please be quiet.
I don't want to.
I don't want to hold back my voice.
Put it in your belly.
It's okay.
I didn't notice it at all.
It's okay, isn't it?
It's really bad.
Please come here.
I didn't notice it at all.
Please be quiet.
I can't do it anymore.
I didn't notice it at all.
It feels good.
It feels really good.
Please drink this from the back.
It's good.
Please don't disturb me.
I'll do it.
I'm sweating a lot.
It's hot.
You shouldn't nip your wrists like that.
Lie down.
I don't know if it's sweat or sweat.
I feel like I'm going to lose my voice.
Get me out of here.
I want to receive a warrior other than that person.
I don't know if it's sweat or sweat.
I'm going to the gym tonight, so please come.
All right.
I'm off.
Have a good day.
Yes.
I saw my husband go out.
Thank you for your viewing.