What will we do on the next wedding anniversary? Do you eat outside?
You don’t have to do anything, right?
The party party was with you.
I would like to eat sushi, but you prefer to eat one of the two, you know?
Open up wine at home.
The lawyer is me.
I am always grateful.
And this, this
This is a new type of insurance that we have in our company.
I think you should write too.
I forgot about money.
I always rely on you.
thanks
Oh, I have come
This is this.
Next time in our company.
The ticket for the animal has come out.
This is Riley, and you should go in too.
Okay, but this is fine.
A little trouble.
Tell me anything.
Talk about money.
Do it to you.
I want you to pretend to be my boyfriend.
What do you mean?
No, this is my mother.
You know too.
My father died in a high speed.
Were you insured?
No, it’s not too delicate.
Okay okay though.
Her mother brought her to marry.
If not, I would be able to meet you.
Something will appear in the eye.
I told him there were some people I met with too.
So, go together and make noise.
I still don’t want to get married.
I am going to get to the girl I am with now and I am not interested in it.
I thought if it was Rio, I would be happy.
But if it is good then what do you do then?
Well, if something goes wrong, then we split up.
It is planned, right?
If you cheat once, you will not say anything for six months.
Well, I am fine.
It looks like a drama, I too.
It is a Korean drama.
Sorry, I will help.
I think you should marry the girlfriend now.
He is bad, he is bad character.
It is bad.
Because you know you too.
You are pretty, but you are not married.
is
I know, but I’ll go home with my insurance.
Please introduce me to five people who want to come in.
A lot of?
Then three people.
Three of them.
Four people.
It is increasing.
5 of them.
Go back to Cousin.
If you introduce me, I will tell you everything myself.
I will try hard. thanks.
Please take it.
Sorry to you, Madame.
at all.
Welcome to.
Sorry to.
Oh, in the Bourbon 6. please.
I was struck.
What is the case?
I said I was still working, and I would come out later.
Oh yeah, that is so.
Yes, I’ve been waiting for you, look at this.
What this?
set up.
My mother, my mother, because she will hear.
Yes to.
A book written.
We met about a year ago.
I was introduced to the wife of Casper.
Come out yourself.
Because it is easier to talk.
We go on a date three times.
He says he is going to marry.
Yes, yes is it.
I want two children.
If possible, boys and girls.
This is Rio.
Rio is called Yu.
It is detailed.
Lies are important in detail.
How many children does Rio want?
Stop playing theatre suddenly.
Two, a boy and a girl.
I too
Will Rio get married to me?
I want to marry Yue.
Celebrate your wedding anniversary well.
of course
Are you not celebrating?
We’ve been together since we were a student and married for five years.
So, is this not embarrassing?
No, I’ll know if you kick.
Yes yes yes
Oh yes
This is
What happened? this.
The engagement ring.
Is he not quite tall?
Oh, I’ll find out it’s fake.
help me.
Wait a little.
Give me
I will return it when it is finished.
This time I am.
Okay is?
thanks to
Okay, it is fine.
Is it today?
Yes
Not too late.
I think we’ll just meet and talk.
I am sorry for far away.
Thanks for your child, and for coming here.
Now I will bring tea.
Mom, I will do it.
Okay, just sit down.
Thanks to.
Because you are a guest.
Please go
If you want, eat sweets too.
Yes, thank you very much.
Yes, even today
If you can get your hand in your father before.
Thanks to.
Yes is
I am modified.
Her mother is Erico.
I call it Asahi.
No to
How did you meet Lulu?
We have a common friend.
by presenting it.
That is a case.
I often came here in high school.
friend of his wife.
What are you doing, Casey?
Healthy house
The house?
So, are you going to get married?
Well then then.
You really want to get this ring.
I thought I could see the ring.
Do you like children?
Come in, Mommy, and talk about it.
Because your father died suddenly.
I won’t die until I see my grandson’s face.
I want to have two.
Say a boy and a girl.
Not well is.
I bought a good drink today.
Who can drink?
We came in the car today.
You should think that it is so.
I will buy sushi.
No No No No No No
I really want to go home today.
I am going home today.
Why, I’m here so I want to talk about it a little bit.
I’ll bring you a drink, so wait.
Oh yeah, I didn’t know, thank you.
Oh is?
Do you stop?
What is it.
You just don’t have to get back on the train?
It is unnatural, but unnatural.
Is it someone who is there?
Oh yeah yeah yeah?
Well, but will not long people know?
Yes, I understand it.
Yes, yes is yes
I borrowed a bathroom and I thank you for the towel.
I am sorry to have to get dressed up.
No, this is here.
It was the first time a couple went to the fishing port.
Well, it really feels like that.
That is not not?
No to no.
Yes, not to
No to?
Yes no no
No to no.
No to
Really not?
No to no.
No to
Do not look.
Do not wear underwear.
Because I didn’t bring clothes.
by
Sorry to
Do not look.
No to
Feel good.
Feel good
Feel good  Feel good
Very beautiful.
Do not look.
Oh no no
Coolly cool
Yes
turn
Me is
No to
Rio, the face is cute.
Is that calling not hard?
Rio, this face is cute.
hurtly
Feels good?
It feels good.
No to no.
Feel badly
No to
No here
No to fuck.
Yes
No to
Oh yeah yeah yeah
by
Oh yeah
Yes
and
Who is someone.
Oh is
also
Cyberpunk is
I hear the children’s voices.
Oh oh oh
Oh yeah yeah.
Yes is
No to
Oh yeah
I am hungry.
son
Go to home.
I was awake.
How was it?
What is?
You pretended to be a lover, right?
Oh, I think it went well.
The mother of the girl was also pleased.
Let us go.
Okay then.
It is not really good to lie like this.
Yes, yes is
I want Rio to pretend to be a little boy.
My mother is going to Tokyo.
I want to see Rio again.
Book a hotel lunch.
Better stop with it.
Be honest, I lied.
No, I can’t say it now.
You and your insurance.
I will put her in my mother.
When is?
Saturday this week.
Have something planned?
Oh well
There is nothing.
Anniversary of marriage.
Oh yeah
It was daytime, and I had no plans to go anywhere.
My mom, take insurance.
Yes, of course
I will explain it well, because I
Okay okay, I understand.
Sorry, let me wait.
Let wait.
Sorry, I have come out.
Hello, I am pleased, thank you.
I have a job in the morning and I can’t go home.
Take more lunch with you.
I am glad, thank you.
well was
You were busy, right?
Totally totally
Sorry to
Thanks to.
My lunch buffet is delicious.
Yes, I am looking forward to.
It feels good.
Yes
by
Oh yeah
No to
Toughly
by
No to
Feels good?
pleased
Liked it
sweetly
Is this feeling good?
greatly
I like it.
Is it already fine?
I too
This is this.
Are you hungry?
Liked
I was hungry.
A lot of stuff.
No to
Oh, I like
go here
I was hungry.
Full of stomach.
Feels good?
Very good feeling.
That is a lie.
that or
Feels good?
OK is
2nd
Oh yeah
by
OK is.
Wake up.
I was hungry.
It hurts.
It is broken.
Yes, he is
Oh, and the feeling?
Oh, it is heavy
Want to enter?
Okay well.
I entered.
Oh, greatly
by ski
by
and now?
Oh well
Go to the back.
Ok to.
I want to do it from behind.
Oh, put it in.
I want you to sleep.
No longer is problem.
and now,
Important is
The Ceu
Sorry to sorry.
Uely
Prepare to
Oh yeah yeah yeah
No well.
No to
It feels good.
I am happy.
well is.
Why are you with us?
wwwww
Sorry about the wedding anniversary.
I should apologize to Mr. Kashmir.
Certainly.
But I am also compassionate.
On the wedding anniversary, I borrowed my wife.
Is he wrong too?
Well, that too.
I touched too much.
Okay is.
Too much touch.
If you think of the best,
Only one water.
No, Mary, let it go.
Fuck it full.
and go.
No to
It hurts there?
Oh well?
What is? Put your feet here.
Oh what?
Are you looking too much?
Okay, just a little.
Come to.
Show me all the time.
I am ashamed.
Do not look like that.
Always only
That is?
No longer hate.
No more, I am ashamed.
What? so what?
No longer is.
Shamefully
Do not look like that.
A little more, 10 minutes.
and then
Seeing too much.
Shamefully
Yes is
No longer
Stop watching too much.
No to
It is over.
by
Have you shown me water?
Not see?
Yes, to exchange
You are getting very well.
See now.
Feels good?
It feels good.
is full of.
Just felt good?
Feel good
Oh that is.
Feels good?
Feel good
up to here.
So far here?
Yes
Feel good
These are
Oh well fuck.
Feels good?
pleased
by Brist
softly
What is it.
What this
Do not feel good?
It is definitely feeling good.
Yes
Come to.
What happened?
No to
What is?
from today
What happened?
I want to get water.
Did you just get out?
Okay is.
Eat it.
OK is.
Do not leave.
Oh Oh Oh
Oh that
I like it.
Do it, Pepper
Feel good
Oh Oh Oh
No to
Oh yeah yeah
Yes, thank you very much.
Yes, here it is okay.
Good to be.
Even if I die.
I can give these kids money.
Do not say ugly things.
Yes to you, mother.
If these children were born.
I have a college insurance, so you will be happy again.
It is still early.
So, you and your wife, Casey.
You are your friend?
What if we eat together next time?
No, it is a bit impossible.
Oh is?
Is it so?
No...
What is?
No, you are good at theatre.
Yes to?
It seemed like they were really dating.
You got a contract, right?
Sorry, let me wait.
Sorry, but I came far away.
I got a contract, okay.
I will send you home.
I just want to get you down in Shinjuku.
I will go to the company and process the documents.
Yes
No longer
Well, in both of the bedrooms.
OK to
Casey is more than people.
The contract is more important.
After giving it a favor.
It doesn’t matter what your wife feels.
Don’t pretend to be a lover, but a lover.
From now on.
You have to pretend to someone else.
Yes
Was it filmed?
I was photographed.
Oh yeah, you did it.
Too big no.
This is too big.
properly
Yes
Look at a little.
Or a cute person.
pleased
Yes
difficulty
No, look at me here.
Yes
Touch the hand.
I too
Stubble
Shamefully
Extreme is
It is growing.
by Pichopo
Feel good
I want to eat.
OK is.
Fuck it.
You look very good.
Shame on me.
Feels good.
It feels good.
I was attracted.
You can drink water.
hurtly
I also drank.
I drank it.
You cannot drink.
Oh yeah
Want to lick?
Feels good?
Why look at me like this?
by
Feels good?
Feel good
He is hungry.
OK is.
Are you happy? feelings?
Yes
Feel too much.
This is feeling.
No, it is damn.
No to it.
Feels good?
What first?
You know, you listen.
Oh yeah
Oh yeah, I know
Go here, here
Oh yeah
Oh, I like it.
Oh well
Oh yeah
Oh yeah yeah
It is there.
by KY
Oh not
by CHI
No to No.
by KY
Oh well fuck.
No to
No to fuck.
by KY
No to
Do you want to sleep?
Go to sleep?
No to?
OK is.
Full of it.
Very well sleep.
Oh well fucking.
Feel good
I will enter.
Put it in.
It hurts.
Oh well fucking.
Feel good
Feels good?
Very good feeling.
I feel good too.
I remember the most beautiful thing.
The most favorite.
by
No to
Try a chip for the staff.
Give up!
Have a good.
Try a little bit of the cane.
Oh, shit, it feels good.
I cannot do.
I backed up.
OK is.
pleased
I too
Historically
No to
Boom is
Oh yeah yeah yeah
money
Re is
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh!
Do not clean.
Oh, oh
Chech
by
followed me.
No to