I can't see the cats anymore.
I started moving around Latte who was bored with the tree
We played again
I'm going to sleep now.
This is the limit.
That's right.
But it was a little cramped.
It's enough if we live together.
That's right.
The rent was very cheap and it was a good deal.
Yeah.
I want to work hard together, save money, and have a big house soon.
That's right.
Let's do our best.
Yeah.
Huh?
Which one is it?
I'm going out for a minute.
Yeah.
Dad.
Long time no see.
I thought it was about time to move.
I brought you a moving card.
Thank you.
It's a small room.
I can't help it.
Now we decided to save money together to buy a house.
My home?
I see.
Then I have to do my best.
I'll do my best.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Thank you.
Dad, please have some tea.
I'm sorry.
It's a little cramped.
Don't rush me.
Here you are.
My home?
Huh?
I see.
It's a little cramped.
I think it's okay.
Young people like that.
If we make it bigger, the rent will be higher.
That's right.
My home is going to be far away.
I think it's cheaper if we make it bigger.
It's been a long time since I saw you.
It's been a while since the wedding.
I see.
Kenji, you haven't been home at all.
How have you been?
I'm sorry.
I was thinking of going home, but I was busy with work.
You haven't been home since your mother died.
You should go out sometimes.
I see.
But I'm going to be home soon.
I'm looking forward to it.
You too.
I see.
Yanai, can I talk to you for a minute?
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
No, I have to work hard.
I see.
You said you were going to buy my home.
By the way, at today's meeting,
Yanai, I've decided your pay.
Really?
Thank you.
Keep up the good work.
Yes, I will.
I see.
Karen is really amazing.
I know.
You should do your best, too.
I can't lose to her.
Hey, open the door.
Is it dad?
Hey, are you there?
I'll be back soon.
Okay.
Dad, what's the matter?
I got a lot of vegetables in the neighborhood.
It's for you.
Thank you very much.
I heard you were saving money.
I wanted to help you a little.
Thank you very much.
Would you like to have dinner with me?
Can I?
I'd love to.
It was delicious.
I know.
His cooking is really good.
Karen, I'm sorry.
I saved money, but you made me a meal.
It's okay because it's not a big meal for one person.
You're kind.
Thank you.
Karen.
Dad.
I happened to see you when I was passing by.
I see.
Are you working at this time?
Yes.
That's great.
That's right.
I'm doing my best because I can get a hand when I work overtime.
Is that so?
Is Kenji at home today?
Kenji is also working overtime today.
I see.
Kenji is working overtime.
I'm in trouble.
What's the matter?
I got a lot of rice from my friend.
I was going to share it with him.
But I'm old and I'm not popular.
I was wondering if Kenji would come to pick me up.
Is that so?
That's right.
If you don't mind, can you come to my house?
Are you popular with me?
Don't worry. I'm popular with you.
I see.
That's good.
Please sit next to me.
I'm home.
This is it.
Dad, thank you so much.
Don't mention it.
I can't eat it all by myself.
You're going to save money, aren't you?
Yes.
I've been saving a lot of money lately.
Take it.
Okay.
It's heavy.
How is it?
I might be a little heavy.
I see.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I wonder if Kenji will come to pick me up.
I think he'll be fine.
Really?
You don't have to push yourself.
I came all the way here.
I see.
It's good to get it, but it's really troublesome.
You should have made it smaller.
Are you okay?
I can't lift it at all.
I see.
I can't help it.
Dad, what are you doing?
I don't know.
Stop it.
I can't stand it.
Dad, what are you doing?
It's my first time.
I can't stand it.
Do you know what you're doing?
I know.
I can't stop.
I can't help it.
Your buttocks were really good.
Your boobs were really good.
I can't help it.
It's the best.
Dad, I can't help it.
Your buttocks were really good.
I can't help it.
It's the best.
Dad.
Stop it.
I can't help it.
Please.
Please stop.
No, please stop.
You're the best, Kana.
Kana.
Please stop.
What are you talking about?
It's too late.
What's this?
What's this buckle?
Why?
Please stop.
Are you inviting me?
No, I'm not.
Look, your panties are rolled up.
Kana.
I can't hide it.
No, you can't.
Please stop.
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
I don't know.
You're the best.
Please stop.
I'll clean it up.
It's okay.
You're the best.
Hey.
No.
Doesn't it feel good?
Please stop.
Please.
No.
My tongue hurts.
Really.
Please stop.
It's okay.
You're the best.
I'll clean it up.
It's okay.
Please stop.
You're the best.
No.
Please stop.
Are you feeling it now?
I don't feel it.
You're lying.
Stop it.
You must be tired from all the work you've done.
Is that so?
No, I'm not.
Stop it, please.
I'm sorry.
I'm waiting for your answer.
Please.
Stop it.
Stop it, please.
I can't stop it, Karen.
Stop it.
Give me a bell.
It'll feel better if you give me a bell.
No.
I'll tell you how to do it.
Give me a bell.
That's right.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll tell you how to do it.
You don't know how to do it, do you?
No, I don't.
Stop it.
Do you feel better now?
No, I don't.
Stop it.
Stop it, please.
I can't stop it.
Give me a bell, please.
Stop it, please.
How is it?
I don't want to do it.
Why not?
You've been doing it for a long time.
You were licked by a dog.
You licked my tail.
What would you do if a dog bit you?
I don't want to do it.
You don't want to do it, do you?
Then it's a secret between us.
Look.
You've been doing it for a long time.
You feel good, don't you?
Hey.
You still don't want to do it?
I don't want to do it.
But if you tell Kenji about this, it'll be a big problem.
Yes.
Right?
Then let's keep it a secret until the end.
No.
Come on.
Stop it, please.
Look.
It's in your mouth.
No.
Please.
What are you going to do if it's in your mouth?
Then, Akane...
No.
It's already in your mouth once.
Look.
Please stop it.
Akane.
Your pussy is the best.
No.
Stop it.
Dad.
I've been alone since I got sick.
I was lonely and I couldn't stand it.
No.
Stop it.
Dad.
You don't feel good anymore, do you?
You're not feeling well.
No.
Stop it.
You're lonely, aren't you?
No.
Stop it.
Don't look at me like that.
Do you hate me?
I'm accepting you.
No, I really don't.
Your pussy is the best.
Stop it.
You have a nice butt.
I love it.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
I really don't want to do it.
You're already in it.
Let's do it until you feel better.
Stop it.
I really don't want to do it.
Come here.
Stop it.
You have a nice face.
I've always wanted to be like you.
Why?
I don't want to.
I don't want to be like you.
Stop it.
It's not over yet.
Let me see.
It's messed up.
I can't stand you.
Stop it.
How is it?
Give me your tongue.
Stop it.
I'm going to kill you.
I'll let you go.
It's a waste to put it out here.
After all, it's here.
No, please stop it.
Please stop it for a moment.
Please stop it.
It's a waste to put it out here.
No, please stop it.
Please stop it for a moment.
Please stop it.
It's a waste to put it out here.
It's a waste to cry.
I've been waiting for this for a long time.
I can't stand it.
Please stop it.
Karen.
If Kenji finds out about this...
You'll understand, won't you?
It's a secret between us.
You're really serious, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
But it's not good to work too hard.
You're married.
You should go home early once in a while.
I'm fine.
I can still work hard.
Forget it.
You should go home early today.
I understand.
Thank you.
I've been waiting for you.
Sit next to me.
I don't want to.
I'll tell Kenji about what happened last time.
Please don't do that.
Then sit next to me.
I can't today.
Kenji said he'd be back soon.
I don't care.
Come on.
Let's go.
Please let me go home.
Kenji may be waiting for me at home.
You don't have time.
You should go home by car.
I don't want to.
Let's go to a hotel.
It'll take time.
I can't.
Let's do it here.
I'll finish it as soon as possible.
I can't.
Let's go back.
You don't have time.
I can't do it here.
You can do it here.
You're a good girl.
You're excited, aren't you?
I can't.
It's okay.
It's your first time, isn't it?
Yes.
You're amazing.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't.
Why?
Someone will come.
I can't.
You're enjoying it, aren't you?
If you want to go home early, you have to talk more.
It's not easy.
You're amazing.
I'll put it in your big boob.
Do you want me to go home early?
If so, you have to talk more.
I can't.
I want to go home early, but I want you to enjoy it.
Put your wings in there.
Show me a better face.
Look at my face.
Tell me more.
Do you like me?
I don't like you.
Why are you doing this?
That's right.
Look at my face.
Tell me more.
You're good at this.
Dad, tell me more.
I know.
It felt good.
There's a tissue over there.
Karen, do you remember?
I'm on a business trip.
I said I was on a business trip for two days from tomorrow.
I remember.
It's sad that I can't see Karen for two days.
Karen, are you listening?
You haven't been well lately, have you?
Did something happen?
Nothing.
I'm just a little tired.
I see.
You're off tomorrow, aren't you?
Take a good rest tomorrow.
Get in the car.
Please stop.
Let's have fun today.
I'm glad to see you again today.
You've been waiting for me all day, haven't you?
No, I haven't.
Please stop.
I haven't been to the prefectural office yet, have I?
No, you haven't.
That's right.
I'm on my way home from shopping.
What are you doing today?
I'm on a business trip.
Are you on a business trip?
I see.
I'm lonely.
I wish I was around when you need someone.
I met you by chance today.
Shall we go for a drive somewhere?
No.
Why not?
I know you feel bored to go home alone.
You won't have anyone with you when you go for a drive.
Shall we go for a drive?
I don't want to.
Let's go to a good restaurant.
Don't look like that.
You should look a little happy.
We met like this today.
I don't want to.
Please don't do it here.
It's okay.
Kenji won't come back to the office.
But...
It's better than doing it by car.
What if Kenji finds out about this?
It's okay.
He's a fool.
I don't want to.
How's Kenji doing lately?
It's none of your business.
I'll do something better than Kenji.
He is listening to me.
It's better to help him at least once.
If you get well soon, you can go home, right?
Do you feel good?
Your nipples are getting harder.
I want to hear your good voice.
Show me your beautiful body.
Do you feel good?
I don't feel good.
But I understand.
Show me your beautiful body.
I'll take this, too.
Please make me feel good.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to sleep.
Do you want to sleep?
I don't want to sleep.
I'm sorry.
Open your mouth and speak.
Do you want me to lick you?
I'm sorry.
Don't say that.
Come here.
Let's lick together.
I'm sorry.
Get up.
Get on my face.
I'm sorry.
Tetsu-kun.
Lie down.
Sit down.
Come on.
I wonder what's inside your belly.
Open your legs more.
Open them with your hands.
Ah...
That's good.
Mm...
Ah...
You're still in a bad mood.
It's in.
Ah...
I'm sorry.
It's too late.
What is it?
Do you want to lick my butt?
Mm...
Ah...
You'll want to lick it, won't you?
Mm...
Ah...
Look.
Look at me.
Ah...
What do you think?
Mm?
Mm...
Ah...
You want to smell Galeano's good smell more?
Mm?
Mm.
If you don't go, you won't be able to go home.
He won't come home anyway, right?
If that's the case, have fun.
He's so stupid.
He won't understand.
Stop it.
We're already having sex.
We've been on several dates.
Stop it.
Look at me.
Karin.
Go to him.
Go to your father.
Father.
Look at me.
It's the best.
Father.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You're shaking.
Karin, you're amazing.
You're amazing.
Give me a kiss.
Karin, you're amazing.
You're shaking.
Give me a kiss.
Stop it.
It's okay.
Karin.
Then my father came to pick me up.
You don't have time today, do you?
No.
Then hurry up and end this relationship.
Dad, let's end this relationship.
Don't say that.
You're looking forward to it, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Don't say that.
Let's talk.
Come on.
Give us a lot of milk.
Make me happy.
This voice...
It's hard, isn't it?
Can you show me your boobs?
It doesn't start until you see this.
It's hard, isn't it?
I can't stop.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Touch me a lot.
You know what I mean, don't you?
You want to talk, don't you?
Can you lick my body?
Put out a big one.
Are you doing this?
I'm glad.
It feels good.
How is the honey?
Do you want to lick it soon?
You want to give it back soon, don't you?
I want you to lick it
Look, it's like this
I'll hold it
You're good at kissing
Move your hands more
You have to wash it soon, or you can't go home
Good
Close it while licking
You have a big tongue
It's the best
It's disgusting
In such a small place
Stop licking it
It's painful
Give me a big tongue
It's disgusting
How is it?
Is it delicious?
You're very good
It feels good
I can't stop licking
It's disgusting
Give me a kiss
I can't stop
Do it harder
It feels good
I can't stop
Show me your tongue
It feels good
Did you like it?
Here we are
You don't have to send me anymore
If Kenji suspects...
I told you before
Kenji is calm, so it's okay
I'll send you every time
It's been 3 months since I started to get along with my dad
I was looking forward to it
I've been looking forward to this
It's a farewell party for Karen
But...
If we keep this relationship...
This time with Karen is my life
Karen is having fun, right?
That's...
I'll give you a stimulus that Kenji can't give you
Dad...
Karen...
You're so soft
Dad...
I want to stop dying, but I can't
Is it delicious today?
Dad...
I can't stop
Karen...
I want to sit next to you
Let's sit together
Come on
Open your mouth
I'll give you a stimulus
Dad...
Open your mouth
It's okay.
I'm happy.
It hurts.
I'll kiss you on the lips.
Get on the bed.
It's warm.
Does it feel good?
It hurts.
I'll go with you.
Does it feel good?
It hurts.
It's the best.
Are you going to be late today?
Maybe I'll be late.
I think so.
It's been a while since I've seen a classmate.
Have fun.
You don't have to worry about the house.
I'm always working hard.
You have to take a break from time to time.
Thank you.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm sorry.
What did you say to Kenji?
I told him I was going to have dinner with a high school classmate.
I see.
You and I don't have a bad relationship.
I can't answer that.
You look like you want to have dinner with me.
You're already wet.
You're a bad woman.
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
You're always beautiful.
I'm sorry.
Let's have a lot of fun today.
Okay.
Come on.
I can't help it.
Let's have fun.
I can't help it today.
I can't help it.
Is it delicious?
It's delicious.
Let's sleep together.
Let's sleep here.
I can't help it.
Give me a kiss.
Do you feel good?
Ah ah ah ah Ah ah ah Ah ah
Ah ah ah
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
Today was delicious.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
Is it the best?
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's the best.
It feels good.
We still have time.
Let's have fun.
I'm sorry.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm going shopping.
What are you going to do with that make-up?
I always do it.
You just don't notice it.
I see.
I'll be back soon.
Okay.
I'm sorry.