I've been married to my husband for five years, and I met him at the company where I work now.
I had a hard time getting a job, but my husband wanted me to get a job after I got married.
Are you going home late today?
I think I can go home relatively early today.
I made you breakfast, so eat it.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
You took a long bath.
It's been cold lately, so I have to take a hot bath.
What do you think?
Does it look good on me?
I haven't worn anything like this lately.
What do you think?
I think it's good.
I'm off tomorrow, so I was wondering if I could wear it.
Does that mean you don't have to wear it?
Besides, it's a day off today.
I'm sorry.
It's already past 1 o'clock, so I'm tired today.
You used to flirt with me so much, but you're not interested in me anymore?
No, I'm really tired.
I like you.
But I'll be anxious if I don't do it for a while.
I'm sorry. Let's do it next time.
Good night.
Sexless, which started in the second year of marriage.
I never thought I would be like that, but I haven't had sex with my husband for more than three years.
I don't know if I don't feel the charm of being a woman anymore, but I'm having days of emptiness.
I want to be a woman until I die.
If you're a woman, you should definitely wish so.
There's a lot to look for.
Hormone beauty esthetics?
You come to my house and do esthetics.
It's convenient.
Hey, do you know about hormone beauty esthetics?
What's that?
It's an esthetic that comes to your house.
Is that so?
Can't I go to the store?
That's fine, but isn't it good to come to my house and give me a massage?
I'm a person who wants to enjoy the atmosphere of the store.
I'm thinking of ordering it next time.
Your skin will be beautiful and you can go back to your youth.
Isn't it okay?
You're not interested in me, are you?
I don't think so.
Thank you.
I'm Nishida, and I'm in charge of plastic surgery today.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
It's my first time doing this.
Is there any part of your wife that bothers you?
I don't have one right now, but I want to make my skin beautiful and young.
Is that so?
You're very beautiful.
I'm not beautiful at all.
No, you're very beautiful.
Thank you.
Let's take a look at your body.
Yes, please.
Let's get started.
Please change here.
This is the original plastic surgeon.
We use oil, so it's a good material for penetration.
This way, please.
Excuse me.
This is very transparent.
This is the original, so it's okay.
But it's my first time doing this, so I'm a little embarrassed.
That's what everyone says at first, but it's okay.
Yes.
Please lie down here.
Excuse me for the oil.
Yes, please.
Is the oil temperature okay?
Yes, it's okay.
I'll apply it all over your body.
I'll start the first procedure.
Yes.
Excuse me.
I'll start with a light massage and get deeper and deeper.
Yes.
Is the pressure okay?
Yes, it's okay.
Is this your first time doing this?
Yes, it's my first time.
I see.
Your body is very beautiful, so I thought you had a lot of hair.
Yes.
Your skin is already shiny.
That's not true.
You want your skin to be more shiny, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Your skin is very beautiful, but I'll do my best to make it more beautiful.
Yes, please.
Please tell me if there's anything you want me to focus on.
Yes.
I'll change the strength of the force depending on the area, so please tell me if you want.
Yes, I see.
Yes.
Your back is a little stiff.
Is it?
Yes.
You must be tired.
Yes, I am.
I'll massage your back.
Yes.
Okay.
Is your upper body okay?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Excuse me.
You massage your back to that point.
This area is where lymph passes through, so I'll focus on it.
Yes.
Are you okay?
I'll continue.
Can you open your legs?
Yes.
Excuse me.
It's a little embarrassing.
Everyone says that at first.
But it's okay.
I'll continue.
Excuse me.
Are you really okay?
It's okay.
Yes.
This area is where lymph passes through, so some people are worried at first.
But you'll get used to it.
It's okay.
Yes.
Can you bend your right leg?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Do you massage your back to that point?
It's part of the massage.
I see.
Please let me know if you have any questions.
Yes.
Is everyone like this?
Yes, everyone is doing this.
I see.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
I think this is done in any esthetician.
Is that so?
Yes.
Is this your first time?
It's a place where lymph passes easily.
I see.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Thank you.
Do you have any problems with your lower body?
Yes, I'm fine.
Can I see your face?
Yes.
How do you feel?
Do you feel hot?
Yes, I do.
That's good.
It means that it's effective.
I'll use more oil.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I warmed it up.
Are you okay?
Yes, the temperature is just right.
That's good.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Okay.
Thank you.
Your skin is beautiful.
Is that so?
Do you do anything at home?
No, I don't do anything at home.
I see.
You are born beautiful.
No, I'm not.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
I'm a little embarrassed.
Do you use this oil?
Yes.
It's easier to apply oil if it's easy to penetrate.
I see.
This is what it looks like.
It's a little embarrassing, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I'm getting used to it.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'll apply this oil, too.
Thank you.
I think the oil is very transparent.
It's okay.
It's easier to penetrate.
I see.
It's easier to apply oil if it's easy to penetrate.
Yes.
It's getting hot, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It means that the oil penetrates into the skin.
Yes.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Can you open your legs?
What?
I'll apply the oil.
Okay.
Thank you.
I think it's very embarrassing.
I think so, too.
This is the most important part.
I'm sorry.
It's getting hot, isn't it?
Yes.
It means that the lymph is flowing.
Please tell me if you have any other questions.
Yes.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes.
This is normal.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Do you apply the oil to such a place?
This is a massage.
Okay.
Does it hurt?
It doesn't hurt.
Thank you.
This is all for today.
Yes.
Thank you.
How was it?
It was very good.
Thank you.
If you don't mind,
how about the next appointment?
Well,
please.
Thank you.
By the way,
I don't need breakfast tomorrow.
Okay.
How was it?
It was good.
What are you talking about?
What?
It was good, wasn't it?
No, it wasn't.
It was very good.
By the way,
you look better than usual.
Really?
I'm glad.
Thank you.
This is a massage.
Okay.
This is all for today.
Yes.
Thank you.
Good night.
What's wrong?
Are you still awake?
Yes.
I was about to go to bed.
I'm sorry to wake you up.
Okay.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Thank you for today.
Thank you.
Today is the second time.
I'm going to use the special oil.
Okay.
For this oil,
I need you to do this procedure.
Okay.
It's different from the last time.
I see.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm going to apply the oil.
Okay.
How was the massage?
It was good.
You feel lighter, don't you?
Yes, I do.
It was good.
I'm going to apply the oil again.
This oil is more effective than the last time.
I see.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Are you off today?
Yes, I'm off today.
That's good.
Do you have a job?
Yes, I do.
I see.
You're married, aren't you?
How long have you been married?
Well...
It's been a long time.
Do you still go out to eat together?
No, I don't.
You don't go out often, do you?
I'm busy.
I see.
If you're married for a long time, you don't have time to go out.
Do you go out to eat or go on a date?
I want to do a lot of things, but I can't.
I see.
You're busy, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
I'll massage your lower body.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Do you usually go out alone?
Yes, I usually go out alone.
I see.
I'm sorry.
It's much lighter than before.
Really?
Yes.
It seems to be effective.
I'm glad.
I'm sorry.
Are you used to this massage machine?
I'm still a little embarrassed.
The material has changed a little compared to the last time.
And the area is smaller.
I agree.
The oil is easy to penetrate.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
I'll focus on the buttocks.
Okay.
Can you open your legs a little?
I'll massage your lymphatic system.
Okay.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
Yes.
It's more effective than the last time.
I see.
Can you open your legs?
Okay.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Is it okay for you to speak?
No.
I think it's a little different from the last time.
Are you used to this?
Yes.
It's more effective than the last time.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It's more effective than the last time.
I see.
Please face me.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
I'll do my best.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It's more effective than the last time.
I see.
I'll do my best.
Okay.
It's more effective than the last time.
I see.
You're amazing.
You can do it so well.
Of course.
I'll do my best.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'll do my best.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I feel hot.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Please relax.
You'll feel better.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
I'm sorry.
What?
I'm embarrassed.
It's okay.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
You're sweating a lot.
Isn't it because of the oil?
No.
You're sweating because of the oil.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you a massage.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
My voice is hoarse.
It's okay.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sorry.
I'll do my best.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
No.
You're sweating a lot.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
I feel good.
I'll give you a massage.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
You're sweating a lot.
No.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
Do you want to continue the massage?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You're sweating a lot.
No.
Please sleep.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Please touch here.
I'm sorry.
I haven't done this for a long time.
I see.
Do you want to continue the massage?
Can I?
Of course.
I'm sorry.
Please sleep.
I haven't done this for a long time.
You can do whatever you want.
I'm sorry.
I'm surprised.
Please drink a lot.
I'm sorry.
Please lick here.
I'm surprised.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
I'm sorry.
Please lick more.
What are you going to do?
What do you mean?
Do you want to continue the massage?
Please feel good.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
Please do more.
I feel good.
No.
Please do more.
I feel good.
Are you sure?
No.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Please do more.
I feel good.
I want to do more.
Can I do more?
Please do more.
I feel good.
No...
Oh, ahhhh!
So, there you go!
I need more medicine.
More, please!
I need more pills!
Feel good...
That's the place of the good feeling!
Alright?
feel so good...
Alright!
Please...
You can do it, Producer!
I can't believe you're leaving such a beautiful woman like Haruka.
Thank you.
I feel so good that I can't stand for a while.
I'm so excited that I'm shaking.
I happened to find a massage therapist on the Internet.
I'm drowning in joy.
Recently, I've been calling home every day.
I've been doing my best.
I'm looking forward to the massage he's going to give me.
As soon as he touched my body, I noticed that my whole body was overflowing with body fluid.
Why are you grinning alone?
Did I grin?
Did something good happen to you?
No, it's not like that.
I was just laughing.
By the way, I'm going to Thailand next week.
Can you give me your passport?
Okay.
Hey, do you still have sausages?
I'll taste it, so wait a minute.
Oh, my God.
Mom.
Your body is tighter and more beautiful than before, isn't it?
Let's use a new tool to massage today.
Okay.
Your body is getting more and more beautiful.
How do you feel?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Okay.
You want me to do it directly, don't you?
Yes.
Okay.
Do you want me to massage more?
Oh, more.
In the middle.
Do you want me to massage more in the middle?
Then please do it more.
Please do it in the middle.
Then I'll do it.
I'm scared.
I'll massage your back.
Okay.
Where do you want me to massage this time?
I'm embarrassed.
Then open your legs.
Open your legs.
I'm scared.
Do you like it?
Do you want me to do it directly this time?
Your body is shaking a lot.
Do you want me to do it directly?
I'm scared.
Open your legs.
Do you like it?
I feel good.
I'll massage your stomach, too.
I'm scared.
I feel good.
Do you like it?
I'm scared.
I feel good.
That's great.
Do you want to feel better?
I want to feel better.
Then I'll use a different tool.
Okay.
Do you like it?
It's more stimulating than before.
That's great.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
I'm scared.
I can't do it.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
You can do it.
I can't do it.
Do you feel good?
It's still a long way to go.
I can't do it.
I'll puke.
Do you want to drink?
Mom, why don't you take a look at how you're doing this time?
Look in the mirror.
It's very exciting, isn't it?
It's embarrassing.
But it's exciting, isn't it?
Look at me.
Yes.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
Come here.
Please lick me more.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
Kimchi
Can I do it?
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
I'm leaving.
Take care.
Haruka, take care of the house.
Yes.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
Hello?
Haruka?
You don't have to come all the way here to pick me up.
It would be terrible if my husband found out about this.
I can't control my sexual desire.
It's embarrassing.
It's my first time coming to your house at night.
I'm nervous.
It's just the two of us.
Take your time.
Yes.
It's embarrassing.
You look beautiful today.
Thank you.
It's embarrassing.
You're sweating a lot.
I feel terrible.
It's embarrassing.
It feels so good.
It's a great sound.
Haruka.
I brought a special oil.
Can I use it?
I brought a better one.
My body is hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
You're breathing heavily.
You're sweating and breathing heavily.
I'm embarrassed.
I can't stand it.
It feels so good.
I like this part.
You like this part, don't you?
It feels so good.
I can't stand it.
It's coming out.
It feels so good.
You're breathing heavily.
You like this part, don't you?
I like this part.
I can't stand it.
It feels so good.
It's coming out.
Come here.
It feels so good.
Please make me feel good, too.
I want to lick your belly.
Please stop.
It's good.
It feels so good.
Does your neck feel good?
I want to lick your belly.
It feels so good.
Do you want it?
I want it.
I want it here.
It feels so good.
It did feel so good.
It felt so good.
It was unbelievable.
It feels so good.
It feels so good!
Please give me more!
I can't do it!
I'm going to do it!
It feels so good!
Please give me more!
I'm going to do it!
It feels so good!
I can't do it!
I'm going to do it!
It feels so good!
Please feel my chest!
I'm going to do it!
It feels so good!
Ah...
Ah, feels good!
A bunch
Do a bunch
Feels good
Yes!
Urgh...
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah...
Ah... It feels good!
Ah, I'm so happy!
Ah...
Ah, ah...
Ah, ah, Ah...
It feels good!
Ah, Ah...
Ah...
Ah, ah...
It feels good!
Ah, it feels good!
Ahhhh!
Ahhhh
Ah, it feels good
I like intense stuff
Ah, let's go, let's go
Ah, it feels good
Ah, I can't do it anymore
Ah, I'm scared
I can't do it anymore
I'll cut this now, so wait a minute.
It's
Tickling
A porcupine
I love you!
I hate the smell!
Haruka-san, the inside of this bag is all messed up.
Messed up?
It's all messed up.
Does it feel good inside your bag?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'm so happy.
Me too.
It feels good.
Let's go!
Please mess up my bag.
Please.
Haruka-san.
It feels good.
Haruka-san, let's do more.
Let's do more.
It feels good.
Let's go!
Haruka-san.
Give me a kiss.
It feels good.
I want to do more.
Haruka-san.
It feels good.
I want to do more.
Do you want to do more?
It feels good.
I can't resist sexual desire.
I made a secret that I can't tell my husband.
Thank you for watching.