This video is a derivative work of the Touhou Project. It may be disrespectful of characteristics of this project, and may not be suitable for all ages.
Hello.
Is she living next door to that weirdo?
She's got a nice butt.
I wonder if she'll let me do it.
Alright.
I'm so tired.
Yes?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Yamada, and I live in the same apartment.
I'd like to talk to you for a bit.
Talk to me?
Yes.
Oh, about that.
I'd like to talk to you for a bit.
Wow, you have a completely different window.
It's a nice sofa.
I'm sorry to bother you.
No, no.
Wow.
I'll be right back.
Here's your tea.
Oh, thank you.
Please sit down.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
I was just thirsty. Thank you.
You live alone, right?
Yes.
Don't you have a boyfriend?
No, I don't.
Oh, you don't?
That's unexpected.
Is that so?
Yes.
You're beautiful.
Thank you.
What kind of person do you like?
What kind of person?
A nice person.
Oh, a cool person.
You know what I mean.
As long as they're nice.
You like a nice person?
What about me?
People say I look nice.
I think you do.
Oh, really?
That's great.
If you don't mind, I'd like to have dinner with you.
You cook, don't you?
Like a kitchen.
Yes.
Do you like cooking?
Well, kind of.
What's your specialty?
Well...
I like omelette.
I love omelette.
I like sweet things.
I see.
Not salty ones.
Yes.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Oh.
Are you...
Yes?
...not feeling well?
I feel like you're sitting in a weird way.
Oh.
You have a bad back, don't you?
It must hurt.
Not really.
I can tell.
I'm a gynecologist.
I massage your pelvis and buttocks.
I can tell.
You're a gynecologist?
Yes, I am.
I'm looking at you now.
Can I?
No, no, no.
You don't have to.
I don't want you to get up.
Please sit in the fourth row.
The fourth row?
Do you know what the fourth row is?
Yes.
It's like this.
Oh, sorry.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, like that.
Yes, yes.
Can you stay like that?
Yes.
Oh, sorry.
Can you not move so much?
I'm looking at your pelvis now.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Oh, sorry.
Can you pull your clothes?
Yes.
A little more.
Can you shake it left and right?
Yes.
Slowly, slowly.
Can you shake it a little more slowly?
You can do it as slowly as you can.
Are you touching it?
If you just look at it, you won't know what it's like.
It's normal for you to touch it.
Is this normal?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Can you stretch your arms?
Stretch.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Can you stay like that?
I'm looking at your pelvis now.
Yes.
Can you move it back and forth a little?
Back and forth?
Yes.
You can do it slowly.
Back and forth.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Is there anything wrong with this part?
I'm sorry.
Can you stay like that?
Yes.
If you don't do it in the right position, it will bend again.
I see.
Yes.
You don't have to be embarrassed.
I also massage female customers.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Can you stay like that?
Yes.
I see.
I'm going to touch it a little.
I don't know which part is stiff or bad.
Can you put your hand here?
I'm sorry.
I also massage this part.
This side muscle is stiff.
Is this part stiff?
Yes.
This part is stiff.
I've never seen a person who is so stiff.
Can you leave it as it is?
You should be able to see your back as much as possible.
Yes.
I'm going to massage this part.
I'm sorry.
This part is stiff.
Is that so?
If you leave it as it is, the pelvis will be distorted.
I see.
This part is stiff.
Are you okay?
Yes.
You can go back to your place.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Is this part stiff?
This part is stiff.
This part is stiff, isn't it?
I see.
You should leave it as it is.
Can you leave it as it is?
I'm sorry.
I see.
If you look at the wrinkles here, you can see the condition of the pelvis.
Are you looking at the wrinkles?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Can you leave it as it is?
Please leave it as it is.
I see.
Don't move.
Can you move your hand?
I'm sorry.
What?
What's wrong?
You're crying.
Why?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
You're crying.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Be quiet.
ah ahead
리나
実は
リナさん
ちょっと
こっち来てください
I can't do it.
Hey.
Yes.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Please take responsibility.
I can't sleep because of you.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
That feels good.
Wait a minute.
I can't do it.
One more time.
Please do it one more time.
I can't do it.
That feels good.
Wow.
That hurts.
I told you to do it.
What are you going to do?
It hurts.
All right.
It smells...
She's slipping away...
I don't want to hear
I think so.
Is it okay to make such a loud noise?
The neighbor will hear it.
Ah, ah, ah!
The sound is gross.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Hmm
Who is
She's really mean.
This doesn't feel good.
The doctor said she has hyperchloremia,
so a surgery could be helpful.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah
Ah
Next.
No more, no more.
I-I'm-I can't-
I'm, I'm, not fine.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Hmm
Yeah
Ra
Here
Ah
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, uh, uh, oh, oh, wow,
Shut up.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
No.
Please understand.
Next is the other side, the other side.
Next is the other side.
ea
It is difficult to move properly.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Yup
ああ
を
wwwwwwwwwwwwww
Hnnn
wwwwwwwwwwwwwwwww
wwwwwwwwwwwww
ahn
w
wwwwwwwww
Why are you eating a dog,
Stand up.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Um ah ah ah ah
Hey
Hmm
yaa
Please be careful.
Please be very careful.
, you will be okay
, you got all wet
Ouch!
Remove your underarm hair
You fine?
I'm not going anywhere!
There's someone here. Please leave.
My brother's here to play.
No, that's not it.
Actually...
I wanted to apologize for the other day.
Sis?
Sis, what are you doing?
No, it's nothing.
Wait a minute. It's okay.
Thank you.
Please leave.
No, really.
Please stop.
Are you okay?
If you make a loud noise,
I'll tell my brother.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Are you okay?
I'm wearing black pants today.
I'm going to the bathroom.
I really want to go.
Are you okay?
I'm worried about my brother.
I'm going to the bathroom.
You have a nice butt today.
Miina?
I hear something.
What is it?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
It's hard.
I think I can see it today.
Don't you want to be found out by your brother?
I'll think about it.
Then, by the way,
Please show me the hole.
Look.
Here.
Please show me the hole.
I'm sorry.
Look.
Please show me the hole.
Please open it properly.
You have to be patient.
If it's a hole, please open it.
No, action.
Action.
What is that noise?
Quiet.
No...
What's wrong with you?
Why are you so nervous?
You have to understand me.
Hurry up.
You have to hurry up.
Are you okay?
Don't be nervous.
I'm sorry.
It's getting better.
You feel better, right?
You'll find out if I make a sound.
Don't be nervous.
I'm going to curse you.
What is it?
You'll find out if I make a sound.
Does it feel good?
Please do it as it is.
I'm going to curse you.
Are you free?
I'll give you a massage.
I thought you'd come.
There's no one here today.
You're getting better.
I'll give you a massage.
What's wrong?
Show me more.
You're wearing flashy clothes today.
What is it?
I thought you'd be happy.
What did you want me to do?
I can't give you a massage.
I'm sorry.
You're rolling around, aren't you?
What is it?
I want you to touch me more.
You're strong.
I love you.
Do you want me to make you feel better?
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
No, I don't have a
What is it?
Why is he crying?
You can just sleep like that, and I will tidy her up
What's up?
Does it feel good?
This won't hit the pussy, so I'll open the chest.
I'll warm it directly with this.
This is a weak stimulation.
Open your legs.
I'm sorry.
That's it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Ho ho ho
Hey
Don't fall asleep
Hey, don't go to sleep
Are you asleep?
Yucchan do not have sleep
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Urgent care can make you dirty.
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Okay.
Ouch!
Keep it open.
That's better.
Keep your back straight.
I'm sorry.
Can you kiss me?
What's wrong with you?
You can do it.
I want you to kiss me.
You want to kiss me, don't you?
Then kiss me more.
I can't.
What's wrong with you?
Give me a massage.
A massage?
You're wearing a lot of underwear.
What's wrong with you?
I didn't expect you to come to my house.
And you're wearing a lot of underwear.
I'm sorry.
I thought it would be easy to give you a massage.
It's hard to give you a massage if you move your neck like that.
I'm sorry.
Be careful.
You don't need a massage, do you?
I don't need a massage.
What's wrong with you?
Give me a massage.
I'll use this today.
Don't move.
I'm sorry.
It's warm.
This is a proper massage oil.
I'm sorry.
Why are you moving?
You want me to massage you, don't you?
Please stay still.
I'm sorry.
What kind of massage do you want me to give you?
I want you to tell me.
Please tell me.
I want you to tell me everything.
I want you to tell me.
You want me to give you a massage, don't you?
I'm sorry.
Did you feel good?
Show me what you're doing.
I'll give you a good massage.
I'm sorry.
I want you to tell me.
Directly.
I'm sorry.
I feel bad.
Are you okay??
Guys!!
Yuckey!!
行っちゃう、行っちゃう。
Something's going on.
Please continue.
I want to see you go out more.
It feels good.
I don't want to!
Please do it yourself.
Don't hesitate.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
eh
Hmm
that
N'n'n Oh
N'n'n
Come on.
Who are you?
You really wanted this, didn't you?
I want it.
Give it to me.
What is it?
I...
I want to lick you.
What do you want?
Your homepage.
I want to lick you.
I'm sorry.
You have a good hand.
You're going to get dirty.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah
Ah
I want to lick myself
Don't stop
Yeah
Ah
Please lick me more
Yeah
Yes
I can't do it.
What?
You can't do it?
You're not talking. You're moving.
I can't do it.
You couldn't stand it, could you?
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
You said you wanted to do it.
Please take responsibility.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Wait a minute.
I can't do it.
You can't move?
What is it?
Please be careful.
I can't do it.
Do you want to go there?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no , no, no, no, no, no,경 Duchess
mi
You can't hold back anything anymore?
Oh, wow!
Oh no, what was that?
Let's play.
Oh no.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Oh! It hurts!
Wait!
It's hurting, isn't it?
It's hurting.
Ah!
It hurts.
It hurts!
It's hurting.
Ah!
It's hard.
It hurts.
It hurts!
Wait!
Ah!
It doesn't feel good!
This...
Ah!
Wait!
This hurts.
This...
Ah!
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm eating kimchi.
I'm gonna die.
I'm going to die.
…
so…
I can't talk properly.
The impact won't stop any more.
It damned bugs in my head.
…
It's just crazy!!!!!!!!
Sorry…
…
Hey.
Nyah!
Wait a minute with the light on.
Makes a weird noise.
Makes sounds while laughing.
I gritted my teeth.
It's embarrassing.
Platform...
Platform's life...
Can I let you out?
No!
Ah...
Thank you for watching!