It's been a long time since I've been to the hospital, so I'm a little worried.
Do you remember me?
Of course I remember you.
Yes.
I'm here.
Wait a minute.
It's been a long time since I've been to the hospital.
Is that so?
Yes.
Since when?
Oh!
Welcome.
It's been a long time.
It's been a long time, too.
Toshi-chan.
Yes.
You've grown up.
I think it's because of this time.
That's right.
It's been a long time.
I'm sorry.
Not at all.
Please come in.
Thank you.
Here you are.
It's a big house.
Really?
You can earn money.
That's not true.
Please sit down.
Thank you.
Here you are.
Tokyo is amazing.
Let's eat.
Toshi-chan, you've become really cool.
Is that so?
Yes.
You are more beautiful than your mother.
Really?
Thank you.
Your mother is beautiful, too.
That's right.
In general, my mother is more beautiful.
She is beautiful.
Do you say that yourself?
Yes.
How are you doing with your boyfriend recently?
Oh!
Will you ask me?
I want to ask you.
My boyfriend is passionate.
At first, I thought he was a man because we knew each other through marriage.
But his sex is the best.
Is that so?
What kind of sex?
He has a long goodwill.
Is that so?
Goodwill?
Does he have a goodwill?
Yes, he licks me a lot.
Is that so?
I don't think there are many people like that.
That's why I think he's a great partner.
That's good.
How are you doing with your husband?
I don't care.
My husband is a man.
He doesn't care about me at all.
Is that so?
That's good.
My husband doesn't care about me at all.
Is that so?
You don't know well.
I came to Tokyo, so I made a promise with my friend.
Is that so?
So I'm going.
I see.
Take care of Toshio.
Hello.
I'm looking forward to it.
Take good care of Toshio.
I know.
See you.
Thank you.
How is Tokyo?
I'm really looking forward to it.
Really?
Yes.
I've been into mentalism lately.
Mentalism?
Yes.
I've been studying fortune-telling and truth-telling.
That sounds difficult.
I thought I'd take a look around.
I see.
There seems to be more in Tokyo.
Yes.
There aren't many places like that in the countryside.
I see.
Yes.
I'm going to clean up.
Don't worry about me.
Thank you.
Yes.
I'm going to clean up.
I'm going to sleep.
Okay.
Ma-san, I'll help you.
It's okay.
Yes.
Take your time.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
I'm sorry to bother you.
It's okay.
You can watch anything on TV.
Thank you.
Yes.
This house is really beautiful.
Really?
Yes.
You like cleaning, don't you?
I'm glad to hear that.
Wow.
It's really beautiful.
Thank you.
I'm going to sleep.
Ma-san.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
No.
I was sucked into your butt.
I'll keep it a secret from your mother.
Please keep it a secret.
Ma-san.
You want to be licked, don't you?
You don't want to be licked by your husband, do you?
I don't know.
I don't like being licked.
I like being licked.
No.
I don't like being licked.
I'll lick you.
You don't have to be a nuisance.
It's okay.
I don't like it.
Come on.
Lick me.
I'll lick you.
You don't like being licked, do you?
You don't like it, do you?
I don't know.
I'll lick you.
I don't like it.
You're so beautiful.
Let me see.
You're beautiful, Doshi-chan.
You're beautiful.
You're so beautiful.
Look at me.
Your boobs are so beautiful.
You're so beautiful.
Don't look at me.
Wow...
Wow, it's amazing...
Your voice is getting hoarse.
How about this side?
Wow...
Your boobs are so soft.
What size cup is this?
Wow...
It's so soft.
Hey, stop it.
Wow...
Hey, Masa.
You like being licked, right?
I'll lick you a lot.
Come here.
Wow...
Wow, that's amazing.
I'm going to take a bath.
I'm going to massage your buttocks, too.
Help me.
That's the best.
It's delicious.
I'm going to lick your buttocks instead of your husband.
Help me.
I'm going to massage your buttocks, too.
I can't do this.
Help me.
Your buttocks are so beautiful.
I'm going to massage your buttocks, too.
I can't do this.
That's amazing.
I'm going to massage your buttocks, too.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't do this.
I'm going to massage your buttocks, too.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't do this.
I'm sorry.
Wow.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
Come here.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
I'm really...
Ouch!
I want to sleep.....
I WANT TO SLEEP......
It feels good to breathe
I'm so sorry.
I know how you feel.
You.
Saku, you're asleep.
she's.)
Dad, stay, please.
I wanna talk with you.
Wait, you must cure yourself.
It's too severe.
The other side, please.
Stop crying then.
Hmm!!!
It hurts!
It hurts!!
Konno-san won't let you go.
Ahh!
Ahhh!
Ahh!!
Oh!
Gahhhh
Here goes
Aha
Ohhhh
Oh
Ahhh
Ahh
Ha
I'm sorry.
I'm going to do it.
You looked happy although daddy licked you.
I was happy, too.
Don't say that.
If you lose faith in mommy and me,
I won't say it.
Can I lick again?
That won't happen.
OK, thank you.
It looks good.
Let's eat.
It looks so good.
It's so good.
You have a bad breath.
I'm sorry.
I have a habit of licking everything.
That's why my girlfriend dumped me.
Did she hate to be licked?
She didn't let me lick her at all.
When I licked her there, she was angry that I licked her too much.
She was very attracted to me and dumped me.
I see.
You are cute like a puppy.
Ma'am.
There is a cream on your lips.
Really?
Let me see.
There is a cream on your lips.
Here.
I have to remove the cream.
I'm sorry.
I'll lick you.
I'll do it again.
I'm sorry.
There is a cream on your lips.
Let me lick you.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it again.
You are the best.
I'm sorry.
Let me see.
It's soft and feels good.
It feels good.
Let's eat a cake.
It's embarrassing.
It's soft.
Let's eat a cake.
There is a cream on your lips.
I'm sorry.
It's embarrassing.
There is a cream on your lips.
Let me see.
I'll lick your lips.
There is a cream on your lips.
Aaaaaah!
Oh !!
Aaaaaah ...
That's amazing ...
Massage ...
Seriously ...
Let's do it ...
Mmm
Hmm
It's true
There's something on your face.
There's something on your face again.
I'll wipe it off for you.
I'm so embarrassed.
It's something on your face again.
It's hot.
Does she want to argue with me?
When you feel own, it's the best situation.
Huko the next day
Yo-rai and Haru-chan went to the romantic hospital together for the first time in 2 years.
Taking care of everything,
Shima is getting along well with my dad...
Keep your eyes on me, okay?
Please...
Shima seems to be tiptoeing.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, smoke,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
homework
It feels good, doesn't it?
Wow, that's amazing.
It's great to be licked by a mother.
It feels good to be licked by a mother.
It feels good, doesn't it?
What are you doing?
I'm doing yoga.
It's good for my body shape.
You're great.
Really?
No, I'm not.
Do you want to pose like this?
Yes.
It feels good to be licked by a mother.
Is it effective?
Yes, it's very effective.
It feels good.
It feels good to be licked by a mother.
Do you do yoga often?
Yes, I do it at home.
I do it sometimes.
You're great.
It feels good to be licked by a mother.
How do you feel after doing yoga?
I feel great.
It feels good to be licked by a mother.
It's good for my body shape.
Really?
No, I'm not.
It feels good to be licked by a mother.
I want to help you do yoga.
No, I'm fine.
I'm interested in it.
Do you want me to help you do yoga?
Yes.
Then, I'll ask you to help me.
What should I do?
I have a cold.
I want you to help me stretch my hip joint.
Do you want me to stretch here?
Yes.
I want you to do it lightly.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're great.
Really?
Yes, it feels good.
I think it's difficult to adjust the time.
I think so, too.
I can't feel anything.
That's not true.
I'm stretching my hip joint.
Really?
Next, I'll help you stretch your arm.
Okay.
I'll stretch my arm.
I didn't know yoga was a pose like this.
I didn't know either.
Here?
Yes.
I have to stretch my arm.
It feels good.
I'm getting interested in yoga.
Really?
I'll stretch my arm.
Okay.
That's not right.
I'm helping you.
Please concentrate on yoga.
Okay.
I'll stretch my arm.
Thank you.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
I have to stretch my arm.
That's not right.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
Hey, TOSHI.
I'm doing yoga.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll stretch my arm.
That's amazing.
I'm sorry.
That hurts.
I have to stretch my arm.
That's amazing.
That hurts.
Tell me a lot about yoga.
I'm sweating.
You're sweating a lot.
Is it hot?
You should take off your clothes.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
You're sweating.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sweating a lot, too.
I'm sweating.
Is this also the effect of yoga?
It's hot.
Let's drink together.
Please stand up.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Hold this.
It's gonna come out.
Please hold it.
You have to do it.
I'll do it slowly.
What's going on??
Oh, my goodness.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
I want to say that I've been feeling ticklish
After this thing, I can't afford to cry
I thought I'd take out my feelings
I...
But your mother seemed happy to hear it.
I'm going to take a bath now.
Let's go in together.
Let's go in.
You can't do that.
I'm going to clean you up.
Let's go in.
I'm going to take your clothes off.
I'm embarrassed.
Wait a minute.
I want to go in with you.
Let's go in.
I'm going to clean you up.
You have a beautiful body.
You can look at me a lot.
You can't lick me.
I'm going to lick you.
I'm going to clean you up.
You smell like sweat.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm going to clean you up.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm embarrassed.
It hurts.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm going to clean you up.
It hurts.
I'm still going to sleep
I'm going to sleep
Ou... It hurts.
You will be fine.
I'm sorry.
Spread it out, spread it out, spread it out
Spread it out and show me a lot
I can't see much
It's embarrassing
I can see it
I can't see it
OK, it's done.
It's so painful.
It's okay.
I'll clean your body.
Let's take a bath.
Come in.
It feels good.
I'll wash your feet.
I'll clean your feet.
It's dirty.
It's okay.
I'll clean your feet.
I didn't mean to do that.
It's okay.
Your feet are clean.
Don't look at me.
It's okay.
You can't lick my feet.
I'll wash your feet.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I'll wash your feet.
It hurts.
It's okay.
I'll wash your feet.
I was licking your feet, but you vomited.
Don't lick my feet.
I'll wash your feet.
It hurts.
Don't lick my feet.
I'll wash your feet.
It hurts.
Thank you for today.
Are you going back to Tokyo today?
Yes.
Did you have fun in Tokyo?
I went to a lot of places I wanted to go.
Really?
I enjoyed it.
That's good.
I enjoyed cooking.
Really?
Yes.
That's good.
Come back to Tokyo soon.
Yes.
Come to my house.
I want to go to your house.
I want to go to your house with my mom.
Yes.
Mom.
Before you go home,
Can I lick you one last time?
One last time.
No.
I won't tell anyone.
I want you to lick me, too.
Yes.
I won't tell anyone.
I'll do it.
I won't say anything.
This is my choice.
You agree with me, don't you?
I agree with the husband.
Um...
Well...
All right.
I want you to sleep, okay?
Okay?
Here, here.
I'm here.
No, no.
Leave it to me.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Come here.
Okay.
I'm here.
I want you to lick me directly.
I understand.
I want you to lick me.
I'm here.
I understand how you feel.
Touch me.
I'm here.
I want you to touch me directly.
I understand how you feel.
Touch me.
I want you to lick me.
Please.
I'm here.
I want you to touch me.
It's getting hard.
I'm here.
It's hot.
I love you.
I'll lick you a lot.
It's hot.
It's getting hard.
I'll lick you a lot.
It's hot.
Take it off.
It feels good.
My tongue is soft.
I'll lick you a lot.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'll lick you a lot.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I'll lick you a lot.
I'll clean it up.
It's still hot.
My back hurts.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Let's go together.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Let's go together.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Let's go together.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Let's go together.
It feels good.
I'm tired.
I can do it.
Let's go together.
Whoa!
Whoa...
Shut up!
Come on.
Momo?
I can't stop crying.
It's disgusting.
It hurts.
I can't stop crying.
It's disgusting.
It hurts.
I can't stop crying.