A few days later
Ren, Kinako, Karu-Karu, thank you as always!
Oh, Nono-chan, thank you!
Can I stay over tonight?
What? You're finally coming over?
Sure, sure. Come, come, come.
That's all for today's stream.
I'll be streaming tomorrow, so please come back!
See you later!
That's all for today's stream.
Who could it be?
Kake-chan, I'm so happy to see you in person!
Who's that?
Nono.
Nono-chan?
You promised me you'd come over.
The stream?
Yeah.
You promised me you'd stay over, so I came over.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hey.
What are you doing?
You're so cute.
No, no, no.
You can't go in there on your own.
Are you really alive?
I'm alive, but...
Can I touch you?
No, no, no. What are you doing?
I'm happy you're here.
No, no, no.
Why did you beat me?
It's a secret.
A secret?
But you always talk about your neighborhood.
It's dangerous to go to a nearby restaurant.
I found out as soon as I looked it up.
Wait, wait, wait.
You're so cute.
What are you doing?
Staying over.
No, go home.
Why?
You promised me.
Wait, the police.
I told you to stay alive.
The police, the police, the police.
Hey, Kaki.
What?
What, what, what?
Let's play.
No, no, no.
Hey, hey, hey.
You're so cute.
No, no, no.
What are you filming?
Why? You're cute.
Huh?
No, no, no.
You're so cute.
Hey, can I post this?
No, really.
Can I post this?
Really, the police.
Why?
You promised me.
I didn't promise you.
Huh?
Hey, Kaki, aren't you cold?
No.
You're not like usual.
No, no, no.
Why were you surprised?
You're so cute.
Go home.
That was cute. I want to see it again.
Hey, hey.
Hey, what are you doing?
Really, the police.
Why?
You were cute.
Show me more.
Hey.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, Kaki.
Hey, hey.
You're so cute.
I've never seen this face before.
Hey, you're so cute.
Show me more.
No, really.
Show me.
Hey.
You're usually cute, too.
Can I kiss you?
No.
Hey, let's kiss.
Softly.
You're so cute.
Hey, really.
You're like a dream.
You're so cute.
Hey.
You have a weak nipple.
Stop it.
Why?
I don't have a strong nipple.
I can't believe I'm doing something to make you happy.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Hey, you don't know about me, do you?
You said you didn't have a girlfriend.
Hey, stop it.
I'm sorry.
You have a weak nipple.
Can I see it directly?
No, no, no.
You have a very sensitive nipple.
I'm sorry.
It really hurts.
Hey, stop it.
How about now?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't do it anymore.
Why?
You look happy.
Aren't you happy?
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
How about now?
You smell good.
I can't do it anymore.
It's hard even though I didn't touch it.
Let me see.
No, no, no.
What are you doing?
It's hot.
Did you touch it together?
Are you tired?
It's hot.
You're cute.
I've been watching all of your streams, but I like your face the most.
I love you.
What are you doing?
I'm sleepy.
I'm warm.
You are so fluffy.
I'm so sleepy.
Go home.
Let's get comfortable together.
No.
What are you doing?
I feel good when I touch your nipples.
I'm so fluffy, too.
I feel good.
I knew you were waiting for me.
I'm not angry.
You are so cute.
I'm sorry.
You are so hard.
Do you feel good?
You have grown up.
Can I lick you?
I'm happy.
I'm not happy.
Don't you feel good?
I feel good.
You have grown up.
Hey, it's really big, isn't it?
No, no, no.
I told you no, Nagi. It's really big.
That's enough.
Your forehead is turning red.
Hey, hey, hey.
Here?
Not there.
I want to remember everything about you.
Does it feel good here?
No, no, no.
I want to remember everything about you.
Here?
No, no, no.
You're cute.
I told you no.
You're going to be weird.
I can't take it anymore.
Why?
I don't know what to do.
I can't take it anymore.
You've grown up.
You're a big boy now.
I can't take it anymore.
You can't?
I can't.
You look so happy.
Why can't you take it?
Why?
I'm so happy for you.
I'm so sorry.
You can take it.
I can take it.
Oh, my...
You're amazing!
Thank goodness.
Does it feel good?
I gotta help but.......
If it's nothing important, I'll be happy when you're happy with it
Can I borrow a place to wash my hands?
yes.
No, no, no!!!
Why?
Today....
My parents are coming from my parents' house
Yeah
So...
I can't, I can't, I can't
Are you going to meet your parents?
No, no, no, no
I'm so happy
Today...
Hey, who are you going to see?
No, no, no, no
I want to see you
If a cute girl suddenly appears
My parents will be surprised
Yeah
Let's go home today
Then can you come short neck next time?
Yeah, yeah, next time, next time, next time
Next time?
Yes
True
Yeah
It's a promise
Oh
Hey, do you love me?
As expected, I love you
Yeah
Let's go home
See you.
You're a good boy, so go home.
Did you say see you?
Yes.
See you.
Keep your promise.
Bye-bye.
I'm in trouble.
It's dangerous.
I should have known better.
Mother...
Father
Let's go home.
Yes.
I'm not stressed, I'm not lonely.
I won't be lonely.
Oh there she is
Welcome back, I've been waiting for you
Have you?In front of your house?
Yeah
Where have you been?
Come on, let's get back home together
Did you have fun?
It was fun. I was just walking around.
I also had fun waiting for you.
I was just waiting for you, right?
I was very excited to wait for you to come back.
I'm home.
The door is open. It's dangerous.
A strange fan will come.
Don't enter the house without permission.
I'm coming in.
This is the place I saw on the live broadcast.
This is Kake-chan's room.
I'm home.
I'll clean up later.
Can you delete the photo I took the other day?
Why?
Do you know the address of this room?
If you go out with me, I'll delete the photo.
Why do you make me so cold?
I've been so nice to you.
You're embarrassed, aren't you?
You want me to be your girlfriend, don't you?
I'll make you feel better.
Take this.
You look cute.
Ake-chan, you're so shy.
I'll do what makes you the happiest.
Oh, I see.
Are you looking forward to it?
I'm looking forward to it.
Here, right?
This pathetic voice is so cute.
I want to hear more.
What?
What's wrong?
It doesn't feel good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Do you feel like you're losing your strength?
I'll do more for you.
You like this, don't you?
I can't.
I know where your nipples are.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't.
You look like you're in a bad mood.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's scary, isn't it?
Your nipples are getting really big.
You look like you're in a bad mood.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't.
It's scary, isn't it?
It feels good, doesn't it?
You look like you're in a bad mood.
I can't.
Let me see.
It's hot.
You have a lot of nipples.
Do you want to touch it with me?
I don't want to.
Let's touch it together.
It's hot.
Your nipples look like they're going to hurt.
I'll make it easier for you.
You're scared?
You're scared, aren't you?
It's warm, right?
I'm not good at this...
It's not good!
It's not good at all.
It's not good?
It's not good.
I'll do this.
I'll do it.
It's hot.
Show me your cute side.
Don't do that.
Sit down.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
I don't want to.
You look happy.
I'm not happy.
You're happy, aren't you?
Why are you getting so big?
I'm sorry.
I've never done that before.
If you get angry at me, I'll do something for you.
I'll do it directly.
It's hot.
Are you tired?
No, I'm not.
You're not tired, are you?
I'm ticklish.
You like this, don't you?
It's the first time I've ever done this.
Let me touch you.
I'm sorry.
Can I hug you?
I'm ticklish.
Don't do that.
Do you feel ticklish?
Yes, I do.
You're ticklish, aren't you?
I'm ticklish.
Let's go to bed.
Are you ticklish?
Do you feel ticklish?
I don't know.
Let me touch you.
I'm ticklish.
It's hot, isn't it?
You're cute, Kake-chan.
I'm ticklish.
But I want to do something more pleasant.
I'll make you feel better.
You'll feel it later.
I'm ticklish.
I'll make you feel better.
Are you ticklish?
I'm ticklish.
I'll make you feel better.
You can look at me.
I'm ticklish.
It feels good.
Hey, Kake-chan.
I'm ticklish.
You can open your mouth.
It feels good.
I'm ticklish.
What are you doing?
I told you I'd make you feel better.
I'm ticklish.
I'm sleepy.
More.
You're not moving.
I can't move.
Ah
Ah, here too
Ah, hey, lick my lips, wait a minute
Ah, hey
Ah
Ah, 3
Ah, lick
Ah, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Ah, ah, ah
Ah, lick
Lick
Ah
It feels good
Ah, lick
Ah
My head is getting bigger
Ake-chan
When I look at you
You're so slimy
Ah
Ah, it feels good
Ake-chan
Ah
Can you see me trying?
Yes
Ah
I can't hold it anymore
You can put it in, right?
Ah
Can I put it in like this?
No
Ah
Ake-chan
It feels good
I'm really
Ah, wait
Nervous
Ah
I don't know
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
It's so hot.
It feels good.
There's a lot in there.
I can't do it directly.
It feels good.
It's fast.
Is it fast?
You can do more.
It's fast.
There's a lot in there.
It feels good.
I'll do more for you.
It's so hot.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Kake-chan.
I want you to do a lot from behind.
If you do it, I'll delete the picture.
I want you to do a lot.
I want you to delete the picture.
It's okay.
It feels good.
It's hot.
There's a lot in there.
It feels good.
I love you.
I love you so much.
It's hot.
Kake-chan.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Ah, that's right!
Ah, that feels good.
Really, really.
More!
It feels good, doesn't it?
Ah, that's right!
One more time!
That's right!
Ah, that's right!
More!
...
I don't like this.....
Oh god...
I don't like this...
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Go! Go! Go!
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Are you angry?
I'm angry.
I'm sorry.
You're the same no matter how many times you do it.
I'm not the same.
I just said it, so I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it anymore.
It's still big.
There's a big one that wasn't done earlier.
You can't erase the picture with that.
I'm still learning to be a gentleman.
You have to do it properly.
I'll make you feel better and make you drop a lot.
Again?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
It's big.
I don't want to do it anymore.
I'm going to sleep.
Wait a minute.
It feels good.
It's getting smaller.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to make you feel better.
It's hot.
I like your face.
It feels good.
It's getting smaller.
It's hot.
Wake up.
No, you can't.
It's still warm.
I can't stop breathing.
I'm going to pee.
I'm going to pee a lot.
I'm going to sleep.
You're sleeping a lot.
I'm happy.
It was good, wasn't it?
Don't come to my house without permission.
Why?
I'm hungry.
I'm going to sleep.
I'll make you feel better.
You were tired, weren't you?
I was tired.
You look tired.
You're tired, but you're doing your best.
I thought you were doing a great job.
Your bangs are a little long.
It's about time you got a haircut.
What's wrong?
You're doing your best.
You didn't look good today.
Are you tired?
I'm a little worried.
It's late.
Let's go home.
Why?
I'm tired, too.
I heard you were tired, so I came here.
I thought I'd like to sleep.
I'm good at massaging.
I'll take care of you when you're tired.
You don't have to worry about it.
Are you sleepy?
You'll feel better.
I'll wipe it off for you.
It's not good.
Can I touch you?
Let's not do that today.
It feels good when I touch you.
How about here?
You don't even touch me.
If I touch you, you'll break.
I'll touch you.
It's noisy.
If you don't like it, you have to endure it.
It's cute, but it's not cool.
It feels good, doesn't it?
If I touch your neck, I'll be able to reach your waist.
It's cute.
Your body is shiny.
You don't have any strength in your body anymore.
Does it feel good?
Which one of us is sensitive?
I know everything about you.
I know.
How do you feel?
Your neck was soft until a while ago.
Your neck is curled up.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, but...
You look very happy.
If you like to be touched, you should say so.
I'm very surprised.
Why?
I want you to touch me.
I hate liars.
Don't speak even if I touch you.
It doesn't feel good, does it?
You want me to stop, don't you?
Can you stand it?
Really?
Don't break your promise.
I'm sorry.
Can you stand it?
I'm trembling.
Hey.
Stop lying.
If your neck feels good, be honest.
Hey.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Can I make you feel better?
I told you I'd give you a massage.
Yes.
My stomach is wet and thick.
My waist.
My waist is crawling so much that I'm realised.
Your waist is very curly.
Are you aware that I'm in love with you?
How do you feel?
I'm going to sleep.
Your face is so soft.
When I touch your nipples, your face becomes soft.
Your nipples are so soft.
You want to feel good right away.
You want to do push-ups with me.
I told you I know.
Look at me.
Let me hear your voice more.
Does it feel good?
I'm going to do push-ups with you.
When we do push-ups together, it will definitely feel good.
Look at me.
I'm going to do push-ups with you.
Give me your hand.
You're tired, but you want me to heal you, right?
No, I don't.
I'm going to do push-ups with you.
You're touching my nipples too much.
You're a massage therapist, right?
I'm going to do push-ups with you.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Do you feel my nipples?
You're sensitive, so you'll know.
There's a lot of tingling in my hands.
I'm really excited.
Do you like to have me on your back?
Yes, I like it.
I told you I liked it!
My sister's cuteness is out of control.
More.
Move your hips around.
It tickles.
Hey Moon.
I remember your face when you were about to take a picture.
I've been looking at that face for a long time.
It's cute.
I've seen a lot of faces, but I like that face the most.
Oh, my God.
Shit, shit, shit.
It's delicious.
Do you want some more?
No, I'm full.
Hey, let's get on the bed.
I'm tired, so let's get it right.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're all muddy.
I think I can do it.
Hey.
Look at this.
It's very soft.
I can't do it.
Why?
Hey.
Daddy.
I'm doing it.
Hey, you still have the spirit for me, don't you?
I told you I don't like to lie.
I can't do it.
Did you drink it?
I love you, so I don't want you to drink it.
I don't think so.
Hey.
You're all wet.
Let's take a bath.
We're going to stay here tonight.
Let's go.
Ready, go.
I can't do it.
Hurry up.
Wait a minute.
This is the bathroom.
You can go in first.
Why?
Let's go in together.
Let's take a bath together.
It's over, isn't it?
It's not over yet.
I'm going to sit down.
You don't have to get so close.
You're too close.
Did you get your back out of the water?
I'm going to sit down.
You're too close.
Do you feel good?
I'm going to sit down.
What is this?
Is this a pink drop?
What?
Did you lie to me?
You said you didn't have a girlfriend.
I did.
I'm sorry.
You said you didn't have a girlfriend.
Tell me.
You said you didn't like me.
Tell me the truth.
Will you do this to me?
I won't.
Will you give me a lot of water?
I'm tired.
I don't know.
I won't.
I see.
Who is the most angry?
You.
You are the most angry.
Will you give me a lot of water?
I'm going to die.
You are not angry.
I'm not angry.
You are the most angry.
Really?
Really.
Do you say that in front of your fans?
I don't know.
Don't you feel angry?
No.
Wait a minute.
You are the most angry.
I'm going to die.
Are you angry now?
Do you keep your promise?
Yes.
If I say I'm the most angry, you will feel better.
You are the most angry.
I'm not lying.
Do you say that a lot?
You are the most angry.
I feel good.
I'm going to die.
It hurts.
Are you angry?
I'm angry.
What, what, what?
What!
uguuguuguugu...
It's still on!
That, that, that, that!
What is this?!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait wait!
I can't do it!
I'm so scared of it!
I'm the only one who can't do it!
I can't do it!
You look so bad when you cry.
But I love you so much.
I lied to you.
Will you listen to me?
I got it.
I love you.
It started.
Hello, everyone.
Someone is asking who I am.
Thank you for coming to my stream.
I lied to everyone today.
I wanted to apologize.
I said I don't have a girlfriend.
But I actually have a girlfriend.
I checked my phone.
I was cheating on a lot of girls.
I was cheating on my girlfriend.
I'm sorry.
Today,
I'll be with this trash.
There are a lot of comments.
I'm glad.
I'm going to apologize to everyone.
I'll get started.
Look at me.
You have a very ugly voice.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad I was able to apologize to you.
It feels good.
Hey, hey, you like this, don't you?
You're making a lot of noise, look
Hey, Kake-chan, you're making a lot of noise
Chinchin, you're twitching
You're twitching just by touching my nipple
Can't you hold it in?
I can't hold it in
I'm streaming
Kake-chan, if you feel good, you can do anything
It feels good, doesn't it?
Look
Your nipple is turning red
Your nipple is coming off
It's so crunchy
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm getting a lot of comments
I'm glad everyone is watching
I don't think anyone has ever seen a stream like this
Kake-chan, I'm glad
Chinchin looks like she's in a lot of pain
Do you want me to show you?
I'm sure a lot of people want to see Kake-chan's nipple
I have to show it to my fans
Did you feel it just by touching my nipple?
It's so crunchy
You're making a lot of noise
You're twitching a lot
I'm going to tickle you
Does it feel good?
You're making a lot of noise
Can you see it?
You can see everything
What if I take a picture of your nipple?
Do you like it?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm going to tickle you
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's so crunchy
Chinchin, you're making a lot of noise
It feels good, doesn't it?
Did you take a picture of my nipple?
You're making a lot of noise
I'm going to tickle you more
Did you reflect on yourself?
You're amazing
Continuous tickling and endurance delivery
The result was a great success
Thank you for watching
I'm going to tickle you more
It was a great success
The number of followers is decreasing
All of them are gone
You're trending
Congratulations
You set a goal
Kake-chan
Your account was banned
All of them are gone
But
I'm on your side
I'm going to tickle you more
She's cute
She's so cute
I'm going to tickle you more
She's a good girl
You're a good girl
You look like you're happy to be born.
I'm holding back.
Do you feel good again?
Are you so happy to be born?
Do you want me to pet you?
I want you to touch me, too.
Touch you?
Please.
I want you to touch me, too.
Good boy.
Are you happy?
How do you feel under your socks?
I'm so happy.
I heard you want to feel good again.
I want to feel good.
I'm ticklish.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
You look cute with a mask on.
Come here.
Show me your face.
You're cute.
I'm ticklish.
You feel good all the time, don't you?
Are you ticklish?
I'll touch your neck and tickle you more.
Let's focus on your chest.
I'm ticklish.
I feel good.
Your chest feels good, doesn't it?
I'll tickle your neck.
I'll tickle your neck, too.
I'm ticklish.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
I'm ticklish.
What's wrong?
Let's tickle together.
I'm ticklish.
I feel good.
You're cute.
I'm ticklish.
I'll tickle you more.
I'll tickle your mouth.
I'm ticklish.
I'll tickle you.
Do you feel better?
I feel better.
That's good.
You can do whatever you want.
I'll tickle you more.
I'm ticklish.
I'll tickle you.
I feel good.
I'll tickle you more.
I'm ticklish.
I feel good.
Come here.
I'm going to sleep.
You like me.
I'm ticklish.
You have to do it properly.
Can I?
I'm so sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
This is the first time you've gone to bed.
Move more.
Try to feel good.
I'm sleepy.
I'm feeling tight around my neck.
It's getting harder.
It feels good.
Move more.
I'm sleepy.
I can't move.
It feels good.
I'm sleepy.
Models
It's so warm.
So cozy.
It's so hot!
Phew Phew Phew
Akie,
Phew
Do you enjoy?
Hm
Hmm
I'm sorry.
I'll make you feel better in the future.
I love you.