It's been a long time since I've seen you, so I'm a little nervous.
You don't remember, do you?
I don't remember.
It was when you were little.
It's been a long time.
Yes, yes.
Oh, I'm coming.
I'm coming now.
Yes.
Are you nervous?
I'm getting nervous.
Welcome.
Long time no see.
You've grown up.
Oh, hello.
It's cold. Please come in.
May I?
Thank you.
Please come in.
By the way, you've grown up.
Yes.
You're getting prettier, too.
Thank you.
I'm happy to live with you.
That's right.
My husband is on a business trip.
I was lonely because there were only rooms left.
I'm glad you came.
I wouldn't be lonely if I lived like this.
I can concentrate and study.
I'm a middle school student.
That's right.
Don't you have any children yet?
I had a plan, but it's been a long time.
It's been a long time.
I see.
But I didn't know you were going to talk about that in the morning.
That's right.
And it was in front of you.
I'm sorry.
No problem.
Are you embarrassed?
No.
That's what I'm saying.
You used to be...
But...
Didn't we talk a lot back then?
Foreigners?
That's right.
I know it's awkward to say this.
I used to hang out with my sister and two foreign brothers.
We traded places, too.
That's right.
I used to put my sister in the club.
And then I stayed in the club all the time.
My friend said the same thing.
She said your sister was famous.
That's right.
But I knew I couldn't afford the big one.
There was a mid-size.
A mid-size?
Yes.
Wow, that's amazing.
It's awkward. I'm sorry.
It's not that big.
He's a grown-up. He's a college student.
That's right.
It's awkward.
It's like a family talk.
It's been a while since we talked like this.
It's getting late. I have to go.
You have to go.
Take care of Tetsu.
I'll see you off.
It's okay.
I'm going home.
Call me if you need anything.
Call me if Tetsu does anything wrong.
See you.
Take care of him.
Okay.
What should I do?
I haven't cleaned up my room yet.
Tetsu, watch TV and wait.
Okay.
I have to clean up my room.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry. I have to clean up my room.
Tetsu, how's your job hunting going?
I'm learning how to hunt.
I see.
I'm more interested in the story of the mailman.
The story of the mailman?
I was surprised.
Isn't the mailman really big?
There are a lot of them.
Do you go to the mailman?
At that time, it was a long business.
It was fun.
Did you feel good?
I felt good.
Because the mailman is big.
But I don't like big mailmen.
I like hard mailmen.
Is that so?
How long did you hunt?
Did you hunt all night?
Maybe so.
I couldn't get a condom.
I couldn't get a condom in Japan.
Did you get a condom in Japan?
Maybe so.
That's amazing.
I was interested in the story of the mailman.
I'm also interested in the story of the mailman.
I see.
You are old.
Don't do that.
Are you done?
I'm sorry.
Do you know that I'm your stepson?
I know.
Why do you do this?
I heard that you used to do this a lot.
It's different from that.
I've never been able to get a condom.
I get a condom right away.
I have a complex about it.
You can't do that to me.
You have a lot of experience.
Can I have sex with you?
You can't do that.
I'm worried about it.
I can talk to you.
But I can't do that to you.
I won't do anything.
Can you rub my butt?
No.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
I won't do anything.
Can you rub my butt?
Please.
I won't do anything.
What should I do?
You want me to rub your butt?
You should have a girlfriend.
Your butt is beautiful.
It's big.
I don't care about that.
Can you rub my butt?
What?
I want to sit here.
Please lie down.
I just want to touch you.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I don't want to touch you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't hear that.
I'm hungry.
I'm sorry.
You can't do that.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
I can't do that.
Can I lie down?
What?
What are you doing?
I just want to touch you.
What?
I'm sorry.
I can't do that.
I didn't ask you to touch me.
I'm sorry.
I can't do that.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I can't do that.
I'm sleepy.
Can I have some water?
Just a little.
I can't do that.
Are you done?
I'm sorry.
I can't do that.
One more time?
One more time.
I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
What are you looking at?
I want to put you in the bath.
Are you kidding me?
That's right.
You need to get in the bath.
It's not a good idea.
I'm sleepy.
I can't do that.
No, you can't do that.
But you said it's been a long time.
No, it's not.
It's just a practice.
Ouch!
No, it's not.
It's just a practice.
Here you go.
That feels good.
Your head is all nervous.
I can't do it anymore.
So cold.
Please stop it.
It is very painful.
Get out of here.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's very beautiful.
It's deep in there.
Is it hit?
It's hit there.
It feels good.
You should practice more.
You should walk more.
It feels good.
It's very hard.
You should walk more.
It feels good.
It's very hard.
You're getting better.
You should walk more.
It feels good.
It's very hard.
It's getting harder.
You're getting better.
You should walk more.
It feels good.
It's very hard.
It's deep in there.
It feels good.
It's very hard.
I'm going to break.
It's almost there.
It hurts.
I feel so good.
I'm breathing so hard.
Move more.
Wow.
I can't do it anymore.
I feel so good.
It's so hard.
I can't do it anymore.
I feel so good.
Move more.
I can't do it anymore.
I feel so good.
Wow.
I can't do it anymore.
It was so hard.
I feel so good.
It was so good.
I want to practice more.
You can practice a lot.
I feel so good.
I can't do it anymore.
It hurts.
I feel so good.
I want to move more.
I can't do it anymore.
Wow.
I feel so good.
It was so hard.
It hurts.
I can't do it anymore.
I feel so good.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
I feel so good.
Did you say it again?
I said it again.
I can't do it anymore.
Can I do it the other way around this time?
You have a beautiful butt.
I'm going to sleep.
Oh, it's so hard.
Are you feeling better?
I'm feeling better.
Oh, it's so hard.
I'll do it again next time.
No, only today.
Oh, only today.
I'll do it today.
You're doing the housework properly.
I have to clean the bath properly.
I don't think you're the type to do that because you're pretty.
I'm a pretty girl.
It's gross to sleep in the bath, isn't it?
That's right.
I'm so dirty.
What are you doing?
I hit my butt again.
I want to practice.
I told you that was the end of it.
Are you going to practice again?
I'm not going to bother you with the cleaning.
I told you that was the end of it.
I'm so dirty.
Wait a minute.
One more time.
I'm so dirty.
Why are you so dirty?
I told you that was the end of it.
Can I practice one more time?
That's amazing.
Why?
Ah
Are you done?
No, not yet
Thank you, dad.
I'm sorry.
Your butt is too big.
I won't do it again.
Are you full?
Yes, I'm full.
I'm glad I made you a bowl.
By the way, how long have you been married?
It's been a long time.
It's been 7 years this year.
Where did you meet?
We went to the same university.
It's been a long time.
It's been 7 years.
I don't know if it's early or late.
Recently, everyone is talking about whether they can have a baby soon.
That's right.
Everyone around me was happy to have a baby.
It's not easy.
You said you didn't have a baby.
Don't you have a baby?
We've been together for a long time, so we're used to it.
I didn't have a baby.
I didn't know that.
Maybe I'm tired.
If you don't have a baby, you'll feel awkward.
That's right.
I feel sorry for my husband.
We've been taking care of each other, so we haven't had a chance to have a baby.
I see.
Are you curious?
No, I don't know why.
I think it's normal for a couple to live together for 7 years.
I'm sad.
I'm sad, too.
I'm going to clean up.
Are you done?
I'm done.
I'm glad you ate a lot.
It was delicious.
Really?
I'm glad.
I don't eat a lot with my husband.
I see.
I'm glad you ate a lot.
Hey.
What are you doing?
I made your favorite food.
Did I put too much garlic in it?
It was delicious.
It's too early for you.
I don't want to.
I want to practice.
Practice?
Do you want to practice?
I want to practice.
Do you like my butt so much?
I love it.
It's very soft.
I'm practicing a lot, so I'm getting better at touching it.
Are you getting better?
I'm getting better.
I'm embarrassed to be looked at.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's very soft.
It's amazing.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm sweating.
I can't move it for a long time.
It feels good.
I can't move it.
Please use this.
This?
I can't move it.
It feels good.
It's very soft.
I can't move it.
It feels good.
Please use this.
I can't move it.
It's hard.
It's very soft.
I can't move it.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I can't move it.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I want to practice more.
Do you want to practice more?
Can I stop?
Please stop.
I can't move it.
It feels good.
It's very interesting.
It's very beautiful.
Really?
I can't move it.
I'm full.
It feels good.
Do you want to lie down and sleep?
Do you want to sleep?
I can't move it.
It feels good.
Do you want to sleep?
I can't move it.
It feels good.
You can't move it?
Yes.
Do you want to sleep?
I can't move it.
It's hard.
You're sweating a lot.
You're sweating a lot again.
I'm sweating a lot again.
Have I improved?
You're getting better.
Do you see the results of my practice?
Yes.
It feels good.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm glad.
What kind of person was your mother when you were young?
My mother?
She was popular.
There were a lot of girls who admired her.
I see.
I admired her, too.
Was she that popular?
Yes.
She was popular.
Was she popular?
Did she do it on purpose?
She was popular.
Maybe she didn't stop it.
I see.
Did she have other partners?
I don't know.
She might have had other partners.
She was young.
I see.
She was popular.
What about you?
Me?
I hung out with popular girls.
Did you?
Did you do it a lot?
I think everyone goes through it.
I see.
What?
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Don't play pranks on me.
I made you dirty.
I was cleaning up.
It's dripping.
What?
I was cleaning up.
It's dripping.
What are you doing?
Clean up by yourself.
I'm sorry.
This is my penis.
It's a prank.
I'm sorry.
I was cleaning up.
You have to clean up.
I see.
It's still hard.
I'm sorry.
What?
Clean up.
I see.
I was playing pranks on you.
I'm sorry.
What?
It stinks.
I was playing pranks on you.
Come here.
Why did you play pranks on me?
I'm sorry.
Couldn't you stand it?
No.
I was playing pranks on you.
I'm sorry.
Stand up.
I was playing pranks on you.
I see.
You're a bad boy.
I'm sorry.
You still have something on your face.
Can you lie down?
I'm sorry.
Lie down.
I'm going to sleep.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
How do I feel?
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
Can I sleep?
I'm going to sleep.
I feel sick.
I think I have a pimple.
You have a pimple.
Let me see.
It's hard.
Ten-chan's pee is so hard that I'm going to pee right away.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Ten-chan's pee is so hard that I'm going to pee right away.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Did you pee a lot?
Ten-chan's pee is so hard that I'm going to pee right away.
I can only get excited when I'm with you.
You don't have to pee in a place like this.
I was very excited.
It felt good.
I'll clean up.
Please.
Ten-chan's pee is so hard that I'm going to pee right away.
Do you change your sheets every day?
That's right.
I have an allergy.
I have to change it regularly.
Do you have an allergy?
That's right.
It's hard every day.
You're good at cleaning.
I think so.
I'm getting used to it every day.
What do you like about him?
I think he's kind.
I'm busy, so I don't have much time to talk to him.
You're always busy.
That's right.
It's good to be busy.
Let's go.
How's your study going?
It's going pretty well.
I see.
I hope it goes well.
That's right.
I'm not good at studying.
I see.
Do you have a hard time?
No.
How's your study going?
It's hard.
It's clean now.
What are you doing?
Close it.
Even if I close it...
You must be tired.
I'll give you a massage.
Really?
Are you going to give me a massage?
I'll massage your lymph nodes.
I'll do it for you.
For me?
Put your hands up.
I'll massage your legs.
Lymph nodes?
Are you good at massaging?
I'm good at massaging.
It tickles a little.
You may be tired.
What are you doing?
It's a little tight here.
Is it really related to the massage?
It's a massage.
Please trust me.
Is it true?
What kind of massage is this?
It's a lymph massage.
Is it a lymph massage?
I didn't do it all.
I'll give you a massage.
Really?
What are you doing?
I'll do it for you.
I'm tired because I have to do housework.
What kind of massage is this?
It's a massage to get rid of your fatigue.
It's a massage machine.
Please turn around.
It's a gentle touch.
Does it feel good?
Is this really a massage?
Don't push it.
What are you doing?
I do a massage in a hard part.
I don't think so.
I can't do it unless it's on my face.
It's a little embarrassing.
What?
It's warm.
What are you doing?
I was massaging with a hard stick.
Is that a massage?
I bought a hard stick.
What is that?
It's very hot.
Is it hot?
Where did you buy it?
It's hot.
Is it massage?
That's right.
It's like acupressure.
It's acupressure.
It's a little uncomfortable.
Is it uncomfortable?
Please lie on your back.
It's very good.
It feels good.
Do you feel good?
It's very good.
It smells good.
You want to feel good, don't you?
I want to feel good.
Lie down.
It's hot.
You like my butt, don't you?
I like your butt.
Can you see it?
I can see it.
It's hot.
I'm glad you gave me a massage.
I want you to rub my body.
Do you want me to rub your body?
It's hot.
It's very good.
Is it warm?
It's good to use your lower back.
I'm getting cold.
I want to sleep.
Do you want to sleep?
Yes.
It's hot.
I want to sleep.
I can't sleep.
I feel good.
Please be patient.
I can't sleep.
It's hot.
I'm sweating a lot.
I want to sleep.
Did you feel good?
I felt good.
I'm sweating a lot.
I want to practice more.
Is it not enough?
Yes.
You're studying hard.
It's hot.
I'm sweating a lot.
Please lie down.
I feel good.
I'm sweating a lot.
It's hot.
I'm sweating.
I feel good.
Please lie down.
Haah...
Hey, hey!
Feeling good?
Gon, what did you do to me?
What did you do to me?
Please
I'm starting to get tired
You did a great job.
Are you feeling good?
Yes, I feel good.
I was surprised.
It's getting harder.
Are you feeling good?
I was surprised.
It's getting harder.
Can I stop?
I was surprised.
It's coming out.
Are you feeling good?
I want you to put it in again.
I want to put it in.
Can you put it in?
Yes.
I like this clothes.
Can you put it on again?
This?
Yes.
I like tight knit.
I'm sorry.
It does not work any more.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
You're amazing.
You're sweating a lot.
Are you taking a break?
I'm sweating a lot.
You're amazing.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sweating a lot.
It's delicious.
You have to practice more.
Don't you?
Yes.
I'll practice more.
Do you practice?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
Can you hear me?
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
Did you feel good?
Yes.
I felt so good.
I think this is the best you've done so far.
Yes.
I want to do it again.
Why don't you date a girl instead of an old lady?
I like an old lady.
Hey.
I think it's good.
I won't do it again.
Find a good girl.
Yes.