It's been a while since I've seen you.
Yeah?
Long time no see.
Are you nervous?
A little.
Oh my!
You've grown up!
Long time no see.
Come on in.
Thank you for having me.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
I haven't seen you in a while.
Me too.
Thank you.
I'm so happy to see you.
I'm sorry to see you all of a sudden.
Not at all.
Take it out.
Did you bring this?
Yes, I did.
Did you?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You've become a man.
You're so stylish.
You're so beautiful.
Am I?
You've become more stylish.
You've got a nice butt.
You're so cool.
I've been working out lately.
Especially my butt.
It's bigger than before, right?
You're so cool.
What are you doing?
I was nearby.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I heard you're going to have an audition for a martial artist.
I know it's sudden, but could you let me stay?
I'm sorry.
Not at all.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Martial artist?
Martial artist.
Are you okay? You look so cool.
Wait a minute.
Why are you embarrassed?
I'm not embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
It's like you're doing your best to catch your dream.
I'm going to go now.
Okay.
I came to Tokyo, so I'll go sightseeing and go home.
See you later.
Bye.
Thank you for coming.
I have to continue cleaning, so I'll watch TV and relax.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Don't help me.
It's okay.
It was far, right?
Take your time.
It was quite far.
Right?
It took about five hours.
Five hours?
It's hard.
By the way, your husband is an artist, isn't he?
Yes, he is.
He's on a tour now.
Is he in the countryside?
No, he's in the world.
The world?
Yes.
The world is amazing.
Is it?
It's not a big deal.
He seems to be doing his best.
Don't you feel lonely on a world tour?
Yes, I do.
But I've been like that since we started dating.
You don't spend much time at home.
That's right.
So when he's at home, I can't help feeling lonely.
That's good.
Do you think I'm bothering you?
No, not at all.
It's good to have a lot of people around.
That's good.
By the way, have you found a girlfriend?
No, not at all.
I see.
I don't know how to approach a girl.
How to approach?
Well, I don't know how to do it unless I have a lot of relationships.
That's right.
What should I do?
It's difficult.
But you have to attack a lot of girls, don't you?
Attack?
It's difficult, isn't it?
I'm going to open the window.
It's been a long time since I cleaned up.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm a guest, so take your time.
You have a great butt.
If you're going to do martial arts, you're training, aren't you?
I'm training, but your body is amazing.
You have a great body.
Don't look at me too much.
Do you work out every day?
Not every day.
It's good to train at home.
Take your time.
Thank you.
There's nothing in this house.
It's a beautiful house.
Really?
I like cleaning.
I'm sorry.
I want to take care of you more.
It's okay.
I'm worried about the groove.
What's wrong?
Wait a minute.
Put it away.
It hurts.
Mom will scold me if I do that.
No.
It hurts.
Take it off.
Put it away.
I'm worried about you.
Don't look at me.
Just look at me.
Just look at me?
I have to clean up a little more.
Don't get in my way.
You're itching.
Don't do that.
It's very soft.
It feels good.
Don't do that.
You're itching.
Please.
Calm down.
I still have a lot to do.
I still have to clean up.
It's not a big deal.
Wait.
Don't do that.
Calm down.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't do that.
Stop it.
We're married.
I can't help it.
Don't do that.
Put it back.
I'm embarrassed.
Stop it.
Don't play with my body.
I can't help it.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't do that.
Stop it.
I can't help it.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't do that.
I can't help it.
Where are you licking?
Don't stick your tongue in there.
I can't help it.
What?
Stop it.
I can't help it.
Don't do that in front of me.
Just don't do it anymore.
Aunt wouldn't do it for me.
Just do this much for me.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
.
Isn't it okay?
Hey Hey Hey, it's
over, isn't it?
Come on, come on.
Ah, wait!
It hurts.
It's over, right?
Wait!
No, no!
Hey, I told you this is all I have.
That's not enough.
No, no!
It feels good.
No, no, no.
No, no.
Aww...
No, my dear.
Aww, no!
No, no, no.
Ah...
I can't do it...
Stop it...
I can't do it.
Let it go.
Let it go...
Ah!
It's hot.
Oh, my God.
No.
I can't do this.
Get out of here.
I can't do this anymore.
It's disgusting.
I can't do this.
I can't do this anymore.
No.
Oh, my goodness.
I can't take it anymore!
Help me!
I beg you!
I can't take it anymore!
Help me!
I'm sorry.
It's not like that.
Calm down.
I want to go to the bathroom.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sorry.
That was so good.
That felt so good.
That felt so good!
This is hot!
This is so hot!
Oh! It's hot!
Ah!
Ah, it's cold.
Ah, it's so cold.
I can't do this.
Ah, I can't do this.
Ah, it's so cold.
Please stop me, Kai-chan.
I can't do this.
Ah, it's so cold.
Kai-chan.
I can't do this.
But, you did it...
You did it, didn't you?
I can't do this.
One more time.
I did it a lot.
One more time?
I'm sorry.
I have a lot of pimples.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
I can't, I can't...
I...
I can't...
What should I do...
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, my back hurts.
Thank you Mima.
Hey
Ah
It's already the end.
Right?
One more time.
One more time?
That's not what we agreed on.
Oh, no.
I can't stand it.
I can't stand it any longer.
ZZzz...
Cough for amputation
Hold...
the...
It's not good to do this anymore, isn't it?
Stop it, please.
I can't do this anymore.
No, no, no.
Let me go.
I can't do this anymore.
No, no, no.
It hurts so much.
I can't do this anymore.
It's so painful.
Peek a boo.
Oh my God!
Don't run, play with me.
I can't do anything.
Oh, my God.
It's over, isn't it?
I'm so sorry.
It's been a while since I've seen you.
Keep it a secret.
What are you doing?
That's a flashy skirt.
What?
I wore it when I was young.
You wore it when you were young?
Yeah.
This kind of thing was popular.
Does it look good on me?
It looks good on you.
Not yet.
Can I?
You can.
I can.
I'm going to wear it from now on.
That's good.
You have a lot of butt hair.
Hey.
Butt again?
Yeah.
Your butt is bigger than before.
It's a little bigger.
Bigger is better.
Is that so?
Yeah.
But I can't complain about your age.
I like bigger.
Is that so?
I see.
You used to rub my butt when you were little.
Like this?
Yeah.
When you were little.
It's big now, isn't it?
Dai-chan.
Don't disturb me when I'm cleaning.
You used to do this when you were little.
Yeah.
You haven't changed.
No, I haven't.
Hey.
Dai-chan, you can clean up.
That's good.
I'll put this away.
Wait.
I can't concentrate.
You don't have to concentrate.
What?
I can't.
It's okay.
Just a little.
I did a lot, didn't I?
Wait.
I can't.
You like it a lot.
I know.
Do you usually do this?
What?
You don't have to draw a line like this.
Don't you know?
But...
What?
Why are you smiling like that?
Because...
I can see your bad eyes.
What?
Really?
Can you see them?
Let me see.
No, no, no.
Wait.
I can see them.
It's okay.
I'm just embarrassed.
I mean...
Can you stop touching me like that?
Like what?
How should I touch you?
How?
I can't.
What should I do?
Look at my eyes.
My eyes.
I can't.
Wait.
I told you I can't.
Don't touch me like that.
I can't.
I love you.
Do you?
Yes.
Come on.
Do you like me when I'm big and soft?
But I can't.
Come on.
I can't.
I can't stop touching you.
Look.
I can't.
I can't stop you.
I can't stop you from touching me like this.
I can't.
What do you mean?
I can't stop you.
Look.
I can't.
Can you listen to me?
I can.
What?
Why are you panting?
I'm not panting.
You're not panting.
I can't.
Don't touch me.
Close your eyes.
I can't.
Don't touch me.
You promised me.
I can't.
Don't touch me.
You promised me.
I can't.
Underneath are...
men, girls, appendages, ...
As they witnessed a young boy's death
in the middle of the forest
spezie drilling
おおきです。 It's cute.
こわいけどう、ぶっちゃけ明らかにかわいいですね。 I think I'm cute.
It's good, isn't it?
You like it, don't you?
Good, isn't it?
It's good, isn't it?
You like it, don't you?
and I just wanna dragon ball
don't care about baby
but I always wanted to eat dragon ball
but in the end, I can't
so I'll just eat by my self
eating is bad
Let's go!
It's hot hot!
Please stop…
Not yet…
I'm started to sweat…
I don't know if warm enough.
Here we go.
Oh no, oh no.
Oops.
Oh god, it hurts.
Take a closer look.
Here, you can eat it with your mouth, right?
Wait!
Hey! What are you doing?
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
You can't do that!
You're a good boy!
Please, don't do that!
You can't do that!
I told you you can't do that!
I couldn't do anything.
You couldn't do anything?
Don't bother her, okay?
This is the last time.
Did you eat?
Good boy.
Sorry, I was cleaning.
I was going to take a bath.
Did you want to take a bath?
It's going to take a while.
I'm sorry.
I'll wait for you.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Do you want to stay longer?
My husband is a clean man.
He told me that when we got married.
I had an impression of him recently.
Impression?
It was a long time ago.
It's hard to say.
You're all normal people.
Tell me.
I did something strange.
Did you do something weird?
That's right.
It's embarrassing.
I wonder if anyone in the store likes it.
People who like to do it themselves.
And I did some strange cosplay.
I thought it was a weird story.
Is that normal?
It's normal, but not yet.
I see.
Not yet.
More?
When I was a student, I was outside.
Outside?
I don't have money.
I see.
Because you don't have money.
Because I don't have money.
I was in the countryside.
I see.
Don't you have money?
You don't have money?
I don't have money.
What?
I have a lot of money.
You know too much.
I have a little knowledge.
You have a lot of curiosity.
What do you want to do?
I want to do a lot of things.
What are you talking about?
You don't allow a lot of things.
I don't allow it.
You are too confused.
You shouldn't do that.
It's not good.
There are many things.
There are many things in the world.
There are many ordinary things.
For example, an opening bar.
An opening bar.
I've been there before.
Have you been there?
I didn't know about it.
I didn't know about such a place.
Have you been there?
I've been there.
It's a bar.
I'm not wrong.
I went to a bar.
He was one of the characters of the film by Mr. Yamazaki.
Mr. Yamazaki?
Mr. Yamazaki was really old.
It was too vec that.
His mother was also a good person.
She was good in choosing good men.
She chose a man with a different personality from others.
She chose a man with good personality.
It's not all good things.
I see.
Yeah, yeah.
There are a lot of hard things in the world.
Yeah.
What are they?
Well, you go to a lot of places like that.
Yeah.
Make a meeting.
Learn a lot.
Like this, with an aunt.
It's not just a joke.
Ah! Wait!
What are you doing?
It's almost over.
Hey, it was almost over.
I was listening to the story.
What? Did you get dizzy?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
I've heard so many strange things.
It wasn't that bad.
What?
Well, was it bad?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Why are you always on your butt?
Ahhh!!
Hey, I can't take a bath.
You'll take a shower.
I want to see...
But I don't want to see.
I'm doing my best.
Oh, my God.
You can see me?
I can see you.
What?
Come on.
Don't look at me like that, okay?
Okay.
Oh, no.
Hey, hey.
What is it this time?
Oh, come on.
Don't touch me.
You're eating again.
Right?
Don't come out.
This?
Oh, come on.
Hang in there with this.
Come on.
Hang in there.
Oh, come on.
I just touched you.
Hey.
Oh, come on.
Don't make me bigger.
Don't do that.
Oh, come on.
Hey.
How many times do I have to do this to make you feel better?
Can't you stop it?
Oh, come on.
No, no, no.
Oh...
Oh, wait a second!
Wait a second!
Oh, no!
Don't go yet
I love you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Ah ah ah ah ah er
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, n
Aggghh...
My stomach's growling.
Exhale, exhale...
I'm going to pass out.
I can't help it.
Again?
What's wrong with you?
What?
No!
Wait a minute.
I told you no.
I can't help it.
It's all my fault.
I told you no.
I can't help it.
You're a good boy.
This is the last time.
Can you keep your promise?
I can't help it.
Dai-chan?
Oh, are you in the bathroom?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, I'm cleaning the bathroom.
It's okay, I can take it.
Do you have a girlfriend?
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
Don't ask me that.
I'm embarrassed.
I don't know.
I thought you were going to say something.
No, I'm not.
I'm just bored.
Bored?
I like it.
I like it so much.
Is that so?
This is the best.
I told you not to do it.
You're a bad boy.
I can't stop you.
What are you doing?
You're so beautiful that I want to lick you.
You can't do that.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Let's stop.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
I'm cleaning your ears.
You don't have to do it here.
I can't help it.
I want to do it here.
You're a bad boy.
What are you doing?
Is that so?
You're a bad boy.
I can't help it.
Why?
Why are you so angry?
I can't help it.
I'm mad.
Why?
I can't help it.
I'm sleepy...
Don't play with my nipples!
No...
I'm sleepy...
Don't play with my nipples!
What's wrong?
I'm sleepy...
Don't play with my nipples!
What?
Wait, what's wrong?
I told you not to play with my nipples!
I said I'm not going to play with your nipples!
I'm not going to play with your nipples!
No! No!
I can't do it.
Oh, my God!
I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it.
Make a fist.
Boo!!
Never mind.
Come on.
There're stuffy spots,
and you got some dirt on your face.
We have to clean up after you.
Can you help me?
Got it?
More.
More?
That's no good.
I'm going to stop touching your butt.
That's no good? Do you want to touch it?
Then I'll be selfish next time.
Thank you for your viewing.
I've never done it.
What?
I don't know how to do it.
How to do it?
Like this?
Can you do it?
I can do it.
You're an artist, aren't you?
That's right.
I think it's unfair.
It's not.
Yeah.
I might have graduated in something like that,
but I don't do that.
That's a little suspicious.
Well,
we're not doing that either.
Oh, yeah?
No.
What are you talking about?
Because...
You have such a beautiful butt.
But that's how it is.
We're a couple.
You have such a beautiful body.
I'm going to fall in love with you.
But you might be in love only now.
No, no.
I'm going to have sex with you forever.
Every day.
Really?
Every day?
That's impossible, isn't it?
I think I can do it every day.
Is that so?
But I used to do it every day before I got married.
It's too much, isn't it?
Well...
My husband used to be cool, too.
Now?
Now, he has a lot of beard, so I can't do it.
You look like that.
I look like that.
How can I put it?
I have the same face as him.
Well...
It's a little dull.
I see.
Don't you feel dizzy?
What? Who?
Your mother.
I don't feel dizzy.
She's always gone, isn't she?
Sometimes I want to, but...
She's almost never at home.
I see.
She always says,
She says,
It's suspicious.
It's suspicious, isn't it?
I'm getting anxious.
I'm going to Europe now.
It's far away.
I'm going.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You have a beautiful butt.
Do I?
Do you like that kind of butt?
It's my favorite butt.
I see.
Which one do you like?
Have you had a butt for a long time?
I've had a butt for a long time.
I see.
It's rare.
I like this kind of butt.
It's a butt.
I see.
I like this kind of butt.
No kidding.
I think there are a lot of big cats these days.
There are a lot of big cats.
I think so, too.
Even if they are small, they are cute.
I see.
I guess you like big buttocks.
I like big buttocks.
I think there are some good parts of the buttocks.
You're watching a lot of girls.
I'm not going to look at it.
You're not going to look at it, are you?
It's okay, it's okay.
You don't want the girl to get mad at you, do you?
I don't want her to get mad at me.
You're going to shake it like that, aren't you?
Oh, wait a minute.
I'm cleaning up.
Oh, I can't do that.
Oh, no.
You're not going to be able to do anything, are you?
Oh, wait a minute.
If you do that, you'll be fine.
You're not good enough for me now.
What if Mom finds out about this?
Oh, wait a minute.
I'm not good enough for Mom.
You're not even good enough to be spoiled.
So, can I just attack other people?
No, you can't.
I'll be in big trouble.
So, except for sex, you can't.
No sex.
No sex?
You can't do it anywhere but sex.
Really?
No sex?
You can't do it anywhere but sex.
You can't do it anywhere but sex?
I don't mind.
You don't mind?
Okay.
You're good. Did you close your mouth?
Yes, I did.
You did.
Can I kiss you?
Sure.
I kissed you.
You did?
Right.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
That's so cute
Yes?
It's good, isn't it?
Do you like it?
Please sit down.
It's good, isn't it?
I'm worried about you.
Does it feel good?
It's good, isn't it?
You want me to massage your face more, don't you?
You're happy, aren't you?
It's good, isn't it?
Do you feel good?
I'll give you a massage.
It's good, isn't it?
I'm worried about you.
Do you like it?
It's good, isn't it?
You want me to massage your face more, don't you?
I'll give you a massage.
It's good, isn't it?
Do you like it?
Do you want me to massage here, too?
It's good, isn't it?
Do you like it?
Ah, it's hot.
It's strange.
Do you want to be licked?
Do you want to lick each other?
Let's lick each other.
It's hot.
It's a little embarrassing.
Do you want to be licked?
Here?
Ah, it's hot.
Do you want to be licked?
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it's hot.
.........
Hey
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did you feel good?
Well, that's it for today.
Oh, wait!
It's over, isn't it?
You don't hate me, do you?
What about the promise?
No, no, no!
It's over, isn't it?
It's over.
Oh, my.
You just let it out, didn't you?
I did.
You let it out, didn't you?
But it hurts.
You should have told me.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, my.
No!
Oh, it's pain.
It's pain.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it hurts.
It's pain.
What's wrong with him?
I don't know what to do.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Here?
It feels good here.
It's amazing.
I can't do it.
It hurts so much.
No!
Oh, it's so cold.
Oh, it feels so good.
Does it work?
Was it good?
It's so sweet.
Stress...
Ah, kimchi...
Ah
Ah , kimchi...
This, this is crazy
Ah, this is crazy
Ah
C Levi
Ah, ah, ah, I don't want it, I don't wanna leave, I don't wanna feel like
Ahhh...
Ahh!
Ahhh!!!
Ahhh...
Ah!
This is amazing!!
Ahh!
A-hh...
roommates!
Ahh, where?
Ahh
Ah, this is okay...
Ohh
Ahh
Ah!
Ah, demons, smells, feeling stiff
Ah
Aaahhhhhhhhhh
Ahhhh
Ahhh
Ah, it's really ticklish
Mmmmm
Want to kiss me?
Mmmmmmm
Ah, ticklish
Ah
Are you trying to give me an eye massage?!
I think this is a good place.
Ah... this is a good space.
Oh, feel good
aha
Oh, it's so hard.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it feels good here.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, no.
Oh, it feels good here.
Oh, it's amazing.
Do you like it here?
It's cute. It's turning red.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it feels good here.
Oh, it's amazing here.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, no. It feels good here.
Oh, it feels good here.
Hey...
Are you okay?
Hey, I'm...
I'm just...
What happen?
Ah!
Ah, it feels so good.
Is it okay?
Not yet?
What are you doing?
You're moving again?
Ah, that's great.
You want to do it again?
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, here?
You want to do it again?
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, here?
I don't know what to do.
This is amazing.
I'm scared.
Ah, my head feels so good!
It hurts!
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
Ah!
Ah, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
Ah, it's amazing!
I made a mess.
You're so naughty.
I'll clean this up for you.
Ah, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
Does it feel good?
So, this is really the end.
What's your promise?
I'm going to break up with my husband.
Let's be together.
No, no, no.
Then, let's be a couple.
A couple?
No, you can't.
You can't be a couple.
Let's be a couple.
I'm going to break up with my husband.