Hi, Kichibana.
Hi.
Oh, Naik.
I'm Uso.
I'm Kichibana.
We're in the same class.
We're both from the same high school.
Yeah.
We're in the same high school.
I'm Kichibana.
I'm Naik.
I'm Uso.
We're both from the same high school.
What's up?
What are you doing? Shopping?
Yeah, I'm buying some stuff for work.
Oh, I see.
Do you have anything remote at home?
Oh, I have a massage salon at home.
Didn't I tell you?
I didn't know because there was no sign at home.
Oh, I see.
I make reservations online, so I have a private salon.
If you don't mind, I'll make it cheaper next time.
Oh, really?
I'll make a reservation.
Yeah, wait for me.
Yes.
Welcome.
Thank you for having me.
Please come in.
Come in.
This way, please.
It's very formal.
Oh, really?
Don't you have any luggage?
Oh, you're already here.
Oh, really?
It's like a salon.
It's like a massage salon.
Oh, I see.
Can I change my clothes here?
I'll change my clothes.
Did you change your clothes?
Let me know when you're done changing.
Yes, I'm done changing.
Okay.
Can I change my clothes here?
It's not cold, is it?
Yes, it's not cold.
Is it okay?
It's not cold, is it?
It's okay.
Don't you get this kind of massage often?
I get this kind of massage once a month.
I've never had this kind of massage before.
Oh, you don't use oil?
No, I don't.
I've never had this kind of massage before.
It's more comfortable here.
You watch a lot of smartphones, don't you?
Yeah, it is.
It's neck and shoulder.
Yeah, neck and shoulder.
Yeah, it's neck and shoulder.
Hey, it's out.
I'm sorry.
It's too small.
You're young.
You're getting shy.
I'm shy.
It's foot.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
It's hard.
That's why you're holding it down.
I have to hold it down.
Don't put your hand out.
I'm sorry.
Do men use this place?
I think so.
I think it's a place for decoration.
It's a place for decoration.
Do you often say decoration?
You know it well, don't you?
No, I don't.
Oh, you don't?
I'm going to decorate it.
It hurts, doesn't it?
It hurts a little, but that's...
Lymph.
Is that so?
Yeah, you'd better let it go.
What?
I thought you were going to move.
My body's moving.
Is your body moving?
Is it too painful?
No.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
It hurts.
It's moving, isn't it?
It hurts a little.
Hey, it's hitting you.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
It's moving.
Yes.
What are you doing?
I was surprised.
I'm sorry.
Here.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Ahh!
Stop.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Stop.
It's fine, isn't it?
Super violent footage from this place.
I'm going to make a hole in the middle of the cake.
What happened to her?
What??
Hey, don't go!
Mom, why?
I'm about to sleep.
Maika, what are you doing?
I don't know what to do.
Rin, Rin, Rin!
Rin!
Rin, wait...
Ah...
I'm sleepy...
You can't sleep like this...
I'm sorry...
It's hot...
No...
You can't sleep in this cold.
But I'm so beautiful...
There are many pretty girls in the university, right?
No, there aren't.
Not like you.
You're so beautiful and sexy.
I can't stand it anymore.
Because...
I'm still standing.
Do you think so?
Yes.
Can I do more?
I want to do more.
I can't do it like this.
Rin, Rin, Rin!
Rin, what's wrong?
It's the best.
I want to sleep.
I can't do it.
Rin, what's wrong?
Mother…
I'm gonna snooze you
This is no good
Don't cry
Smile
Cry
Come on
Food!
It's no good...
I wonder what you might think of that...
Children don't
Children don't need
children don't need
根
It's
it's
I
is
You
are
evil
I
Did i just
tell
I
them
that
well
are
that
Oh, no, oh, no...
My multiple rheumatoid arthritis.
I want you to accept my condition.
I think I've seen this happen before.
This happens over and over again.
Oh, it's coming down...
I panic.
More than I thought, I was pressured by Mom.
Please raise your head.
Good boy.
Pervert...
Stop laughing.
Please put an end to this huehuehue
You just released one accidentally how do you still have some of this left
I don't want to do this, it gets me sad.
I don't know what I'm doing, but I'm trying to do my best.
I'm trying to do my best, but I'm trying to do my best.
I'm trying to do my best, but I'm not trying to do it.
I'm trying to do my best when I'm struggling.
I'm struggling when I'm trying to do my best.
Trying to do my best when I'm struggling.
Is the beginning heavy?
It's too big for you.
How is it compared to your husband?
Don't ask me that.
It's bigger than my husband.
I'm glad to hear that.
Ouch!
What?
What's wrong?
I told you it's over.
What?
I don't feel good.
Thank you very much
ah
ah, feels good
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
ah ah%&¥≡¥≡$≡∥
Ahcraftkan
Ah
No.
Which one do you feel better?
I feel better.
I'm glad you're okay.
I feel great.
Calm down.
I'm glad you're okay.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Ahhhhhhhhhhh
呼
はぁ
ぁ
気持ちよかったですね
旦那には絶対内緒にして
I'm so excited.
Don't say that.
I want you to continue massaging.
No, but it's too late today, so let's do it next time.
All right.
I'm so excited.
Dai, weren't you supposed to be home?
I was going to sweat a bit.
Can I use the shower?
I didn't notice.
I'm going to shower now. Can you wait a minute?
Let's take a shower together.
I'll wash my hair.
I'm really sorry.
Poco, you aren't shooting like you're going to fight, are you?
Poco can't help the power ofpletty.
I can't believe he's taking it all off.
It's been a while since I've had someone wash my hair.
Have you ever had a husband wash your hair?
No, I haven't had a husband for a long time.
Have you ever had sex?
No, I haven't.
How old is your husband?
He's an old man. He's over 10 years older than me.
Oh, is that so? He's a long way from me.
So, you've been married for a long time.
Yes, I have.
I see. You've lost your husband.
Yes, we're a family.
Your breasts are too big.
I have to get bigger breasts.
Oh, my God.
It's already clean.
I haven't washed it yet.
It's not that dirty.
I have to wash it gently.
It's dirty.
Oh, my God.
By the way, you said you were different from your husband.
What did I say?
You said you were different from your husband.
That's not true.
You're bigger.
Which one do you like?
Why are you asking me that?
This one.
Oh, my God.
It's already clean.
It's already clean?
You said the same thing as me.
Do you want me to wash it?
I'll wash it.
What is it?
Oh, my God.
I can't do this..
Oops!
I haven't got it yet!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
, um, um, um,
Yes,
yeah,
ah, ah, ah,
Yeah,
yeah,
yuk
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
ahhhhhhhhh
ahhhhhhhhhh
ahhh
ahhhhhhhhhhh
gsh
hhhhhh
posso
(?)
~~~~
rr
gas
ahhhhhh
hhhhhhhhhhhhh
go!
I got dirty again.
I'll be back in a few minutes, so let's get this over with.
I'll come back again.
I'm back.
You're back.
I'll be back.
Oh, right. You don't have anything like last time, do you?
I'm fine.
I've pulled out all my muscles.
Is that so?
I think I'm fine.
I'll start with your legs.
You've loosened up a lot since last time.
You're touching my boobs.
Why?
You've pulled it out to the limit, haven't you?
Wasn't that enough?
What's that?
I told you not to do that.
It's sticking out.
What?
You can't do that.
I'll do it directly.
Wait a minute.
I'm wearing a sexy dress today.
That's not true.
I'm sorry.
I'm just touching your boobs.
You can do it directly.
What?
Directly?
Yes.
No.
My boobs are out.
Hey, that's not a poop.
That's not a poop.
No.
Ame♥
Momma....
What?
Mom!?
I want you to lick my teeth~~
You?
What? What are you gonna do??
Eh!??
numb
Eh? Are you okay with that?
Lick your teeth, my Product consent
I will never get your teeth licked
You want it to get licked?
Yeah
What are you doing?
Are you a baby?
Are you still a baby?
Babies don't lick like that.
What are you doing?
Are you still a baby?
What?
What are you doing?
What do you want me to do?
Do you want me to pat you?
What are you doing?
I made it moist with oil.
Does it feel good?
Wow!
Oh, it's hot.
Thank you for your hard work.
Could you do it a little more?
Why? It's not.
It's annoying.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
Yeah,
I see,
you were
Haha
On top of the face?
Good boy.
Here.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, reflecting, um, um
Um
Give me your hand...
No...
There, there...
There.
Give me your hand...
I am sorry.
My boyfriend isn't a child anymore.
Don't mind me.
The reason you feel stressed out is that you are no longer able to touch your baby.
You can tell that your babies generally care about your home.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
ah ah ah ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah ah ah pag
Bacon
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
You're way too young.
You still feel a little strange on your feet, don't you?
But I can't do this anymore.
I maybe shouldn't have dated you.
You're too kind, ma'am.
I shouldn't compliment you.
In the future, I want to be a massage therapist.
Is that so?
I want to be cool when I massage your stomach.
I see. Thank you.
Can you teach me?
Teach you?
What should I do?
I'm the type to learn in real life.
Can I do it?
Oh, I see.
Do you want me to do it?
Do you remember what I did?
Yes.
Like this, right?
I think it's a little stronger.
Stronger?
Then I'll do it a little stronger.
How is it?
It's very soft.
How do you say it?
I'll check the softness.
It's not stiff, is it?
Is it soft?
I think it's normal.
Is it stiff?
Did you teach me?
Did you do this?
Yes, it's good.
It's very soft.
Your buttocks did this, right?
Yes.
Here, too.
It's good.
Please turn your head.
Turn my head?
Yes.
What do you mean, it's good?
I mean it's soft.
Oh, you mean it's soft.
It's good.
Please turn your head a little.
Why?
Because it's soft.
Here, too.
It's good.
You did this, too.
Yes.
It's a little hard on the inside.
Here, too.
It's a little hard.
It's good.
It's like this.
It's a little uneven.
It's uneven?
Yes.
Here, too.
Here, too?
Yes.
It's good.
Why?
It's not good.
I don't massage here.
You don't massage here?
Yes.
It's here.
It's uneven.
It's just right.
It's here.
What?
I don't massage here.
No.
What?
It feels good.
I don't massage here.
That's not the kind of massage I want to learn.
I want to learn this kind of massage.
Is that so?
I don't massage here.
You don't massage here?
I want to try oil massage.
What?
You know, when you put on clothes, you have to take them off, right?
You mean take them off?
Yes.
No, that's embarrassing.
Please.
Are you serious?
What? Are you serious?
No way.
Pants?
Yes.
Hey, it's embarrassing.
What? What? What? You surprised me.
What?
What? What?
This side too?
Pants is the best.
Pants?
What?
What? It's embarrassing.
Okay.
Wow.
No way.
Hey.
Okay, let's get started.
How much should I put on?
I don't know.
About that much?
Okay, I'll go.
Okay.
No.
Hey, no.
More?
No.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Vicki.
I'm sorry, but I can't help but laugh when I see you like this.
Hey, do you want to practice?
If you pinch me with this, I might be able to calm down.
What do you mean?
I'm not a calm person.
If you pinch me with this, I'll calm down.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
Do you want me to pinch you?
I'm sorry.
Do you have time tomorrow?
I have an appointment tomorrow, but I can't come.
Then I'll take a break.
Are you sure?
I don't mind if I'm fired.
I don't mind.
See you tomorrow.
I'm looking forward to it.
Are you sure?
I'm glad to hear that.
Then I'll have you sit over there.
I'm looking forward to it.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm hitting your boobs.
What?
Your boobs.
I'm not hitting anything.
Are you doing it on purpose?
What do you mean?
I'm inviting you.
I'm not inviting you.
You're hitting me a lot.
What?
You said you wanted me to decorate your boobs.
It feels good.
What's wrong?
It's good.
Look up slowly!
You look exhausted.
You look really hungry.
Okay, I'm going to apply it.
OK, I'm going to apply it.
Okay, I'm going to apply it..
Okay, I'm going to apply.
Is my voice coming out?
My voice is coming out, isn't it?
I have to hold it in.
I haven't finished yet!
I will get a stomachache sometimes.
Sleep tight, okay?
Now, please stand facing me
Go ahead!
I can't do it anymore.
What should I do?
You can still do it, right?
You have a big belly.
Does it feel good?
I can't do it anymore.
It's so hot.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
It's so hard.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
It feels good.
Do you want more?
I'll give you more.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Did you drink up everything?
It's hot.
It felt good.
Could you marry me?
I can't.
Could you be my wife?
Thank you for watching.