How is it?
I think I can do it in a little while.
I think I'm done.
Really?
That's amazing.
That was fast.
That was a great help.
How is it?
Can I see?
I think I'm done.
That's great.
I was worried about you.
Not at all.
My husband is on a business trip.
I don't think I can help you.
What should I do with this?
That's great.
Can I see?
Where is your husband on a business trip?
He is in India now.
He is far away.
He won't be back for a while.
I'm in trouble.
That was a great help.
You can call me anytime.
Are you okay? Are you a student?
I'm a college student.
I see.
What are you studying?
I'm studying economics.
You look smart.
I know economics.
You know economics.
What is 1 plus 1?
I don't know.
You are smart.
You don't have to go to college.
Are you in bad conditions?
Not really.
Maybe I'll call you anytime.
You are so difficult.
You are so stupid.
There are so many questions in this book.
I'm going to go home now.
Why?
Take your time.
I'll make you some tea.
I'm sorry I didn't make you any tea.
Is that okay?
I have delicious tea.
Take your time.
I'm going home.
Hayashi, are you in a club?
I'm in a club, but I don't go much.
You're a college student, so you have to be young.
I have a lot of plans.
What did you do?
I had a girlfriend last night.
Really?
That's great.
But we broke up.
Why?
I don't know.
You don't seem to be in a relationship.
What happened?
It's okay. I have a lot of experience.
Really?
I've been to a lot of places.
How do you say it?
At night...
It happens.
Really?
What do you mean?
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Why did you do that?
You're wet.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
You're wet.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I just need to wash my hair.
I don't think it's wet.
I'm sorry.
How much do you have?
What are you doing?
Don't do that.
That's why you got wet.
That's not true.
What are you doing?
This.
It's too big.
This is the reason why girls like me.
Can you do me a favor?
What is it?
Wait a minute.
I think it's good to like someone for the first time.
You said you were walking around.
I wanted someone who had a lot of experience to do it.
It's important to do it for the first time.
I think you should do it.
Really?
Are you really a virgin?
I'm really a virgin.
It's the third time.
The third time?
I can't live like this anymore.
Please.
I'm really sorry.
Are you okay?
But...
I have a husband.
After all...
That's not good, is it?
Wait a minute.
At least...
Then...
Can you take a closer look at this?
What?
It's big.
Is it big?
Because...
Am I as big as my arm?
Well...
My wrist...
It's as big as my arm.
That's amazing.
This is still a handle.
What?
Is it going to be bigger?
It's going to be a little bigger.
I...
Can't I?
Wait a minute.
Can I?
I can't.
I really want to put it in.
I want to graduate as a virgin.
But this...
I...
I don't think it's going to fit.
Just a little bit.
Just here.
If you do that, I won't be a virgin.
Isn't it okay?
If this is the case...
I don't know.
Please.
If this is the case, isn't it okay?
Well...
If that's the case...
That's good.
That's not true.
I don't want to go.
You said it was okay.
Please.
I don't know.
Wait a minute.
But...
I can't put it in.
Can you put it on your panties?
Can I put it on my panties?
Put it on your panties.
Please.
Here.
Then...
Just rub it.
Just a little bit.
It's amazing.
It's big.
Just a little bit.
Please rub it a little more.
It's big.
Wait a minute.
Just rub it a little more.
I think I can put it in.
Leave it to me.
It's here, isn't it?
It's amazing.
Here...
This is...
It's amazing.
I can't put it in.
Just a little bit.
Is it okay?
Wait a minute.
I'll do everything.
Leave it to me.
I'll let you graduate.
That's all.
I don't know if I can put it in.
Wait a minute.
Just a centimeter.
I think it's okay.
I'll keep it a secret.
I'll do my best.
Wait a minute.
This is...
Just a little bit.
No, no, no.
Don't move.
I think I can put it in.
It's a little big.
Just a centimeter.
I can't put it in.
I can't do it anymore.
I'll get a bump.
I can't put it in.
I'll put it in.
It's really big.
You've already lost weight, so it's fine.
I still can't feel it.
I'd like you to roll around.
I can't do it.
It's big.
I was surprised.
It feels good.
It's big.
I'm sorry.
Yeah...
It's hot...
Thank god I'm fine...
I'm finally graduated...
Yeah.
Yeah...
I'm feeling good...
Oh, my heart...
What's happening...
Oh, my god...
Oh, my god!
Is this going to keep happening to me?
Oh, my gosh!
Oh!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry I slept.
Why?
I'm sorry.
Why did you sleep?
And you slept a lot.
I'm sorry.
I have a husband.
Well, you're my wife.
You're amazing.
You slept a lot.
Is this your first time?
It's my first time.
Was it okay?
It felt good.
Is that okay?
It's like a warrior.
What?
Do you want to taste it?
It's not good.
It wasn't good.
Have you ever kissed?
I've never kissed.
Your first kiss was like a warrior.
I can't forget it.
What's wrong?
My boobs.
What?
Your boobs?
My boobs.
What's wrong?
Do you want to touch it?
It's amazing.
Have you ever touched your boobs?
It's my first time.
You can touch it.
Wow.
You're amazing.
You have a lot of boobs.
Do you want to touch it?
It's okay.
This is how you touch your boobs.
Gently.
It's funny.
Do you want to touch it?
It's okay.
It's hard to touch your boobs.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Let me see.
I'll show you.
Is this okay?
It's okay.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
It's been a while.
It's okay.
Wow.
You like boobs, don't you?
Yes.
I love boobs.
It's cute.
Do you want to lick it?
You have a lot of boobs.
Do you like boobs?
Yes.
I have a lot of boobs, too.
Lick it.
Let me do it.
Are you happy?
Give me your hand.
That's amazing.
Are you interested in boobs?
I'm very interested in boobs.
Really?
I want you to lick it.
Do you want to lick it?
That's amazing.
Use your tongue.
You're very good at this.
That's amazing.
It's amazing that you're interested in boobs.
Do you want to lick your pussy?
That's right.
No, no, no.
Slowly.
That's right.
Like this.
Don't move it.
There's a place where it tickles, right?
That's right.
It feels good.
That's amazing.
Were you surprised?
It's okay.
It's not scary.
It feels good.
It's dirty, so lick it.
Please open your mouth.
I got you to lick me, so I'll lick you, too.
It feels good.
Really?
I didn't touch you, but you were standing all the time.
Wow!
I've never seen such a big one.
It's the size of my face, isn't it?
I can't put my mouth in.
Just a little bit.
It's all in.
But this is a little...
If it's this big...
I think I'm going to be swallowed.
I have to be as experienced as I am.
I can only put my mouth in.
That's amazing.
I can't put my mouth in.
I don't want to bother you.
I'm going to put my mouth in.
I can't put my mouth in.
It's getting bigger.
I think I can put my mouth in again.
I'm just helping my neighbor.
I can't put my mouth in.
I only put my mouth in a little bit.
I think it's okay.
That's amazing.
I only put my mouth in a little bit.
I put my mouth in.
That's amazing.
I only put my mouth in a little bit.
I'm not cheating.
I'm just a volunteer.
What's wrong?
I'm going to put my mouth in.
That's amazing.
I put my mouth in.
I'm sorry.
That's amazing.
What should I do?
Do you want to try it?
It's your first time, right?
I'll help you.
Really?
Come here.
Okay.
That's amazing.
Do you know where it is?
It's here.
Slowly.
I put my mouth in slowly.
That's amazing.
That's right.
I put my mouth in a little bit.
That's amazing.
I move my waist like this.
I move my waist back and forth.
Not up.
Like this?
That's right.
Wait a minute.
That's amazing.
You're moving.
No, no, no.
Don't put it in right away.
Put it in right away.
That's amazing.
No, no, no.
What's wrong?
That's amazing.
I move my waist like this.
Don't do that.
That's amazing.
You're doing it again.
I won't forgive you.
You can still do it.
Because you're energetic.
I knew you could do it.
You're very energetic.
That's amazing.
You're a little too energetic.
You just did it.
That's amazing.
You're doing it again.
You're moving a lot.
That's amazing.
I'm tired.
I fell asleep.
The chair is about to break.
Come here.
From behind.
I'm tired.
It's easy to move.
From behind.
All of it.
You can see it.
That's how it feels.
That's...
I can't move.
That's how it feels.
I'm sorry.
I was surprised.
Did you want to move?
You're doing it all the time.
That's amazing.
That's great.
I'm drunk.
It's been a long time since I had sex.
I don't know why.
That's amazing.
Hold on.
I told you.
I told you again.
I'm sorry.
How many times do I have to tell you?
That's amazing.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
I see.
That's good.
What do you want to talk about?
I'm sorry.
I can't sleep.
There's no reaction at all.
It's open.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I turned on the intercom.
Really?
I didn't notice.
What's wrong?
I put my luggage in the wrong place.
Really?
What's wrong?
Thank you.
What were you doing?
Yoga.
Don't you know?
Have you ever done it?
I've never done it.
Do you want to try it?
I'll try it.
I'll show you how to do it.
Look at it.
Okay.
Thank you for your luggage.
Put it there.
Stretch your upper body like this.
It feels good.
It stretches a lot.
It stretches, doesn't it?
Put your legs together like this.
It's fun.
It's soft.
Really?
If you do yoga, you'll get softer.
If you do yoga, you'll be like a cat.
I want to be a cat.
I want to run on the back road.
I want to run anywhere.
I want to stretch my hip joints like this.
If your hip joints are stiff, you'll get back pain.
It's better to stretch.
It's stretching.
It's stretching a lot.
It's stretching, isn't it?
It stretches like this.
It's also good for muscle training.
It's good.
It's tightening here.
I think this is a good example.
It's like a cat.
Right?
It's like a cat peeing.
That's right.
It really feels good.
It's stretching a lot.
Take a deep breath like this.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
Repeat this slowly.
If you do that, you'll feel like you're getting stronger.
The rest is like this.
Like this.
Shrink.
Stretch.
Like this.
It's really good.
Really?
Do you want me to help you?
No, I just want to help you.
Look at me.
It's surprisingly difficult.
It's pretty good.
It's good, isn't it?
Wait a minute.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Hayashi-kun became a cat.
I'm lost.
I'm sorry.
What were you doing?
What's wrong with you?
I was looking at your butt.
What's this?
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It's good, isn't it?
The blood flow is good.
The blood flow here is good, too.
Hayashi-kun's blood flow is good, too.
Will you improve my blood flow?
Yes.
Give me your hand.
You really like my boobs.
I love your boobs.
I love your butt, too.
Yes.
I think my blood flow will improve.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's not good for you.
I was surprised.
I was surprised to see your sexy body.
Your blood flow has improved.
Yes.
I can see it.
It's just a little.
Do you lick me?
It's okay.
You're rubbing my boobs.
It's just a little.
I can't stand it anymore.
If you rub my boobs so much, I can't stand it anymore.
It's just a little.
I can't stand it anymore.
Your buttocks are amazing.
I love your buttocks.
You can touch me as much as you want.
Do you touch me so much?
It's just a little.
It's okay.
Your buttocks are amazing.
It's just a little.
Is it soft?
If I take it off, it'll be even softer.
It's just a little.
I took it off.
You have a lot of panties.
You look like a virgin.
I used to be a virgin.
Can you see all my buttocks?
Are you excited to wear panties?
I'm excited.
You're cute.
What's wrong?
It's just a little.
Your buttocks?
I can't help it.
It's just a little.
Does it feel good?
I'm training.
I'm sorry.
I want to train more.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
It's warm.
What are you doing?
It's just a little.
You have a lot of panties.
I'm sorry.
It's hard.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Isn't it a little intense?
It's just a little.
You're getting faster.
What's wrong?
It's just a little.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I was too excited.
You're calm.
I'm sorry.
I can't believe you'll forgive me.
I'll forgive you.
It's just a little.
You're really calm.
It's still a long way off.
It's just a little.
Can you rub me a little more?
It's hot.
Is it close?
Can you rub me a little more?
It's just a little.
I can't.
I'll definitely move my hips.
It's just a little.
It's hot.
What?
Can you rub me a little more?
Can I?
It's just a little.
It's hot.
Can I?
It's just a little.
It's hot.
Can you rub me a little more?
It's just a little.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's just a little.
You slept a lot.
Really?
Really.
You slept a lot.
It's hot.
It's just a little.
You slept a lot.
It's hot.
It's just a little.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sorry.
You can't do it anymore?
I can't do it anymore.
It was just a little.
It's hot.
I'm done cleaning.
Really?
Wait a minute.
I have to clean the bath.
You're good at cleaning.
I am.
It's very clean.
Thank you.
Doesn't your husband clean?
My husband?
My husband...
I don't think he does much.
Does Ayashi clean a lot?
I like cleaning.
That's great.
It's disgusting.
You're cleaning your room.
I am.
You're a boy.
Boys don't throw away plastic bottles.
That's right.
That's great.
You're cleaning your room.
No, I'm not.
What's wrong?
Is your husband like that, too?
My husband...
I think he's a free spirit.
People in the past...
There are a lot of people.
There are people who get stuck.
That's right.
What kind of people?
Let me see.
People who like to go outside.
People who want to pee.
Did you do that?
I don't know if I did it or not.
That's great.
I cosplay.
I want people to step on me.
There are a lot of people.
What do you like?
Me?
When I look around, I think I'm the most normal.
When you look around...
I'd like to ask you something.
What is it?
How was my penis compared to your husband's?
It's big.
Hayashi-kun's is bigger.
If my husband was a hamster, Hayashi-kun would be a dog.
It's completely different.
What do you think?
It feels good.
Did it feel good to have a penis?
What are you talking about?
It's a secret.
Please tell me.
Hayashi-kun...
You have to increase your experience.
You just graduated.
That's right.
That's great.
I was surprised to see you swing so much.
It was amazing.
When I looked at your butt, it moved naturally.
It was amazing to see you swing so much.
It felt good.
Why is your butt so big?
Did you do something?
I didn't do anything.
It's embarrassing to have a big butt.
There aren't many people who can wear skirts.
It's amazing.
The shape is beautiful.
It's soft.
If you praise me so much, I want to make you something delicious.
Really?
I'm hungry.
What do you like?
Curry.
Let's have curry tonight.
Really?
Your house is amazing.
I wanted to be a child.
Do you want to be a child?
No.
It's embarrassing to have such a big child.
It's amazing.
It's pretty clean.
Look in the mirror.
What's wrong?
The mirror is a little dirty.
Really?
What are you doing?
I was wondering what was wrong.
Something is hitting you.
It's too soft.
Is it hard?
It's going to leak.
It's disgusting.
What is it?
Is it here?
It's dirty.
I keep cleaning.
It's hard.
Is there any alcohol in it?
No.
Did you fart?
It's too dirty.
I'm cleaning.
Don't fall.
I'm fine.
What are you doing?
It's a little damp.
That's not true.
It's hot.
I'm sweating.
Mom.
I'm polishing my technique.
Please polish the mirror.
I can't polish it.
I'm being polished.
Don't polish me.
It's hot.
I hit my head.
It's okay.
Can I take it off?
What is it?
What are you doing?
I don't understand.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It's damp.
It's hot.
It's damp because of you.
It's amazing.
Let me touch you.
I don't want to touch you.
Does it feel good?
You're cute.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
What are you doing?
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
You're sweating a lot.
I'll clean your ears.
It's hot.
You're good at cleaning ears.
I'm good at cleaning ears.
I'll do it again.
It's hot.
You're lucky.
What is it?
You don't like it?
You want to drink more, don't you?
Because you're big.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
It's a spice.
It's a feeling.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. It's a feeling.
You put it in your mouth.
It's a feeling.
It was sweet, wasn't it?
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
You're standing up.
Hey.
I'm not satisfied.
I'm sorry.
Come here.
I knew you could do it.
I'm sorry.
I'll clean up for you.
Oh, no.
It's amazing.
It's normal now.
It's a feeling.
I've been holding back until now.
It's amazing.
It's a feeling.
I can't stop.
Oh, no.
It's a feeling.
I'm sorry.
You've been holding back, haven't you?
I'll clean up for you.
Let's have dinner together.
Come and eat.
It's curry tonight.
It's curry.
The food was really good.
Really?
I'm glad.
Do you drink?
Yes, I do.
I drink alcohol.
There are many kinds.
Do you want me to bring something else?
Do you still have it?
Yes, I do.
Wait a minute.
It's amazing.
I didn't have this one.
Thank you very much.
I'll put it here.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know what to bring.
What's wrong?
You're getting bigger.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
Look at your butt again.
You're getting bigger.
You're a tough guy.
It's amazing.
You're getting bigger.
What's wrong?
What are you looking at?
What?
What's wrong with your boobs?
What's wrong?
It's amazing.
You're getting tougher.
Did you want to touch me?
Yes.
My nipples are exposed.
I see.
Your nipples.
My nipples are exposed.
My nipples are even more exposed.
Let me touch your nipples.
Yes.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
What's wrong?
You're cute.
I'll pat you directly.
What's wrong?
You're more energetic.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
What?
Do you want to sleep?
I want to sleep.
Really?
You're cute.
Did you get excited because of my nipples?
Yes.
Your nipples are really big.
It's amazing.
I thought you'd get excited.
Do you want to sleep?
I'm going to sleep.
What's wrong?
I'll pat you directly.
Do you want to sleep?
You're cute.
It's amazing.
Why are your nipples so hard?
What's wrong?
Your ears are getting hot.
Your body is hot.
It's amazing.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying again?
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
I didn't say it's okay.
There's a lot.
Are you okay?
I'm in trouble.
It's amazing.
What's wrong?
I'm surprised.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
I just took it out.
Your butt is amazing.
It's too erotic.
How's your day going?
I've gained weight again.
Really?
Let me see.
It's true.
It's amazing.
Are you sleepy?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
What's wrong?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
You've gained weight again.
It's amazing.
What's wrong?
I might go again.
What?
I'm going.
Are you sure?
I can't do it.
Please wait.
It's amazing.
You've gained a lot of weight.
Let me see.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Thank you for the meal.
It's amazing.
What?
You shouldn't look at me like this.
It's amazing.
What was that all of a sudden?
I was surprised.
You were the one who called me, weren't you?
You came in when I was peeing.
I was surprised.
You were showing off.
Let's go.
Thank you for the meal.
I was wondering when you'd come.
I was surprised.
It was like the beginning.
It's amazing.
You came in today.
You came in right away.
It's amazing.
What?
It feels good here, too.
Do you know that?
It's the soles of my feet.
It's getting bigger again.
It's always big.
It's amazing.
You're good at touching.
Do you want to put your fingers in here?
Yeah.
It's in there.
What's wrong?
Did it hurt?
Can you get in there?
You couldn't get in there.
You want this side, don't you?
One.
Two.
Five.
Hug me.
Yuu-chan.
Nine.
Touch me.
I'm scared.
It's amazing.
I hugged you.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I love you.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's a little tight here.
Is it good?
It's amazing.
I was excited while I was holding you.
But I didn't think you'd be able to get in there.
I want you to show me your feet.
It's okay.
Come here.
You're out.
You're already wet.
It's all tangled up.
Put your fingers in.
It's wrong, isn't it?
I told you to put your fingers in.
It feels good to put your fingers in.
Show me more of your feet.
That's right. Move your feet.
It's amazing.
You're getting better.
You're good.
Stop it.
Make it clean.
It's amazing.
Who made you wet?
You're wet.
It's amazing.
It's like this.
It's okay if it's just a centimeter.
Is it a centimeter again?
It's just a centimeter.
It's just a little more.
Try moving it.
It's a little shaky.
It's just a centimeter.
I can't stand it.
Move it further.
What?
Please move it further.
I can't stand it.
It's just a centimeter.
Please move it further.
I can't stand it.
Young people are amazing.
I can stand it easily.
A neighbor asked me if I was biting a dog.
I'm scared.
I'm tired.
What?
Do you want to put it in here again?
It's just a little.
I can't stand it.
It hurts.
It's just a little.
I'm tired.
My back hurts.
What's wrong?
It's pretty swollen.
Wait a minute.
I can't do it.
It hurts.
Urgh...
Oh, god...
How many times do I have to do this?
It's so slimy...
Oh, god...
I want to do it again.
Can I do it again?
Yes, you can.
Come here.
Rub my back.
Okay.
Oh, god...
Why?
Again?
Again.
But here...
Oh, god...
If I rub your back a little more, it'll feel better.
Just one centimeter.
No, I can't.
Oh, god...
Hang in there.
I can't stand it anymore.
Oh, god...
You like being healed, don't you?
Hang in there.
Is it that hard?
I can't do it anymore.
Hang in there.
Oh, god...
You remember that, right?
Yes.
It feels so good.
From the beginning.
It's good.
It's big and hard.
But it feels so good.
Oh, god...
Do it more.
It feels so good.
Oh, god...
I can't do it anymore.
Hang in there.
Oh, god...
I can't do it anymore.
Come here.
Do it more.
Oh, god...
I forgot that it's just a little bit.
It's okay.
I want to do it more.
I'll do it just a little bit more.
Oh, god...
I can't do it anymore.
I threw up.
Oh, god...
I can't do it anymore.
It's like a custom massage.
I'll do it more.
What?
No.
How much do you want me to do?
I want you to do it.
What should I do?
I mean...
Oh, god...
Why...
Why do you pull it out again?
I'll do it more.
Oh, god...
I can't do it anymore.
Why did you do that?
I didn't.
I'll do it more.
Oh, god...
It feels good.
I'll do it more.
Don't stop me.
What?
I didn't do that.
Make me feel better.
Don't stop me.
I can't do it.
I'll do it more.
I know.
Don't stop me.
I can't do it anymore.
It hurts.
I'm full.
I almost died.
I'll do it more.
I can't do it anymore.
You're getting old.
I can do it more.
I can't do it anymore.
I'll do it more.
I can do it more, I can do it more.
I can't do it anymore.
I'll do it more.
I can do it more, I can do it more.
I can't do it anymore.
I'll give you a little more.
I'll give you 1 cm more.
You don't want to?
You don't want to, do you?
pregnancy
You gotteraught
There is no time
Oh my god
I got it
I can feel your breath.
Ah, it's heavy...
Mana, are you going to spit it out?
Don't do that.
How's the number?
Here it goes.
Ah~~~
One centimeter.
You do feel weird when I blow your top.
You had a full top earlier.
Yeah, it's weird, but nice.
That feels great.
Oh~!
I want to put it in my mouth.
I can't let go of it.
You want to let it out, don't you?
I want to let it out.
I want to put it in my mouth.
I'm glad I let it out.
I didn't say it was okay until now.
It was the best.
What time is it now?
It's sweet.
My husband is coming home today, isn't he?
I see.
When is he coming back?
Today.
Is he coming back?
He said he was at the station.
Isn't he coming back soon?
Wait a minute.
I'm going home.
I'm glad to hear that.
Wait a minute.
Come here.
I'm going home.
I've missed you.
I'm sorry.
I'll look forward to seeing you.
See you later.
Be careful.
Thank you for watching!