You've been running all this time, haven't you?
Hey, you.
No, no.
You're from the lower floor?
Yes.
Oh, I see.
Hey, if you don't mind, would you like to have a drink with me?
With you?
Yes, in my room.
Let's go.
Can I?
Wait a minute.
Here we go.
Here you are.
Is this enough?
That's enough.
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's have a toast.
Yes.
To our meeting.
Cheers.
Oh, it's delicious.
It's good to drink wine in the afternoon.
It's good.
I'm happy to have a glass of wine after work.
Do you do this job?
Yes, I do.
I bought this wine locally.
Oh, really?
Isn't it a good wine?
Yes, it is.
It's a French wine.
Oh, really?
Did you go to France?
Yes, I did.
I've seen a lot of places.
I envy you.
Can you go to France for work?
Yes, but it's hard.
It's a long flight.
My shoulders hurt, my back hurts, and my legs hurt.
I see.
Yes.
Can you go sightseeing?
Sightseeing?
Just a little.
Just a little?
Yes, just a little.
But I've been there many times.
I see.
That's right.
Oh, my legs are tired.
Oh, my legs are swollen.
Can someone give me a massage?
Let's do it.
What?
Can I?
I've already had a massage.
That's kind of you.
Then I'll give you a massage.
I'll give you a massage.
Like this?
Oh, yeah.
I'll give you a stronger massage.
Like this?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's swollen, isn't it?
It's very soft.
Is it soft?
Oh, yeah.
Yes, yes.
Like this.
Like this?
Yes, yes.
Like this.
You're pretty good at it.
Have you ever had a massage?
I've never had a massage with my mom.
Oh, really?
Oh.
Yes, yes, yes.
This leg, too.
This leg?
Yes.
It feels pretty good.
Legs?
Oh, yeah.
There's a lot of acupuncture points on the back of your legs.
How long are your legs?
My legs?
Yes.
Only 23.5 centimeters.
That's just right.
Is it just right?
Oh, really?
Oh, yeah.
It tickles.
Oh, yeah?
I don't think so.
Does it bother you that much?
No, I'm just massaging.
Oh, thank you.
I'm concentrating.
Don't you smell it?
No, I don't.
Really?
Can I lick you?
Look.
Legs.
Yes.
Can I pet you?
Can I?
Yes.
I don't think so.
You want to lick me, don't you?
Look.
It tickles.
Do you like stockings?
I like stockings.
You're different.
You're funny.
Don't you smell it?
No, I don't.
Then lick me more.
Look.
It tickles, doesn't it?
Come on, lick me.
It's warm.
You're sitting on me.
Don't you smell it?
No, I don't.
I don't smell it.
You're like a pervert.
It tickles a lot.
It tickles.
I'm going to lick you with a towel.
I'm drooling and my feet are sticky.
Is it good?
If you lick me so much, I'll feel like a pervert.
Your face is sticky.
You're drooling.
Come here.
You're sticky.
What does it taste like?
You're drooling.
Open your mouth.
Is it good?
You're drooling.
Do you like my neck?
You're cute.
I'm tickling you.
It's amazing here.
I can tell you're standing on my pants.
It's painful, isn't it?
You're stuck.
Your pants are so tight that you can't take them off.
You're a pervert from noon.
Look at this.
It's amazing.
Did you get so excited by the smell of my feet?
You're drooling.
Your pants are dirty.
I'm in trouble.
I'm trying to be patient.
You're drooling again.
It's hot.
You're drooling.
You're scared.
I'm watching you grow up.
Don't do that.
It's amazing.
You're ticklish.
You're drooling.
Can I do it harder?
I'm going to lick this side, too.
Do you like Tama Tama?
It's noisy, isn't it?
If you're licked here.
My hand went to my butt without permission.
Does it feel good?
I'm going to kiss you.
You're excited like a pervert.
You're drooling.
Does it feel good?
Did you drink it?
Did you feel good?
I see.
I want to feel good, too.
Can you make me feel good, too?
Really?
It's not good to do it in this uniform.
It's a little painful.
Your blouse is too small to wear.
Do you like my boobs, too?
Do you like both?
How is it?
It's bigger than I thought, isn't it?
I think the button will come off.
I think it's going to pop.
You want to take off your uniform, right?
Please take it off.
Oh, my God.
You're so cute.
Boobs are coming out.
I'm a little sweaty.
Do you like to sweat?
I'm glad to hear that.
Then I'll hug you more.
Take a deep breath.
I'll hug you more.
Don't breathe.
Touch me more.
I feel good every day.
I'm happy to touch a lot of girls' bodies.
Look at me more.
You want to make your face look smaller, don't you?
I'm glad to hear that.
Please make your face smaller.
You're happy, aren't you?
I feel good.
I'm glad to hear that.
Is it delicious?
You can't forget my butt, can you?
I've been watching you all the time.
I love your butt.
You want to make your face smaller, don't you?
I'll give you a massage.
You smell better than your feet, don't you?
I'm glad to hear that.
I'll hug you more.
You've been standing for a long time.
Are you excited?
I'm glad to hear that.
I feel good.
I love your butt.
You want to make your face smaller, don't you?
I'm glad to hear that.
I'll rub your butt a lot.
I love your butt.
Is your butt soft?
I'll rub your butt a lot.
I love your butt.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'll rub your butt a lot.
I don't need these panties.
I'm going to cry.
But...
I thought you were going to cry.
I'm a pervert.
No, no, no.
Wait, wait.
I'll leave it to you.
Hold my feet and face.
I'll show you something better.
I think this is more exciting.
It's a pervert to put a mark on the first star.
It's cold.
I'm getting used to it.
How is it?
I tore it.
I can't hide anything.
I'm getting sleepy.
I'm getting messy.
I'm sleepy.
No, no, no.
I thought you were going to cry.
I'm getting used to it.
I feel good.
I feel like I'm an adult.
Wait...
One more time!
You're getting full, aren't you?
A piece of your cheek's out.
You want to do more, don't you?
You're still hard, so you can do it!
You're still hard, so you can it!
Woof...
You're crazy...
Why are you do so much work?
It looks weird...
What's so good?
Ah, yuck!
Ah...!
Oh! I can't do it...!
I have to go!!
ah!
Ah!
Oh my....
Oh...
Oh, I'm going crazy...
Ah, it was a good place.
Oh my...
Oh, it was out....
It's so hot.
I want to sleep more.
I see.
It's so hot.
It feels so good.
I'm poisoned.
It's so hot.
It feels so good.
It's so intense.
It's so hot.
I'm drooling.
It feels so good.
I want to sleep more.
No, no, no.
It feels so good.
I want to sleep more.
I'm drooling again.
You can do more, right?
You're drooling.
You can do more.
It feels so good.
I want to do more.
I want to sleep more.
No, no, no.
It feels so good.
I want to do more.
I want to sleep more.
It feels so good.
I can't help it.
My stomach hurts.
Give me more.
Help me.
It stings.
It feels good.
It's the best.
Give me more.
It's still hard.
It's the best.
It's hard.
It's getting worse, isn't it?
I know how hard it is.
I can't do it.
I want to do it more.
Do your best.
Hurry up.
It's the best.
I can't do it.
Give me more.
I can do it more.
It's the best.
It feels good.
It's getting worse.
It's the best.
It's hard, isn't it?
Let's do it more.
Let's pretend to be tired.
It's the best.
It's still hard, isn't it?
I'm going to cry.
I'm sure I can do it.
It's hard.
It's the best.
Give me more.
It feels good.
It's the best.
Hit me as hard as you can.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's the best.
You're sweating a lot.
It's a mess.
It's hard.
You're a good boy.
Come to my house again.
Can I?
You can.
I'll wait for you every day.
You're cute.
How many times did I do it?
You're in a good place.
I'm working out right now.
I don't know if you're listening to my muscles.
Can you touch my butt muscles?
I see.
I wonder if you're listening to the radio.
I feel like I'm listening.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
I've got a lot of butt.
Can you help me with muscle training?
Sure.
Lie down there.
Next is arm and chest training.
Support me.
I'm helping you.
If you don't, you'll collapse.
Let's do it again.
My arm muscles are not working.
I can't stand up.
I'm getting hot.
I'm sweating.
Are you sweating?
Do you know that?
How do you feel?
It's hot.
Can I do muscle training in this state?
My nipples are in my mouth.
Next is the hip joint.
I have to stretch this part.
Do your best.
Does it hurt?
The stretching isn't finished yet.
But you're out of breathe
Here it comes
She seems to be quite nervous
Here she goes
But she seems to be a little nervous
She's really heavily breathing.
Ah, can I do it?
Yeah.
Hey,
Hey, take a deep breath, and let's go.
Hush.
Are you softer?
Hey, there's a mess in front of you.
Hey, here.
Don't rub your face.
You did it.
I'm sorry.
Hey, why are you rubbing your face?
Does it feel good?
Hey, why are you drooling?
You can't pee if you're drooling.
What?
Hey, I was working out.
You have to train this side of your butt.
I'll train your butt.
Here.
I'll rub it.
Does it feel good?
You can't pee if you're drooling.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
Why?
Hey, you can't pee, can you?
Do you want me to rub your butt?
Did you want to rub your face?
That's right.
You like butt, don't you?
I'm sorry.
You can't pee if you're drooling.
You're drooling because I put a bandage on your foot, right?
It smells good.
I'm sorry.
I want you to relax your butt more.
I'm going to rub your butt more because you're drooling.
I'm sorry.
More.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Look at me.
Did you want to see this?
You're drooling because I put a bandage on your foot.
It hurts.
You really like it, don't you?
Do you want me to rub your butt more?
I'm sorry.
You're drooling because I put a bandage on your foot, right?
Can I rub your butt?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to rub your butt with my big butt.
You're drooling because I put a bandage on your foot, right?
Does it feel good to rub your butt?
I'm sorry.
Can I put a bandage on your foot?
It feels like I'm hugging you from behind.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm sorry.
Can I put a bandage on your butt?
You're drooling because I put a bandage on your foot, right?
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Can you help me with muscle training again?
You're drooling because I put a bandage on your foot, right?
I'm sorry.
It's okay. I'll call you.
Thank you.
When you work as a cabin attendant, do you get picked up?
I get picked up.
The other day, I got a business card to contact me.
I paid 10,000 yen for six business cards.
Are you a first-class cabin attendant?
That's right.
I used to have a lot of money.
Do you have a lot of pilots?
Yes, I have a lot of pilots.
I don't know.
I think I'm a pretty popular job.
It's hot.
Next, I'll clean this side.
I'll do it.
It's said that if you clean it while saying,
It's said that it will be beautiful.
I'll do it.
Is it okay?
It's hard to clean the bath.
That's right.
I'm going to hurt my back again.
I'll do it.
Is it okay?
Thank you.
I'll do it.
Is it okay?
What are you doing?
I thought you were cleaning my back.
Why?
I thought your face was hurt.
I knew it.
I'm sure you'll see my butt.
What do you mean?
Do you mean my butt?
It's very beautiful and big.
Then I'll look at it more.
My butt is very transparent.
Do you want to look at my transparent butt?
Is it okay?
It's okay.
I'll do it.
You really like my butt.
Is it painful?
It's painful.
You can lick it as much as you like.
I can't help it.
Do you want me to lick your butt?
It's painful.
Your butt is sticky.
Why don't you lick my butt?
I was surprised.
You licked my butt.
Is it delicious?
It's hot.
Your butt is sticky.
It's hot, isn't it?
I can't help it.
I'm cleaning up, but I can't help it.
Is it my fault?
I'm sure it's your fault.
You licked my butt.
Do you want to look at my butt so much?
You can look at my butt closely.
Thank you.
Please lick my butt.
I can't help it.
I always do what I want to do.
Your butt is getting bigger.
I can't help it.
It's painful, isn't it?
It's amazing.
Your butt is sticky.
I'll put your butt between my thighs.
I'll hug you.
I can't help it.
I'll hug you as you are.
I'm sorry.
Ah, your hand is wet.
It felt good.
Thank you for the comfortable service.
We look forward to seeing you again.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's funny.
You came to the right place.
Hey, can you hold my shoulder?
Yes, I can.
I can't stop laughing.
Do you want a massage?
Yes, I do.
It's soft.
Is it hard?
Yes, it's hard.
Ah, it's good.
It feels good.
It feels good, but I'm a little weak.
I'm weak.
I have to be strong.
Yes, that's right.
It's good.
It feels good.
Yes, it feels good.
It's like a decollete.
It's like a collarbone.
It feels good.
Yes, that's right.
And a little lower.
Yes.
Massage my chest, too.
Yes, I will.
A little lower.
Yes, there.
Here?
Yes.
This is also hard.
Yes, that's right.
Massage me.
My breasts are stiff.
Yes, your breasts are stiff.
I'll massage your breasts.
Here?
Yes.
Is it stiff?
No, it's soft.
Really?
It's good.
You're good.
It feels good.
Hey.
This.
I want you to massage me more.
Is it soft?
It's good.
It's hard around here.
Can you massage it well?
Yes.
Hey.
Massage here, too.
Here?
Yes.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I want you to massage me directly.
Yes.
Yes, that's good.
Hey.
Do you like my breasts?
Yes.
How much?
This much.
This much?
How much is it?
A lot.
A lot?
I can't understand you.
Massage here, too.
Massage the pointy part, too.
How is it?
It's good.
It's getting harder, isn't it?
It's hard.
Massage there, too.
Yes.
Massage here, too.
Try to pull me.
Yes.
Yes, pull me.
It feels good.
Yes.
Massage here, too.
Massage the pointy part.
Yes.
Massage here, too.
More.
It's not enough.
If I give you an erotic massage like this, you'll feel dizzy, won't you?
I feel dizzy, too.
Yes.
It feels good.
It's good.
Hey, I want you to massage me more.
Yes.
Hey, I want you to massage here, too.
Do you know how to use it?
Like this?
Thank you.
Yes.
Massage here, too.
Oh, it's hot.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Hey, do it again.
Like this.
Tell me how to do it.
Oh, it feels good.
Massage my favorite part.
Oh, it's hot.
Go, go, go.
You're good at massaging.
I can't stop massaging you.
Do you want me to massage here, too?
Oh, it's hot.
I'm surprised because you just left.
Do you want me to massage here, too?
Touch me more.
Oh, it's hot.
I can't stop massaging you.
You like my butt, don't you?
Touch me more.
Oh, it's hot.
I can't stop massaging you.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's hot.
Rub me a lot.
Hey, let me massage you more.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it feels good.
Rub me a lot.
Oh, it's hot.
You're the best.
I'll massage you.
Come here.
Oh, it's hot.
Rub me a lot.
Oh, it feels good.
I'll rub you a lot.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it feels good.
I just massaged you.
How do I look?
You look cute today, too.
What's wrong with your outfit?
You look fashionable.
Are you going to a party?
No, I'm just going to see my boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
Do you have a boyfriend?
No, I don't have a boyfriend.
I'm just playing with you.
You don't have a boyfriend?
Didn't you say you had a boyfriend?
No, I didn't.
Oh, really?
I didn't know that.
Is that so?
Yes, it is.
I'm going to see my boyfriend now, so go home.
What?
I'm just playing with you.
Are you going to see your boyfriend now?
Yes.
See you.
What?
Aren't you going?
No, I'm not.
I'm going to be late.
Let me go.
No, no, no.
You were just playing with me.
I didn't know that.
I thought you had a boyfriend.
Is that so?
Are you serious?
Yes, I am.
I can't help it.
I'm going to be late.
But you are going to be late.
What should I do?
I'm not going today.
I'm thinking about it if you are a technician rather than my boyfriend.
What?
I'm going to be late.
Are you going to show me your cool side?
Yes.
I'm going to be late.
You just want to show me your cool side.
Are you sure?
Are you serious about me?
Yes, I am.
I'm going to be late.
You touch me in a perverted way.
But I don't feel it at all.
I don't feel it at all.
I'm going to be late.
Do you like me?
Don't you stop me?
I'm going to be late.
I'm not going today.
What should I do?
I'm going to be late.
You are not wet yet.
Are you going to be late?
I'm going to be late.
You are cute.
I feel good.
I feel better than before.
I'm going to be late.
I feel good.
You are good at licking me.
I'm going to be late.
What should I do?
I'm going to go to my boyfriend.
Are you jealous of me?
Yes, I am.
I'm going to make you feel good.
Please stay here for 10 minutes.
How can I make you feel good?
Do you want to stay with me?
No.
I can't stand it.
You are the only one who makes me feel good.
I can see you.
Do you like to do this?
I'm going to grab your butt.
I'm going to make you feel good.
You can see me well, right?
I can feel your fingers.
I can't stand it.
I'm getting wet.
Can you pat me?
Do you like my butt?
Please pat my butt as much as you like.
I'm getting wet.
I can't stand it.
Ah
Ah...
She's petting me so much.
So many
Hi, Hi.
She gave me a lot of petting.
So will my sister turn it back?
Will she??
Did I make you jealous?
Do you want to ride on my back?
I see.
Don't be so manly.
You shouldn't be so stiff on your neck.
I'm sorry.
Why are you being so manly?
You're getting warmer.
I know you're trying hard, but I'm standing on my back.
I'm going to take it off.
It's stuck.
I can't take it off.
You're too big.
I like someone who can stand on my back all the time.
Really?
You're so chubby.
I can't take it off.
You always put it in your mouth and take it out right away, don't you?
Do you want me to hold it in?
No.
I'm going to lick you.
I'm sorry.
You licked the hole in my butt, didn't you?
You're the only one who licks and enjoys this place.
It's hot.
You got a cramp.
I'm going to lick the hole in your butt and get excited.
It's hot.
You're really tired.
I'm sleepy.
You're holding up.
You're holding up better than usual.
Can I do it harder?
I'm going to lick you.
It's hot.
You're holding up a lot.
I feel good, too.
Do you want to feel good together?
Do you want me to lick you together?
It's hot.
It feels good.
It feels good, but I'll do my best, too.
Don't lick your mouth.
Do your best.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Do you want to do something more pleasant?
It's hot.
You've been standing for a long time.
I'll put you in here.
It's hot.
It feels good.
If you don't cheer up, you can't beat your boyfriend.
Do your best.
It's hot.
Do you want me to touch you more?
It feels good.
Can you do your best?
It's hot.
It feels good.
Do you want me to do something more pleasant?
It's hot.
Let me stroke your neck.
You can't see anything from there.
It feels good.
It's out.
Put me in here.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I want to touch you.
It's hot.
It's good.
Can you do your best?
You look like you're having a hard time.
It feels good.
What?
Do you want to get out?
Do you want to get out of here?
I won't stop.
You want to get out, don't you?
What's wrong with you?
It's hot.
You can still do it, can't you?
I know you can do it many times.
You can do it more and more, can't you?
Put me in here.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's getting hot.
You're the best.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Let me get you out of here.
It's hot.
It's getting hot.
You know I like bags, don't you?
Let's put on a bag.
Put it in from behind.
It's hot.
It's getting hot.
You know I like bags, don't you?
Tickle me.
It feels good.
A
Good Bad
Gimoti
It's hard
I...
A
Un
Stre
.
Un
G
Koichi!
If you want me to be your girlfriend, let me go more.
That's great.
You can do it if you do it.
I'm happy.
Ah!
Let me see your face.
There are a lot of my favorite parts.
Wait, wait.
Why are you crying?
It hurts.
Ah!
You're the slowest.
Hey.
It's frustrating that I'm being used a lot.
Hey, can you do it more?
Go ahead.
I'm going to be next.
It feels good.
Ah!
Ah, it feels good.
This is good.
It feels good.
You're sensitive because I put out a lot, right?
It feels good in my stomach.
Look.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it hurts.
It hurts where I put out a lot.
What?
I'll take my time.
It'll go away soon, right?
I'll go first.
It feels good.
Ah, it feels good.
Let's go together.
Ah.
I became a spoiled child.
It was amazing.
You put out a lot.
Ah.
It's bitter.
It's bitter in my mouth.
It felt good, right?
It was amazing.
Let's break up and go out again.
I'll think about it.