I'm going to make a hole in the middle of the board.
What?
Why do I look at my mother's house?
Did I extend the digging drive?
I have not much money.
I called my father's store and my father is here.
Oh, no.
Aiko?
You're up?
Good morning.
Aiko.
I'm sorry.
I don't have money.
What are you talking about?
I don't have money to pay the extension fee.
Money?
Don't you remember anything?
I had a lot of fun yesterday.
I drank a lot.
Don't you remember?
Then I'll remind you.
It felt really good.
Thank you very much.
Call me again.
I'd like to ask you next month.
Do you know when I'm going to be discharged?
Look around the office.
Is the room smell okay?
Doesn't it smell?
It's okay.
I'm used to it.
Do you have a favorite scent?
I don't have a favorite scent.
Hello.
It's over.
What?
Why?
Can't I pick you up?
Taxi?
I'll get you a receipt.
Yes.
What should I do?
Do you have a taxi?
Are you in trouble?
I'm picking you up.
I can't pick you up.
I can't get out of the car.
I'm not looking for a taxi.
I'm just going home.
I can't go home.
That's terrible.
Why don't you stay at home until the rain stops?
What?
It's an extension.
I see.
I'll extend it until the rain stops.
Are you serious?
Do you have money?
I can't let you get wet in the rain.
I see.
Can I ask you a favor?
Would you like a drink?
Do you have a drink?
I have a drink.
I got it from my senior.
Can I have a drink?
I'll get you a drink.
Are you listening to me?
I'm listening to you.
It's really terrible.
Don't you usually go out?
Don't you want to do something outside?
It's a big veranda.
It's okay.
If you do it in such a place,
it's cold.
Are you trying to do it on the veranda?
It's okay to do it in the room.
What kind of person are you?
I don't want to take you outside.
And I do it every time.
Every time?
I said yes to the first time.
I don't want to take you outside.
I see.
It's hard.
I told the manager.
He doesn't respond to my calls.
He doesn't care about my calls.
He didn't even respond when I said no.
That's mean.
There's such a person?
I was surprised.
I think he's a good person.
I think he's a very nice person.
Really?
He doesn't say weird things.
He doesn't get persistent.
He doesn't talk even when I have an excuse.
Seriously.
I'm just happy.
What do you like about me?
Well...
You look like a junior in junior high school.
I admired you.
Was I like that?
Yes.
I had a crush on you.
I'm just happy to be able to talk to you.
I see.
It's fun.
What's your name?
Ken.
Well...
I like you.
I like you, too.
You're cute and funny.
I thought I'd give you a little service.
You look like that senior.
Yes.
I thought you were that senior.
Are you happy?
I'm very happy.
What's this hand?
I'm sorry.
Do you like butt?
Yes.
I like it.
I'm embarrassed to say something.
I'm a little drunk.
I'm sleeping here, so don't get mad if I touch your butt.
Can I touch your butt?
Yes.
It's the power of someone who really likes butt.
Do you know that?
I don't know.
I really like your butt.
Really?
Yes.
Did you chase after your favorite senior's butt?
I chased after that senior's butt.
I see.
Yes.
You like it very much.
I've been admiring you a lot.
Yes.
How you touch me is erotic.
I'm getting sick of it.
I want to kiss you again.
Do you want to see my butt?
Yes.
I'm getting sick of it.
Are you okay?
Wait a minute.
I'm getting sick of it.
What's that face?
Are you okay?
I'm getting sick of it.
I want you to do more.
Take this.
I'm getting sick of it.
I'm scared.
It feels good.
No, no, no.
I'm going to go.
Oh, my God.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm going to go.
Oh, my God.
Where did you get that technique?
It feels so good.
I want to do something for you, too.
I just did it.
Oh, my God.
It's so hot.
I've never been this serious because I've always been a little sloppy.
Oh, my God.
It's hot.
I'm going to go.
I love you.
You're cute.
It's harder than before.
What?
I can't do this.
Hey, you have to be nice to girls.
Take your time.
I can't stand it.
You can't stand it.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's so hard.
I'm sure you ran away.
It's hard.
It's really hard.
Oh, my God.
I feel like I'm going to die.
It feels good.
I can't do this.
One more time.
Oh, my God.
I'm waiting for you.
Did you take it out?
I took it out.
Did you put some air in it?
It's coming out.
It feels good.
One more time.
Come here.
What?
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
I can't breathe.
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
The one I took out earlier came out.
Oh, my God.
What is this?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I can't breathe.
Oh, my God.
Ah, it hurts.
I'm going to die.
Oh, my God.
What's this?
I can't do it yet.
You've done it twice, haven't you?
Yes, I have.
You can't do it yet?
I can't do it anymore.
You can't?
You're so energetic.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize that.
You're so energetic.
I'm sorry.
It's because of the alcohol.
It's okay.
I was drunk yesterday.
You can do it, right?
There's no way you can't do it.
Is it okay?
It's not impossible.
It's amazing.
It's the best.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels so good.
I want to move, too.
You can't just move.
I can't do it anymore.
I'll give you a massage.
Are you okay?
I can't do it anymore.
Why can't I move?
I can't move anymore.
I can't do it anymore.
Ah, ah, ah.
I told you my arm is in pain.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, ah, ah.
No, no, no, no, no.
Ah, it feels good.
Can I do it again?
No, no.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, ah, ah.
Wait, this is bad.
Why can you do it so many times?
Wait.
Are you a genius?
Because you are beautiful.
Ah, ah, ah.
You are too cute.
Wow!
Ah, is this still coming out?
I'm a little sick.
This is bad.
Ah, ah, ah.
It's still standing.
This is bad.
But I can't do it anymore.
I'm going to die.
Ah.
I've done a lot.
It felt so good.
Ayaka-san.
Hmm?
I'm sorry I got carried away.
I've done it many times.
It's true. What are you going to do?
Ah.
It's a lie.
That's also a lie.
Eh?
In the end.
How much do you think it's cute?
Eh?
It's a lie.
Hey, why are you so cute?
Please forgive me.
Ah.
I was surprised.
You're too good.
Eh?
How was it?
It's okay.
I felt really good.
Ah, that's good.
You don't have to worry about it.
I felt really good too.
You've done a lot.
Yes.
My manju is messed up.
Do you want to take a shower together?
Ah.
Can we do it together?
Can I change the bath?
Yes.
Let's do it.
Let's go.
I can't move.
Wait, wait.
I'll help you.
Are you okay?
Ah.
It's a mess.
Okay.
Ah.
Is it really okay?
What?
To go in together.
I have to take a bath.
Take it off.
Ah.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Yes.
I'll wash it for you.
Eh?
Is it okay?
Yes.
That kind of...
I made a bubble.
Can I do something like a boyfriend?
It's really like a boyfriend.
It's like dating.
It's fun.
I'm very happy.
Here you go.
Thank you.
That's funny.
It's hidden properly.
Thank you.
It's a little...
It's really small.
Isn't it terrible?
It's a bikini.
Ah.
That's...
I shouldn't have said such a good thing.
Ah.
Sister.
It's like a bikini.
It's getting fun.
What should I do?
You haven't washed it at all.
It's fun.
It's like a boyfriend.
It's embarrassing to see.
It's a good news.
It's cute.
Sister.
It's gone.
I made it.
Here you go.
Does it feel good?
It feels really good.
I feel good, too.
Here you go.
Fingers.
It's sandwiched.
You have too many fingers.
Ah.
It feels good.
The foam is getting wet and it feels good.
Ah.
I'm doing this, too.
What?
Here you go.
What are you doing?
Playing a bikini.
It's a lie.
Ah.
It's amazing.
It's really warm.
Is it warm?
Yes.
I've never done this before.
Really?
You've never done this before?
No, I haven't.
Really?
Yes, I have.
You've never done this before?
No, I have.
I've only used your shop.
Wow.
Stop being so cute.
What are you doing?
The other way around.
Wow.
Ah.
I'm scared.
It's hot.
Ah.
It's warm.
I'm scared.
Ah.
You're starting to move your butt again.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
It's okay.
I'm going to wash your butt.
Okay.
Stand up.
Ah.
Your butt is so big.
Wow.
Bend down a little more.
I'm going to massage your neck.
Ah.
It feels good.
I'm hitting something.
Ah.
I'm going to hit you.
Oh.
I'm hitting something.
Ah.
I have to wash your butt.
It feels good.
Ah.
Oh.
I'm going to massage your neck.
Ah.
Again.
I'm going to massage your neck.
Ah.
Ahh.
I'm sorry.
You can't do it yet.
I'm already doing it.
Why do you become a human just by washing this?
No, it's not like that.
It's not like that?
Is it normal?
It's normal.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm doing it by myself.
I'm really kind.
Really?
I just don't get sick at work.
I see.
You're trying not to get sick.
I have to do something.
You have to do something.
I'll do something for you.
Look at me.
What will happen?
I was surprised.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
You can't do it.
It feels good.
Look at me.
It's dangerous.
I know.
You have to wash the bubbles off.
Wait a minute.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It's hot.
It's delicious.
What?
Wait a minute.
This is a little...
It's hot.
It's dangerous.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
You did it again.
Why don't you apologize?
You don't have to apologize.
It's amazing.
How many bubbles are there?
It's hot.
Ayaka's technique is amazing.
Did you feel good?
It feels good.
It's like a decoration, so I'll put it on.
I'll leave it as it is.
I'll do it, too.
Why?
I want to feel good, too.
Why do I have to do it alone?
Do it.
I'll do it again.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
Can I lick it?
I did it.
It's amazing.
No, no, no.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Give it to me.
Are you okay?
It's still hot.
Of course.
It's okay.
It's hot.
It's too hot.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I want to do it more.
Why is this soup so hard?
It's too hot.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
I'll do it again.
I'll do it slowly.
It's amazing.
There's still a lot left.
It's hot.
What are you doing in the bath?
I came to wash you.
I'm sorry.
I'll wash you.
Let's drink again.
Let's do that.
I want to drink.
It's amazing.
I'll wash you.
It felt good.
It was very hot.
It was good.
I'm happy to be with you.
Thank you.
Me, too.
Don't you have body oil?
I have it.
I want you to use it.
Thank you.
My shoulders hurt.
Do you want me to massage your shoulders?
It's okay.
It's cute to pay for an extension and massage.
I'm happy to be with you.
It feels good.
You're good at it.
Is it true?
It felt good.
Can I do it?
My back hurts.
This hand.
I'm happy to be with you.
It feels good.
Raise your hand.
I understand.
It's a bad hand.
It feels good.
I don't know.
When I feel sexy, I feel pain when I touch my boobs.
I don't feel pain when I massage.
I just feel good.
Is that so?
I think so.
I think it's a correction.
I think it's a massage.
Don't you think it's erotic?
I feel good.
I want to touch it.
It feels good.
Don't you play with me?
You're a bad boy.
I don't need it anymore.
Why do you feel so good?
I want to make you feel good.
I feel like I'm in a different world.
Can I give you this?
What?
I gave it to you easily.
You're cute.
What is it?
I gave it to you easily.
I'm in trouble.
I feel like I'm going to get a cramp again.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm in trouble.
I'm in trouble again.
I feel good.
I can't do it anymore.
I may have said it from the extension of the massage.
You like my butt, don't you?
That's right.
I'll show you my butt.
Can I?
I'm in trouble.
Can I put this on you?
You can put it on me.
I need to moisturize you.
You put on a lot.
I put on too much.
I feel good.
I don't care about your butt.
I'm in trouble.
I can't do it anymore.
Are you still going to do it?
I'm in trouble.
Can I put this on you?
I feel good.
You really like my butt.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
It's funny.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm looking at your butt.
Do you stand up just by looking at my butt?
I can't do it anymore.
Are you kidding me?
I can't believe it.
Did you just go because you were sweating?
I'm in trouble.
I feel good.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sorry.
Did you feel good?
I can't let you do this.
I'll make it up to you.
Do the same pose as me.
You did a good job.
I'll give you a massage.
Your skin is still hard.
You still have a lot of hair on your head.
Can you reflect the light with your butt?
If you do this, you'll be able to reflect the light.
I can't do it anymore.
I'll give you a massage.
I'll rub your head.
Look up.
I feel good.
You can lie down.
Did you feel good?
You're amazing.
I feel good.
We did it again.
It's not raining yet.
Let's sleep together.
Can I?
I can't go home.
I said I could go home.
Let's sleep together.
I'm sorry.
I thought I felt good.
It wasn't a dream.
You can sleep.
It's hard just to sleep.
It's okay.
I want to see your boobs.
Do you want to see my boobs?
Okay.
It's like a dream.
What?
Are you still sleepy?
I'm sleepy.
It's okay.
It's hard.
I want to kiss you.
My nipples are wrinkled.
It feels good.
It's hard.
My nipples are wrinkled.
I'm excited.
It might be a dream.
I don't know.
It feels good.
It's hard.
You look like you're going to wake up.
It's hot.
It's hard.
I'm having fun.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's hard.
I don't know.
It's hot.
Your butt is moving a lot.
You can't sleep yet.
Do you want to sleep with me?
I'll hug you.
He's moving.
So painful...!
I'm going to throw up.
How long are you going to lick me?
It feels so good.
It's the same as before.
I'm going to throw up.
No, no, no, no, no.
You made me sleep for a long time.
I'm playing with you.
You are so cute.
It feels good.
Does it hurt?
No, it doesn't.
No.
It feels so good.
What?
Are you okay?
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
It's going to come out.
I couldn't hold it in.
Oh, it's gone.
What?
Did you drink it?
I drank it.
It was good.
It felt so good.
Did it feel good?
You put up with it a lot.
Since you woke up.
Maybe it's not a dream.
Maybe it's a dream.
I wonder what will happen when I wake up in the morning.
Let's sleep again.
I feel like I can sleep.
Because I let you go once.
It's going to get cold.
I thought it would be okay.
I'm sorry.
Aiko?
Did you wake up?
Good morning.
Aiko, I'm sorry.
I don't have money.
What are you talking about?
I don't have money to pay the extension fee.
Money?
Wait a minute.
Don't you remember anything?
I had a lot of fun yesterday.
I drank alcohol.
Don't you remember?
I'll remind you.
What is this?
Did you see this in your dream?
In my dream...
I'll remind you.
Don't you remember this?
Don't you remember?
Is this a dream?
Did you see this in your dream?
I think so.
But it wasn't a dream.
This is the real reality.
I had a lot of fun yesterday.
Don't you remember?
It's lonely to remember only one person.
I thought I was going to drink alcohol.
Is it okay?
Don't you remember?
I've had a hard time since this morning.
I'm sleepy.
Can I sleep a little?
I'll drink again.
Again?
It's cold in the morning.
It's disgusting.
Good morning.
It's too hard.
It's disgusting.
Show me more.
I remember a little.
Do you remember?
I don't remember.
I'll squeeze it out and give it to you.
Then I'll go home.
It's disgusting.
There's still a lot left.
Show me more.
I have to say hello here.
What's wrong?
It doesn't look good.
What?
Why?
You licked it all.
You look like you're in a bad mood.
Can you still have a drink?
It's a waste of time.
You want to get out of here, don't you?
Can I?
I need you to let me sleep before that.
It tickles.
It's like a dream.
It's not a dream.
It tickles.
But...
Why are you avoiding it?
See?
I'll take it off if you don't like it.
It tickles.
You're shaking.
It's good to stand up in the morning.
It tickles.
Oh, my.
It's the best.
Let's do it a little faster.
This...
This is not good.
Oh, no.
I'm at my limit.
I'm about to vomit.
What should I do?
Oh, no.
I'm about to puke.
We're good friends.
I'm sorry.
This is not a dream.
Are you okay?
I remember a lot of things.
Do you remember?
You're late.
I'm sorry.
You said you were hungry.
I'm not good at drinking.
What do you mean you can't remember if you don't say it?
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Something went in.
Take it out.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good.
Why?
Oh, no.
I can't move like this.
I can't move.
Oh, my God.
Shin-chan, are you still okay?
Yes.
Really?
I'm going out.
Yes.
Put me in.
Are you okay?
I want to do a lot more.
I did it.
It feels good.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good.
Shin-chan.
Oh, my God.
It's the best.
It feels so good.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to be a fool.
Can I put you in?
I'm in trouble if you don't put me in.
Oh, my God.
No.
It feels so good.
Oh, my God.
Do it slowly.
I'm under a lot of pressure.
It's coming out.
It's stuck, but it's coming out.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good.
I'm going to be a fool if you don't put me in.
Oh, my God.
I can't do this.
It feels so good.
I'm going to be a fool if you don't put me in.
Oh, my God.
It's the best.
It's really good.
It's heavy.
Oh, my God.
I want to move, too.
Can you move?
I'm being pushed too much.
I have to attack, too.
It's so cold.
I can't do this anymore.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good.
I'm going to be a fool if you don't put me in.
I wanted to attack you.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good.
I'm going to be a fool if you don't put me in.
Oh, my God.
Is this a weak?
No, no, no, no.
Oh, my God.
I don't want you to go, but did you come out?
I came out again.
Oh, my God.
Hey, I want to take a picture.
Wow, can you really go?
Oh, my God.
Seriously.
I feel like I can't fly.
It feels so good.
Oh, my God.
I don't think I can fly.
It feels so good.
Oh, my God.
I'm going.
It feels so good.
Oh, my God.
I'm going.
I slept too much.
Oh, my God.
Can you still go?
What is this?
It's amazing.
It's a lump.
I got it out.
I didn't get it out.
What?
You didn't get it out.
It's a lump, look.
No, it's still...
What is this lump?
It's still a lump!
I got it out.
I didn't know that.
Oh, my God.
I got it out.
It's so hard that I don't think I've done it all, but I think I can do it about 100 more times.
100 times?
Yeah.
If it's Aiko, I'll do it 100 times.
I told you.
Yeah.
I won't go home until I do it 100 times.
Are you sure?
It's the best.
You said it was impossible earlier.
Yeah, it's impossible, but it's the best.
What is it, really?
Yeah.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, no.
I'll do it one more time.
Are you kidding me?
It's amazing.
Wait, A-kun.
Are you a genius?
Oh, no.
Hey, how did you do it?
Aiko is amazing.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I'm really impressed.
Why?
Let's do it again.
Are you serious about doing it 100 times?
Yeah.
Oh, no.
I can't do it.
I really can't do it.
Why?
I can't do it.
Let's do it in five minutes.
Why?
You'll go home if you do that.
What should I do?
It's raining now.
It felt so good.
It felt good, didn't it?
Yeah.
Where was it?
I don't know.
Well,
you know,
the extension cord is in trouble.
Are you still saying that?
I don't need an extension cord.
What?
I'm the one who couldn't go home.
Oh, I see.
It can't be helped that you didn't come to pick me up.
It's their fault.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
It's just a hobby.
A hobby?
Thank you very much.
I'll call you again soon.
Really?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'll go home with you.
Thank you.
But,
is it only possible to meet you at the shop?
What?
Only at the shop?
Only at the shop.
What else can I do?
I don't want to.
You're so cute.
Wait a minute.
Why?
Let's go on a date outside,
not only at the shop.
Is it okay?
Yes.
I'm so happy.
Let's go eat something delicious.
I'd love to.
What do you like?
Well...
Sukiyaki is really good.
I want to eat shrimp.