It's been a long time since I've seen you, so I'm a little nervous.
Are you nervous?
I'm a little nervous.
Why?
It's been a long time.
Because you're my relative.
Yes.
Yui, I'm here.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
It's been a while since I've seen you, too.
Yui.
Long time no see.
You've grown up.
It's been a long time.
Come in.
Thank you for your time.
I'll put it straight here.
Yes.
You haven't come since you came here.
That's right.
It's a beautiful house.
Please come in.
Thank you for your time.
It's very beautiful.
It feels good.
Thank you for your time.
By the way, you've become more manly.
Have I?
Yes.
You're handsome.
You're getting more and more beautiful.
I'm embarrassed.
I think you've become more manly.
Really?
No, I haven't.
Your breasts are getting bigger.
No, I'm embarrassed.
Don't look at me.
I'm not looking at you.
You're not looking at me, are you?
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't do that.
I won't do that.
I talked to you on the phone.
I'd like to work here.
Can I work here for a while?
It's okay.
Leave it to me.
Thank you.
It's hard work, but do your best.
I have to go now.
You have to go?
I came here, so I made a promise with my friend.
I see.
I made a promise with my friend.
See you later.
Get a hold of yourself.
Get a job and study what you can.
I'm going to go now.
See you later.
She's busy.
Are you going to work in Tokyo?
I want to do that.
I see.
That's amazing.
I want to go to the city.
There are many things to do in the city.
There are many things to do.
Don't do anything weird.
Don't do anything weird?
Don't do anything bad.
I won't do anything bad.
Are you okay?
For example?
For example, you can go out with a bad person.
I'm going to study hard for my job.
Thank you for your time.
Take your time.
What are you aiming for?
I'm studying plastic surgery.
That's amazing.
Are you really studying?
I'm studying plastic surgery.
Katakana is difficult.
I'm studying sports massage.
That's amazing.
I don't know what it's like.
It's like a pelvis exercise that's popular in the U.S.
Is it popular in the U.S.?
That's amazing.
I'm trying it.
I've never done it before.
Is that so?
I'm doing it as a dream training.
Do you do it with your mother?
I don't do it with my mother.
Can you do it?
I'll try it.
Really?
Do you do it like this?
I'll try it.
You have to help your mother to study.
What are you going to do?
Try it on my waist.
Really?
That's right.
Like this?
Try it on my waist.
Sit down.
Here?
Is it really right?
That's right.
Really?
Like this?
Like this.
That's right.
That's amazing.
Move your pelvis like this.
I see.
That's amazing.
Is that so?
That's right.
I didn't know there was such a thing.
It's effective.
I didn't know that.
It's good for the pelvis.
It's good for the posture.
There's a machine like this, right?
That's right.
Move your pelvis like this.
I think it's better for people to do it.
Is that so?
That's right.
That's amazing.
It's difficult to adjust the machine.
I see.
I think it's better for humans to do it.
That's right.
I'm just studying.
You're studying properly.
If a professional does it, it's beautiful.
It's amazing, isn't it?
That's amazing.
I feel like I'm listening.
Are you listening?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
What?
Well...
Wait a minute.
What?
The skirt was a little in the way.
Is it in the way?
Yes.
But...
It's better to be direct.
It's okay.
I'm a little embarrassed.
But that's what plastic surgery is all about.
That's right.
I'm sure you wear pajamas.
I'd like to have a little bit of back skin.
Is that so?
I'm going to do this.
I'm listening.
Yes.
But it's also good for your muscles.
That's right.
It's good for the muscles.
That's great.
I'm wearing a lot.
Like this.
Yes.
That's right.
Try moving like this.
By myself?
That's right.
Like this?
Like I did earlier.
It's a little difficult.
A little more like this.
That's great.
What?
Can you move this much by yourself?
That's right.
I heard this is good.
What?
About once.
But I'm sweating a lot.
Really?
Yes.
Like this?
That's right.
Once.
What?
What are you doing?
This is...
The pants are a little too thick.
It's better to have a thin fabric.
Is that so?
It's absolutely effective.
This is something.
I'm self-taught.
Did you come up with it yourself?
That's right.
It's better to have a thin fabric.
You're studying a lot.
It's better for the body temperature to touch each other.
But I'm sure it's warm.
That's right.
Massage is more effective when it's warm.
That's great.
It's better for the skin to touch each other.
That's what I think.
That's great.
You're studying hard.
I'm not just studying.
I'm thinking about what I should do.
I see.
That's great.
I thought you weren't studying, but you are.
I'm studying a lot.
That's great.
I'm sweating.
It's good to be hot.
It's effective.
I think it's going to be tight around here.
That's right.
I think the buttocks will be beautiful.
I'm glad I was worried about my buttocks.
That's great.
What?
What are you doing?
It's more effective for people to touch each other.
Really?
Really.
What?
That's why I took it off.
That's why you took it off?
Didn't you press it?
No, I didn't.
I didn't press it.
That's because it's more effective.
Is that so?
It's better to be warm.
That's true.
That's true, but I don't like it.
It's definitely effective.
Is it effective?
Don't worry about that.
Really?
Definitely.
If you say it with such a serious face, I wonder if it's true.
That's true.
Really.
But it's hard.
Is it hard?
Yes.
It's hard.
It's not hard, is it?
It's not hard.
This is a massage.
Massage is good for osteoporosis.
It's a little hard.
What?
Are you okay?
It's a strange feeling.
I can't do that.
Wait a minute.
Really?
Really.
I can't do that.
Wait a minute.
I want to make it more effective.
What?
I'll do it directly.
No.
I'll do it like this.
Wait a minute.
I can't do that.
I'll do it like this.
Do you understand?
I can't do that.
More.
Wait a minute.
I can't do that.
Ouch!
No.
What are you doing?
Hey!
Get in there.
Wait!
I'm sorry.
You said you'd just rub it, didn't you?
I'll just rub it.
Ah!
What's this?
Don't move!
No, no, no!
Wait, wait, wait!
Ah!
Are you okay?
Wait, wait, wait!
Stand on your feet.
Like this.
It's different from before.
Ah!
Wait, wait.
Wait!
Ah!
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
It hurts.
Wait a minute.
No way.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
You can't do that.
Why did you let it out?
You said you'd just rub it.
I'm sorry.
What are you going to do?
You can't do that.
You know it hurts.
No, I don't.
I'm sorry.
Calm down.
I can't calm down.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry?
It's all your fault.
No way.
If I hadn't rubbed it, it wouldn't have been this bad.
I can't help it.
No way.
Let me see.
I can't help it.
You can't do that.
I'm just looking at you.
Just looking at me?
No, I'm not.
Why are you just looking at me?
Hey.
It's so soft.
No way.
It's too soft.
Really?
Don't touch me like that.
I'm not touching you like that.
You are.
What are you doing?
Hey.
Don't do that.
You're sweating.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sweating.
If you do this to me...
Don't do that.
Hey.
I'm embarrassed.
Let me see more.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't do that.
Calm down.
I can't calm down.
Let's calm down.
Your teeth are too beautiful.
It's your fault.
It's my fault?
Let's do it again.
Don't do that.
My stomach hurts.
Let's do it again.
Can I rub your butt?
Calm down.
Where are you licking?
Can I rub your butt?
My butt?
My butt hurts.
Let's do it again.
What are you doing?
Your butt is beautiful.
Wait a minute.
Why are you licking my butt?
Why are you licking my fingers?
It's warm here.
It's dangerous.
Wait a minute.
Come here.
Don't go.
What are you doing?
Come here.
What is it?
I like you.
Come here.
Wait a minute.
Don't lick my butt.
Are you kidding me?
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Don't lick my butt.
What are you doing?
It's hot.
Don't lick my butt.
My butt.
I'll put my hand in your mouth.
It's rubbing.
Don't lick my butt.
It's hot.
Are you still going to do it?
Come here.
Sit here.
It's hot.
that haunts you.
Come on.
Are you all right?
Ah!
This is amazing.
Ouch!
Ah!
Oh!
Ouch!
Ouch!
Come on!
I'm going to put it in your ear.
Put it in your ear.
I did it!
I didn't cut it.
Rub it in.
Stop it!
You're crazy.
Don't do that.
Stop it.
Dai-chan.
What's wrong again?
You did it.
Dai-chan.
It's definitely a secret to your mother.
Episode 2
Mom.
Yes?
I have something to tell you.
Is that so?
Yes.
It's not something erotic, is it?
No.
I want you to tell me more about it when you have a new girlfriend.
I see.
If that's the case, that's fine.
That's fine.
Come here.
Well...
What should I do?
You're going to cook for your girlfriend, right?
Yes.
I wonder if there's something.
I'm going to cook for her when I have a girlfriend.
You don't have a girlfriend?
No, I don't.
I see.
I should have remembered.
It's easier to cook if you cut the vegetables evenly.
I see.
Mix it well.
Sauce and noodles.
Yes.
It looks good.
Doesn't it?
Put the vegetables in.
Yes.
Did you forget the meat?
I couldn't find the meat.
I really want to put it in.
If it's meat, put it in.
Yes.
You can put whatever you like.
It looks good.
Is this enough?
It looks delicious.
What are you touching?
Stop it.
Just a little.
Hey.
You shouldn't do that.
You were cooking.
It's beautiful.
It's very beautiful.
I want to touch it.
Be gentle.
It's okay.
You shouldn't do that.
It's dangerous.
You're using fire.
It's okay.
Hey.
It smells good.
You shouldn't do that.
What are you doing?
It's beautiful.
Just a little.
I'll finish it soon.
What?
You finished cooking, didn't you?
I finished cooking, but...
The frying pan is still hot.
It's dangerous, isn't it?
I'll finish cooking soon.
Oh, no.
It's dangerous.
Tanai.
What?
Don't smell it.
I want to smell it.
What?
Hey.
Don't do that.
Are you kidding me?
It's because you're too beautiful.
What are you talking about?
You're too beautiful.
You shouldn't do that.
No, I shouldn't.
I shouldn't do that.
But it's already like this.
Tanai.
It's a little long, isn't it?
What?
It's already like this.
Ouch.
Hey.
It's your fault.
What? It's my fault?
You have a bad back, don't you?
No, I don't.
I'm fine.
Hey.
It feels good.
What are you doing?
Ouch.
You like it, don't you?
Yes.
I'll do it on the other side.
Don't do that.
Tanai.
I have a bad back, too.
Don't do that.
Wait.
Ouch.
Tanai.
I want to do it again.
What?
Again?
Wait.
Here.
It feels good.
Ouch.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Don't do that.
Ouch.
Tanai.
What are you doing?
Ouch.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Ouch.
That's all.
I didn't know you were a girl.
It's okay.
That's all.
What?
I didn't know you were a girl.
That's all.
Ouch.
It's okay.
It's so painful.
Ouch.
Wait a minute.
This side, too.
Show me your cute back.
Come on.
You're so cute.
Let me see.
You're so sexy.
No, I'm not.
You're sexy.
I'm normal.
You're not normal.
I'm normal, aren't I?
I'm normal.
You're weird.
I'm not weird.
You're sexy.
This is not the bra you're wearing.
No, it's not.
This is a normal bra.
Ouch.
It's so painful.
Wait a minute.
Let me see.
What's wrong with you?
Wait a minute.
It's not good, is it?
It's not good.
I can't stand it.
I know it's not good.
What's wrong with you?
Don't touch me in a sexy way.
This is not a sexy way.
It's a sexy way, isn't it?
Really?
Yes, it is.
Isn't it?
No, it's not.
I don't understand.
I just want to touch you.
I want to do this.
No, it's not good.
It's not good.
Ouch.
Wait a minute.
I'm licking you.
It's not good.
Don't touch me in a sexy way.
More.
More?
I want to do this.
What?
Are you licking me?
Don't do that.
It's not good.
I can't help it.
Just a little.
Ouch.
You have a lot of hair.
It's too much.
Ouch.
It's not good.
Dai-chan.
Don't put it in your mouth.
It's not good.
It's too much.
Wait a minute.
What?
It's so itchy.
Did it hurt?
It's too much.
Are you rubbing your ears?
I'm just rubbing my ears.
I can't help it.
You can just rub your ears.
I'll put it in your mouth.
No.
Don't put it in your mouth.
Wait a minute.
I told you it wasn't good.
It's not good.
Dai-chan.
Wait a minute.
It's not good.
Dai-chan.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
There's a lot in there.
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
I didn't know it was a girl.
What would you do if you had a girlfriend?
You'll get in trouble.
Be careful.
I'm something.
Was it chiropractic?
Yes.
Is it hard to study?
It's hard.
scientific
It's hard to study.
It's about a human body.
It's hard to do it in real life, so I have to learn it with my body.
It's hard.
By the way, I'm developing a new massage for the plastic circuit.
A new massage?
I was wondering if it would be okay to do this on my own.
Do you want to do it?
I want you to do it for me.
I learned a lot from you.
What is this?
This?
Really?
This is the opposite of what I did before.
I see.
Do you want me to put more pressure on you?
Like this?
Really?
I put too much pressure on you.
I thought it would be better to put more pressure on you.
Open your legs a little more.
Like this?
Put your hands in a stable position.
Open your legs a little more.
Open your legs.
My neck hurts.
It's hot.
Oh, no.
Ah!
I'm going to...
I'm going to pin it here...
Ah!
Come on!
Come here.
What?
Wait a minute.
Can I rub your back?
Rub my back again?
Again?
My back hurts.
You rubbed my back.
Come on!
My back hurts.
Can I rub your back?
It feels good.
My back hurts.
Again?
Rub my back.
Like this?
My back hurts.
It feels good.
What?
My back hurts.
It feels good.
Rub my back.
My back hurts.
Again?
It feels good.
My back hurts.
I told you I couldn't do it.
Why?
You asked me to do it.
What?
I didn't ask you to do it.
I told you I couldn't do it.
Aunt.
What?
What is it?
I'm going to use this.
No.
Let's use it together.
Why?
I don't care.
Do you know this?
What is this?
I use this when I pee.
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
I use this when I pee.
I don't use this when I pee.
I don't pee.
What are you talking about?
I use this for a new massage.
I'm not your girlfriend.
I want to try it.
I only have you.
I feel good.
I think it's just right.
What do you mean by that?
I'm nervous.
I put this on your head.
Now, I'm going to put some cream on your back.
It's so moist.
It's warm, isn't it?
I'm warming it up.
Oh, you're warming it up.
It's because I'm going to give you a massage.
It feels better when it's warm on the skin.
I see.
It's because it's warm.
I'm going to put some cream on your back.
I see.
What?
Why?
It's a massage, isn't it?
It's a massage.
Where are you turning, Dai-chan?
You don't have to give me a massage there.
What?
Give me your hand.
My hand?
I'm going to stretch your back.
It's a little loose.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to stretch your back.
Does it feel good?
There you go.
It feels good, doesn't it?
What?
What are you doing?
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's a little loose.
I'm going to stretch your buttocks and nose.
My buttocks?
Look at me.
I'm going to stretch your buttocks.
I'm going to stretch your back.
What?
That's right.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Can I rub your buttocks?
Rub my buttocks?
I want to rub your buttocks.
Put your legs up like this.
What?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Put your legs up like this.
Come here.
What?
What are you doing?
I'll give you some water.
Let me rub your buttocks more.
What?
Let me rub your buttocks.
I want to rub your buttocks.
It feels good, doesn't it?
What are you doing?
What?
I can't stand it.
What are you doing?
I'm rubbing your buttocks.
I'm not rubbing your buttocks.
No, I'm not.
I'll give you some water.
You're moving, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're not moving.
I'm still rubbing your buttocks.
Stop!
You're moving, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Ai-chan, come on.
Get out of there.
Why are you in my head?
I'm sorry. I was nervous.
What? Get out of there.
Get out of there.
I got it.
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
I'm cleaning the bed.
Is it small?
No, it's okay.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Are you close with your wife recently?
Yes, we are.
Are you close?
Yes.
What do you like about her?
Let me see.
She is kind.
And sometimes she cooks for me.
Really?
Yes.
Where did you meet her?
At the same company.
Really?
Yes.
We knew each other at the same company.
Really?
Yes.
Does she have a crush on you?
What?
Why are you asking me that?
Don't say that.
You don't have a crush on her, do you?
No, I don't.
It doesn't matter.
She might have a crush on you.
Don't say that.
You are so mean.
No, I'm not.
What are you talking about?
Don't joke with me.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Don't do that.
You can keep cleaning.
I can't.
No.
You can't do that.
I'll do it on my own.
No, you can't.
You can't clean like this.
I'll do it on my own.
Hey, Dai-chan.
What are you doing?
You can't do that.
What color is this?
Close your eyes.
It's a rainbow-colored underwear.
It's not a rainbow-colored underwear.
You said it's a rainbow-colored underwear.
Don't joke with me.
I'll put it here.
I'll put it between my legs.
No.
Wait a minute.
Hey.
I told you not to do that.
Dai-chan.
Stop it.
Hey.
You can't move.
Dai-chan.
Hey.
What are you doing?
It's over.
Hey.
Dai-chan.
Stop it.
What?
Hey.
You can't do that.
I can't...
I need to help you out.
What are you doing?
Hey!
No!
Don't be selfish.
Do you understand?
What are you doing?
That's no good.
Stop it!
What?
What are you doing?
Toto tore up Mom's clothes.
Toto is crying.
Cat licks the litter.
There was something like a bull in my leg
that I rubbed my leg
so hard.
Oh, my God.
What's wrong?
You scared me.
Don't do that.
No?
Let's do it again.
No.
I told you no.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
No.
Girls will hate you if you say that.
I'm sorry.
You didn't feel good, did you?
No, I didn't.
I didn't.
Really?
No, I didn't.
You said you were sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's the last time.
You said you were going to rub it.
But you did it.
And you did it in person.
If your mom finds out, you'll be in trouble.
I didn't just rub it.
It's the last time, so I rubbed it.
Did you really just rub it?
Yes.
Really?
I'm just going to rub it on you.
Do you understand?
Don't rub it on your body.
I'm just going to rub it on you.
Yes, I'm just going to rub it on you.
What?
I'm just going to look at it.
You're just going to look at it?
Are you going to take it off?
You're going to take it off.
I can't take it off because I don't want to see my body.
You don't want to see your body?
I understand.
Calm down.
You can't touch it.
It's a promise.
I understand. Go to bed.
I'll rub it on you.
You really can't touch it.
Do you understand?
Like this?
Is this okay?
What are you going to do?
I'm going to rub it on you.
I'm sorry.
It's over.
I want to rub it more.
More?
I'm sorry.
I'm not strong.
Ouch!
I just rubbed it.
I'm sorry.
Ouch!
I apologize...
I'm going to sleep.
It's okay if you're still here, isn't it?
I'm still here?
You still have a long way to go.
You can do it.
I'm still here.
It hurts.
It's okay if you're still here.
You can do it.
I'm still here.
It hurts.
Don't move.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Ouch, ouch!
Ouch!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
siniuos conviction BOYou
Oh, my dear.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30.
Oh, my dear.
Mommy, I gave you vitamins, but I'm gonna have to get you a inchworm so don't move!
Mommy!
I'm gonna give you a mammoth inchworm
Thanks mom!
Mommy!
If you frown your face, you lose!
stop it, come on!!!!
if you don't stop, you will lose
One more time!