It's been a long time since I've seen you, so I'm a little nervous, but I'll do my best.
Are you nervous?
No, I'm not nervous.
I'm here.
Welcome.
It's been a long time since I've seen you.
You've grown up.
Come in.
Take off your clothes.
Thank you.
You look beautiful.
Really?
Thank you.
You didn't mess up, did you?
No, I didn't.
Everyone has laundry at home.
You're right.
Did you finish your work?
Yes, I just finished.
You've grown up.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
She wants to see you.
Really?
Yes.
Is she a college student?
I see.
Does she want to ask you something?
Yes.
She wants to hear about you.
I'll tell you.
Thank you.
You've grown up.
You've grown up, too.
You're a good talker.
Where is Wataru?
He's on a business trip.
I'll take care of him.
I'll take care of him for a few days.
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
Really?
I'm sorry.
I came here to see you.
I see.
Did you have fun?
Yes.
You're a good boy.
Are you a good boy?
Yes.
I have to go.
See you.
Call me if you need anything.
You're a good boy.
Okay.
See you.
Do you want some snacks?
No, thank you.
See you.
I'm sorry.
My house is messy.
No, it's not.
Really?
My house is beautiful.
No, it's not.
My house is messy.
I'm sorry.
Is it hard to be a teacher?
Yes, it's hard.
I have a lot to learn.
I see.
Do you get up early every day?
Yes, I do.
I have a test.
I usually get home late when I make something.
I see.
So your house is messy because you have to work.
So my house is messy because you have to work.
It's so messy because it's not ready.
My house is not messy at all.
Really?
Just a moment.
I'm chopping off the stem.
It's hard to get a job, isn't it?
Well, it was a long time ago.
But I studied a lot.
That's right.
Education is also quite difficult, isn't it?
Education. It's hard, but it's fun.
Oh, really?
It's hard, but it's fun.
Jun, where do you want to be when you are in elementary school, junior high school, and high school?
Well, maybe junior high school.
What is it? It's the most memorable for me.
I see.
It's just like youth, isn't it?
That's right.
It may be the most memorable for me when I was in elementary school.
I've never seen a teacher as beautiful as you.
You say something nice.
If you praise me, I'll give you a snack.
Thank you.
You look like a teacher.
Really?
I'm glad.
Jun?
What's wrong?
Hey.
Hey, Jun.
What?
I was so excited that I did too much.
Wait a minute, Jun.
Jun, calm down.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Are you going to do it?
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I was so excited that I did too much.
But...
No, Jun.
Stop it.
I can't stop it.
No, Jun.
Wait a minute.
I'm really sorry.
No.
Wait a minute.
Calm down.
No.
Wait a minute.
I'm really sorry.
I can't do this.
Wait a minute.
Jun.
Why did you do this?
I'm sorry.
Your boobs...
Boobs?
I can't do this.
I'm sorry.
Your body was beautiful.
It's not beautiful.
I can't do this.
I'm sorry.
I'll be quiet.
Okay.
And...
Yes?
I'll clean up the mess.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Jun.
I told you to be quiet.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Jun.
I can't do this.
Hey.
I'll spoil you.
Spoil me?
I'll spoil you a little.
I want to spoil you.
What?
Wait a minute.
What's wrong with you?
I didn't mean to spoil you.
Jun.
Hey.
I'm just spoiling you.
What?
I want you to pat my head.
My head?
Like this?
I want you to pat my head more.
More?
Like this?
I think I'm studying too much.
Isn't that painful?
I see.
Wait a minute.
Jun.
I'm just spoiling you.
What's wrong with you?
I see.
I'm sorry.
You've grown up.
What?
Wait a minute.
I'll do it directly.
Directly?
It's cold.
I'll do it directly.
Wait a minute.
I'll do it.
I'm sorry.
I pat your head.
I see.
Do you have a lot of stress?
I'm studying hard.
That's right. I've heard that.
I'm proud of you.
You're a good boy.
You're studying hard.
I'm proud of you.
It's a little different, isn't it?
Stop it.
It's a little annoying...
That's not all!
I'll check it out again.
You're just licking it.
Fin.
You okay?
Are you listening me?
Eh?
Are you okay with it?
No more?
Okay this is enough?
⚡ΣΣΣΣ
⚡ΣΣΣ
⚡ΣΣ⚡
Is that enough?
Hey...
Kil...
⚡ΣΣ⚡
⚡Σ⚡
Well, then...
Don't cry...
Chu...
Hey, hey!
Not there!
I said no!
You're a good boy, aren't you?
You're a good boy, so you can listen to me, right?
You can listen to me, right?
Hey!
I'm sorry.
I don't want to do this anymore.
Let's be friends.
I don't have any friends.
You do.
You're cute and young.
I want to be spoiled by you.
You're always away from me.
I know.
I don't think this is a good idea.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Just a little bit.
Calm down.
I can't calm down.
Let's calm down.
I'm just tired from studying.
Let's eat something sweet.
I'm sorry.
Just a little bit.
No.
Please.
You're such a good boy.
That's enough.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
Stop it.
Let me go.
No.
You can't do that.
Let me go.
No.
You can't do that.
I'm sorry.
No.
You can't do that.
I'm sorry.
What?
No.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
No.
I'm sorry.
It's warm here.
I am sorry.
Are you kidding me?
I just felt sick.
I'm sorry.
Hey! Shut up!
I'm pinching you!
I'll pinch your mouth.
Mouth?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Uh, uh Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
Hmph Ah ah ah ah milk
Ahh...
Ah...
It's hot...
Wait...
Wait, Ju...
Please...
Ahh...
Yo!
Where?
Ahh...
Ah!
Huh?
It's warm...
Hey
I want you to pinch me...
Pinch me...
Like this?
I didn't know you were this big...
Pinch me...
Wow...
It's hard...
Your tongue is so gentle...
It feels good...
It's cold...
Pinch me...
It's okay now, right?
Let me hug you one last time...
Hug me...
Really...
One last time...
Okay...
I'm just going to hug you...
I'm going to hug you.
Wait a minute...
Let me hug you...
Let me hug you.
Oh, Chun-kun.
all I did was hug him.
No, I was about to cry, but...
The happening is...
Chun-kun.
What...
I'm sorry.
Oh!!
Oh!
Oh, no...
I'm sorry.
You've been spoiled, haven't you?
You still have a long way to go.
I want to be spoiled by you more.
You're too spoiled.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
You still have a long way to go.
I want to be spoiled by you more.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I'm not done yet.
What did you do?
I want to see you more.
Do you want to see me more?
I understand.
So, I'm a little...
I moved you.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
You're getting bigger.
I'm proud of you.
I'm sorry.
You're a good boy.
Ugh...
What the?
Come on Jun, seriously?
It's really not a good idea to do anything on yourself…
What do you mean?
Well…
You look grumpy
No, I don't think that's a good idea.
I want to lick your boobs.
It's blood, isn't it?
Are you okay?
I can't move.
I can't move at all.
What?
Can you wash my body?
You can do it yourself, right?
I want you to wash my body.
Do I have to wash your body?
Can't I?
I can't help it.
I wanted to come in with you.
Did you peep at me?
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to wash your body?
Can I?
You want me to wash your body, don't you?
Yes.
Did you sweat?
Yes, I did.
That's not good.
You're so spoiled.
I want you to wash my boobs.
Boobs?
Yes.
Yes, boobs.
I've never done that before.
How do I do it?
Like this?
I want you to rub my boobs.
How about my hands?
Like this?
Wow.
It looks like you're laughing at me.
Does it hurt?
Can you pinch me?
Like this?
Yes.
Does this really work?
I don't think so.
It feels good.
You do this a lot, don't you?
I wanted you to do this.
Is that so?
Why are you so spoiled?
I don't know.
You don't know?
When I look at your body, I want to get wet.
When you look at my body?
I wonder why.
Maybe it's because it's hard to study at university.
I don't know.
It's hard.
Is that why you're so spoiled?
Yes.
I can't help it.
I'll wash your boobs.
I'll wash your boobs, too.
Here?
I got it.
I'll wash your boobs.
I'll do this.
I'll rub your boobs.
This feels good.
This?
I'll do this.
Did you sweat?
It's your body.
You sweated.
You studied a lot and sweated.
I'm sorry.
It's really hard.
You're too spoiled.
I'll warm you up.
What should I do?
I'll wash your boobs, too.
I'm sweating.
I got it.
I'll wash your boobs.
I'll do my best.
Is this okay?
I'll wash your boobs, too.
It's great.
It's so hot here.
It feels good.
I'm glad.
Did you wash your boobs?
I'll wash your boobs.
It's clean, isn't it?
What's wrong?
It's nice.
I'll wash your boobs, too.
Can you dance?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's tough for the dog today.
But, you can do it.
The dog will follow you.
You can do it.
Don't touch me.
No...
When I got back, I felt something was wrong with you.
It wasn't that bad...
Why?
Don't lie to me.
Uma...
I'm going crazy from laughing....
I'm going to die from laughter..
I can't live without laughing more than this..
It's painful to hide behind a person like this.
I feel good from this moment on.
First, I'll try to not spit out the water!
This is the second time I'm horrible at not spitting it out...
I'maha it was I who spitted out the water first!
I'm going to drink it all.
It's warm.
...
That's it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I want to touch you.
That's great.
It's refreshing, isn't it?
It's hot.
I want to lick you.
It's refreshing, isn't it?
It's hot.
Wait a minute.
No, no, no.
I want to lick you.
I can't do it anymore.
That's enough.
I'm going to take a bath.
Wait a minute.
I can't do it.
Why did you put me in the bath?
I'm glad you're here.
Oh!
No...
Ahhhhh...
Ah...!
Ugh...
I can't do it anymore.
It's over already.
You can go to bed.
How is it?
It's really good.
I'm glad to hear that.
It's good to eat a lot.
Hey, Grandma.
I want you to say ah.
What?
What are you talking about?
I want you to eat it.
It's not good.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
It's good.
Is it good?
It's special.
Which one do you want to eat?
It's hot.
Here you are.
It's good.
You don't do this at home, do you?
No, I don't.
I don't want to do this at home.
You should eat vegetables, too.
It's good.
Is it good?
Hey.
When I eat this, I want to be spoiled by you.
Do you want to be spoiled?
Yes.
You are spoiled.
How about rice?
I want to be spoiled more.
More?
Really?
Do you want more rice?
No, I don't.
Oh, my God.
Don't be spoiled.
Hey.
I don't mean I don't want to be spoiled.
It's hot.
I don't want to be spoiled.
I like your boobs.
I think so, too.
Oh, my God.
I don't remember where I touched your boobs.
I just touch your boobs as I like.
Do you think so?
Oh, my God.
I don't want to be spoiled.
You don't want to be spoiled, do you?
No, I don't.
Oh, my God.
It's soft.
Yes, it is.
Oh, my God.
You have beautiful boobs.
No, I don't.
I don't want to be spoiled.
Look at me.
Don't take this off.
I'll take it off.
I want you to touch my boobs directly.
I'm in the middle of a meal.
I can't help it.
Like this?
I like this more.
Do you like this?
Oh, my God.
I can't help it.
Why are your boobs so soft?
What do you mean?
I don't know.
My boobs are getting bigger.
It's not fair.
I can't help it.
I don't understand why you touch my boobs.
I touch them like this.
I'm not good at this.
I can feel it in my neck.
That's why you're so weak.
What are you doing?
Ah!
I rubbed my head against your head.
What?
There's something wrong with your neck.
That's not because I'm touching it.
My fingers...
It's in there.
Ah!
Hey!
It hurts a lot.
That's not good.
It's because your neck is standing like this.
No, it's my fault.
Because...
It hurts a lot.
Really?
A little more.
Ah!
It's hot.
Why?
Did you grow up with such a sweet voice?
I'm getting sleepy.
Really?
It's good.
Is it good?
Your breasts are delicious.
I'm getting sleepy.
Don't get sleepy.
What?
I'm not sleepy.
Ah!
Ma'am.
What?
I want you to take care of me, too.
Take care of you?
I'm in trouble.
What should I do, ma'am?
I want you to take care of me.
Like this?
You're selfish.
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
I'll forgive you.
Does it feel good?
Your hands are warm.
That's right.
It's warm.
I feel relieved.
You're shaking a lot.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Really?
I'm sleepy.
Ma'am.
I want you to wipe my drool.
Drool?
Here?
Do you want me to wipe your drool?
Yes.
Thank you.
It's hard.
It's in my mouth.
Does it feel good?
It's warm.
I'm drooling.
Are you drooling?
Do you want me to wipe your drool?
Yes.
I'm drooling because I'm drooling from the tip of my nose.
I'm excited.
Ma'am.
Here?
Wait a minute.
Do you want me to wipe your drool more?
More?
I'll wipe your drool with my mouth.
With your mouth?
Can't you wipe your drool?
I can't.
I can't help it.
It's hard.
More?
Does it feel good?
Thank you.
It's warm.
Does it feel good?
Ma'am.
I'll wipe your drool with my mouth.
Like this?
It's warm.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's warm.
I'll hug you.
I'm happy.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I love you.
If I don't do this, you won't be satisfied, right?
I won't be satisfied.
I'll hug you.
I'm sorry.
It's a special day.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's very hard.
If you eat this, you can eat properly.
I'll hug you.
Do you want me to do it faster?
Like this?
I'm sorry.
Let me do it.
It's okay.
It's so hard.
It's too much, isn't it?
I wish I had a mask.
Ma'am.
Let me take it off.
Is it dirty?
I'll have to wash it.
Is this okay?
Ma'am.
I don't want to lick it.
Don't you want to lick it?
Your breasts?
I don't want to lick your breasts.
I understand.
This, too.
This, too?
Do you really lick it?
I want you to lick it.
Like this?
I'm sorry.
I want to lick it.
Is it cute?
It's cute.
Can you lick it?
I'm sorry.
I like your breasts.
Do you like my breasts?
I want you to like me more than my breasts.
I want to lick your breasts.
I'm sorry.
I want you to be happy.
Scratch! Scratch!
Oh, it feels good.
Can you do it?
You can do it, right?
It hurts!!!
Mom may bleed!
Hey!
Mom!
I'm going crazy.
It hurts a lot.
I'm tired.
You were crying.
It felt good.
I'm hungry again.
Again?
I'm really hungry.
I'll feed you again.
Again?
I can't help it.
I'll feed you again.
Okay.
I'm hungry.
I'm not sure if it's a good thing or a bad thing, but I think it's a good thing.
I'm not sure if it's a good thing or a bad thing.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, stop it.
What?
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
I'm going to wake up.
I can't sleep if I don't kiss you.
Kiss me.
I'm sorry. Let me kiss you.
I can't kiss you.
Can I sleep if I kiss you?
I can't sleep if I don't kiss you.
Then I'll just kiss you.
I'm sorry.
You're like a child.
How is it?
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
I'm sorry.
Isn't it painful?
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's delicious.
How is it?
I can't sleep if I don't kiss you.
You've been sleeping all this time.
Where are you touching?
You're sleeping, aren't you?
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry for doing this.
What should I do?
I can't sleep if I don't kiss you.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
Does it feel good to be kissed?
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
I might have blown into your clothes.
It's okay.
Do you feel better now?
You can sleep now, right?
I can't sleep yet.
What?
Wait a minute.
Don't lick me.
Don't do that.
Does it feel good?
I told you not to do that.
Wait a minute.
Don't do that.
Study.
You can't sleep, can you?
I'll give you a lot of kisses.
I can't help it.
Does it feel good?
Can I stand up?
It's okay.
I'll give you a kiss.
Did I make a lot of little sounds?
You can sleep now, right?
I can sleep now.
Good night.
I want to sleep here.
Go to your room.
I have to go home today.
It was fun.
Really?
Did you tell me everything?
I'll keep it a secret.
You promise?
Yes, I promise.
Are you going out?
Yes, I'm going out.
Why?
What's wrong?
I thought this was the end.
I was lonely.
You've become a spoiled child.
I'll spoil you a lot at the end.
I don't want to go home.
You have to go home.
I'm waiting for you.
I'll do my best.
It's okay.
I can do my best.
Give me a kiss.
Okay.
You like my breasts, right?
I love it.
I love your breasts, too.
Really?
Yes.
You can touch my breasts.
I love you.
Where are you putting your fingers?
It's hard to roll up your sleeves.
Can I touch your breasts?
I'm sweating.
Don't say that.
Wait a minute.
It's beautiful.
Is it?
It's cold.
Is it cold?
I want you to hug me.
Okay.
If I touch you, you'll catch a cold.
I don't want to.
You don't want to?
Yes.
Thank you.
I don't want to.
I don't want to touch your breasts.
I'm tired of it.
Can I touch your breasts now?
I'm sweating.
I'm tired of it.
I feel like I'm being touched.
Really?
I thought your breasts were getting bigger, but they're still small.
It's hard to breathe, isn't it?
It's cold.
How about this?
It's cold, isn't it?
Is it good?
Yes.
I want you to push me from above.
From above?
I want to be crushed.
How about your face?
I want you to crush me with your breasts.
Yes.
It's amazing.
It's like a dream.
It's real.
It's hard to breathe, isn't it?
How about this?
I'm happy.
It's hard to breathe, isn't it?
Can you do your best?
It's hard.
If you sleep like this, you won't be able to do your best.
You have to do your best.
It's hard.
It's very soft.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's hard.
How is it?
Can you do your best with this?
It's hard.
You have something you like, don't you?
I know.
It's this, isn't it?
I'm happy.
I'll give you a lot of sweets.
Do you like me?
Or do you like me?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
How about this?
Do you want me to tickle you a lot?
You're drooling a lot.
I'll tickle you here, too.
You're purring, aren't you?
I'm scared.
I'll tickle you a lot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
My legs are moving.
Do you like this?
I love it.
Look at me.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It's amazing.
Can I pet you?
It's hard again.
It's okay.
You want to be spoiled, don't you?
You're laughing.
Do you like it fast?
What?
It's okay.
Can I give it to you?
No, no.
You're drooling again.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
I did it myself.
Are you used to it?
I'm not used to it yet.
Is this okay?
That's fine.
Does it smell good?
It smells good.
It's warm.
My legs are moving.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
You're dirty.
What?
My butt?
I don't like it.
My face?
Can you see it?
I'm sorry.
Where did you remember that butt?
I remember everything.
What?
Everything.
Don't say that to me.
I'm sorry.
I want more.
You are cute.
Oh, really.
Are you scared?
I'm scared.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I can't stand it.
You can't stand it?
It's so hard.
It's been hard for a long time.
This is my house.
No, it's not.
Come here.
I'm scared.
Oh, my God.
How do you feel?
I don't feel good, either.
I don't feel good.
Come here.
I'm scared.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
!
Dick
Iu is trying to give us a massage after this.
Gosh...
Sorry.
Good boy.
There, there.
That's nice.
There, there.....
Good.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
It's warm.
It's beautiful.
Is it beautiful?
It's warm.
It's the most beautiful when it's cold.
Is that so?
It's warm.
It feels good.
Are you crazy?
I feel good, too.
It's warm.
It feels good.
Let me go.
It's warm.
Do you feel refreshed?
Not yet.
It's warm.
I'll move you this time.
Let me go.
It feels good.
It's warm.
I'll move you again.
It's good, isn't it?
This is the last time.
Can't get rid of it?
Help me...
Go to bed early.
It tickles!
It feels good.
Ouch!
Come here.
Praise me more.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're doing your best.
You're great.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
Come here.
You're getting bigger.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't do it anymore.
What are you doing?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't do it anymore.
You can't do it anymore?
You're amazing.
I'll give you a massage.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're amazing.
Yes!
Come here
Good boy, good boy
It's great to have a lot of hair
I'm going to take it out
I can't breathe
I'm going to drown
It's great to have a lot of hair
Good boy
I'm going to move your hair
A lot
It's great
It's great to have a lot of hair
It's really good
It's really great
It's great
You can do it.
One more time.
You've done a lot, so you can do it.
Thank you very much.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thank you very much.