Kissing
Once upon a time, I was 40 years old.
When I got married, I had a baby.
Tsurengo has been Spring of enter chap for ten years..
There was an old man in the children's room.
When I was five years old and came to this house,
I thought I shouldn't be like this,
so I worked hard and worked hard,
but in the end it didn't go well.
So I went back to Hikikomori again.
He was like that,
but unexpectedly I got used to him,
and we started talking about various things.
His biggest concern was that he was a virgin.
I heard about it, but I said to him,
that the last battle was impossible.
Instead, I used my hands and mouth to do plastic surgery,
but on the night when my husband died ...
Come on, come on.
Take it off, take it off.
You can take it off, right?
It's like this.
You put it out earlier, didn't you?
That's why I can't do it without taking it off five times.
It's going to be fun.
It feels good with your mother's hands.
It's good.
Hey, mom,
do it like you always do.
But before that,
Like I always do?
Oh, I see.
With your hands,
like this.
Is this okay?
It's okay, right?
Do it harder.
Really?
Yes.
Like this?
Put more water on your face.
What's going on?
I cried a lot, but it's tickling.
Your mother has a very good body.
I won't say that.
Wow, that's amazing.
Give me a kiss.
Give me a kiss under my nose.
Give me a kiss?
It's okay, right?
It can't be helped.
Wow, that's amazing.
It's really big.
Give me a kiss.
It's really soft.
Mom, I want to put it in your bowl.
I told you not to do that.
But I heard that it feels good to put it in your bowl.
If you insist, I won't take it out for you.
I won't say that, so take it out.
Then I won't insist.
But instead, I want to lick it.
Lick it?
Then I'll just lick it.
I'll just lick it.
Open your legs.
Do you show it like this?
You can't see it well.
It's slippery, so you can see it very well.
I don't like it.
It smells gross.
I won't say that.
What's wrong?
It's tickling.
It's really gross.
Give me a kiss.
Don't do that.
If you do more than that...
If you do more than that, I won't eat it.
Give me a kiss.
Why is it tickling so much?
It's nothing.
It's tickling a lot.
Don't open it like that.
I can see the inside.
It's weird, isn't it?
I'm just embarrassed.
Don't say more than that.
It's tickling.
Give me a kiss.
What's wrong, mom?
I won't do anything.
It's tickling a lot.
It's nothing, isn't it?
I'll lick it for you.
It's tickling.
It feels good.
Give me a kiss.
It's really dripping.
It feels good.
Give me a kiss.
I just put it out a while ago.
It came out like this.
It feels good.
Thank you.
You...
I...
Even though it's a funeral,
I'm still in the room.
From now on,
I'll be alone with that girl.
What will happen to my life?
I...
Why didn't you ask about the funeral?
I don't like relatives.
That's why.
From now on, I'll give you 1,000.
Mom...
I told my dead father
that I'd make friends with you.
I see.
Let's make friends.
I'm glad.
You think so, too.
Of course.
We're parents.
From now on,
we're not parents.
Hey, Masashi.
What are you doing?
My father died.
Let me have sex.
Hey.
What are you saying in front of your father?
Hey, stop it.
I'll make friends with you.
Hey.
Let's make friends.
Masashi,
your father is watching.
I want to see your father.
I want to see you making friends.
Hey.
Stop it.
Masashi.
Hey.
Wow.
This dress looks good on you.
Stop it, Masashi.
Hey.
I want to see you making friends.
Masashi.
Wow.
Your breast is soft.
You're wearing such a tight dress.
Hey.
Stop it.
I showed this dress to my relatives.
Your voice is so cute.
No.
Your father is watching.
I told you no.
Why not?
Because
I'm in front of your father's house.
What?
I want to see you making friends.
But I don't want to see you like this.
Stop it.
You've been doing this since you were born.
Yes.
But...
Stop it.
Hey.
Your father.
Your mother is wearing a light blue bra.
Wow.
Masashi.
Hey.
You're sticking out.
No.
I'm going to touch your neck.
You've been doing this since you were born.
Stop it.
Hey.
Wow.
Your neck is soft.
Hey.
You've been doing this since you were born.
No.
Stop it.
I'm in front of your father's house.
You've been doing this since you were born.
Wow.
Your mother's breast is big.
Stop it.
Please make more noise.
I'll let your father hear it.
Stop it.
No.
Your mother's breast is bigger.
Stop it.
I like this part.
Your mother's breast is big.
Stop it.
Your mother's breast is bigger.
I'm still on your bra.
Stop it.
Stop!
I'm still on your bra.
Stop it.
It may seem your mother clings on your hair.
You are like this.
Aren't you —
You behave badly.
No, don't do that
You can hear her voice
No, mom, you can feel it
No, you can feel it
She is more sensitive than usual
I feel that her nails are harder than usual
Her nails are very hard
No, I can't
Why not?
I can feel it
No, you can't
Show her that you are getting along with her
Dad, look at me
No, you can't
Show her that you are getting along with her
Dad, look at me
No, you can't
Show her that you are getting along with her
Wow, you are getting along with her
No, you can't
Show her that you are getting along with her
Please
I can't tell it because she has no more weight
No, you can't
I can see that
Are you excited to be touched in front of your father?
Don't say such a thing
You don't deny it
You feel it after all
You smell it
You smell it all the time
Give me a kiss
Show me your butt
Give me a hand
Let's do it in front of your father
Show your father that you are getting along with him
Give me a hand
Isn't this skirt short?
It's not
I can see your butt a little more
I can't do it
It's so itchy
I want to see more
What's wrong with your pants?
It's too short
It's so itchy
Don't grab me so much
Why?
Because you feel it?
Give me a hand
It's getting tighter
I'm embarrassed
It's overflowing
Show me your butt
A funeral is not a white dress and a white dress
You expected me to do this, didn't you?
I didn't think so
You can look at it directly
I'm scared
You were pulling the string
You have to feel it to do it
It's overflowing
Don't do that
The inside is better
It went in easily
Don't do that
No
I'm embarrassed
Look at this
It's the finger that was in the locker
No
Don't do that
It's so wet
It's so itchy
It's so stiff
Does it feel good just by rubbing it?
Don't rub it so much
Don't rub it
Put it in your mouth
Look at this
It's like this
Gently
Look at me
More
3, 2, 1
Mom
Which one is bigger, your dad's or mine?
Mine is bigger
I see
It feels better when a woman's nipples are bigger, right?
I don't think so
But actually
Your mom is also excited to lick her nipples
I don't think so
You're drooling
It's so big
It's better when it's bigger
Mom
I want to put it in your nipples
I can't
Why?
It's really good
Your nipples are always flat
It's good, right?
No, you can't
It feels good when it's your mom
You're drooling
No, you can't
I don't know
Look at me
It hurts
Gently
It feels good
Don't move too much
Don't move
It feels good
What did you say?
Don't move too much
Whose nipples feel good?
No, my nipples feel good
No, it feels good
It feels good
Mom
Did you say that
in front of your dad?
Don't say that
Your mom kissed you
No
Your nipples are bad
It feels good
when it's your mom
No
You're drooling
Gently
It's hot
You're drooling
No, it feels good
It feels good
No
My nipples are hot
Don't take it out
Ah
I'll clean your nipples
It's not clean
It's clean
But your nipples
felt good
Now I'm
graduated
Yes
Now you're
graduated
But
sex
is
the last
We're
not real parents
but we can't
have sex
No
I want to have more sex
One more time
No
Please
forgive me
for having sex
with Masashi
Please
What's wrong?
I want to have sex
with you
So
you said no
Why?
You said
my nipples felt good
Yes
Masashi's nipples
are big
and feel good
But
we're
not real parents
I know
but I can't stand it
Then
will you listen
to me?
Can I have sex?
Really?
What should I do?
How can I
live
without nipples?
You can live with your dad's insurance
No
I will die one day
What should I do?
I work
so
can you stop
working outside?
No
You want to get along with your mom
I want to get along with her
Then
you can have sex
Please
work
I will
Please
No
Stop working
Okay
I will
No
Feel so good
Feels good?
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I
'm sorry
I'm sorry
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it feels good
Ah
Oh
I'm sorry.
It's gotten so big.
Why are you licking your fingers?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
Here.
You're licking so hard.
It's getting bigger, right?
Yes.
Here.
I'm going to lick you.
Okay.
Here.
It's gotten so big.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
I want to lick you.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You want to lick me?
Yes.
It's gotten so big.
Here.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
It's gotten so big.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
It's amazing.
I knew it.
It feels so good.
Really?
Here.
It's gotten so much softer.
It's gotten softer, right?
It's so good.
Oh, I see.
It seems that you put it in.
Does it feel good inside your boobs?
Yes, it feels good.
Oh, great.
It feels good inside your boobs.
Does it feel good inside your boobs?
Yes, it does.
Please do it with your mouth.
With my mouth?
Yes.
Oh, great.
It feels good.
Please do it with your mouth.
Oh, great.
It feels good, doesn't it?
No, it's not enough.
I want to have sex with you.
Oh, great.
Your boobs are soaked.
It's wet because you said no.
Oh, great.
No, no, no.
Please do it with your mouth.
Hey.
Yes?
Go to sleep.
I want to do it again.
Your boobs will break in the morning, right?
Oh, great.
Your boobs are like this.
They are touching your legs.
Oh, great.
Yes?
Your boobs got bigger.
Yes, because my boobs are getting closer.
I want to have sex with you.
Oh, great.
Yes.
Do you want a kiss?
I want to have a kiss.
Oh, great.
It's oily, so you don't know where your boobs are.
Here, right?
Yes.
Here.
Oh, great.
You are so young.
I can feel your nipples.
They are too big.
Oh, great.
I can feel it.
I can feel your nipples.
Oh, great.
Your nipples are empty.
I can feel your nipples.
I have something good for you today.
What is it?
Look at this.
What's wrong with it?
I saw you using it in the video.
I want to use it.
Do you know how to use it?
I saw the manual.
Really?
It says you can vibrate like this.
How do you feel?
I can feel it.
It says you can vibrate like this.
I can feel your nipples.
I can feel it.
I can feel both of your nipples.
Your nipples are bigger than before.
I can feel it.
I can feel both of your nipples.
How do you feel?
I can feel it.
There was a different place.
You can feel it by yourself.
I can feel it.
I feel good
Not yet
Did you go from the top of the pants?
I feel good
I wanted to see more
Mom, over there
It's true
The pants are soaked
I feel good
It's so wet
Be patient
I feel good
You're moving your hips
I'm moving
I feel good
No
You're moving
You feel good
Around here?
I feel good
Mom
Do you want to go?
Let me go
I'm going
I feel good
I'm sweating
You're sweating
I think you can put your finger in
I want to put my finger in
Where?
In mom's belly
You put your finger in
I feel good
Slowly
More
I feel good
I will try to put two hands
I think it's easy to put two hands
I feel good
Ah...
Amazing...
Feels good.
Ah, it feels good...
Ah, it feels good, it feels good...
Here.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Amazing.
It's getting really, really tight.
No.
Mom.
It feels so good.
You're the only one who feels good.
You can do it.
I see.
I hope it doesn't feel too good.
I want to give it to you.
I love you.
Kiss.
Amazing.
It's so good.
Your ears feel good too, right?
Yes.
Are you nervous?
Yes, I am.
Ah.
What?
You can lick that part too.
It feels good, right?
Yes, it does.
Ah.
It feels good.
What?
Ah.
It feels good, right?
Yes.
Ah.
Amazing.
Kiss.
Ah.
I feel like I'm being pinched.
Yes.
Ah.
Ah?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh
It's painful, isn't it?
Yes, it's painful.
Well, then,
Let's have a petting match with my mother.
Yes.
My butt is tingling.
It's getting harder and harder.
It's so hot.
It's so hard.
I can't stand it anymore.
Mom,
It's so hot.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's so hard.
It's so big.
It's so hot.
It's so hard.
It's so big.
I can feel it inside my mom.
It's so hot.
It feels good.
It feels good here.
It's so hot.
I can feel it inside my mom.
It feels so good.
This is the best.
Move like that from the bottom.
It feels so good.
I can't stop.
Move from the back.
It feels so good.
Slowly.
What?
Give me a kiss.
That feels good.
That feels really good.
That feels really kicky.
It feels great.
Good...
Wow, that's heavy.
Philip, it feels good, Philip.
No, turn it on!
It tickles.
This feels great.
Ah ah ah ah hhhing hihinh sweet ah ahh ah ah ahhehehe
Ah amazing
Ah patients
It's been a while since I felt so good.
I can't stop.
It feels so good.
I told you not to take it out.
My son and I have sex every day.
And we have sex every day.
Our two children...