I don't want to do any housework even though I'm on a break.
But I'm hungry.
I wonder if someone's going to cook for me.
Huh?
Housework?
I don't have anything to eat.
Oh, this is pretty cheap.
I didn't know.
I wonder if I can order it.
Oh, and I can play it from that day.
What time is it now?
Oh, I can play it.
I wonder if I can order it.
Huh?
Is it coming soon?
Yes?
Hello.
Excuse me.
I'm Oishi, from Village Kaseif Center.
Nice to meet you today.
I'm Yoshino.
Please come in.
Yes, excuse me.
Well, then.
Please come in.
Okay.
Well, today...
Would you like to clean the room and prepare the food?
Yes, please.
Well, then...
I'm going to clean up around the house.
Yes.
And then I'll prepare the food.
Yes, please.
Where should I put this?
Oh, excuse me.
I'll put it here.
Do you have any dishes you'd like to eat?
Well...
There are potatoes, too.
Well, then.
How about curry and salad?
That sounds good. I love curry.
That's good.
Wow.
I'd be happy if I could see your mouth.
Would you like to try some?
Oh, yes.
Then I'll eat it right away.
How is it?
It's so delicious.
I'm so glad.
It's amazing.
I can do anything.
Don't you always feel lonely at convenience stores and supermarkets?
Yes.
It's been a long time since I've had such a home-cooked meal.
I've been thinking about my girlfriend for a long time.
It's been a long time since I've had such a home-cooked meal because I've been alone with my girlfriend all the time.
Really?
Well, then.
I'll treat you to sweets today.
Oh, yes.
What?
Is it okay?
I've never been treated like this before.
Really?
Is it okay?
Then again.
How is it?
Is it delicious?
Yes.
Yoshino.
I've been telling you that I don't have a girlfriend.
Don't you have a girlfriend over there?
Oh, no.
I've been looking at my boyfriend all the time.
If you don't mind,
would you like to serve him?
Please come over here.
Well, then.
Is it okay?
Would you like to serve him?
No, thank you.
Wow.
Are you all having a good time?
No, we are not.
What?
Are you talking about me?
I'm so happy.
It's a secret to the company, isn't it?
Of course.
I'm so happy.
It's been a long time since I've done something like this.
I want to see you in person.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
Would you look at this?
Wow.
It's been a long time since I've done something like this.
I'm nervous.
Is it because of the vinegar?
Wow.
It's getting really hard.
I see.
Wow.
I'm sorry for asking you to do something like this.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm kissing you.
Do you like kisses?
Yes.
Then, I'll kiss you in person.
In person?
Wow.
It's so big.
It's sticking out a little.
Do you hate sticking out?
No, I love it.
I'm glad.
Can you see it?
It's dangerous.
It's dripping.
Would you like to touch it?
Is it okay?
It's soft.
It's been a long time since I've done something like this.
Really?
It's coming out.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's been a long time since I've done something like this.
I'm sorry.
I'm rude to you.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Can I touch it more?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It's big.
Is it?
I can see the bottom.
It's good.
It's elastic.
I love butt.
Me too.
What?
What's wrong with your back?
It smells bad.
Don't say that.
I love the smell here.
Please apply a lot.
Okay.
It feels good.
I'm interested in your butt.
Can I see it?
Yes.
It's pink.
It feels good.
It's good to have a little protruding butt.
Sit down on your own.
Your butt is soft.
I want to ride it.
It's good.
I can't stand it.
I'm sorry.
I hurt myself.
It's tickling.
I want to see it.
It's not good to see it.
Just a little.
Is it okay?
Yes.
It's good.
It's moving.
Is it okay?
It's not good.
I haven't washed it yet.
It's okay.
I want to make you feel better.
I'm sorry.
Is it okay?
Yes.
It's not good.
I want to see your butt.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
Yes.
It's good.
It's tickling.
The tongue is moving.
It's moving.
It looks very good.
Yes.
It's good.
I have to put it on the other side, but is it okay?
Oh, that's it.
Oh, it's hot.
That's right.
Oh,
it's hot.
Can I put that much?
Oh,
oh,
Ouch!
I'm fine.
Oh.
Did you drink it?
I drank it.
It's so cold.
Were you waiting for me?
Did you feel refreshed?
Yes.
Next, let's clean the bedroom.
Thank you.
The bathroom has been cleaned.
Uh-oh...
Can I sleep here?
Sure.
It's so warm.
I'm so happy.
It feels good.
Can I sleep here?
Yes.
Sure.
Can I sleep here?
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Your thighs are more fluffy.
Really?
Yes.
It's touching.
It's so soft.
It's amazing.
It's a service.
It's a good service.
It's so soft.
I don't like this kind of service.
I see.
I love it.
It's touching.
Here?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's touching.
Can I sleep here?
Sure.
Are you having a hard time?
No.
Why?
Because your boobs are puffy.
I'm having a hard time.
I see.
It's so painful.
Can I raise my hand?
Yes.
It's touching.
Can I sleep here?
It's amazing.
It's touching.
Can I sleep here?
Sure.
It's touching.
It's amazing.
Thank you.
It's touching.
Here you go.
You're doing this for free, right?
Yes.
I'm doing a lot of free stuff.
Really?
Yes.
I'm sweating.
Do you want some milk?
Yes.
Do you like this kind of stuff?
Do you want some milk?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Do you feel it?
I feel it.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
It was hard to move, right?
Are you ready?
Yes.
It's oozing.
It's amazing.
You can't clean this room, right?
I'll clean it.
It's amazing.
I feel like it's more dirty than before.
I'll clean it.
Is it okay?
I'm going to massage your ears
It's so tight
Your ears are going to tear
I'm going to massage your ears
Your ears are moving
Your ears are going down
I'm going to massage your ears
It's so tight
It's a good service
It feels so good
Even the details
I'm losing my mind
It's so tight
I'm going to sleep
It feels so good
It's so tight
I'm going to wash your ears
It's so soft
I'm going to massage your ears
It's so tight
I'm going to cry
It feels so good
It's so tight
It's a good service
It feels so good
It's so tight
I'm sorry
It's a good service
It's so tight
It feels so good
I'm going to massage your ears
It's so tight
It feels so good
Can I stop here?
It's so tight
My hips hurt
Ah, it's cold.
It's cold.
It's moving.
It's moving a lot.
It's here.
Can you see it?
Look.
It's amazing.
It's moving a lot.
It's cold.
It's amazing.
It's here.
It feels good.
It's moving a lot.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's moving a lot.
It's amazing.
Can you see it?
It's moving a lot.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's moving a lot.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Here, here.
It's very sticky.
Amazing.
It's amazing.
Here, here.
It's very sticky.
Amazing.
Here, here.
It's amazing.
Look at the back.
Can you see it?
It's very sticky.
What should I do?
Don't close it like that.
It will come out.
It won't come out.
Is it okay if it comes out?
It's okay.
Give me a lot.
Is it okay?
It's amazing.
Look.
Can you see it?
It's amazing.
Is it beautiful?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Oishi-san, please come here again.
Is it okay?
You can ask the students for help to help to make Oishi-san will go to school.
Thank you.
Siwan...
Since then, Oishi-san came to my house once a week.
I did everything I could for Oishi-san who was on duty every time.
Thanks to that, the relationship deepened and he answered my various requests.
The He's my damn enemy, I know!
Even if I went through hell and put my life in danger.
I can never learn anything from Oishi-san.
Turn to me once that he has changed.
We were fighting back then, right?
I knew we had this stuff.
Is it good?
Looks tasty!
I don't want you to eat this
It's so delicious!
Oh, it's hot.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's hot.
I'm nervous.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
I want to be clean.
I'm sorry for calling you.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Today...
Can you clean this with this?
Please.
What is this?
This is...
Wow.
This...
Do you want me to put this on?
Yes, please.
It's embarrassing.
I like the way you clean.
I want to see you clean.
I understand.
May I?
Yes.
Can I help you?
Which one is higher?
This one is lower.
Like this?
Yes.
I want to be in a good position.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Like this?
That's good.
Is this okay?
Is it higher?
Yes.
I don't know if I can put it on.
What?
What's wrong?
Yes.
In a good position?
Is it okay?
Can I start cleaning?
Yes.
Please.
Are you here?
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Is the radio on?
Yes, it's on.
That's good.
Please.
What's wrong?
I can't move.
I'm not good at this.
Is the radio on?
Yes, it is.
Let me see.
Can I start cleaning in this state?
Yes.
Is it really moving?
Is it okay?
It's okay.
The sound is getting louder.
There it is.
It's amazing.
The sound of the motor is amazing.
Does it hurt?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's moving.
I'm sorry.
There's a beat.
It's amazing.
It's moving.
Let me see.
It's a weak stimulus.
Is it okay?
It's not okay.
It's okay.
Which one is stronger and which one is weaker?
It's stronger.
Which one is better?
This one?
More?
It's amazing.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
This one is stronger.
It's amazing.
This one is better.
It's moving.
It's amazing.
It's not okay.
It's okay.
Can I sit down?
Move your hips forward.
It's good.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
You like it.
Oishi-san, the other day...
You said you were going to do it alone.
Right?
It's amazing.
When you do it alone...
Which toy do you use?
Do you use this one?
Sometimes.
Is this okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
It's hitting here.
It's sleeping.
Then...
This one.
Hold on.
Please spread your legs.
I'm sorry.
I want to put a lot of pressure on your buttocks.
It's already messy.
It's going to be smooth from here.
Hold on.
Amazing.
It's pushing out.
Is it going to fall?
Hold on.
It's not coming out.
The pressure is amazing.
It's closing the entrance.
I'm sorry.
Can you show it to me?
Did you see it?
Is it going to fall?
It's moving.
Amazing.
Just like this.
It's looking at you.
Amazing.
Please spread your legs.
I'm sorry.
The right?
The left?
It's going to be lonely.
It's doing this.
It's not stopping.
Can I see from here?
This way.
It's good.
Amazing.
From here.
It's moving.
That's right.
Amazing.
It's moving.
It's good.
Amazing.
I'm spinning and eating and I'm only in this state.
If I eat up all the snacks and get dizzy...
I'm going to be sorry.
queena
Oh, it's the best.
You're sweating, aren't you?
Let's keep you warm.
Breathe in.
You're sweating, aren't you?
This side, too.
Wow.
This is the best.
Please do it.
Can you feel it here?
Yes, I can.
Wow.
It feels good.
Your nose is full.
Wow.
Slowly.
It's hot.
It's really hot.
Is your finger strong or weak?
It's strong.
This side, too.
It's going to be like this.
Wow.
You're crying.
That's good.
Wow.
Please sit down.
How do you feel?
It's hot.
It's really hot.
Let's have a shower.
Okay.
Let's see it.
It's over there.
Can I have a seat?
This is nice.
It's over there.
Damn it.
Calm down.
Lower, lower.
It feels so good.
It's over today.
Lower, lower.
It feels so good.
I can't.
Lower.
It's over there.
I can't.
It feels so good.
It's over.
I see.
I can't.
It feels so good.
It's over there.
It feels so good, so good.
I can't.
It feels so good.
Wow, that's amazing.
That's the place, right?
This is it.
Wow, this is amazing.
It feels so good.
When you get in here, you just do whatever you want.
It's amazing.
Wow, that's amazing.
That's amazing.
It's so hard and amazing.
That's because you're moving.
That's why it's hard.
I'm so happy.
That's because you're moving.
That's amazing.
Look at that.
Wow, that's amazing.
That's amazing.
You need to breathe more.
Wow, that's amazing.
That's amazing.
I'm so happy.
I'm so tired
It's okay
No, no, no
Amazing!
Oh, no.
Miss.
It's not good to do this.
I'll do it.
Oh, Miss.
Like this.
Yes, yes.
Oh...
Don't cry.
Don't cry...
Stop...
Stop, please...
Please...
Let's go.
Thank you for watching!