I see. You won't be able to come back this holiday, will you?
It's okay to be busy, but don't break your body.
Me? I'm fine.
But I haven't seen you for half a year, so I'm just lonely.
There's no way I'm cheating on you.
You're the one who's cheating on me, aren't you?
I'm kidding. I know.
Then come back soon.
I'll be patient until then.
By the way, Yui is bringing a boy friend to my house tomorrow.
I don't know if it's a boyfriend or not.
But you don't have to worry about that.
Yui is at an age where it's not strange to have one or two boyfriends.
Oh, I see.
Good night.
Hey, Yui.
Is the boy you're bringing to my house today your boyfriend?
No, he's a friend of mine.
You know him? Who is he?
He's Ryota from Yamada's house.
Ryota?
You used to come to my house a lot, didn't you?
I happened to see him the other day.
I haven't seen him in years.
He said he'd come to my house next time and I was so happy.
I see.
Hey, Ryota.
Did you become handsome?
Don't talk about that.
Hurry up and put on your bra.
He'll be here soon.
I don't care about that.
But it's hot.
And Ryota is a childhood friend, so he's like a family.
No, he's a boy in puberty.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Yes.
Oh, Ryota.
Long time no see.
Come in.
Excuse me.
You've grown up.
And you've become handsome.
No, I haven't.
But you're still beautiful.
What?
I didn't expect you to say that to me.
Welcome, Ryota.
Hi, Yui.
Yui told me that you still think I'm beautiful.
That's obvious.
What?
Is that true?
No, it's not.
You're really beautiful.
Thank you.
Come in.
Let's look at old photos in my room.
Sounds good.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
I'll bring you some snacks later.
Thank you.
Hey, don't you feel nostalgic?
You're right.
We were so little.
It's so nostalgic.
How long ago was it?
Wait.
12 or 13 years ago?
I think so.
Wow.
Look at this.
Do you remember?
When we were in the academy.
This is when I played Santa Claus.
Yes, I played the daughter of a blacksmith.
You're right.
By the way, I forgot to tell you this.
You helped me, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
I can't stop laughing when I remember that time.
Wait a minute.
Look at this.
I brought you some snacks.
Thank you.
I'll go to the bathroom.
Okay.
Yuta, I brought you some snacks.
Thank you.
Is it okay to drink tea?
Yes.
Ryota, can I ask you something?
What is it?
Well...
Actually...
You're dating Yui, aren't you?
What?
Even if you're dating Yui, I won't object to it, so don't worry.
Is Ryota your boyfriend?
No, he's just a friend.
Is that so?
Yes.
We've just met a few years ago.
I see.
Then, don't worry about it.
Were you looking at the album?
Yes.
Let me see it, too.
This is a picture of you when you were a student.
I miss it.
You two look so young.
I'm cold.
Let me see the other one.
Let me see the other one, too.
This is so cute.
I was watching this with Yui.
Yui played the role of a housekeeper's daughter.
She helped me a lot.
I see.
Do you remember this?
Yes, I do.
But I don't think he remembers.
Ryota, you confessed to me at that time, didn't you?
Yes, I remember.
I remember.
You said you wanted to marry me, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
But at that time, you said,
You said,
You patted my head, didn't you?
You remember it well.
But I was happy at that time.
Yui's mother was the woman I admired.
Really?
Yes.
Ryota, you're so cute.
I don't know what to do.
You're my daughter's friend.
I think I feel your love for me.
But you're not Yui's boyfriend.
It's okay.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What are you looking at?
I miss this.
I know.
I'm going.
Take your time.
Thank you, Mom.
I'm going.
No.
The more I think about it, the more I care about you.
I'm sure you think of me as a woman.
When I think about it, I feel sick.
No.
I'm sorry.
What?
Come on.
Ryota.
I feel a little sorry to think about a boy who is the same age as my daughter.
But he is not Yui's boyfriend.
It's been a while since then, but Ryota's feelings and delusions have become stronger.
Mom's hamburger steak is delicious.
Is that so? That's good.
Hey, Yui. Have you seen Ryota recently?
Well, I see him sometimes.
Oh, I went to Ryota's house the other day.
Eh? Ryota's house? You mean Mr. Yamada's house?
Yes.
Oh, I see.
Oh, I went to Ryota's house the other day.
Eh? Ryota's house? You mean Mr. Yamada's house?
Yes. My uncle and aunt wanted to see my mom.
Hey, why didn't you tell me?
I'm sorry. I forgot.
Then I have to call Ryota's mom and dad.
Hey, Mom.
Yes?
What?
Actually, Ryota and I are going out.
Oh, really?
Since when?
He sent me home when I went to Ryota's house the other day.
He asked me if I wanted to go out with him.
Eh?
Then...
Did you already do it?
Eh? Mom, why do you ask me that?
Because it's my duty as a parent to protect my daughter.
I haven't done it yet.
I see.
Mom, I'll support you.
Thank you.
By the way, bring Ryota to my house again.
How about next Saturday and Sunday?
Eh? I can't.
It's a club activity.
I'm not at home.
I see.
That's right.
I'm a bad mother to call my daughter's boyfriend home on a day off.
But I had no choice.
When I called Mr. Yamada, he answered the phone.
Here you are.
Thank you.
What?
Well...
What did you want to talk to me about?
Ryota, Yui told me that you two are dating.
Eh?
Actually, we're going to date.
I see.
Yui is my precious daughter.
So I thought it would be better to know her boyfriend.
Can you take good care of Yui?
Eh?
Yes, of course.
Ryota, have you ever dated a girl?
Yes, I have.
I see.
Ouch!
Have you ever had sex?
Eh?
A little.
Can you have sex with Yui?
Eh?
Of course, I can.
Really?
I'm a little worried.
For example...
Yes?
How do you hold hands?
Hands?
Yes.
Can I hold your hands?
Go ahead.
Like this?
Eh?
Then...
How do you kiss?
Eh?
Kiss?
Yes.
You have to know how your daughter's boyfriend kisses.
Eh?
Try it.
Yes.
It's hard.
Be gentle.
Eh?
Yes.
Give me your tongue.
My tongue?
Yes.
You can't do that.
You can't let Yui have her first kiss.
Yes.
Try it again.
Don't put pressure on your tongue.
Yes.
Be gentle.
How do you touch Yui?
Touch her?
My chest?
Try touching her.
Yes.
At first, I'll do it gently.
Slowly.
Don't touch your nipples so soon.
If you do it like this, you can stroke your whole chest.
That's right.
Your nipples are getting stiff, aren't they?
Yes, they are.
If that's the case, I'll do it gently.
I'll do it gently.
I'll try to pinch your nipples.
Like this?
Yes.
I'll do it gently.
That's right.
That's good.
Can you see that your nipples are getting stiff?
Yes, they are.
If that's the case, not only your hands, but also your mouth.
My mouth?
Excuse me.
That's right.
I'll do it gently.
Try to put it in your mouth.
Don't rub your back. Do it gently.
Yes.
Don't rub your back.
That's right.
That's good.
No.
Mom, this is...
But you have to do it properly.
It's for Yui.
Yes.
Can you see that it's getting hot?
Yes, I can.
It's hot and cold.
You can touch it like this.
No.
Ryota, how are you going to touch it?
Think of it as Yui and try it.
Yes.
Do it gently like this.
That's right.
Gently.
Is it hard?
I understand.
Then...
Touch it directly.
Directly?
That's right.
Is it really okay?
If Yui gets hurt, she'll be in trouble.
Try it.
Come on.
It's hot.
It's really hot.
That's right.
Soak the whole thing.
Let it soak in.
How is it?
That's right.
Touch it gently.
Try to push it against your head.
That's right.
That's good.
Can you let Yui live?
Yes, I'll do my best.
Let her live.
That's right.
Gently.
That's good.
Try to lick it.
That's right.
Gently.
Excuse me.
That's right.
Let me cut the tip of your tongue.
Like a plastic surgeon.
That's good.
Do it from the back.
Excuse me.
That's good.
That's cold.
That's right.
Keep doing it.
That's good.
Then...
This time...
I have to check this side, too.
That's amazing.
It's gotten so hard.
But...
I have to check the size.
I have to check the size of your penis.
I have to make sure.
But...
If I don't, I can't leave Yui in peace.
Let me see.
Let me make sure.
That's good.
That's amazing.
You have a great penis.
Thank you.
It's grown well.
Let me check the taste, too.
That's good.
It feels so good.
I'm going to puke.
You can't.
There are other things I want to try.
I can't.
Can't you stand it?
I can't stand it.
But...
I have to check the taste, too.
Taste?
What do you mean?
You have sex with Yui, right?
Then...
I have to check the taste, too.
Can you do it well?
Can I really do this?
If I don't, I can't leave Yui in peace.
Okay.
Don't do it all of a sudden.
Let me do it.
Slowly.
If it's too short...
Put it in slowly.
Okay.
Don't move yet.
I'm sorry.
If you move right after putting it in...
Yui is a virgin.
You'll be surprised, right?
Yes.
Can you go over there?
If you think it's Yui, hug her.
Yui.
Call her.
Tell her how you feel.
Yui, does it hurt?
It's okay.
Move it slowly.
Ryota, how do you feel now?
I don't feel good.
Then, you have to tell her how you feel.
Yui's body is hot.
It's too hot and I don't feel good.
Give me a kiss.
It's hot.
Whisper a lot of words of love.
Yui, I love you.
I'll take good care of you.
Come closer.
How do you feel?
Ryota, how do you feel?
Over there.
I don't feel good.
Don't move.
Don't move yet.
You have to make Yui move.
I don't feel good.
Over there.
Ryota, it's hot.
I can't move.
Ryota, it's hot and I don't feel good.
I don't feel good.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
It's not good yet.
Hang in there.
I'll do my best.
Can you do it from behind?
I'll do it from behind.
If I do it too hard,
I'll hurt Yui.
Be gentle.
Like this?
I'm sorry.
I don't feel good.
Help me.
I have to move as if I'm shaking.
I'm sweating.
I don't feel good.
I have to go again.
I have to go.
I don't feel good.
I don't feel good now.
But I can't be strong like AV.
I can't do it.
But I can do it now.
I can do it.
I don't feel good.
Did you hit her as hard as you did now?
I'm sure she was in pain.
Yui.
You drank too much AV.
I'm sorry.
If you get too much power on an inexperienced person, it'll hurt.
Remember that.
I got it.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad.
But it's okay for me.
You want to get a lot of power, don't you?
Yes, I do.
You can do whatever you want this time.
Come here.
I'm sorry.
Yui.
I love you.
Call me Ai.
Ai.
I don't feel good.
I can't stand it anymore.
Do you want to go?
Yes.
I'm glad you feel better.
Ai.
Yui.
Don't cry.
You can cry now.
Ai.
Yui.
I'm going.
Come here.
Ai.
I'm going.
Wow.
Are you really okay?
I'm okay.
I told you before.
Don't do this to Yui.
Thank you.
I understand.
It's a promise.
Ryota.
You passed the exam.
Thank you.
Ryota.
Do you remember that you took a bath with me when you came to my house when you were little?
No.
I don't remember because I was little.
I see.
When we took a bath together, you touched my boobs all the time.
When you were little, you loved my boobs.
I didn't know you were such a good boy.
When I look at your boobs now, I get excited.
I'll wash your favorite boobs.
What?
I know you're excited.
Wow.
It's very soft.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Your boobs are very big.
I love them.
You haven't changed since you were little.
It's hot.
I guess you didn't wash your boobs like this when you were little.
You're right.
It's hot.
I can't stand it anymore.
Ryota is looking at my boobs.
I'll wash your boobs.
Okay.
Thank you.
Close your legs.
Okay.
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm about to cry.
I love your boobs.
Are you talking about me?
Yes.
Look at me.
Does your neck feel good?
Yes.
It's hot.
I'm tired.
I'll do something more sexy.
I'll do it from behind.
I'll wash your boobs.
It's hot.
Your neck feels good.
Your boobs feel good.
You're just laughing.
I'm too nervous.
I'm going crazy.
It's hot.
Is your nipple weak?
Yes.
It's dangerous.
Your waist is crooked.
It's too hot.
It's hot.
I'll do something more sexy.
More?
It's hot.
I'll do it from behind.
Okay.
Stand still.
It's hot.
I'll clean your mouth.
I've never been licked this way.
It's hot.
I'll teach you how to lick your nipples.
Your tongue is tangled.
I'm too nervous.
Your nipples are delicious, so I'll lick them a lot.
It's hot.
I'm going to cry.
Do you want to feel good?
I want to.
Okay.
It's hot.
Do you want to lick your nipples again?
I can't.
It's hot.
I'll clean your mouth.
Did you feel good?
It was really good.
I couldn't stand it when you licked my nipples.
Let's take a bath and continue.
I don't want to.
It's hot.
I've been watching you.
How many times did you take a bath?
I took a bath as much as I wanted.
It's hot.
Do you want to take a bath?
You've been standing all the time.
It's hot.
I like you.
I can't breathe.
But you like nipples, don't you?
It's hot.
I'm happy.
I'm touching your nipples.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
It's really good.
Your nipples are big.
It's hard.
Look at me.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
I couldn't stand it when you licked my nipples.
Don't do that.
It's hot.
It's hot when you touch my nipples.
I can't stand it.
I can't stand it either.
Do you feel good?
How about you?
It's really good.
Make yourself feel better.
It's hot.
I can't stand it when you lick my nipples.
I'm sweating a lot.
It's hot.
It's really good.
You made me feel better.
I'll do something more pleasant for you.
Raise your hips.
It's hot.
I feel good just by rubbing your nipples.
Have you ever done something like this?
No, I haven't.
I've never had such a big nipple.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Thank you.
It's hot.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm ticklish.
It's too ticklish.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Your nipples are overflowing.
It's embarrassing.
It's hot.
Be careful of your mouth.
Are you okay with just your mouth?
Don't you want more?
Thank you.
It's hot.
I want to put it in your nipples.
I'm sick, too.
Can I put it in your nipples?
Let me do it.
It's hot.
It hurts.
It's coming in.
It's all in.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Can I do it again?
It's hot.
It's all in.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's all over my body.
It's all over your body.
It's hot.
Can I do it again?
Of course.
You said you like big buttocks, right?
I like big buttocks.
It hurts a lot.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's all over my body.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's all over my body.
You said you like big buttocks.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It feels good to rub it on my back, right?
It feels good.
It's hot.
I want to do it more.
I want to rub it on my back.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You shouldn't do that.
When I close my legs like this, it feels good.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You shouldn't do that.
It feels weird.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I want to do it more.
I can only hear the sound of my legs.
It feels good.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
I can't do it anymore.
It's okay.
It hurts.
Keep doing it.
I can't do it anymore.
You can't do it.
You can only do it to me.
I'm the only one who can do it.
Do you understand?
It's hot.
Ryota is really bad at this.
You did it a while ago.
Are you going to do it again?
Did it feel so good?
It's the best.
It's hot.
I love you.
While my daughter was away, I kept doing it with my daughter's boyfriend.
I knew I shouldn't do this.
I'll end it with Ryota.
I just have to put up with it.
It's hot.
Why are you drinking so much today?
I want to drink.
It happens sometimes.
I see.
How was the camp?
I'm tired.
I'm going to sleep well today.
I see.
Did you talk to Ryota?
I called him several times during the camp.
He didn't answer the phone.
I'll call him now.
Hello, Ryota?
I'm back from the camp today.
Why didn't you answer the phone recently?
Were you busy?
I see.
Today?
It's late and I'm tired.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
What did Ryota say?
He said he was busy.
Did he cheat on me?
No, he didn't.
You know, he loves you.
I hope so.
I'm sleepy.
Go back to your room if you're going to sleep.
Wait a minute.
I want to sleep on the sofa.
I can't betray my daughter.
I won't see Ryota anymore.
I'll drink and forget about him.
Ryota.
Ai.
You should be sleeping.
No.
I want to see Ai, not Yui.
I'm sorry.
Ryota, go back to your room.
I'll drink and forget about him.
I can't forget about Ai.
Don't say that.
I've been thinking about Ai even when I'm with Yui.
So, it's better not to be with Yui.
Don't say that.
Let's forget about it.
I want to be with Yui.
Then, I'll keep thinking about Ai.
I'm sorry.
Go back to your room.
Ai.
Wait.
Yui is sleeping there.
So, please go back to your room.
Go back to your room.
I can't forget about Ai.
Don't say that.
Go back to your room.
I've fallen in love with Ai.
Don't say that.
Go back to your room.
So, please go back to your room.
Please accept my love.
Go back to your room.
Ryota, don't say that.
Ai, you can feel my love, can't you?
Don't say that.
I'll help you.
So, please go back to your room.
Don't say that.
I love you.
Stop it.
Don't say that.
It's not about you.
I can only think about Ai.
I can't forget our sex.
I want to end it.
I don't want to betray you anymore.
This is the last time.
Don't say that.
It's disgusting.
I can't do it anymore.
Don't say that.
I can't stand it anymore.
I love you.
Please accept my feelings.
I can't do that.
Don't say that.
I love you.
I'm going to wake up.
Mom?
What's wrong?
You were there.
I'm sleepy.
I'm going to bed.
Good night.
Don't say that.
Ryota, listen to me.
I can't betray Yui and my daughter.
I love Ryota.
I want to support them as a mother.
I'll support them.
Let's end this.
Then, let me do it with Ai.
Then, I'll think about it.
I'll do my best.
Can you promise me?
I promise.
Can you go out with Yui?
Yes.
It's a promise.
Ryota.
It's disgusting.
I want to rub your butt.
If I had done this with Ryota, it would have been here.
It's disgusting.
I want to do it too.
It's the last one.
I want to feel good.
It's disgusting.
I want to do it with Ai.
My legs.
Come here.
It's disgusting.
Ryota.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I want to rub Ryota's butt.
It's disgusting.
Please don't forget this feeling.
If you touch me I'll stop it.
Are you okay?
Teacher
I'm feeling the pressure
It feels so good
You are not good at expressing your feelings
My face feels so tight
I feel like we're wrapped withire
It's the best to connect with people you love.
Please don't stop.
I'm sweating.
It's working.
I'm connecting with Ryota.
I'll never forget my sex with you.
Me too.
I'll never forget.
I'm sweating.
It's hot.
It's disgusting.
I'm sweating.
I love you.
I want to do more.
I'm sweating.
You're the first woman to make me so crazy.
Don't say anymore.
I love you.
I'm sweating.
I'll take care of you.
Can I take you out?
I'm fine.
I'll take you out.
It hurts.
It doesn't hurt.
I'll take care of you.
Leave it to me.
It's over.
Just one more time.
You promised me.
It's over.
From now on, you're my daughter's boyfriend.
Take good care of her.
I love you.
I'll take care of you.
It took me a long time.
It's okay.
Did you forget anything?
I'm fine.
I'm looking forward to it.
Me, too.
Mom, I'm leaving.
Take care of yourself.
I'm leaving.
Ryota.
Get along with your daughter.
Yes.
I'm leaving.
How long can I stand it?
I'm sorry.