Ao-chan has always been kind to me with a book, so I've always been grateful to him.
So, I've been writing about something about a funeral for over 20 years.
I'm glad that the idea of a previousのacademy has finally come up.
In any case, I'm planning to start talking with Ao-chan.
As for the books he'll give me,
I didn't know there was a place like this.
I left my parents' house and moved to a place near the university.
I'm finally going to live alone,
and I'm looking forward to the rest of my student life.
Maybe I thought about the life I wanted to do as a girl when I became an adult.
Now, I tend to think such a nice thing.
It's true that time is passing and I'm starting to worry stopping those days.
The rest time is fun for stop-overing to recommend a lesson with a friend,
Well...
I'm sorry.
Yes?
I'm Yoshikawa. I moved in the other day.
I'm here to say hello.
I see.
My husband is here, so I'll go get him.
Who is he?
Nice to meet you.
You just moved in, right?
I'm Yayoi.
I'm Yoshikawa. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
This is boring, but please take it.
Oh, this is...
Thank you for your concern.
Are you a student?
I'm in Reimei University.
What's your major?
Economics.
You're my junior.
Oh, really?
I'm glad you're my junior.
I'm glad, too.
If you don't mind,
why don't we have dinner together?
Is that okay?
Why not?
Okay.
It's decided.
I'll see you at 6 o'clock.
I'll be waiting for you.
Okay, I'll do as you say.
Thank you.
I'm glad the couple next to me are kind.
It seems that my first time living alone will have a good start.
I see.
You're living alone for the first time.
Yes.
My parents were against it.
But I wanted to live alone when I was a student.
So they forced me to live alone.
I understand.
When I was a student,
I invited my friends to the dormitory and played mahjong.
By the way,
do you have a girlfriend?
No, I don't.
What kind of woman do you like?
Well...
How about Mizuki?
When my husband told me that,
I was honestly surprised.
When I first saw my wife,
I was really curious about her.
I imagined her body hidden in plain clothes.
Mizuki is struggling to find a partner.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have asked you that.
Mizuki gets nervous when a man looks at her.
She's too serious.
I'm so happy that Yoshikawa moved in today.
I'm so glad.
I'm sorry. My husband is always like this when he's drunk.
If you're going to sleep, why don't you lie down on the sofa?
Honey, you're...
Can I help you?
Can I move you to the sofa?
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'll take off your belt.
You didn't even take a bath.
Are you sleepy?
It can't be helped.
I'm sorry.
I'm going home.
Okay.
My husband likes you, too.
Please come again.
Thank you very much.
The next day
And then, it was midnight.
Who is it at this hour?
Who is it?
Hey, come closer.
It's okay.
What's wrong with you?
Come on, show me your face.
More.
Come closer.
Give me your tongue.
Oh, it's hot.
Hey.
Give me your tongue.
Come on.
Hey.
Your underwear is in the way.
Come on.
Cute.
It feels good, right?
It's hot.
Come on.
You're getting fatter.
I'll come again.
I'm looking forward to it.
See you.
Good morning.
How was it yesterday?
Thank you very much.
My husband was very happy.
Before I went to work this morning, he praised me for being a good person.
No, it's not like that.
After that, in the middle of the night, you came to my room.
I didn't think you were the same person.
No way.
I...
Actually, it happened before.
The other me...
While I didn't know...
The other Mizuki?
Yes.
For some reason, there's a time when I don't remember.
At that time, the other me...
With men I don't know...
I'm doing something I don't remember.
What do you mean by something you don't remember?
Well...
What should I say?
Like sex...
Did I do something to you yesterday?
No, how should I say it?
I didn't have sex.
Yes.
Usually, I'm not good at men.
I don't have much experience.
But...
Suddenly, a man I didn't know in the city...
He asked me to have sex again.
He said I was good at flirting.
He suddenly asked me out.
He posted a picture of me on social media.
Sometimes...
When I wake up in the morning...
From there...
A man's...
A man's miserable face comes out.
You don't remember that at all?
No.
For the past few years...
The other me hasn't come out.
I met Yoshikawa-san.
I think I came out again.
Please.
Please help me.
Is there anything I can do?
Yes.
If you see me again...
Please don't let me in your room.
If I do something terrible...
I'll be embarrassed.
I can't even look at you.
I understand.
I won't let you in my room.
I'll talk to you.
Thank you.
Please keep this a secret.
Of course.
While I was listening to Mizuki-san's story...
Not only did I sympathize with her, but I was also drawn to her charm.
After a while, the other Mizuki-san didn't show up.
One day...
I drank too much the day before and overslept.
Hello?
Mr. Yoshikawa?
I'm in trouble.
Can you come to the first floor by elevator?
Yes, I'll be right there.
I'm sorry.
That's strange.
Mizuki-san?
You're the other Mizuki-san?
You tricked me.
Please leave.
Again?
You want to do something erotic with me.
Why?
I promised Mizuki-san that I won't let her in my room.
Do you like serious Mizuki?
But she won't let you.
That's not the problem.
You're mistaken.
The real Mizuki is here.
The Mizuki you like has a different personality.
In other words, she's a fake.
I don't know what to say.
It's okay.
You don't remember her anyway.
You won't know if you don't say anything.
Let's have fun together while Mizuki doesn't know.
You want to do something erotic with me, right?
I'm sorry.
I'm saying sorry, but my body is shaking.
That's not true.
It's okay.
I won't say anything to the other Mizuki.
Okay?
What's wrong? Your back is cold.
Did you have an abortion?
No.
I'm sorry.
Did you want to kiss me?
No.
Did you think you could kiss Mizuki?
Please go home.
Can I really go home?
You can smell Mizuki, right?
The smell of your favorite serious Mizuki.
You're really sensitive.
No, I'm not.
Don't do this.
Is this how you kiss?
You don't have to laugh.
You don't have to do this.
Be careful.
Don't do this.
It's painful, isn't it?
You're getting bigger.
No, I'm not.
Don't hide it.
You're cute.
I'm getting excited when you make me look like this.
I'll rub your favorite body.
Don't do this.
You're getting bigger, so I'll rub it.
You don't have to rub it.
It's painful, isn't it?
You always look at my big butt.
I'll rub your favorite big butt.
You can't see my face with this, can you?
Imagine being rubbed by your favorite Mizuki.
You're getting excited, aren't you?
You want to have an affair with Mizuki, don't you?
Be honest.
You can touch my body.
We have the same body.
Both Mizuki and I have the same body.
You have such a big breast.
I'm gentle, so I'll rub it a lot.
Isn't this enough?
I can't help it.
I'll show you something special.
Don't you want to see it?
I'll take off my panties.
I took it off.
You're not wearing underwear, are you?
You want to see it, don't you?
You're so sexy right now.
If you don't want to see it, I'll make you feel good.
You like it here, don't you?
Don't do it.
I'm telling you not to do it.
I'm doing my best.
Don't do it.
Don't touch Mizuki's body.
I think you're better than Mizuki.
You're so fat.
Don't do it.
You feel sexy, don't you?
Look at Mizuki's body.
You can't stop moving, can you?
Don't do it.
You're so fat.
Make it bigger.
Show me your belly.
Don't do it.
You can rub here.
I don't want to.
You don't want to, but your waist moves, doesn't it?
I'm just rubbing your belly, aren't I?
But you make me stand up.
Don't do it.
I'll make you feel better.
I'll rub your belly.
It's hard, isn't it?
You feel good, don't you?
You're getting fatter.
You're getting fatter because you don't like it.
You feel good, don't you?
Be honest.
It's hard.
Here.
It's hard, isn't it?
You're drooling.
Do you want me to help you?
It's hard.
You feel good, don't you?
You're getting fatter.
Be honest.
You're drooling, aren't you?
You want me to make you feel good, don't you?
Did you want to go now?
Did you want to get out of here?
No, you can't.
I'm going to do something worse than before.
I'll leave it to you.
You want me to do something worse than before, don't you?
You're getting used to it, aren't you?
You're getting used to looking at me, aren't you?
You want me to touch your boobs, don't you?
I'll be quiet.
How is it?
I'm sorry, Mizuki.
It's okay.
I don't remember anything.
You can see my nipples, can't you?
Nipples.
Here.
You like my nipples, don't you?
Touch them.
Here.
Does it feel good?
Touch me more.
Here.
I want you to touch me directly.
Come on.
When you touch me,
your body, my body, and my nipples stand up.
That's right.
Touch me more.
It feels good.
Here.
More.
It feels good.
You're sweating, aren't you?
It smells good, doesn't it?
It smells like me, doesn't it?
You can smell as much as you want.
Or...
Do you want to smell this side?
Here.
You don't have any more nipples, do you?
Do you want me to touch you more?
Here.
You want me to massage your face, don't you?
Do you want me to massage your face?
Here.
I'll be quiet.
I couldn't wait to massage you.
You're breathing warmly.
Here.
More.
You want to see more, don't you?
I'll show you.
Your nipples.
Here.
You can take a good look.
Your favorite nipples.
You wanted to see them, didn't you?
Don't say that.
You can talk to me.
Here.
It feels good, doesn't it?
He's gone.
You're very good at it.
I want you to massage me more.
Here.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Is it good?
Your body.
Don't say that.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Here.
I want you to lick me, too.
I'll open your mouth.
Come and lick me.
Here.
That's right.
You want to be licked, don't you?
You're a boy.
You can lick me as much as you want.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Do it again.
That's right.
I can't let you use your body like that.
Lick me more.
That's right.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Was it good?
I'm massaging you.
Let's do something better.
Come here.
You like this bath better than the one you like, don't you?
You're excited, aren't you?
That's right.
It's hot.
It's painful here, isn't it?
Don't you think it's easier to let it out?
Come on.
You want to let it out, don't you?
It's hot.
I want to be here.
Here.
You want to be here, don't you?
No, I can't.
You can't?
It's okay, I'll be quiet.
I'll lend you my coat.
Come here.
It tickles, doesn't it?
It's okay, I'll be quiet.
It's okay.
It's in.
It tickles, doesn't it?
How do you feel?
You love to have sex with the one you like, don't you?
It tickles, doesn't it?
You look like you're enjoying it.
Why?
You're going to drink some more?
Ah…
Feels good.
We have good legs, don't we?
We are in good place.
We are forgetting.
Do you want to see where you reach?
You are in my arms.
This is good.
Ah…
You can still do it, can't you?
It's okay.
I'll do a lot of nice things for you.
You want to go inside, don't you?
You want to go inside again, don't you?
You wanted to go inside again, didn't you?
You wanted to come back inside me, didn't you?
I'll do a lot of nice things for you.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Can you see where I'm in?
You want to see where you're in, don't you?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm talking to you.
I'll try to move my waist this time.
Come here.
It's okay.
I won't tell you.
I won't tell you that I was shaking my waist.
Come here.
It hurts.
You have to move your waist by yourself.
You have to move it to the place you like.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Do you like that place?
I like that place, too.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Forget everything and move your waist.
Let me go.
I'm just a man and a woman.
You just have to feel good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Over there.
No, no, no.
It feels good.
I want you to follow me more and more.
You just have to feel good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Let me kiss you more.
It feels good.
You like intense things, don't you?
Do it more.
Don't shake your waist like an animal.
It feels good.
Forget everything and move your waist.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll make you feel better.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's more intense than before, isn't it?
You like it here, don't you?
No, no, no.
Let's feel it together.
I'll do everything you like.
I'll make you feel good.
It hurts.
No, no, no.
It feels good.
What do you like?
I want to hold your hand.
I'll hold your hand.
I'll hold your soft hand.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You moved your waist a little, didn't you?
That's why I lifted you up.
It hurts.
Sex feels good, doesn't it?
You're getting fatter and fatter.
You're getting fatter and fatter, aren't you?
I know.
You've been putting on weight for a long time.
What are you going to do?
You can't go on like this forever, can you?
You can take it out.
No, I can't.
Why not?
I don't know if you keep quiet.
You want to make friends with me.
I'll take it out.
Wait, wait.
You wanted to go out, didn't you?
I'll take it out.
It's out.
You took it out.
I'm sorry I'm late.
You're amazing.
You're very sexy today, too.
You felt good, didn't you?
You're amazing.
I'll come again.
Let's have more fun while Mizuki doesn't know.
I broke my promise with Mizuki.
And then Mizuki came.
I couldn't remember the memory of the day.
I thought it might be.
What did I do to Yoshikawa?
No.
As promised, I couldn't tell my family.
I'm glad.
I was worried that I might have done something terrible.
Yes.
I'm so pissed off thinking you're making such a fuss.
Mr. Yoshikawa.
Yes?
I...
I thought all men would come close to you to work on their body.
I'm so happy to have a man like Yoshikawa-san.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
I realized that what I really want is not a flashy Mizuki-san, but a plain Mizuki-san.
Even so, I was drowning in the play with a flashy Mizuki-san.
There is no woman today, so let's have fun in this room.
But I'm sorry to do it in our room.
You don't have to be so careful.
Or do you still like another Mizuki?
What?
Where is the other Mizuki-san when you are out?
I don't know.
Maybe she is not conscious.
I don't remember when I was a plain Mizuki.
Let's leave such a difficult thing and do something more fun.
Fun?
More and more.
Maybe around here.
What is this?
Ta-da!
My husband and Mizuki don't know that there is such a thing in my room.
My body is the same as Mizuki's.
I think it's Mizuki's favorite body.
Let's use this toy and have fun.
Let's do it.
You can look at Mizuki's tongue closer.
Hold it.
Are you excited?
With your favorite Mizuki's body,
can we do something more fun?
Look.
We can use something like this.
A serious Mizuki wouldn't do such a thing alone.
The power of the telephone is too strong.
Ah, it feels good.
My favorite Mizuki is looking at me.
It's erotic.
I'm getting used to it.
Look at me more.
It hurts.
Look at me.
Ah, it hurts.
Ah, it feels good.
Hold it more.
I'm going to hit you directly.
Just like that.
It feels good.
This body is the same as your favorite Mizuki's body.
I'm not going to hit you.
It feels good.
Ah, it feels good.
Hey.
This is not enough.
I'm going to put this vibe in here.
Hey.
Do you want to see?
There is a thick vibe in here.
Do you want to see a man who is eating in Mizuki's stomach?
Yes.
Let me see.
The big and thick one.
Yes.
I'm going to show you up close.
It's a special seat.
I can see that you are getting used to it.
You are getting used to it.
It's dripping.
Ah, it's in.
It's in.
Ah.
You can see it well from there.
There is a thick one in and out.
There is a small one.
Ah, it feels good.
This is a good place.
Ah.
Ah, it's in.
Ah, it feels good.
I'm hitting the upper part of the stomach.
Ah, it feels good here.
Ah.
My stomach is getting loose.
Look at this.
There is a small one in here.
Ah.
I'm going to close my stomach.
Look at this.
Ah, it's in.
Ah.
It feels good.
Hold this.
Hold it tight so that it doesn't come out.
Ah.
Hold it tight.
Here.
Ah.
There is a small one in here.
I can't stop moving my waist.
Your favorite swimsuit might be a good one.
You might want it.
Ah.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it hurts.
It hurts.
Ah.
Ah, it feels good.
I can't stop moving my waist.
Hold it tight.
Ah.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it hurts.
Ah.
Hey.
I can't stop moving my waist.
Ah.
My body is so luxurious that I can't stop moving my waist.
Hey.
Put that bed here.
Give it to me.
Ah.
Ah, it hurts.
You can see that I'm panting, right?
Ah.
Your favorite swimsuit might be a good one.
What's this?
Ah.
It looks like I'm wearing something heavy.
It feels good.
I want to be more comfortable here.
Ah.
It's amazing.
Let's do it together.
Ah.
Ah, it feels good.
It's amazing.
You look like a real baby.
I can imagine you having a baby.
I'll make you a snack.
Ah.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, no.
I'm going to fall asleep.
Ah.
Ah, it tickles.
You look like a real baby.
Hey.
Your favorite Mizuki is here.
You made me feel good.
I'll give it back.
Ah.
There are only two of us today.
I'm going to do a lot of naughty things until you wake up.
It's okay. I'll put everything back in place so you don't get drunk.
I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
I want you to wear glasses.
And I want you to wear another Mizuki's clothes.
What's wrong?
Go home.
Why?
Just go home.
What?
I won't show up in front of you anymore.
You can get along with another Mizuki.
Just go home.
I didn't understand.
Since then, I couldn't show up in front of her anymore.
And one day...
Have a good day.
Thank you.
Good morning.
How's school?
It's going well.
Oh, right.
How about having dinner with me?
I'm always on a day off.
Wait.
Don't say that.
Please be nice to me.
Okay, Mizuki?
Yes, of course.
Let's do that.
I'll be nice to you.
Good.
See you.
You fell asleep again, didn't you?
I was like this the other day, too.
You don't show up in front of Mizuki anymore, do you?
Yes.
I lost my memory.
Thanks to you.
Thanks to me?
Because you persuaded me.
Persuasion?
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Actually...
I...
I want to be with another Mizuki.
It's okay.
Don't say anything.
No matter what happens to me...
You want to be with me, don't you?
Please do it.
Right now.
Not another me.
The me in front of you.
Your husband is here.
It's okay.
Here.
I won't say anything.
I love you.
Wait a minute.
I want you to touch me more.
Okay.
I love you.
Mikawa...
I'm here.
Can you get excited?
Yes.
I'm here.
Mikawa...
My hips hurt.
I'm embarrassed.
I wanted to kill you.
Mikawa...
My hips are big, so it's strange, isn't it?
Not at all.
It's very nice.
I'm glad.
Can I scratch you?
Yes.
Please.
I'm embarrassed.
It's very nice.
My hips are big.
Mikawa...
You like my hips, don't you?
So I need to get up early.
This is to make you feel alive
This is difficult
You are very weak.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't do that.
I'm getting more and more excited.
I want you to touch my hips and whole body.
You can touch me as much as you want.
I'm getting more and more excited.
Don't do that.
It's dirty.
It's not dirty.
Your body is not dirty.
I'm sorry.
It's hard.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
It's hard.
Yoshikawa is used to my chest.
I'm embarrassed.
You are very cute.
It's hard.
It feels good.
I want to return it.
It's hard.
Please bear with me.
Can you come here?
It's hard.
I'm glad you're patting me.
Are you thinking the same thing as me?
It's my corpse.
Let's do it here.
It's hard.
Does this feel good?
Let's do it together.
I'll do my best.
It's okay.
You can do whatever you want.
Wait.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
It feels good.
It's hot.
You put it in another swimsuit, didn't you?
Put it in my swimsuit, too.
It's hot.
You can do whatever you want.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I thought about it later.
I don't know which Mizuki is at this time.
I don't know if her words were true or not.
I don't know how it is now, but it doesn't matter anymore.
Good morning.