I'm going to take a break.
Hey!
Tetsuto!
Hey, Tetsuto!
What are you doing? Were you sleeping?
Here.
This is the watermelon I picked in my field.
Do you want to eat it?
No, I'm fine now.
I'm fine, so go to sleep.
I've been sleeping all day.
I was a little nervous, but I'm not nervous forever.
I'm going to sleep.
What are you doing here?
I haven't finished hunting yet.
It's hot today, so I'm going to take a break.
But it's hot today.
Tetsuto, did you take a break again?
No, I didn't.
Mom, you're my fan.
When I was in Homamura the other day, I was very excited.
You're exaggerating.
I know you're not good at hunting.
You've been spending too much time at home.
Thank you.
By the way, why is the air conditioner broken in this house?
I can't sleep because it's hot.
I don't need an air conditioner.
It's cool at night.
After a long time, I came back to my hometown in the countryside where I was born and raised.
My parents, who raised me in baseball, are proud of me as a professional baseball player.
A few days ago, I was forcibly disposed of for a certain reason.
Sometimes I came back to my hometown to relax in the countryside.
Hello.
This is from Sayama-san.
Taro-san, this was caught in my field.
If you like, you can eat it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Tetsu-chan, you're back.
It's been a long time.
Hello.
This is cucumber.
It's fresh and delicious.
This is bread.
Taro-san, you like soil.
It's delicious.
I'm taking care of it.
Thank you very much.
I'm proud to be on TV.
That's good.
You are really good.
Thank you for always sending me off.
If you buy my desk, it's okay, isn't it?
Of course.
It's okay.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you, son.
Where is the sea grape?
It wasn't there.
I ate it.
You ate it yesterday.
I ate it because I couldn't open it.
I'll buy it for you.
I see.
I have something to do with my mom tomorrow.
I'm going out.
Is it tomorrow?
I see.
It will take a while until the evening.
Please stay a little longer.
I'll be back in a year or so.
It's okay.
I'll take this off.
Warm it up and eat it.
It was soft.
Thank you.
Hello.
Taro?
Taro, aren't you here?
I'm sorry.
Did I wake you up?
No.
Where is Taro?
He went out to go to the pharmacy.
I see.
How long will he be back?
About an hour.
He will be back in the evening.
I see.
What should I do?
I'll leave him here.
Tetsuto, did you have lunch?
I'm waiting for you.
I'll cook something.
Would you like to eat with me?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I haven't eaten yet.
Okay?
Okay.
How is it? Is it good?
Yes, it's very good.
Is that so? That's good.
I made it on my own. Is it okay?
I think it's okay.
I made it on my own.
I see.
By the way, are you single?
Yes, I'm single.
I see.
But you're popular, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
I only play baseball, so I don't meet many people.
Is that so?
I see.
Can I ask you something strange?
It's about the scoop, isn't it?
No, it's not.
I'm curious about it.
I've heard a lot about it on the Internet.
Well...
It's a fact, but...
I've been tricked by someone.
What do you mean?
It was my fan.
He came into contact with me.
He said,
I'll keep it a secret.
Please make me a local wife.
I was a strong man.
I got drunk first.
That's how we got to know each other.
Right?
Everyone is a sports player, isn't it?
I often go to the countryside.
It's easy to get drunk.
But I can't get drunk once.
I want to do it over and over again.
You have a strong desire to get drunk.
I can't talk about this with anyone else.
I see.
If I refuse to ask her out,
I'll end up like this.
I see.
I'm sorry I asked you a strange question.
It's okay.
I see.
I envy you.
What do you mean?
You can't do it many times.
I haven't been here for a long time.
The countryside is nice.
Is that so?
There's nothing here.
The air is fresh.
The stars are beautiful.
I can't get drunk during the season.
I see.
I envy you.
What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
Well...
It's your fault, isn't it?
Yes.
I heard what you said.
I'm wet.
What?
I'm sorry.
You're married.
I want to do it once.
With a professional baseball player.
Can't I do it?
I'm pregnant.
I can't do it.
There's nothing else to do in the country.
You have a lot of money.
We have a lot of money.
Please.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
Do you hear me?
Let me do it.
I'm not pregnant.
I don't want to be found out.
I'm sorry.
I'm sweating.
It smells bad.
It's dirty.
What are you doing?
Don't you like it?
I'm sorry.
I'm pregnant.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared.
I'm pregnant.
I know.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I'm sweating.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
I know.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sorry.
It's painful, isn't it?
I can't take it anymore.
Let me see.
Are you okay?
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
It's okay.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm sorry.
You're sweating a lot.
It's dirty.
It's not dirty.
Do you hate this?
You know the reason why I can't take it anymore.
It's okay.
I won't tell anyone.
If they find out, I'll be in trouble.
I'm sorry.
You're amazing.
What are you looking at?
I'm getting hot.
You're sweating a lot.
That's why I told you.
I'm envious of you.
Is this how you feel?
It feels good.
Do you want me to do it more?
I love you.
I'm sweating.
You can take it back now.
Why?
I can't take it back.
I won't tell anyone.
It's hot.
I touched you directly.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Please get up.
I need your help.
Do you need a rubber band?
I don't need a rubber band.
Are you okay?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It hurts.
What should I do?
I can't stop.
It hurts.
It's hot.
Did you feel better?
I was moved.
It's hot.
You're sweating.
I'm sorry.
You're sweating a lot.
Would you like to take a bath together?
Yes.
It's refreshing.
I can't move.
It's a muscle.
Let's do it again.
It's hot.
It's hot today.
I'm going to the field.
If you're hungry, you can eat in the refrigerator.
Okay.
It's hot.
I fell in love with Sayama's body.
Sayama has come to see me like someone who had a fan.
Sayama was looking for me on a day when my father wasn't home.
I couldn't deny the invitation.
This cucumber is really good with Ai-chan.
Really?
What is it?
It's different.
I'm sure you're good at putting it on.
Ai-chan, are you putting it on?
You put it on for me, didn't you?
No, no.
What is it?
I don't know how to do it.
Sorry, sorry.
You're good at drinking, aren't you?
You're right.
It's cold, isn't it?
Ai-chan, are you going to be okay at this time?
I'm fine.
My husband is already sleeping.
Is that so?
I'm close to him, so I'm fine.
Ai-chan, what if I stay at home?
What?
Are you sure?
I'm fine.
It's already this time.
Ai-chan, put the futon in the back room.
Okay?
Let's drink.
Let's drink a lot.
Cheers!
Ai-chan!
Ai-chan, you're good at drinking.
What is it today?
It's delicious.
Really?
It's been a long time since it was so lively.
It's different from Ai-chan.
That's right.
It's been a long time.
I have to go out at 5 o'clock.
It's early.
That's right.
I want you to do your best alone tomorrow.
Ai-chan, you can sleep here.
It's better to leave it alone.
Let me help you.
I'm sorry to ask you to prepare the futon alone.
That's not true.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You're a good girl.
Hush.
Masa, are you drunk?
What?
Your parents are over there.
It's okay.
I have to speak up.
Miki-chan.
You woke up.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
It's okay.
I'll be quiet.
No.
I didn't do it today.
You didn't do it?
No.
Look at this.
It's full of iron.
I don't like it.
You don't like it, do you?
I didn't do it.
It's a little rusty.
I have to be careful not to be found out.
What are you doing?
It's a baby.
I thought it was a baby.
I thought so, too.
It's not a baby.
What's wrong?
It's a baby.
But you're sleeping.
I'm so excited.
Don't speak up.
I'll be quiet.
It's a baby.
It's gone.
I'll be quiet.
It's a baby.
Do it.
Yeah.
Just once...
It's hot, hot, hot.
It's hot, hot.
Where did Tetsu go?
He was in the futon.
He should be back by now.
What about Ai-chan?
She was in the futon, too.
I think Tetsu is out for a walk.
Did he go for a walk?
Tetsu is out for a walk.
He's putting on a mask.
Tetsu...
It's okay.
Is that so?
That's amazing.
Shizuka, do you want some water?
It's too hot.
Shizuka, is it hard to do?
I see.
I didn't know.
It's hot.
It's too hot.
I'm not sure if it's a good thing or a bad thing
but I think it's a good thing
I think it's a good thing
I'm not sure if it's a good thing
because the last time I found
in a far way
I think it's a good thing
It's a good thing
and it's the best thing
I've found so far
It's hot.
It's perfect.
It's too hot.
It's hot.
I love this.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't stand it.
It's hot.
I'll go to the field again.
Okay.
I didn't see you there.
Well.
You're right.
You were sleeping, weren't you?
Yes.
You were weak.
Did I make your bed?
Yes, of course.
Are you still sleeping?
I think so.
Really?
You'll go home when you wake up.
Your house is close.
I'll go to the field.
Okay.
Be careful.
It's hot.
What are you doing?
What?
Did you wake up?
I'm glad you woke up.
No.
What are you doing in the morning?
Wait a minute.
I'm afraid you'll wake up.
Don't worry.
We didn't go to the field.
Okay.
If you sleep like this, you can't stand it.
It's hot.
It's hard.
It tickles.
Can I lick you?
I'll make you feel better.
It's hot.
It tickles.
I'll play with you with my boobs.
Come here.
Oh, my God.
Does it feel good?
Oh, my God. It's slippery.
My boobs are sticky.
Oh, my God.
I can't take it anymore.
I want to do it.
Put it in.
I want you to show me your boobs.
A little more.
A little more?
I have no choice.
Do your boobs feel so good?
Oh, my God.
Do you want me to do it?
Did you feel good?
Oh, my God.
But I have to go home soon.
Before that...
Let's do it one more time.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
I can't stop them.
I can't do it anymore.
Oh, my God.
It was a hot summer night.
The fireworks were beautiful, weren't they?
Yes, they were.
Summer festivals are great.
Yes.
But was it okay to leave your husband behind?
Yes, it was.
He drinks until late every year.
I see.
Well, my parents seemed to enjoy it, so it's okay.
But you're leaving tomorrow, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
I'm going to miss you.
Yes.
I want to do it again.
But my parents will be back soon.
But it's the last night.
The fireworks are over.
Yes.
What are you going to do?
Nothing.
Okay?
No.
What are you going to do?
The last thing.
Yes, the last memory.
Okay?
Yes.
I'm going to miss you.
I love you.
I love you, too.
No!
Oh, no!
Oh my god!
That tickles...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no no no no no no no no
ni
No, I learned
ano
No, no
no
No...
Urgh...
Oh!
Ugh...
Some water...
Oh!
Don't...
Oh...
Oh~~~~
Ugh...
Ahh...
Ah!
Oh, no...
Oh...
Agh!
Father...
Father!
Ah!
Ohhhhhhhhh!
That hurts!
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Ah, it's gross.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ah, ah, ah, ah
Ahahaha
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah !
hahahahahaha
Thanks.
Thank you so much.
Thanks so much.
Thank you.
It feels so good.
Give me a hug.
I...
I'll do my best.
My back hurts.
It's disgusting.
It hurts.
It feels so good.
My bed is wet.
It hurts.
It's all wet.
It's still wet.
I can't sleep.
I'm tired.
Give me a little more.
I made the best memory.
Me too.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
Me too.
Take care.
Come back anytime.
I'm cheering for you on TV.
I'm looking forward to it.
If I'm not chosen as a representative, I'll do my best.
Let's go.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
See you.
It's been a long time since I came back to my hometown.
I was mentally depressed after being discharged from prison.
I feel like I've been encouraged in many ways.
I don't have a game center or a convenience store.
I'm really grateful to Ai.
Thank you for watching.