It's the third time today.
Let's go to the fourth time.
I can't study.
I'll talk to you, so come alone.
Don't make me concentrate.
I'm your mother from today.
I'm Aika.
I'll talk to you, so come alone.
My father brought a young partner.
He is a man who has a lot of money.
My father is deceived.
But I don't have money.
I wonder if my father will have a lot of sex.
I'm angry.
I'm a bitch.
I've done a lot of sex, but I've never seen anything like that.
I'm angry.
Aika's cooking is great.
Thank you.
Aika is family-oriented.
This is delicious.
Is it always like this?
I'm sorry.
What?
I'm tired.
It's okay.
Let's do it next time.
I agree.
Let's do it tomorrow.
Do you want to sleep?
Let's do it.
Okay.
I'm tired.
My father is not good at all.
He has a small dick.
Good night.
My father is not good at all.
He has a small dick.
Why is he so popular?
Damn it.
I have to stop him.
I have to educate him as a parent.
Hey.
If you do that, your dick will melt.
What?
Don't hide your dick.
I've never seen it before.
I'll help you.
Take it off.
What am I saying?
I'm not cheating.
I'm a parent.
It's not strange at all.
Hey.
Your father will wake up.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Why?
I just held your dick.
What?
It's amazing.
It's the biggest dick I've ever seen.
You still have a penis.
I can't stand it.
You can still do it.
I can do it myself.
No.
You were holding it so hard.
You can't do that.
You can't hold it so hard.
You can't hold a girl's dick so hard.
Do you understand?
If you get used to it, you can't do it.
So you have to hold it so softly.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
It tickles because I just told you.
It's very hard.
It's my fifth time today.
What?
Is it your fifth time?
Yes.
What?
How many times?
At least seven times a day.
That's right.
That's too much.
Did you hold it so hard every time?
Yes.
It's hard when you have sex.
I'll teach you how to do it.
It's still too big.
It's very hard.
Do you feel better when you have sex?
Yes.
That's great.
It's hard when you have sex.
You're not holding it so hard.
It feels good.
It's important to hold it like this.
I'll do it a little faster.
You can't hold it too hard.
You have to remember how to do it.
I can't hold it.
You can't hold it.
That's right.
I need a little bit more time to practice.
Do you like your boobies?
Yes, I do.
If you can bear to look at this...
You've grown a lot.
But my boobies...
You want to touch them, don't you?
Don't touch them. Just look at them.
Just bear with it for five seconds.
1...
2...
3...
4...
5...
You can't bear to look at them, can you?
Put your hands out.
You really couldn't bear to look at them.
That's amazing.
You've grown this much again.
How many did you say you had? Five?
So this is your sixth?
Yes.
Next...
I'll massage your mouth.
My mouth?
I'm not going to tighten your mouth that much.
Do you understand?
That's amazing.
Men's bodies can be upsetting.
What?
It's fine.
So you don't have to lick it?
Can I leave it as it is?
He's definitely a former yariman.
How many times has he licked his boobies?
You have to be able to do it with your mouth.
You're going to be like this.
I'm not going to do it anymore.
Is that okay?
What's wrong with you?
Why don't you say anything?
Hey.
Your boobies are big, but your heart is small.
I'm going to do it.
Get comfortable.
I'll do it.
Ouch.
Mom.
I can't do it with my mouth.
Why not?
Why can't you do it with your mouth?
I don't understand.
You're noisy.
Dad's going to wake up.
That's right.
The moment I put it in my mouth, it got really hard.
You don't like it?
It doesn't look like you don't like it.
You don't want to be able to do it with your hands, do you?
You can do it with your mouth.
That's why I'm training you.
It's hot.
I'm going to do it.
Do you want to do it again?
Isn't it amazing how much you can do it?
You said you could do it at least seven times.
At least seven times?
Did I say that?
You did.
Isn't that too much?
What do you mean?
You said you could do it at least seven times?
Then you can still do it.
Then do it more.
If you say you can do it at least seven times.
Seven times is over.
You've achieved your goal, haven't you?
You can still do it.
You can do it.
You said you could do it at least seven times.
Did I say that?
You can't do it at least seven times.
It's hot.
Are you going to do it again?
Do you want me to do it eight times?
I'm going to do it.
Okay.
You really did it.
Isn't it amazing?
You said you could do it at least seven times.
You can't do it any more.
But if I keep doing it...
It's dangerous when you do it by yourself.
If you do it that much,
I'll do it every day.
I'll do it with my hands and mouth.
It's too hard to do it seven times.
Did you get it?
You got it, didn't you?
If you don't, I'll continue.
That's a good answer.
My hands and jaw are tired.
I'm going to sleep tonight.
Good night.
You have to close your eyes and sleep.
It's hot.
I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
What are you doing?
Please help me.
How many times did you do it last night?
Your jaw is about to come off.
I can do it with my hands.
Your wrists are weak.
Is that so?
I don't mind.
I don't hate it.
I like it.
Is that so?
Please help me.
I can't do it.
You don't have a girlfriend.
Why don't you practice with me?
Practice with me?
I'm talking about sex.
Sex?
You've seen our bedroom.
You've seen it, haven't you?
I haven't done it since I came here.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I can't help it.
I have to deal with this.
I'm sick of it.
Is that okay?
Don't pee all the time.
Touch me.
It feels good.
I'll do it directly.
You can lick me.
Is that okay?
You're good at licking me.
Touch me.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
You're weak.
Your boobs are boring, aren't they?
It feels good.
Do you want to see my boobs?
Can you lick me?
It feels good.
I peed a lot.
Does it feel good?
You're lying.
You really peed.
You peed.
You're still going to pee.
You're lying.
It's hot.
I miss Mukbang.
Right, it's Mukbang Str.
Hi, creepy!
Haikyu, haikyu!
M MUKBANG STRATEGY
MUNCH MUNCH
Yum Yum.
Mmm.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
You're doing well today.
How much are you eating today?
It's hot.
Are you going to put it in?
You haven't taken it out yet, have you?
Yes, please.
I don't want you to put it in this big one.
Oh, you're going to put it in.
It's good, isn't it?
What's this?
It's full inside.
This is bad.
It's hot.
Do you want me to put it in your hand?
It's disgusting.
I can't stop.
Don't go so soon.
Hang in there.
It's disgusting.
It's hard.
It's getting harder and harder.
It's disgusting.
It's still not good, is it?
It's hot.
Can you see my hand?
It's the best.
It's hot.
What?
It feels good.
Me, too.
It hurts.
It's hot.
Hang on.
How about this?
I'm sorry.
It feels good, too.
It's hot.
I can't stop.
Hang on.
My waist is moving.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I can't stop.
It feels good.
What?
Do you want to move?
Can you move?
What kind of posture do you want?
Can I start from the back?
It's hot.
Hang on.
It's disgusting.
It's hot.
I can't stop.
Why are you moving so much?
It's hot.
Do you like me?
It feels good.
You can move a lot.
What's going on?
It's hot.
I can't do it.
It's too intense.
It's hot.
I can't do it.
It's too intense.
It's hot.
I can't do it.
Wait.
Take it out.
It's hot.
It's disgusting.
I can't do it.
Why are you still standing?
Why?
I can't do it.
It's so hard.
How can you be so weak?
It's okay.
Do it slowly.
Don't you feel ticklish?
It's okay.
Your shoulders are back to normal.
You're so sticky.
I can't do it.
It's hard.
Your shoulders are back to normal.
I can't do it.
Does it feel good?
It's my debut.
I can't do it.
It's delicious.
I need a break.
Let's take a break.
Again?
I'm busy these days.
You must be tired.
Don't push yourself.
Let's sleep again.
Do you want to sleep?
Good night.
Give me a blanket.
It's cold.
I'm thirsty.
Good night.
It's cold.
Are you thirsty?
Can you do it?
It's cold.
You haven't done it, have you?
I just pulled it out.
You can do it because you've just pulled it out.
You'll fall asleep if you don't pull it out.
I'm going to make you look a little embarrassed.
Are you still going to come out?
Look over there.
What are you going to do?
Open your legs.
Put your left foot here.
That's right.
You look embarrassed.
You didn't think I'd do that, did you?
I've never done that.
I'm going to make you look a little embarrassed.
That's pretty bad.
Lower your hips.
Are you embarrassed?
That's right.
It's really open.
You're holding it in.
It's easy.
I'm nervous.
I'm getting eggs.
I'm going to make you look a little embarrassed.
I'm nervous.
It's getting warm.
It's hard.
It's really hard.
How much are you going to do today?
I'm going to do a lot.
Can you do a lot?
Show me your face.
I'm nervous.
Go.
Feel so good!
Hmm
Come here
It's so delicious that I can't stop eating it.
Oh, that's a lot.
You can still do it, can't you?
Drink more.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
What is it?
Drink more.
It's hot.
It's coming out.
What is it?
It's a soup stock.
It's not over yet.
Come here.
It's hot.
Do you want to see Ichatomon?
I'm getting wet.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
It's hot.
I just said it's poisonous.
What?
It's about to come out again.
It's hot.
It's coming out again.
It's a soup stock.
It's hot.
It's the third time.
Can you still do it?
I can't stand it anymore.
It's hot.
I want to open it.
It's hard.
It's hot.
I can't do it.
It hurts so much.
Let's go.
It's hot.
I feel sick.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'll do it for you next time.
Will you do it for me?
It's hot.
It feels good.
Let's go.
It's hot.
I can't do it anymore.
Let's go.
It's hot.
I can't do it anymore.
How's your head today?
It's still hot.
It's hot.
It's too hot.
It's too dark.
I can't do it anymore.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Let's go.
It's hot.
It's too hot.
How's your head?
It's hot.
Why are you moving?
Look at me.
Why?
You want to move, don't you?
You moved a lot.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels good.
This is bad.
It's hot.
You're tired.
It feels good.
When did you start moving like this?
You've grown a lot.
You're going to melt.
Shunji.
It's hot.
I can't do it anymore.
You can't do it anymore.
It's hot.
I can't do it anymore.
It's a waste.
It's good.
Do you want to do it again?
You can do it.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm back.
I was so nervous that I cried at the end.
It felt good.
I want to do it again.
I want to do it, too.
This is the best.
It's big.
It's bigger than me.
I think you can do it.
I'm still half way there.
Are you still half way there?
I lost.
I lost my wife.
I think you can do it.
You're good.
You're good at it.
Wait a minute.
Are you praising me?
I'm praising you.
I didn't think you were good at it.
It's hard.
Move your waist.
Wait a minute.
It's too hard.
I can't do it.
How many did I do?
Six?
Seven?
I can't do it.
It's seven.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
I can't do it.
Don't you want to do it alone?
Yes, I did.
Really?
You don't want to do it alone, do you?
No, I don't.
You're a good boy.
You don't want to do it alone, do you?
I'll do it until my dad comes.
Of course.