A few days later
Yuzuru, hurry up!
Yuzuru!
You don't have to pick me up.
Don't be lazy.
I won't be lazy because I don't have a set schedule.
It's normal.
I've been studying until late.
Cleanliness is also important.
Shut up.
If you remarry without permission, you'll be a father.
Oh, it's here.
Welcome. Please come in.
Excuse me.
I'm glad you came.
It's the first time for you two, isn't it?
Nice to meet you, Dad.
Dad, please take care of me from now on.
This is a souvenir.
Thank you for your trouble.
Yuzuru, why don't you say hello to your new mother and sister?
Thank you.
Yuzuru, nice to meet you.
Yuzuru, you're cuter than you look in the picture.
We're going to be a family from now on.
Nice to meet you.
Come on in.
Excuse me.
Would you like a cigarette?
Thank you.
I see.
You're working part-time at a cafe.
That's right.
Would you like to come, Dad?
Cheesecake is really good.
Cheesecake is good.
And the manager over there is handsome, isn't he?
Mel comes here often to see the manager.
I see.
Who is more handsome, the manager or Dad?
You're getting old.
I'm just kidding.
Dad is more handsome, isn't he?
Is that so?
Dad is a handsome man, so I'll take it from Mom.
No, no, no.
You're handsome from the back, but you're always welcome.
You're strict from the first day.
This is a souvenir for you.
This is delicious, so please eat it.
Thank you very much.
I see.
Oh, that's right.
I haven't talked to Yuzuru yet.
I'm going to live with you from today because of my mother's apartment contract.
Why don't you say something so important?
I'll move in next month.
It's a short time, but can you sleep in the same room?
My room isn't that big.
It's a nuisance for the two of us.
Yuzuru, I'm cute, so I don't care.
I'm fine because I sleep in the same tent as the boys at the circle camp.
If you don't like it, Yuzuru will sleep with his father and the three of us will sleep separately.
We're not stupid enough to get in the way of a passionate newlyweds.
Don't say that.
Yuzuru, nice to meet you.
Yuzuru, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
How about this?
It doesn't look good on you.
But I don't know which one is better.
This one.
This one?
This one looks good on you.
Yes.
Oh, it does.
What kind of clothes do you like?
Like this?
But I...
Does this look good on me?
Yes, it does.
But I don't have much clothes.
Let's go shopping next time.
No, you go by yourself.
Next Sunday.
You're free, aren't you?
Let's go.
What should I wear?
Shut up!
Don't talk too much.
You're talking too much.
I'm sorry, Jel.
By the way,
Meg,
don't you think you look cuter with a bob cut?
Are you listening to me?
It's almost time for the final exam.
The final exam?
Oh, it's XX, isn't it?
We're living together.
You should be more careful.
Like your clothes.
But,
don't you think this dress is cute?
Right?
It's cute, isn't it?
It's a matching dress.
You're sleeping on the bed,
but I'm sleeping on the bed.
You two sleep on the floor.
I don't like the floor.
The floor is cold.
It's cold.
I like the bed.
Anyway,
I'll study in the living room.
Meg
She's sleeping on the bed.
I'm getting sick of her.
What?
Are you finally awake?
You were so cute when you were asleep.
I'm sorry.
What?
Today,
we were scolded by Yuzuru.
Yes.
I was so shocked.
I talked to Airi.
We're not related,
but we are
Yuzuru's sisters.
Yes.
So,
I thought I had to clarify the relationship between us.
What?
So, I decided.
I'll educate your rebellious brother.
What education?
Let me go.
No.
Why?
Let me go.
No.
Listen to me.
We're sisters.
I don't know that.
I can't move.
Don't mess with me.
Let me sleep.
I'll educate you.
Be quiet.
What education?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Where are you hiding?
I'm not hiding.
What are you doing?
Wait.
I know.
What?
What's this?
It's transparent.
No.
Really?
Wait.
What?
I know.
It's okay.
Why are you making a strange sound?
Nothing.
Do you feel it?
No.
What's wrong?
Did I educate you too much?
I know.
I'll push you.
It's okay.
What?
Wait.
What's that face?
Nothing.
Your waist is moving.
Don't move.
What?
What's wrong?
Wait.
Why?
Nothing.
Where are you hiding?
It's okay.
Where?
I don't know.
Tell me.
Where?
What did you say?
It's okay.
I'll sleep on the bed.
Wait.
Don't move.
I won't.
You're so cute.
You react like this.
Right?
Wait.
It's okay.
It's not over yet.
Why?
You're floating.
I don't need this.
Right?
It's not good.
It's hot.
It's cold.
Wait.
Don't hide it.
Why?
What's that voice?
Nothing.
You're so cute.
What's that voice?
Why is that voice?
Nothing.
Wait.
Stop it.
Don't tell her to stop.
She's older than me.
Why did you say that?
What did I say?
It's okay.
You're going to fall.
I won't.
Let's go to a bigger one.
Okay?
It's okay.
Hurry up.
I'm going to fall.
I dropped it.
You dropped it.
Wait.
Come here.
Don't hide it.
Wait.
It's a little hard.
Why?
I don't know.
Why is it hard?
You have a strange voice.
Are you embarrassed?
Wait.
It's okay.
I can hear you.
Hey.
What?
Stop it.
Wait.
I'm going to lick you.
It's okay.
Wait.
If you make a loud voice,
Mom and Dad will wake up.
That's right.
Stop it.
Do you feel it?
No.
You're older than me.
What is it?
It's okay.
What's okay?
Stop it.
I bit you.
I'll bite you, too.
It's okay.
If you move, it'll hurt.
Wait.
Stay still.
Stop it.
Wait.
Your voice is louder than before.
What's wrong with your hand?
It's okay.
You said it's okay, but your body reacted.
I said it's okay.
You should be quiet.
That's right.
Stop it.
That was erotic.
Look at me.
You feel it, don't you?
It's small.
You have a big neck.
That's right.
That's great.
You feel it, don't you?
Be honest.
No.
Take a deep breath.
Say it feels good.
No.
Does it feel good?
You don't feel good?
You're lying.
Stop it.
Is that how you talk?
Why are you talking like that?
Why?
Because it feels good.
No.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
No.
You reacted a lot when you bit me.
Stop it.
You like to be bitten.
Is that your hobby?
We'll teach you many things.
Stop it.
It hurts.
Airi.
It's dangerous here.
Wait.
Touch it.
Stop it.
What's this?
No.
What's wrong?
I know what it looks like.
Don't hide it.
Show me.
I can't see anything.
You're excited.
No.
I want to see it.
Show me.
No.
What's this?
I saw it.
It's dangerous.
It's dangerous, isn't it?
Yes.
Did you do an abdominal exercise?
Why do you have to say that?
Why?
Show me.
I just looked at your nipples.
Why are you standing like this?
Touch it.
It's dangerous.
It's dangerous, isn't it?
What's wrong?
It's dangerous.
You've grown up.
You can't say anything.
You feel good, so you can't help it.
What's wrong?
Can't I touch it?
Don't touch it.
I want to touch it.
You're doing an abdominal exercise.
Does it feel good?
Tell me.
Don't do it.
Why do you want me to stop?
Why?
It's dangerous, so be quiet.
That's right.
It's dangerous.
Let's do it quickly.
Don't do it.
You're reacting very well.
Don't get the carpet dirty.
What?
You know that, don't you?
Wait a minute.
You're going to drop it.
That's not true.
You're a bad boy.
It's dangerous.
Is it dangerous?
Don't do it.
Hey.
What?
That's enough.
Why?
What's wrong?
What's going to happen?
Wait a minute.
What?
Stop it.
Why?
That's enough.
Stop it.
You're panting a lot.
Can I stop it?
Stop it.
Yuzuru, you're good at putting up with it.
If you put up with it, your pride will be hurt.
I'll put up with it.
Wait a minute.
Can't you put up with it?
Stop it.
What?
It's dangerous.
I'm going to drop it.
Are you going to drop it?
You're panting a lot.
Stop it.
Did you feel good?
You can be honest.
I felt good.
We're going to teach you a lot of things.
Let's play a lot.
Look forward to it.
You're panting a lot.
What?
Are you awake?
Why are you sleeping in a place like this?
Are you trying to avoid us?
The exam is coming up, so I want to sleep.
You can't get a good night's sleep on this sofa.
Let us help you get a good night's sleep.
Leave me alone.
I'll help you.
No, I won't help you.
What?
It's okay.
We taught you a lot of things yesterday.
Are you going to talk back?
No.
You don't have enough education.
I'll teach you more.
I just touched you a little.
Your nipples are standing up.
Are you sensitive?
Be quiet.
What?
You have a very sexy kiss.
Sexy?
Your body is trembling.
It's because I touch you.
You want to bully me, don't you?
No, I don't.
Let me sleep.
What should I do?
Do you want me to do something more tiring than sleeping?
I can't do that.
You're so obedient.
You're the only one who's obedient.
That's true.
Please.
What?
Let me sleep today.
It's okay.
It's not okay.
I have to teach you more.
I know.
I want to touch you directly.
No.
Are you sure?
You're making a lot of noise.
It's not okay, is it?
No.
You don't have to lie to me.
It's hot.
My voice is coming out.
You have a very sensitive neck.
Why are you so sensitive?
Because of you two.
Because of us?
It's not because of us.
It's because of you two.
I'll put my shirt back on.
No.
Why are you talking back to me?
Why?
Shut up.
It's hot.
You can talk more.
I can't.
You're holding it in, aren't you?
It's okay.
I can't.
Talk more.
It's not good for you to hold it in.
Stop it.
I won't stop.
It's hot.
Hey.
Isn't your neck stiff?
I can't help it.
I can't hold it in.
It's hot.
Your body doesn't lie.
It's cute.
It's in the way, isn't it?
It's in the way.
What?
It's dangerous to be seen.
It's okay.
Why?
I can't.
I'm awake.
You are.
That was great.
You studied too much.
Let's eat.
I can't.
You can't, can you?
That was great.
Wait.
Don't do that.
I can't help it.
You can show me a lot of reactions.
I want to see a lot of your reactions.
I'll watch you.
Look.
I want to touch you too.
I can't.
I can't do that.
What is it?
Tell me what it is.
I can't move my arms.
Because it feels good?
That's right.
I can't move my arms.
It feels good.
It sounds like a scratch.
It's moving.
I can't.
Please.
Do you want me to stop?
You said you wouldn't tell me.
Do I have to stop if you don't tell me?
That's right.
I won't tell you, so I won't stop.
It feels good to be licked on the mouth, right?
It feels good.
Your body has been shaking for a while.
It's unfair that only Yuzuru feels good.
Make us feel good, too.
I'm getting dizzy.
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
Make us feel good, too.
Okay.
What are you talking about?
It's small here, so come here.
Come here.
Lie down.
Wait.
Are you going to continue?
Make us feel good, too.
I want to feel good.
But...
You'll make us feel good, right?
But the place is...
It's nice to have a big space here.
But...
Are you going to make us feel good?
I'll do it.
It's hot, so I'll take it off.
How about our naked body?
I took it off.
Did you change your mind again?
Then make us feel good.
What?
What's that?
It looks good.
It feels good.
Your shoulders are touching mine.
Why are you licking me like that?
It's good to make us feel good.
You like to lick me.
It's hot.
Why are you so nervous?
Do you like to be licked?
Yes.
It feels good.
You're getting bigger and bigger.
I'm going to lick you again.
Your pants are in the way.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's good to be licked.
Does it feel good?
It feels good here, too.
Really?
Do you want to change?
You like to be licked.
I'll do it, too.
It's hot.
Does it hurt?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's a little cold.
Is it?
Does it feel good here?
It feels good.
I'm going to take off my pants, too.
You're looking at me.
It's hot.
Concentrate here, too.
Yes.
It's hot.
It feels good to be licked.
If you do this, you'll get in there by mistake.
I'm sure you'll get in there.
I'll lick you a lot.
Lick me.
It feels good.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
What is it?
Is it in there?
It's in there.
What should I do?
Is it in there?
It's in there.
I can't help it.
You can't help it, can you?
Does it feel good?
I can't help it.
Wait a minute.
Which one do you like?
This one?
Or this one?
I knew it.
You look like you're in a good mood.
It's very intense.
It feels good.
What are you doing?
I can't help it.
Wait a minute.
It feels good.
I can't help it.
It smells.
Stand up.
It feels good.
I want you to rub this side.
Look at the place where it's in.
Can you see it?
It's very deep.
Wait a minute.
You look like you're in a good mood.
You like intense things.
I can't help it.
You look like you're in a good mood.
Can you stand up and follow me from behind?
What are you talking about?
I can't.
You want to do it, don't you?
Stand up and follow me from behind.
Do it.
You can do it.
Let's do it together.
More.
It's intense.
You can do this, too.
You're so erotic.
I'm scared.
I'm going to strangle you using the necklace, good night?
What's going on?
Go to sleep.
What are you doing?
I can't believe it.
You can't?
You two are stuck together.
You wanted to do this, didn't you?
Look, Chikubi, you two are stuck together.
You can't do that.
Do you like her, too?
Oh, no.
Chinko is in a good mood.
She's in a good mood.
Does it hurt again?
Are you tired?
I'm tired.
You're tired, aren't you?
I'll move you again.
I'll move you.
Lie down.
You're a luxury.
You're tired, aren't you?
I'm in a good mood.
Can I put my finger in?
Put your finger in.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'll do a lot of nice things for you.
How do you feel?
I feel good, too.
Do I have to die?
Not yet.
I feel good.
You're so cute.
Does it feel good?
I feel good.
You can't run away anymore, can you?
You can't do that.
Do you feel good?
Can I stop now?
No.
What do you want to do?
Where's your sister?
Please let me go.
You're a man.
It's warm.
What's wrong with you?
You're drooling.
You're amazing.
You're drooling a lot.
You must be tired.
You can study for the exam with this.
What are you doing?
What are you two doing?
I'm sorry.
Let's play with your sister.
You're cute.
Where is he?
Maybe he's taking a bath.
He's cute.
He's here.
I was going to play with you while I was out shopping.
But I was in a hurry.
I'm sorry.
And you can't forget the taste of my manko, can you?
No, that's not what I meant.
Oh, you're already working out, aren't you?
Isn't that fast?
I'm sorry.
Your nipples are really hard.
You're moving a lot.
I'm sorry.
This is what happens when you don't take a bath.
You're making a lot of noise.
It's getting harder and harder.
I want to lick it.
Can I lick it?
It's really hard.
It's crazy, isn't it?
You like my nipples, don't you?
No, I don't.
Be quiet.
It's crazy.
What's wrong?
Does it feel good?
No.
What's wrong?
It's crazy.
Does it feel good?
It's really hard.
You like my nipples, don't you?
Your nipples are really hard.
It's crazy.
Are you in the bath?
Let's do it harder.
Answer me.
I had an exam today.
My mom made me a sukiyaki.
Thank you.
How was the exam?
It wasn't good.
Did you take a bath?
No.
I just took a bath.
Anyway, I'm rooting for you.
Do your best to pass the exam.
Okay.
I'm going to take a bath.
It was dangerous.
It's good that you're quiet.
I want to lick you.
What's wrong?
Do you want me to lick you?
I'm going to be back.
Up.
What will you do if you get used to it?
You're moving too much.
No.
You're so fluffy.
What?
You'll be found out.
I'm not quiet.
What?
You're too quiet.
Listen to me.
You'll be found out.
What should I do?
You're fluffier than before.
You'll be found out.
Wait a minute.
Do you like it?
Are you asking me if I like it or not?
It's not like I don't like it.
I like it.
Let's do it one more time.
No, no.
Can't you stand up straight?
If you feel refreshed here, you can concentrate on your exam.
That's right.
What are you going to do?
Be quiet.
Are you in trouble?
I'm in trouble.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to do more exercise?
Let's do it.
I have a slight dizziness.
Are you feeling good?
Let's do it faster.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
Why not?
Be quiet.
I'm going to be exposed.
I can't do it.
My nipples are also very hard.
It's getting harder.
Your face is getting more and more relaxed.
Does this feel good?
Yes.
Is it bad?
It's bad.
I'm sorry.
Your face is red.
Are you okay?
My face is very red.
Did I make a loud voice?
No, you didn't.
I'm sure I'll be exposed.
I can't do it.
You look like you're in a lot of pain.
I'm going to be exposed.
You can do it.
I was surprised.
It's too much.
I'm getting a lot of pimples.
You're getting a lot of pimples.
How does it taste?
It tastes like a strong stone.
Let's eat a lot at night.
Isn't this good?
It looks good.
Let's go next time.
I want to go.
Is that so?
I want to use this.
I came to a good place.
We're going to work at Este.
I'm going to study.
What is this?
It's because you're resisting.
But I don't do this.
Do you know what you're doing?
I'm touching your nipples.
You're sensitive to your nipples.
You can't see anything.
You're sensitive.
You're making a lot of noise.
Does it feel good?
Do you like to be poked by your nails?
You're about to get a scar.
No, I won't.
What should I do?
I can't see you, so I don't know what to do.
Right?
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
What did you just do?
You know what I did, don't you?
What did you do?
Um...
I think you licked me.
Here you are.
You're so slimy.
Huh?
Is it bad?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
Wow, you're getting better.
You're getting better.
Hey, do you want to use this?
Do you want to use it?
What is it?
What do you think it is?
I don't know.
You're so slimy.
What is it?
What do you think it is?
I don't know.
Hey, if you move, you'll get on the bed.
Don't say that.
You're so slimy.
You have a big nipple.
I'll massage your nipple.
I'll make you tired.
You're so slimy.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
You're so slimy.
Don't move.
Please stay still.
Okay.
What is it?
I think you're going to get it out of your pants.
Oh, my God.
You're going to get it out.
It's coming out.
It's already out.
Can I get it out?
Can I?
I'm sorry.
It can't be helped if it's this big.
That's right.
It looks painful.
You're going to get it out?
I'm going to get it out.
Do you like being tickled?
Yes.
This is also a part of the massage.
Massage.
I'm sorry.
You're very sensitive.
You're fine.
I'm sorry.
Is there a pet service at a pet store?
There isn't, is there?
What should I do?
There isn't, but...
Do you want a special service?
Let's do it.
Let's give you a massage.
I'll loosen you up with this.
This is...
Can't you see it?
What is it?
I'll loosen you up with this.
Wow.
What is this?
It's so soft.
I've put a lot on you.
Oh, no.
Wow.
Your breathing is getting rougher and rougher.
Are you okay?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'm glad.
I'll give you a lot of massage.
Yes.
Wow.
I'll give you a strong massage.
I'll give you a strong massage on your neck, too.
Does it hurt?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Wow.
Your voice is leaking a lot.
It feels good.
Does it feel that good?
Yes.
Your nails are stinging a lot.
Do you want more?
I'll apply it to your head, too.
Yes.
Wow.
It feels good.
I'll massage your head, too.
Yes.
I have to massage your lymphatic system.
You have a lot of tiredness here.
Wow.
It feels good.
What's wrong?
Does the massage feel good?
Yes.
Your mouth is wide open.
Why do you move so violently?
I'm giving you a massage.
Yes.
Wow.
We were so excited when you gave us a massage.
Yes.
What will you do for us?
Don't say that.
How will you take responsibility?
Responsibility?
Don't say that.
Do you want to feel good by yourself?
No.
I can't do anything.
I want to feel good.
My stomach is hard.
Do you want to put it in my stomach?
What?
Or do you want to put it in my stomach?
Wait a minute.
Which one?
I'm going to cry.
Do you want me to massage your hands?
Or do you want to put it in my stomach?
Which one do you want?
I want you to put it in my stomach.
Your stomach massage is the best.
Do you want to put it in my stomach?
Do you want to experience my stomach massage?
Yes.
I want to experience it.
I'll put it in your stomach.
That's not fair.
Do you want to see me put it in your stomach?
Yes.
I'll take it off for you.
I'll take it off for you, too.
You feel better, don't you?
Yes.
Do you want me to put it in your stomach?
You'll feel better from now on.
Do you know my stomach is wet?
Yes.
Do you want me to put it in your stomach?
You look very happy.
I'm sorry.
I'll put it in your stomach.
I feel good.
You're very hard.
Sir.
Yes.
You can't put it in my stomach.
Please be patient.
Yes.
I'll put it in your stomach.
Why are you making such a loud voice?
Because it's hard.
Do you hate it?
I like it.
You like it.
I feel good.
Sir, please be patient.
You can't.
I feel good.
What's wrong?
You can't concentrate on that.
You need a massage.
This?
It's hot.
It's deep inside.
Please massage my stomach.
Please.
It's hot.
You can't move.
I'm sorry.
You can't.
I feel good.
I'm going to leave.
Sir, this side.
Yes.
It's amazing.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
You said you felt good.
You're not fair.
I want you to feel good, too.
Yes.
I'm sad that you're leaving.
I'll move a lot.
Yes.
Please lick my stomach.
Please look at me.
You can't see me now.
I'm going to leave, so look at me.
I'll look at you.
You can't see me now.
I feel good.
It's amazing.
Your penis is in my pussy.
Sir, how do you like my massage?
It's amazing.
Do you like it?
Yes.
You like it, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I feel good.
Sir, please stop.
You're greedy.
Sir.
Do you want to move?
Can I?
You can move as you like.
As I like?
Yes.
Please lift your penis from the bottom.
From the bottom?
Yes.
Can I?
Can you do it?
I'll try.
It's amazing.
It's painful.
I'm panting a lot.
I can't.
Sir, you're panting a lot.
It's painful.
It's amazing.
If you do that, I'll go there again.
You can't go there again.
I can't?
You can't.
Please do it.
It's amazing.
Is that enough?
No, it's not.
It's not enough?
No.
You can move more.
Can you move?
Yes.
It's amazing.
You can move more.
Are you panting?
It's not fair.
It feels good.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
If you do that, I'll go there again.
I'll go.
It's amazing.
Sir, are you tired?
No, I'm not.
Why are you touching me?
It's amazing.
Why are you moving?
Do you feel good?
That's why you can't move.
I'm sorry.
Please move.
You can move more.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'll go there again.
It's not fair.
It feels good.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Is that enough?
I want to go there again.
I can't go there again.
You can move more.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You can feel good.
You can't go there again.
I can't go there again.
Do you want to go there again?
It's amazing.
Wait.
Don't move.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Do you want to stop massaging?
I want to do it.
Please move more.
It's raining.
It feels good.
I can't go there again.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You can't go there again.
It's amazing.
I can't go there again.
I'll move.
What was dangerous?
I almost fell down.
You almost fell down?
Please lie down.
You can't lie down.
It's hard.
Is your pain limit?
I can't lie down.
You can't lie down.
It's amazing.
You like this, don't you?
Does it feel good?
I can't stop my waist.
Please lie down.
What's that face?
Is it dangerous?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's cute to kiss.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
You have a cute face.
Please forget about me.
What's this?
It's amazing.
It's hard.
You can't do it with me.
I'll do it.
Really?
Please do it.
Do it.
Did you let it out?
Did you hold it so tight?
It's hot.
Did you let it out?
Did you hold it so tight?
Wait.
Do you want me to bite you?
No.
It's a punishment for letting me go.
How was our massage?
It was very pleasant.
Please come again.
You're still sensitive.
I thought I'd found a fun toy.
I can't enjoy it like I used to.
But even at a time like this...
I'm sorry.
I have to bully you.
You're standing up.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to touch you more?
You don't need this, do you?
Take it off.
I'm sorry.
Your nipples are swollen.
Does it feel good?
You talk a lot.
You look really bad.
It's not fair to dormitory.
Let me do it, too.
You're ugly too.
I'm sorry.
Shut up.
Be quiet.
You're sensitive, too.
I'll let you be quiet.
Do you want some soba?
You want some, right?
Open your mouth.
Yeah.
Drink mine, too.
Is it good?
It's good.
Which one is better?
Mine or yours?
Mine.
You can't choose?
Which one do you like?
Mine?
No, yours.
I like both.
You're greedy.
I'm sorry.
I have to do something about this.
Your nipples are so slimy.
I'll make them slimy.
I'll make your nipples slimy, too.
Okay.
Ouch.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
You like being scratched with your nails, too.
I do.
You're a pervert.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
How do you feel about being pinched?
I might like it.
You might like it.
You're a pervert.
Ouch.
Don't move.
I'm sorry.
I can't move.
Can't you stay still?
I can't. I feel too good.
You're an honest person.
Yes.
Ouch.
Let me touch your nipples.
Oh, no.
It's hard.
Do you want me to touch your nipples?
Yes, I do.
You're amazing.
You're still on your back.
Ouch.
Why are you on your back?
It feels good.
You like being pinched by us, don't you?
Yes, I do.
You like it.
It feels good.
Ouch.
Oh, no.
Let's tickle together.
It feels good.
You're reacting well.
I want to tease you more.
It's too early.
What?
You like it, don't you?
Yes, I do.
It's too early.
You can't do that.
You don't have to do that.
It feels good.
It feels good, so...
What?
You don't know?
You can't do that.
You're cheeky.
I'm sorry.
I'm your brother, so listen to me.
You look like you're in a good mood when I lick your nipples.
Your face is cute.
Ouch.
You can't do that.
Which one?
Why are you laughing?
I'm sorry.
I'll lick your nipples.
Can I lick your nipples first?
Yes.
I'll let you lick my nipples.
Ouch.
I only licked a little.
Okay.
Don't move.
I can't.
Stay still.
Okay.
It feels good.
You can show me your face when you're in a good mood.
Show me.
Okay.
Ouch.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
I'm going to puke.
I told you.
Hang in there.
You're so grumpy.
What's that?
That's...
That's bad.
Be quiet.
Mom and Dad will wake up.
It feels good.
You're so grumpy.
I want to lick your nipples.
I'll let you lick my nipples.
Thank you.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Do you want me to do it?
Let's do it together.
I can't.
You can't?
I'm going to puke.
Wait a minute.
You're so grumpy.
If you puke here,
the sheets will get dirty.
Are you okay?
You're so grumpy.
That's not good.
What's not good?
It feels good.
Your breathing is getting rough.
Stop it.
I won't stop it.
Talk to me.
I'm going to puke.
What are you going to puke?
You can't.
But...
You're so noisy.
I'm going to shut you up.
It's not coming out.
It's coming out.
Open your mouth.
Okay.
It's coming out.
Be quiet.
You've been so noisy.
I'm sorry.
Do you like being on your knees?
It feels good.
You're so chubby.
Do you want to do it together?
I want to do it together.
You're so chubby.
I'm sorry.
You can't puke.
You can hold it in, right?
Yes.
You're good at holding it in.
Does it hurt?
It feels good.
Doesn't it hurt?
It feels good and hurts.
Really?
You're so chubby.
Isn't it unfair that you feel good when you're chubby?
I'm sorry, but...
It's unfair.
Make us feel good, too.
What should I do?
For now, I want you to hit my buttocks.
My buttocks?
My buttocks hurt.
Your buttocks hurt.
I'm sorry.
You only say it feels good.
You're studying so hard.
How does it feel to be pinched by our buttocks?
It feels soft and good.
Your buttocks hurt so much that you're stupid.
I'll pinch you harder.
Get up.
It feels good to be pinched.
I'm sorry.
It's a little tight.
You're a pervert.
We want to feel better, too.
What are you going to do?
What should I do?
Let's put it on your face.
On my face?
Can I put it on your face?
Do you want me to lick your buttocks?
Yes.
You're licking my buttocks.
Is it good?
Yes.
It feels good.
Are you going to die?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know what to do.
Lick my buttocks more.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Can I lick your buttocks more?
You said it yourself.
I think you'll feel better.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'm sleepy.
Did you say it?
It feels good.
Are you okay?
Are you going to die?
Lick my buttocks.
I want to lick your buttocks.
Lick my buttocks more.
Okay.
Meg, you're licking my buttocks.
My buttocks are flat.
You're licking my buttocks.
It feels good.
You're getting better.
You're my brother.
You're too good.
You're getting heavier.
Did you change?
Are you happy?
You're so cute.
Do you want to lick my buttocks?
My buttocks feel good.
Do you want to lick my buttocks more?
More.
More?
Yes, more.
You like it, don't you?
Yes.
I can't.
I'm going.
You're greedy.
Does it feel good?
My buttocks feel good.
I'm glad.
Do you want to lick my buttocks more?
Yes.
It hurts.
It hurts a lot.
It's your fault.
I'm sorry.
We're sorry, too.
Do you want to lick my buttocks more?
More.
It's not enough.
You can stick your finger in my buttocks.
Yes.
How about this side?
It hurts.
My buttocks feel good.
It's hot, isn't it?
Yes.
It feels good.
I can't.
If you do that, I'll go.
I'll go.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I want to stick my finger in your buttocks.
I want to stick my finger in your buttocks, too.
I'll stick my finger in your buttocks first.
Pick one.
Me?
Which one do you want?
Which one do you want to stick first?
I can't choose.
Hurry up.
Pick one.
Megu.
Why?
You're older than me.
It doesn't matter.
But...
Then, I'll go with Ai.
I'm older than you.
Then, I'll go with Megu.
I'll stick my finger in your buttocks first.
Then, I'll go with you.
Okay.
I can't help it.
I'll stick my finger in your buttocks.
I can see your buttocks.
What?
Don't you want to stick your finger in my buttocks?
I want to.
You want to, don't you?
You're sticking your finger in my buttocks.
I like to stick my finger in your buttocks.
So, I'll stick my finger in your buttocks.
You're amazing, Megu.
I like to stick my finger in your buttocks.
I like to.
Then, I'll stick my finger in your buttocks.
Do you like it faster or slower?
I like both.
You're so greedy.
I'm sorry.
You've been saying you like both.
Because they feel good.
It feels so good.
I feel like I'm on the earth.
Don't do it on your own.
You can bear it, can't you?
Yes.
You're amazing, Kyoro.
What?
You're so fast.
You don't like being fast, do you?
I like it.
You do, don't you?
Yes.
You're so fast.
I feel so good, too.
Do you like it?
I want to stick my finger in your buttocks, too.
Wait a minute.
Then, I'll stick my finger in your buttocks.
I can see your buttocks.
Look at my buttocks, too.
You're so fast.
You're amazing.
Does this feel good?
Yes, it does.
You're so fast.
It doesn't feel good.
Even if it doesn't feel good, you have to bear it.
Yes.
Can you bear it?
There's some left for me, too.
Yes.
It feels so good.
It's dangerous here.
Where do you feel good?
I want to stick my finger in your buttocks.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
What are you trying to do?
I can't.
Do you want to stick your finger in my buttocks, too?
I want to stick my finger in your buttocks.
Before you stick your finger in my buttocks, let's stick your finger in mine.
Okay.
I love you.
Do you want to stick your finger in my buttocks?
I want to stick my finger in your buttocks.
Say, you want to stick your finger in my buttocks, too.
Okay.
You're so honest.
I want to stick my finger in your buttocks.
I'm going to stick my finger in your buttocks.
Okay.
It feels so good.
Where do you feel good?
Here?
I can't stick my finger in your buttocks.
You can't?
I can stick my finger in your buttocks.
How far do you want to stick your finger in my buttocks?
Does this feel good, too?
I'm about to stick my finger in your buttocks.
You can't stick your finger in my buttocks.
It feels so good.
You like taking your time, don't you?
You stick your finger in my buttocks if I hurry.
But I want you to hurry.
You want me to hurry?
Yes.
Please.
Please hurry.
You're greedy.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels so good.
You stick your finger in my buttocks.
Can't you hear me?
It feels so good.
What is it?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Then I'll stick my finger in your buttocks.
It feels so good.
You stick your finger in my buttocks.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels so good.
Look at your eyes.
It's embarrassing.
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
Oh, no.
I can't help it.
Why?
Hey.
You can't stick your finger in my buttocks.
I'm sorry.
Look at my buttocks.
I want to feel better, too.
Please bear with it.
You stick your finger in my buttocks a lot.
I want you to like my buttocks.
I'll hold it for you.
I can't help it.
Please bear with it.
You stick your finger in my buttocks a lot.
Really?
Please bear with it.
Look at my buttocks.
You stick your finger in my buttocks a lot.
It feels so good.
What did you say?
I can't help it.
You're moving from Nizuru.
You're so active.
It feels so good.
I want to stick my finger in your buttocks, too.
Do you want to switch?
Switch.
Switch again?
What do you want to do next?
What do I want to do?
I don't know.
Do you want me to move?
Decide.
Can I move?
I want to move.
I like to get tired from behind.
Let's switch.
Okay.
You're cheating.
I want you to stick your finger in my buttocks a lot.
Stick your finger in.
I can see your buttocks a lot.
It feels so good.
Which do you like better, Meg's buttocks or Airi's buttocks?
I like both.
It feels so good.
Stick your finger in more.
Meg's buttocks are amazing.
You can move so much.
My buttocks move on their own.
You're amazing.
It feels so good.
I like your buttocks.
Make me feel good.
Your buttocks are moving a lot.
You're cheating.
It hurts.
Let me see.
Your buttocks are moving a lot.
You like to move fast.
I like it.
I feel like I'm going to puke.
Don't do that.
Leave it to me.
It feels so good.
What about me?
My buttocks feel better.
Don't do that.
Leave it to me.
What about Aeri?
Not yet.
It's too early.
Yuzuru moved a lot.
I'll give you a reward.
Thank you.
What about me?
Wait a minute.
You're cheating.
Go back to sleep.
Touch me.
It feels so good.
Yuzuru.
You like to be pushed from above, don't you?
I like it.
This?
It feels so good.
You like it, don't you?
Your hands aren't moving.
It feels so good.
Do you hate Aeri?
No, I don't.
Why do you look so sad?
I can't stand it.
You can't stand it?
Yes.
I can't stand it.
Do you want to take it out?
Can I?
If you can't stand it,
put it inside.
Do you want to put it inside?
What are you saying?
You can't.
Put it inside.
I want to put it inside.
You can put it inside.
Can I?
I want to put it inside.
It feels so good.
You can't.
Do you want to take it out?
What?
Is it dangerous?
It's dangerous all the time.
It feels so good.
You can't.
Leave it.
It feels so good.
It might come out.
You can't.
I'm sorry.
Leave it.
It's amazing.
You're lying, aren't you?
You didn't take it out, did you?
It's coming out a lot.
Why do you feel good?
But...
I was told I could take it out.
It felt so good.
What about me?
I haven't done it at all yet.
Welcome back.
Megu is cheating.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
I want you to follow me from behind.
From behind?
I see.
Follow me while looking at my butt.
I'm sorry.
It's so round.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Come closer.
Move.
Do your best.
Thank you.
It's hot.
It feels good.
More.
More?
Do your best, Meguru.
Move.
It's hot.
I was so scared.
Did you get it?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's hot again.
I'm sleepy.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I want to do it more.
Aren't you tired?
I want to do it.
But it's hard.
You can't.
Then...
I'm a little tired.
Do you want me to do it?
Can you do it?
I can't help it.
It feels good.
You just did it.
But it feels good all the time.
It feels good.
You're good at it.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
What's wrong?
I can't do it.
I'm about to do it.
Again?
Do it.
Can I?
You don't have to do it.
I can't do it.
What should I do?
I'm about to do it.
You're shaking.
You're shaking a lot.
I think I slept too much.
Did you see me?
I saw you.
Oh, my God.
It's the second time.
You're strong.
It felt good.
You're young.
I'll clean it up for you.
Wait. I'm old.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
We still have time.
Let's continue until my mom and dad wake up.
Let's do it.
You can still do it, right?
Until I wake up?
Until morning?
You can do it until morning, right?
Let's do it again tomorrow.
Until morning?
Until morning.
Okay.
I'll do it.
My nipples.
My nipples are red.
It's morning.
It's true.
But it's not enough.
I want you to make it worse.
Let's continue until my mom and dad wake up.
I can't do it anymore.
Wait.
My nipples.
My nipples are falling off.
Ah.