Yes, that's what I thought.
I've sent you the report with all the results.
I believe it will arrive by the day after tomorrow.
Thank you very much.
Well then,
I'm going to bed.
Good night.
Huh?
What's wrong?
The door is locked.
I wonder if Masa is there.
I'll call him.
Hello?
Hello, Mom?
Are you at home now?
No, I'm out shopping.
I see.
I'm going to study with Hayato today.
Can I call you over?
Yes.
Is there anything you want?
No, it's okay.
Okay.
See you.
Mom, I'm out shopping.
I see.
I hid the key here for you.
Hurry up before Mom comes back.
Okay.
Hey.
What?
You're in a hurry.
Hurry up before Mom comes back.
Okay.
You're in a hurry.
You're so cute.
Mom will be back soon.
It's okay.
We won't see each other for a while.
I know.
It's okay.
She'll be back soon.
Where are you going?
I'm going to Nagasaki.
Nagasaki?
Where are you going?
I'm going to Nijima.
I see.
It's hot.
Hey.
Don't throw up.
Are you worried?
I'm worried.
I can't stand it if I don't do it every day.
It's okay.
I'll do it alone.
Instead, eat something erotic.
I don't want to.
It's okay.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
It's okay.
You're back.
I bought some sweets.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Your friend's boyfriend cheated on you.
He said he was your boyfriend.
I can't believe it.
Hey.
Are you listening?
I'm listening.
Hayato.
Which do you like better, older or younger?
Older.
That's why I'm dating you.
Really?
It's delicious.
I like you.
What do you want to eat?
Do you want to eat this?
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
Where do you want to go?
It's hot.
What's wrong?
It's rare for you to contact me.
You're too busy to come back for the next vacation.
I don't mind if you send me money.
What?
I don't want to spend money like this.
Wait a minute.
Kana is here.
Is that your father?
Yes.
I'm going to talk to Kana.
Hello, dad.
I'm fine.
I'm going on a school trip tomorrow.
I'm going to Nagasaki.
I'm going on a school trip.
Thank you.
I'm going to Nagasaki.
Hayato, what's wrong?
I left my charger in Kana's room yesterday.
Please come in.
Excuse me.
I was cleaning.
What did you forget?
My charger.
Your charger.
You don't have it.
Did you really forget it here?
I don't think it's in my bag.
I'm sorry.
I forgot my charger in my house.
I wanted to be alone with Kana.
I was worried about you.
That's not true.
You're worried about me, aren't you?
Stop it.
What are you talking about?
I'm listening to you.
You're worried about me, aren't you?
No.
Stop it.
Do you know what you're doing?
You have a good style.
Unlike Kana.
Stop it.
Get out of the way.
I just want to feel good.
Stop it.
Get out of the way.
I'll take care of you.
Go home.
Get out of the way.
Stop it.
You're upset, aren't you?
I'll take care of you.
Get out of the way.
You're upset, aren't you?
I'll take care of you.
Get out of the way.
You're upset, aren't you?
I just want to feel good.
Get out of the way.
Unlike Kana.
You're upset, aren't you?
Get out of the way.
I'll take care of you every day.
You don't like my voice?
What are you doing?
I'll take care of you.
You have beautiful eyes.
Stop it.
I'll take care of you.
Stay still.
You're in pain.
You look like you're in pain.
Don't be afraid.
Do you feel good?
Stop it.
You have beautiful skin.
Your pants are wet.
No.
What's wrong?
Did you wet your pants?
No.
Are you wet?
Here?
What's wrong?
Did you get wet?
You're not satisfied.
I'll make you feel better.
Stop it.
Stay still.
You have beautiful skin.
Let me go.
Let me take a good look at you.
Stop it.
You look different.
It's easy for you to get wet.
Stop it.
Let me go.
It's easy for you to get wet.
Stop it.
I'll make you feel better.
It's easy for you to get wet.
Stop it.
Did you get wet?
It's easy for you to get wet.
No.
Stop it.
Can I stop looking at you?
No.
Look at me.
Stop it.
Let me go.
Why are you so scared?
I knew it.
It's different.
What's different?
You're too excited.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
I'm not here.
Let me go.
It's easy for you to get wet.
I'm not here.
What are you doing?
It's easy for you to get wet.
Stop it.
I can't do it.
You can't stop it.
It's your fault.
Let me go.
I can't do it.
Open your mouth.
Stop it.
I can't do it.
Open your mouth.
Where are you going?
Look at me.
How is it?
How is it compared to your husband?
Tell me.
I can't do it.
Let me go.
Open your mouth.
It's painful, isn't it?
You don't have to breathe so much.
Let me put this on you.
You can use a rubber band.
What are you doing?
I can't do it.
Stop it.
Don't do it.
I can't do it.
It's clean, isn't it?
Why are you doing this?
Shut up, or I'll get angry.
I'm not doing anything.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
It feels good.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
I can't do it.
Stop it.
I'm going to get angry.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
You're squeezing too much.
You're already out.
Look at this.
I can't do it.
I'm going to squeeze you.
You're already out.
I can't do it.
Go home.
I only did it once.
I can't do it.
You're already out.
Go home.
It feels good, doesn't it?
What are you talking about?
I can't do it.
Stop it.
Let go of me.
You're already out.
Stop it.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You can do it.
Do you see this?
There's a lot in here.
Look at this.
I'm going to squeeze you.
There's a lot in here.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't do it.
It hurts.
You haven't slept yet, have you?
It hurts, doesn't it?
Do you want to sleep?
Let go of me.
It's tight here.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Be careful.
I'm going to squeeze you.
This is the best.
I can't do it anymore.
Stop it.
It feels good.
It's still out.
It's getting bigger again.
Let's do it again.
Go home.
What are you doing?
Don't come in.
Go home.
Stop it.
I'll wash you.
It's okay.
It's still out.
Stop it.
Don't do that.
I'll wash you.
It's still out.
You're pregnant.
Stop it.
It's hard, isn't it?
I can do it myself.
You should wash yourself.
Stop it.
I won't tell my family if I go home now.
You don't have to tell your family.
I'm sure you're tired of me.
I don't want you to be like me.
You're very erotic.
I'll wash you.
Go home.
It's still out.
You don't have to do that.
You should wash yourself.
I washed myself.
It's still out.
Stop it.
You should wash yourself.
It's still out.
Open your mouth.
If you don't, you'll die.
It's still out.
You'll die.
You can't go home like this.
You have to do it right.
You want me to go home soon, right?
Then do it right.
When you feel better, you can go home.
It's still out.
There's still water left.
You want me to go home, right?
Then do it right.
Keep your mouth clean
Come on, lick me
Can you stop that?
Please.
I'll lick you.
Stop it.
Will you lick me?
I don't know.
I'll wipe your nose.
I said, stop it.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
I feel good.
Let's get some more.
Okay?
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to get some more.
You did such a nice job today.
Remember?
Crank it.
That's right.
You'll drink them, won't you?
Just a little more.
Come on, stay still.
Pleasen just a little.
Don't shriek, come on.
Yes, I've read the report.
Are you done with the investigation?
Yes, thank you.
Welcome back.
Why are you here?
I asked Kana where the key was.
What are you doing?
Kana's father is crying.
He's a single man.
He can't take care of his family.
He has a beautiful wife and a cute daughter.
He's the worst.
You betrayed Kana, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
Are you going to get a divorce?
No, I'm not.
Kana needs her father.
So you're going to put up with it.
I feel sorry for you.
I'll comfort you.
I'm sorry.
Kana's father is sick.
We can take care of him.
No, I'm Kana's mother.
It doesn't matter.
I'm sorry.
You want me to do this, right?
Don't do it.
Do you feel it?
No, I don't.
You're getting sensitive.
Stop it.
I won't tell you until you say you want it.
I'll lend you a lot of money.
Don't do it.
I don't need it.
You don't need it?
You really want it, don't you?
You felt it, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
I'll lend you a lot of money.
Don't do it.
I won't tell you until you say you want it.
Stop it.
What are you hiding?
I'm here.
I don't like it.
Don't say that.
My waist is moving.
You feel good, don't you?
I'm not strong.
I won't tell you until you say you want it.
I'll lend you a lot of money.
Don't do it.
You feel good, don't you?
Do you like this kind of play?
What are you talking about?
Don't do it.
I like this kind of play.
Like this.
Don't do it.
You feel good, don't you?
I don't feel good.
Really?
You feel good, don't you?
Don't do it.
More.
Like this.
Your hips are getting red.
You feel good.
I don't feel good.
You're a pervert.
Look at this.
Your panties are stained.
Don't do it.
Look at this.
Your panties are stained.
You like this kind of play, don't you?
Look at this.
Don't do it.
What is this sound?
You're a pervert.
Don't do it.
You want me to do this, don't you?
You like this kind of play, don't you?
Don't do it.
You want me to do this, don't you?
I'll lend you a lot of money.
Look at this.
You want me to do this, don't you?
Don't do it.
Look at this.
You just said that.
I didn't say that.
I'll hold you until you go.
I feel sorry for you.
What's wrong with you?
Tell me you're going.
You want me to do this, don't you?
Don't do it.
You're scared, aren't you?
You want me to do this, don't you?
Listen to me.
Don't do it.
Come on.
You want me to do this, don't you?
Are you okay?
I hope it's not too hard.
Sorry.
Good girl!
You feel good, don't you?
You're so cute, Kazuma.
I'm going to pat you.
Do you want me to pat you?
I'm going to pat you on the back.
It's hard.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
There's a lot on your back.
Tell me.
It's hard, isn't it?
It feels good.
I can't hear you.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Let me hear you better.
It feels good.
I see.
It looks fun.
Champon?
What's that? Is it good?
I haven't eaten yet.
I'm hungry.
What should I eat?
Oh, right.
By the way,
When are you going to send me
the video I told you before?
It's okay.
I'm the only one who sees it.
I'm going to use it as a bonus.
Really?
Will you send it to me?
I'll be waiting.
Have fun.
See you.
Bye-bye.
I see.
Let's eat.
Don't your parents worry about you?
What?
Oh, they do.
I'm a law-abiding person.
My father has a job.
My mother
made a man
a few years ago.
Do you hate your mother?
No, I don't.
It's good to be honest.
It looks fun.
It's Kana.
She really sent me a video.
Hayato.
Hey.
I'm taking a video as I promised.
Are you cheating on me?
You can't cheat on me.
I'll do my best to take a video.
Please bear with me.
I love you.
You're so mean.
You're so cute.
You can do anything to me.
Hey.
Turn it off.
Why?
You're going to show it to other people, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
You're so mean.
You're going to break up with Kana, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
You're so cute.
You can do anything to me.
You're so mean.
You're going to break up with Kana, aren't you?
Why?
Are you jealous of me?
No, I'm not.
You're so mean.
You're so cute.
Hey.
What?
Do you want me to turn it off?
Turn it off.
What should I do?
Hey.
Stop it.
Okay.
Mom.
Do the same thing as Kana.
If you're more erotic than Kana,
I'll turn it off.
Okay?
What should I do?
You're so cute.
Stop it.
Okay.
You're so mean.
You're going to break up with Kana, aren't you?
Do you get it?
You're so mean.
Hey.
What's that?
Is that all?
What?
You're so erotic.
Do like this.
Hey.
You're so erotic.
Do you get it?
You'll turn it off, won't you?
I'll turn it off.
I'll do it for you.
What?
What are you doing?
You can't see anything.
You're not erotic at all.
What?
What's wrong?
Let me see.
Open your eyes.
What?
You can't see anything.
You're not erotic at all.
No, I'm not.
You're so erotic.
You're not erotic at all.
Do it properly.
What's going on?
What?
Tell me.
What's going on?
You're not erotic at all.
Don't you get excited?
Hey.
Look at me.
You're not erotic at all.
I'll do it for you.
Look at me.
Do it properly.
What's going on?
You're looking at me.
Open your mouth.
What are you doing?
You smell like a warrior.
Can I take it out?
No.
Why?
I want it.
What do you want?
This.
What's going on?
I want it.
Look at me.
You're licking me.
You can't stand it anymore?
You're cute.
Why are you licking me?
Didn't I tell you to lick me?
But what?
Please.
Let me lick you.
No.
Lick me.
Use your tongue.
Make me feel good.
You want to put this in, don't you?
I don't want to do that.
You have to lick me.
What's going on?
I want to lick you.
You're getting better.
What's going on?
You feel good, don't you?
I feel good, too.
I'll do something you can't do.
What is it?
Like this.
You can't do this.
Are you jealous?
You're jealous.
I'll do it for you.
Let's break up.
I can do this.
Do you feel good?
I'll do it for you.
You've never done this before, have you?
I can do a lot of things.
I feel good.
I'll rub you more.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
Like this.
I'll rub you more.
I feel good.
I'll touch you.
You can't do this.
I can't do this.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
I'll rub you more.
You've changed.
You used to be so good.
I feel good.
I can do this for you.
I didn't know you could make that sound.
I feel good.
I'll rub you more.
I can do a lot of things.
I feel good.
I'll rub you more.
I can do a lot of things.
I feel good.
I'll rub you more.
I can do a lot of things.
I feel good.
Are you going to Tokyo?
What time?
Do you have a meeting?
I see.
What do you want for dinner?
Anything?
Okay.
Be careful on your way home.
I'll be home soon.
I see.
Let's go home.
I want to hug you one last time.
I feel good.
I can do it one more time.
Give me some.
I feel good.
It's getting harder.
It's good, isn't it?
I want to put it in.
I still want to put it in.
It's my first time.
It's good, isn't it?
I want to put it in too.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's good, isn't it?
But this feels good too.
I want to put it in.
Then I'll put it in.
It's good, isn't it?
It feels good.
I feel good too.
It's good, isn't it?
It's really hard.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's good, isn't it?
I want to go more.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's good, isn't it?
Here we go
Is it this easy?
Everything feels great
You feel great?
Is this less painful?
Yeah, more painful.
I feel like I'm going to break up with you.
Please don't do that.
Don't hug me.
Don't do that.
I'm going to cry.
Please hold me more.
I want you to hold me more.
Please let me use all my strength.
Please hold me more.
I feel sick.
Don't cry.
Please hold me more.
I feel sick.
Did you want me to hold you?
Yes.
Did you want me to use all my strength?
Please hold me more.
What is this?
What are you thinking about?
You should think about it.
Please let me use all my strength.
I'm going to use all my strength.
Please hold me more.
What is this?
Please let me use all my strength.
I'm going to use all my strength.
Please hold me more.
Do you understand?
I don't understand.
I'm going to use all my strength.
Do you have anything to say?
Thank you very much.
I'm going to use all my strength.
Do you like this?
I like it.
I'm going to use all my strength.
Are you happy?
You're still a beginner.
I'm still a beginner.
You need to tighten your muscles.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Please give me more.
Which one?
This one?
I want you to take it off.
Please give me more.
Don't die.
I hate you.
Please give me more.
I'm not done yet.
Don't do it all by yourself.
I'll do it.
I'm going to die.
I feel sick.
I hate you.
Don't do it all by yourself.
I'm not done yet.
I feel sick.
I'm going to do it all by myself.
I'm not done yet.
I feel sick.
I hate you.
I'm not done yet.
Oh, come on....
Oh...I wanna go home....
I....
I can't...
I can't do...
Please take a deep breath.
Give it a try, ok?
I can't move anymore.
Please give me a lot of noodles.
Give me a lot of noodles.
I'll give you a lot of noodles.
I can't move anymore.
I'm back.
Why are you back?
I couldn't wait to see you.
Really?
I'm glad to hear that.
Why don't you change your clothes?
Okay.
Thank you for watching.