I'm looking forward to going to Ayabe-chan's house. I've always wanted to go.
Yeah, the two of us are going on a trip today.
Ayabe-chan's house
I wonder if Ayabe-chan is still there.
If we suddenly stop going on a trip, she'll be surprised.
That's right.
You're thinking about something nice, aren't you?
That's not true.
Is that so?
That's good.
Ayabe-chan's house
Is your boyfriend cute?
You can't touch him.
Is he Ayabe's boyfriend?
You're saying that, and you're aiming for your sister.
Ayabe-chan's house
I'm a little nervous.
Is that so?
I'm home.
Excuse me.
It's perfect.
Ayabe-chan's house
What is Ayabe doing?
Who is this girl?
My sister and I went on a trip.
And who is that girl?
A friend's new house.
It's not a friend, it's a boyfriend, isn't it?
You were trying to stop us from staying at home, weren't you?
You were trying to hide from us and do something nasty with your boyfriend, weren't you?
It's a perfect match for Sumi.
Don't say that.
That's good.
No.
Why?
That's good.
You always say that, don't you?
I'm sorry.
This girl has a bad mouth.
I'm always taking care of Ayame.
I'm Himari, the eldest daughter.
Nice to meet you.
I came all the way here.
Let me hear about Ayame.
I'm Hinako, the first daughter.
Nice to meet you.
Let's go.
Please come in.
Ayame, what were you going to do with your boyfriend today?
I just promised him to cook for him.
It's already noon.
Shinichi, aren't you hungry?
I'm sorry.
I'll cook for you right away.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I'm talking to Shinichi.
Don't worry about me.
Focus on cooking.
Thank you.
What do you like about Ayame?
She's kind.
I see.
And she's cute.
She's cute, isn't she?
Did you have sex with her?
What?
What are you talking about?
It's funny.
Let's go.
Hey.
My boobs are bigger than hers, aren't they?
What?
Well...
What do you mean?
Hinako.
Shinichi doesn't like it.
Do you want to touch it?
No, it's okay.
It's okay.
What do you think?
You like boobs, don't you?
Well...
Do you like boobs?
What?
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Hey.
If you like boobs, touch my boobs.
My boobs are bigger than yours.
Hey.
I did it.
Let me touch your boobs.
Don't touch my boobs.
Come here.
Let me touch your boobs.
Which one is bigger?
I don't know.
It's mine, isn't it?
No, I don't know.
Did you touch my boobs?
Yes, I did.
No, I didn't.
What do you think?
My boobs are soft and comfortable, aren't they?
Well...
I get a lot of compliments.
No, I don't think so.
Hey, drink more.
I like stronger boobs.
No, I don't think so.
My boobs are bigger than yours and Ayame's, aren't they?
Well...
I don't know.
Let me show you.
No, it's okay.
Ta-da.
No, I don't think so.
Touch my boobs.
Did you feel my boobs?
I'm sorry.
Hey, touch my boobs.
No, I didn't.
It feels good.
Shinichi, can you eat a cucumber?
You surprised me.
I was surprised.
You didn't notice, did you?
No, I didn't.
I didn't see it.
Really?
It's okay.
What's wrong?
What?
What are you doing?
Hey.
Your boobs are getting harder.
What are you doing?
It's not fair.
What's this?
Nothing.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Shinichi, you're a pervert.
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
You're in my way.
Hey.
No, I'm not.
No.
You're getting bigger.
No, I'm not.
What's going on?
Hey.
No, I'm not.
Your boobs are getting harder.
What are you doing?
Get out of my way.
You're in my way.
No, I'm not.
Get out of my way.
No.
Hey.
You're in my way.
Ouch.
Shinichi, stop it.
You're getting bigger.
No, I'm not.
You're a pervert.
You're getting bigger.
Which one?
Hey.
This is my penis.
No, it's not.
Hey.
You feel good, don't you?
Stop it.
You're getting bigger.
No, I'm not.
Shinichi, what's wrong?
Nothing.
I have a stomachache.
I'm sorry.
I'll go to the bathroom.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I don't know.
Do you know where the bathroom is?
You don't know, do you?
I'm sure it's over there.
I'll go check it out.
Go ahead.
What's wrong?
Do you have a stomachache?
You ate too much, didn't you?
Let me see your stomach.
Come on.
Let me see.
What?
You're a little hungry, aren't you?
What did you think?
You did that in front of Ayame.
Don't you really want to get excited?
It's okay.
If I speak out loud, you might find out.
Look, your nipples are so long.
You're a real pervert.
I'm going to tie you up here.
What do you think, Ayame?
If I speak out loud, you might find out.
Look.
It's like this.
I'm sorry to get your nipples dirty.
Be quiet, Ayame.
You were so cute earlier.
Your nipples are so hard.
What are you going to do with your nipples like this?
Let me see.
You're so cute.
What do you think?
Look.
You're too sensitive.
I'm just touching you.
What kind of sex do you usually have with Ayame?
Will you do this for me?
I'm sorry.
This place is so cramped.
It's okay.
This happened because of us.
Let me see.
Your nipples are so long.
I'll take responsibility and make you feel better.
It's okay, right?
Because I'm definitely better than you.
Can I lick your nipples?
It's okay.
I was quiet.
What do you think of my nipples?
It's the best, isn't it?
What?
Are you so scared?
It can't be helped.
Let's continue over there.
In Ayame's room,
How do you feel when Ayame does this to you?
You're really excited, aren't you?
But you've come this far, so it's okay.
Let's do something normal.
Your tongue is so soft and it feels good.
Stick out your tongue a lot.
It's okay.
I can't hear your voice.
You're too nervous.
Stick out your tongue a lot.
It tickles.
Which one do you like?
Tell me.
This one?
Ayami might have come.
What are you doing?
Don't disturb me.
What is that?
Stop it.
Let me join you.
What are you doing?
Why are you making a fool out of me?
You're the worst.
It's my turn.
Stop it.
You only have me on your mind.
You're mine, aren't you?
Hello?
You snatched something from someone!
I want to get it back.
Your hobby is miserable.
Then what do you do?
When I tell you that...
Kiss Dance-Top!
Chikuri gave you a kiss?
You get up right away, don't you?
What do you know?
Because you were licking me all the time.
Annoying.
Your tongue is very soft, isn't it?
Which one do you feel better?
It's me, isn't it?
No way.
I feel better because my lips are soft.
No, it's not.
I feel better because I'm older than you.
Which one do you feel better?
It's me, isn't it?
What?
Say something.
It's ticklish here.
Look at me.
I'll give you something good.
What are you doing?
Is it good?
It's good, isn't it?
I want to drink it, too.
How is it?
Your tongue is very soft, isn't it?
You're a pervert.
Shinichi, you're a pervert.
Let's play together.
What?
Why?
We were playing together just now.
Why are you touching me?
Because you're very hard.
Did you get bigger after I came?
No.
I see.
I'm glad.
No.
How is it?
Tell me.
What?
Shinichi.
It's mine.
You're cheating.
I don't want it.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good for me, doesn't it?
Which one?
Tell me.
It's mine.
I'll lick it.
It's different from yours.
What's that?
You're a pervert.
Shinichi, I want you to look at my body.
You don't have to look at it.
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
Look.
I have a better body, don't I?
Why are you taking it off?
It's hard here.
Let's take it off.
Okay?
Look at me.
Let's look at each other.
You look comfortable.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Touch my boobs.
Why are you taking it off?
It's not your boobs.
It's your butt.
No.
You like my butt, don't you?
You like my boobs, don't you?
Which one?
Tell me.
You don't like my boobs?
It's wrinkled again.
It's true.
You're excited about my boobs.
It's your butt, isn't it?
No.
You can touch it.
Which one?
Touch it.
It feels good.
Touch it a lot.
Do you want to see more?
It's enough.
Which one?
This one.
I can see it.
What are you doing?
You can see it well.
Do you like this one?
Which one?
This one.
This one, right?
Look.
It's getting bigger.
You like my butt, don't you?
No.
Which one do you like?
Which one?
Tell me.
Look at me.
You're making a weird face.
It's true.
What?
Did you expect it?
You wanted to kiss me, didn't you?
Show me.
It's getting bigger.
What's this?
It's amazing.
It's hot.
It's so hot.
Let's eat.
Wait a minute.
I want to sleep.
No.
I had a drink.
Give it back to me.
Don't take it.
I had a drink.
You're not a grown-up.
Give it to me.
You're older than me, aren't you?
It doesn't matter.
I'll drink this.
It's hot.
It's delicious here, too.
It's a little weird.
It's getting bigger.
Do you like it?
Which one do you like?
Tell me.
It's me, isn't it?
I know you're making a weird face.
What are you filming?
I'm getting a lot of your juice.
Did you feel it in your mouth?
It's a little sour.
But it's delicious.
Don't bite me.
Get out of my way.
Do you like to be teased by your parents?
Do you like it?
I like it.
I'm nervous.
What if I become a warrior?
No, I'll do it.
I'm nervous.
I got it.
You want to see my boobs, don't you?
I'll show you.
I told you to stop.
You want to see it, don't you?
I don't want to see it.
This is better, isn't it?
Concentrate on me.
I'm licking your boobs.
You want to do it, don't you?
Put your tongue out.
Concentrate only on my boobs.
Concentrate on me, too.
Look at me.
It feels good.
Don't you touch my boobs?
Don't touch my boobs.
I'm nervous.
Do you like it?
You like it, don't you?
Oh, no.
Your nipples.
How is it?
It feels good.
It's very crunchy.
You don't talk to me like this, do you?
I was heavier than you.
I'm the only one who can make you feel good.
I can't do it.
Why?
I want to do it, too.
I don't want to do it.
Oh, no.
Give me back my boobs.
You have a lot of boobs.
Don't you do it?
Do you have a lot of boobs?
Give me back my boobs.
Don't you do it?
Why?
Which one do you like better?
Me, right?
It's me, isn't it?
No.
Oh, no.
Give me back my boobs.
You have a lot of boobs.
Don't take it off.
I like your boobs.
Give me back my boobs.
You like my boobs, don't you?
You have a lot of boobs.
Give me back my boobs.
No.
I won't give it to you.
Give me back my boobs.
I like your boobs.
You have a lot of boobs.
Give me back my boobs.
I don't like it.
Why are you being mean to me?
I like your boobs.
You have a lot of boobs.
Give me back my boobs.
Why did you do that?
You did it suddenly.
I wanted to do it.
I'm scared.
You have a lot of boobs.
You're amazing.
You said, stop it.
I wanted to have sex with you.
Why did you do that?
You're going to have sex with me, aren't you?
No.
You want to have sex with me, don't you?
Did you feel good?
It was my fault.
It was my fault, wasn't it?
What are you talking about?
Shut up.
Go away.
No.
I don't like you.
You have a lot of boobs.
Did you spill something?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Don't look at me.
Do you want me to do it?
I don't do that.
I see.
Don't do it in person.
I'm pregnant.
I see.
I have a rubber band.
Do you want me to put it on you?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
You don't look well.
I'm fine.
Do you feel sick?
No, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
It's hot.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm sorry.
You're bigger than before.
I see.
I'm glad.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to the bathroom.
I'll be right back.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Why did you come here?
Did you lose to our temptation?
Is that so?
You've never kissed me like this, have you?
You won't do it, will you?
Stop it.
It's protein.
You had a boring sex.
I'm not sorry.
But that's not enough stimulation, is it?
No, it's not.
What about here?
Have you ever had your nipples licked?
No, I haven't.
No?
It feels so good.
It's so tight.
You have a rubber band on your nipples.
Oh, my God.
Did you put a rubber band on your nipples?
No, I didn't.
Why did you put a rubber band on your nipples?
I don't need it.
I don't need a rubber band.
I can do it myself.
Oh, my God.
It's so tight.
You lost to me today.
What are you doing now?
Are you okay?
Are you sure?
Are you sure you don't have to go back?
You're so clumsy.
But...
Are you okay?
It's so tight.
You're so clumsy.
You're a pervert.
Can you still do this?
No, I can't.
You've never done this, have you?
No, I haven't.
You're so clumsy.
You're so cute.
Let's eat.
You're eating too fast.
It's so good.
What kind of pervert are you?
No, I'm not.
Are you a pervert?
What?
I'm not a pervert.
Really?
You've never been a pervert?
No, I haven't.
You're a pervert, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
I don't want to be a pervert.
I want to talk a lot.
You don't want me to do this, do you?
No, I don't.
It feels so good.
It's so good.
You're so clumsy.
I'll put your mouth up.
Oh, oh, oh.
If you make a loud noise, they'll find out.
Is that okay?
I have to be quiet.
You're so clumsy.
You don't want to be eaten so soon, do you?
I'm embarrassed.
You're so clumsy.
Oh, oh, oh.
I'm going to mix it up.
I'm scared.
Open your mouth.
Is it good?
What are you doing?
Oh, no.
You're so clumsy.
Drink mine, too.
I'll drink it.
How is it?
Drink it clean.
Are you excited about something you shouldn't be excited about?
Do you like the Yantai Ochinpo?
I'm sorry.
I'm so thirsty.
It's so nice.
Be quiet, please.
Is that okay?
Or do you want to do it with three people?
Do you want to do it with four people?
No, I don't want to.
Why?
I can't?
I can't do this earlier.
My tongue feels better, doesn't it?
What?
It's me, isn't it?
You'll be surprised if I eat it.
That's a misunderstanding.
No, it's not. It's a gentle kiss.
Both of them feel good.
Why?
I can't choose.
You can't choose?
It's so good.
Look at my teeth.
I'll do it again.
I want you to look at mine.
It's totally different, isn't it?
You like my body, don't you?
Mine is bigger.
What?
Do you want to touch my boobs again?
I want you to touch them.
What? What's wrong?
You don't want to touch them?
I'll touch them.
Do you want to go back?
Don't do that.
Touch them.
Which one do you like?
Maya, choose one.
I like both of them.
You like both of them.
You're greedy.
I'm sorry.
Touch my nipples.
I got angry.
It's good, isn't it?
It feels good.
I'm glad.
I've never done this before.
It'll feel good if I put this in.
Do you want to put it in?
I'm getting wet.
I'm getting wet, too.
I'll get my underwear dirty.
Make it clean.
Make it clean?
I'll drink this.
Put your tongue out.
Take a sip.
I can do it.
I'll do my best.
Do your best.
It feels good.
You're licking me.
I like it.
Are you doing this to Ayame, too?
Don't you do it?
You don't let me do it, do you?
That's right.
Let me do it.
It's good, isn't it?
It feels good.
I'll do my best.
I want you to do your best.
You've been doing it all the time.
It feels good.
I can't see you licking me.
You're licking my tongue.
It feels good.
Do you want more?
Oh, my God.
You're licking me.
You're licking me a lot.
It feels good.
I'll do my best.
You're licking me.
It feels good.
You can't do that.
I wanted to do it first.
No.
I'm the best.
It feels good.
Don't you feel better without a rubber band?
You're the best.
I'm doing it.
You don't have a rubber band, do you?
You're always wearing a rubber band.
How do you feel?
What's the difference?
Ayame and you.
It's tight.
You know how it feels, don't you?
It feels good.
What?
Oh, my God.
You're being mean to me.
You were about to go.
You can't do that.
I didn't say anything.
Let me go.
I can't stop.
Can you stand it?
Oh, my God.
Don't film me.
I don't want to be filmed.
You can't do that.
Oh, my God.
It feels better without a rubber band.
It feels the best without a rubber band.
Let's do it together.
What did you say?
I said, let's do it together.
Let's do it together.
I don't want to do it.
You're doing it again.
All three of us are doing it today.
You're a pervert.
Is it good?
It's delicious.
Look at my boobs.
I like boobs.
How do you feel?
Oh, my God.
Aren't you going too fast?
You're a pervert.
Can I say more?
Yes.
My boobs were the best, right?
That's a lie.
Do you remember?
Yes.
Do you remember my boobs?
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
I'm in pain.
Look at me.
You're not holding back, are you?
I can do more.
I'll give you a massage.
Do you want a massage?
No, no, no.
I can feel it.
Are you okay?
Can I do it from behind?
Why?
I'll do it next time.
I've been doing it all the time.
I want to do it more.
What should I do?
Lick me again.
You're bored, aren't you?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
I'm in pain.
I want to do it more.
Oh, my God.
I'm so scared.
I'm afraid you'll find out.
Let's go.
I'm in pain.
I can't stop.
I don't want to do it.
I want to do it more.
No, you can't.
Oh, my God.
I've been doing it all the time.
I don't want to do it.
I'm in pain.
Oh, my God.
I don't want to do it anymore.
Let me do it.
I want to do it.
Come on, come on.
No, no, no, no.
No.
I'm not going to do it.
I'm going to take it off.
Can I move?
No, no, no.
No!
But...
Why are you taking it off?
Because it was right in front of me.
What?
What's that?
What do you want me to do with your back?
What do you want me to do?
Do you want me to hold you?
I want you to hold me.
How?
Like this?
I want you to hold me.
I really want to move violently.
Like this?
Why are you moving more violently than before?
Because it feels good.
It feels good?
I want you to hold me.
You have to shake your waist like this.
You can't do that.
I'm sorry.
I want to hold you.
I'm so excited.
It feels good.
I want to hold you.
I don't want to do it anymore.
I have a butt here.
You like my butt, don't you?
It feels good.
I have a butt in front of me.
You like my butt, don't you?
It feels good.
It hurts.
Put your hand in here.
It feels good.
Look at me.
Can you see me?
Can you touch me?
Put your hand in here.
Don't do that.
It hurts.
Why didn't you put your hand in here?
It feels good.
I can do it.
You didn't put all your hand in here?
I'll put them all in here.
I can do it.
Kind of weird to be doing this at our age.
Welcome home.
Doesn't he look small compared to the size of Dhaddu?
They all eat well, so don't worry when trying to agree on food.
Right?
It feels good!
Oh no!
You can't do it all at once.
Just a little more.
Hey!
Oh no!
Just a little more.
Easy, easy.
Just another minute.
It's not going well.
Oh no.
Just a little more.
Oh no!
Don't be afraid, Aren't I doing good?
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Why?
No, no, no.
You're really good at this.
You like it, don't you?
You're getting bigger.
I'm doing this with my little sister's boyfriend, and it's so much fun.
I don't like that.
It's fine.
Come over to my house again soon.
Okay?
But...
I can't.
Why?
You just got bigger.
That's not what I meant.
Oh, I see.
I get it.
Okay, okay.
Oh, you're doing it again.
You're doing it again.
No, no, no, no.
You're eating too much.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
You're doing it again.
I'm next, right?
Yes.
Okay, then.
It's over there.
Over there?
Which way?
This way, this way.
Come on, this way.
This way.
You're doing it again.
You want to kiss each other, don't you?
Kiss each other?
You're not going to look at me, are you?
No, I'm not.
You were looking at me.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
What's this?
Do you want to look at me again?
Oh, that's...
Down, down.
Down.
Come here.
Does it feel good?
Oh, my God.
Your nipples are sticking out a lot.
Kiss me, too.
My nipples are sticking out.
Oh, my God.
Why?
It's not fair.
Kiss me.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Do you like me?
I like you.
Is it okay to say that?
But...
I'm going to kill you.
What?
Oh, my God.
Over there.
Hey, don't cry.
I had a heart attack.
Did you see the last one?
Wasn't that all?
You still have a lot.
No way.
It hurts.
I'm sure I have more.
I have a lot.
Why?
I might have more than before.
I'm going to put it in.
I'm going to get pregnant.
I don't care.
I don't know who it is.
You're so playful.
I'm not playful.
I don't do that.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
You're so playful.
I know.
You have a lot.
It's great to be friends.
I don't think I can have sex with you anymore.
I can't even wear a rubber band.
It was great, wasn't it?
Yes.
Don't you have to go back?
I don't know.
You'd better go back.
Yes.
You can't go back like this.
Go back.
Hurry up.
I didn't ask you.
I'm sorry.
Did I overdo it?
It's okay.
Where have you been?
I'm sorry.
I have a stomachache.
I'm not feeling well.
That can't be helped.
What's wrong?
You're sweating a lot.
Is that so?
You're right.
You'd better take a bath.
Okay.
What are you wearing?
Let's take a bath together.
It's okay.
It's warm.
It's really warm.
What are you doing?
I was wondering what you were doing.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Did Ayame tell you anything?
Did you find out?
No.
Did you have sex with Ayame?
No, I didn't.
We had sex twice.
It's bad if you find out.
Don't say that.
If you don't say it, you won't find out.
Don't worry about it.
This side is more painful.
I'm sorry.
You're doing it properly.
You're surprisingly good at it.
No, I'm not.
You like it, don't you?
Wait a minute.
You gave me a lot at the end.
I'm sorry.
Why are you standing in the basement?
No, I'm not.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel better?
This side is also painful.
I'm sorry.
You laughed.
It wasn't all a joke.
Don't touch me.
You felt good, didn't you?
Is this your first time?
Yes.
You're cute.
Come here.
Sit here.
Why?
I'll make you drink it.
Did you wash your body?
No, I didn't.
Then I'll wash it for you.
I'm just here to sweat.
It's okay.
Then I'll do it myself.
We're good at cooking.
I'm good at it.
It's okay.
Didn't you know?
A little.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Why are you standing in the basement?
Why?
I'm sorry.
Don't do it.
Don't do it?
You're always doing it.
No, I'm not.
You're not good at it.
Don't do it.
You're cute.
I'm sorry.
I'll rub your neck.
Let's clean it up.
Don't wash it cleanly.
You might get caught.
I'll get caught.
Are you okay?
You're not going to get caught, are you?
I'm not.
You probably got caught.
You can't get caught.
Wait.
Are you okay?
No, I'm not.
I'll wash it cleanly.
It's okay.
I'm just washing it.
You might get caught.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
You're not going to get caught, are you?
I'm sorry.
Let's play more.
I want to do a lot of great things.
Let's make mistakes that we've never done before.
We know a lot of things.
That's right.
Have you ever been chosen by a cat?
No, I haven't.
I'm sure you haven't.
Do you want me to do it for you?
No, it's okay.
I'll wash it for you.
Look at this.
Wait a minute.
It's been a long time since you've seen a cat, hasn't it?
I'll clean it up.
I'll wash it for you.
You're getting a lot of massage.
How do you feel?
I hope you can feel it.
It feels good.
I'm in trouble.
I feel like I'm the strongest.
I'm going.
I'm in trouble.
You're in trouble.
How was it?
Did you feel good?
I feel good.
The water is clean.
It's clean.
Is it clean?
Yes, it's clean.
It's okay.
It's still not clean.
No, it's not.
It's hot.
You're standing up so soon.
You're standing up too much.
I'm standing up too much.
You're a pervert.
Because there are two of us.
Is it our fault?
You like to do this.
How do you feel?
I'm a pervert.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
You're a pervert.
What's this?
Wait a minute.
Look at me.
You're a pervert.
Where do you feel the most comfortable?
Imagine you're being bullied by me.
I'll lick you.
Say something.
You're a pervert.
What are you doing?
It's funny.
You're a pervert.
I'm sorry.
You like me, don't you?
He's still a baby.
It's nice to have a young grandpa.
He's cute.
He's so cute.
What's wrong with you?
He's a little out of breath.
What about me?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
You're about to fall asleep, aren't you?
Hey, sit down.
You're shaking.
Say something.
He's falling asleep.
He's sleeping.
It's a natural law of welcome.
If you're going to be like this, I'm going to go.
If you can't hold it in, I'll keep it a secret.
How do you feel?
You look like you're feeling it.
That's right.
Are you happy?
You're very energetic.
That's right.
Do you like it?
How do you feel?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
You're energetic again.
Do you want me to pat you on the back?
But it's coming out.
It's still accumulating, isn't it?
Hang in there.
It's coming out.
You shouldn't do that.
I'm sorry.
Don't you want to do something more pleasant?
What is it?
It's coming out.
Let's sleep together.
It feels good.
Have you ever done this before?
No.
It's a bad dream, isn't it?
It's a mess.
I'm going crazy.
I have to put up with it.
I'm sorry.
Let's sleep together.
It's coming out.
You shouldn't do that.
You're so cute.
I want to tease you more.
It's your favorite boob.
It feels good.
Do you feel good?
It's getting harder.
I can feel the heat.
My waist is moving.
Do you like this?
Look at me.
I feel good, too.
I feel good.
It's getting harder.
I'm happy.
You want to put it in your stomach, don't you?
I want to put it in my stomach.
You did it.
I'm a human.
You can't stand it, can you?
You've never had someone who could stand it, have you?
I don't have anyone.
Can you put it in your stomach?
I can't.
I feel good.
It's getting harder.
My waist is moving.
I feel good.
You're breathing heavily.
I'm sorry.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's amazing.
You're breathing heavily.
I want to put you in.
There's a lot of bacteria in there.
If you live like that, you'll get wet.
I'm going to puke.
Oh, my God.
Give it to me.
Give it to me, doctor.
Oh, my God.
It's on your boobs.
I told you to hold it in.
Do you like your boobs that much?
I'm sorry.
It doesn't feel good.
I thought you were going to puke.
I wanted to do it.
But it's a long night.
Maybe...
Let's go play.
You want to play, don't you?
But I don't want to be found out.
I don't want to be found out.
It's bitter.
It's really bitter.
I had a great time today.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
Good morning.
It's hard to get up in the morning, isn't it?
I'll make you feel better.
It's bitter.
Don't make a sound.
That's right.
You'll get sick.
You have to be quiet.
Can I look at you like this?
Then let's be quiet.
It's really hard.
I'm waiting for you to get up.
I'll make you feel better.
How is it?
Can you see it?
It's delicious.
I'm so tired.
You had a lot of sex yesterday.
Did you have a lot of sex?
How strong is your sexual desire?
I can't do that.
You can't do that.
It's okay.
You can have sex with her.
I can't do that.
You can't stand it, can you?
If you move too much, you'll be found out.
I'm hungry.
You're hungry, aren't you?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I spilled the soy sauce.
I'll go get it.
Wait for me for 30 minutes.
Okay.
Shinichi.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hello.
What are you doing?
Where did you go?
I went shopping.
I see.
Let's do it again in the morning.
Again?
You had a lot of sex in the morning.
But I can't do that anymore.
Why?
Ayumi told me to do that.
What?
What's wrong with you?
You look lonely.
I'm sorry.
I can't do that anymore.
You're going to stand up, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
You said you wanted to do it.
No, I didn't.
I'll tell Ayumi.
I can't do that anymore.
It's okay if you don't tell her.
You went out, didn't you?
Why are you telling her now?
Well...
I'm afraid she'll find out.
You went shopping, didn't you?
I want to go home.
You can't go home for a while.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I can't do that anymore.
Where's your nipple?
I found it.
You're right.
No, I'm not.
Can I check it?
No, you can't.
I can't do that anymore.
I'm sorry.
Shut up.
Be quiet.
You're so noisy.
Can you be quiet?
I can't do that anymore.
Don't make a loud noise in my house.
I'll get a warning.
I'll get a blackout.
I'm in trouble.
You're so noisy.
You have a big nipple.
I can't do that anymore.
Why did you lie to me?
I'm honest with you.
Don't take it off.
I can't do that anymore.
Shut up.
Be quiet.
Why did you do that?
I told you not to do that.
What's going on?
I can't hear you.
What are you doing?
I can't do that anymore.
You really can't?
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
You had a lot of sex.
I can't do that anymore.
You felt good, right?
You were so nice.
Let's have sex again before you go home.
I can't do that anymore.
You felt good, right?
You can't do that anymore, right?
You had a lot of sex.
I can't do that anymore.
It's not enough, right?
I can satisfy you.
You have a big nipple.
You're so noisy.
You were expecting it, right?
You're lying.
I'm not lying.
I can feel it.
Make your nipple bigger.
Make it bigger.
Make it as big as you like.
We're only interested in your nipples.
I don't need your nipples.
It's getting bigger.
It's hot in this room.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It's the best.
What about here?
You have a lot of nipples.
I can't do that.
What's wrong with you?
Isn't it enough?
It's hot.
I'm getting wet.
I can't stand it.
It's true.
I love you.
Can I lick you?
I don't need it.
Look at me.
What's the difference between you and Ayame?
You won't lick me, right?
That's right.
I feel good when you lick my nipples.
You look happy.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It feels good, but I can't do it.
Are you still doing it?
Do you want to do it again?
How do you feel?
Does my mouth feel good?
Don't you feel good?
Do you want to stop?
Let's stop.
Ayame...
What?
What are you doing?
You'll be licked by Ayame.
It's true.
If you want me to do it again, please do it.
But...
What?
Don't you listen to us?
Please.
How do you want me to do it?
What?
I'll make your boobs feel good.
You like boobs, don't you?
It feels good.
How do you feel?
My boobs are the best.
It feels good.
My nipples are standing up.
I'll roll your nipples.
It's hot.
It's full.
It's going to come out.
You can't do that.
It feels good.
It's going to come out.
Are you going to betray Ayame?
That's...
You said it earlier.
It's going to come out.
Look at me.
It's hot.
Did it hurt?
You like my boobs, don't you?
You've never been told that, have you?
It's hot.
You're kissing me.
It feels good.
Do you feel it here, too?
You're moving.
How do you feel?
You're moving a lot.
I'm sleepy.
I feel bad.
You are also awesome.
You like this?
You're a great favorite of his girlfriend.
You shouldn't have done such a bad thing.
I'm sorry.
Look at me.
You have a cute face.
I'm going to puke.
Are you sure?
You have a girlfriend, right?
Yes, I do.
Are you going to puke?
I'm going to puke.
I'm sorry.
You're cheating.
You should lick me, too.
Come here.
Don't worry.
You're our dog, right?
Yes, I am.
Can you hear me?
Show me your tongue.
Lick me.
I'm going to puke.
Don't lick my tongue.
Lick me.
I'm going to puke.
You're licking me.
Let me lick you.
Can you do it?
Use your tongue.
It must feel good.
It feels good.
You have a boob on your back.
Boob.
It's your favorite boob.
Wow.
You have a boob on your back.
I'm going to puke.
You did it.
You did a good job.
You did a better job than yesterday.
You're right.
Lick me, too.
I'm going to make you feel good.
You're still wearing socks.
I have socks, too.
I'm going to make you feel good.
Wow.
It feels good.
You have to be patient.
I like it.
Su-i-chi, lick me.
This.
I'm going to lick you.
Wow.
Does it feel good?
Lick me, too.
You like my butt, don't you?
I have two.
Wow.
What are you talking about?
Does it hurt?
It's true.
Wow.
Oh, my goodness.
I'm going to lick you.
Let me lick your bottom, too.
I can't stand it anymore.
Are you all right?
It feels good, doesn't it?
You lost to the feeling, didn't you?
Wow.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't stand it anymore.
You can't have sex in the middle of the night.
I can't.
Oh, my goodness.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You like it, don't you?
Let me lick your bottom, too.
Oh, my goodness.
You're great.
No, I'm not.
Does my bottom feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it, Chiyoko?
It's here.
Oh no! I can see everything from here.
I can see it.
Oh no!
I can't. I'm watching and I want to cry.
You can't.
Hey, hurry up and change, sis.
You can't yet.
I can't.
It feels good.
My mark is good, right?
It's hot.
Hey, you're overdoing it.
It feels good.
No, this side too.
It's amazing.
Open your mouth.
Is it good?
It's good, right?
It's hot.
It's better than the one you're having now, right?
Yes.
It's hot.
It hurts so much.
Do it like this.
Hey, do it like this.
How many times are you licking me?
I have a pimple on this side too.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's hot.
You're licking me so much.
It's getting worse.
One more time.
It's hot.
It's okay now, right?
Please, sister.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I got a pimple.
It's hot.
It tastes like you.
It's embarrassing.
It's okay.
I'll give it to you.
It tastes like you.
How many times are you going to lick me?
You can do it, right?
Can you do it?
Come here.
Are you tired?
Are you okay?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It feels so good.
It went deep.
It's in the shape of my mom's butt.
Really?
What are you going to do to me?
It feels good.
It fell off.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You say that a lot.
It feels good.
Shinichi, are you going to get a pimple, too?
Yes.
You can't do anything else, can you?
It's amazing.
You can drink a lot.
I'm getting a pimple.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I'm getting a pimple.
Are you okay?
You're going to die, aren't you?
It feels good.
You've been standing for a long time.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't stand it.
This room is a mess.
It's a mess.
It's amazing.
Let's have a lot of sex.
It's a mess.
You can't move on your own.
You're moving your hips on your own.
It's a live performance.
That's the way it is.
You're mean.
You're in the way.
I'm in the way.
Let's have a bad day.
Oh no.
I'm in the way.
How do you like it?
Nichikun...
Don't whine.
I'm very...
I can't do it anymore.
Look at my butt.
This is the best.
I want to go to sleep.
I can't do it anymore.
Can you put me in this blanket again?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
Stand up.
Go further.
I like you, so go further.
Go further?
Okay.
Go further.
I can't do it anymore.
Look at me.
Isn't it harder than yesterday?
That's right.
I love you.
Wait.
Don't fantasize.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels good.
I love you.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
There's a lot coming out.
Wow!
It's coming off.
Hey!
Why are you taking it off?
Don't take it off.
My sperm.
I have to clean it up.
Ah!
It still tastes like sperm.
It's still standing, isn't it?
Yeah.
By the way,
to her sister,
I'm pretty sad.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
You're a bad boyfriend.
You're right.
Hey,
put your sperm in me.
I'll do it.
Come here.
Here you go.
I want you to make me cry.
I'll put it in you, too.
Yeah.
Like you made me cry.
Please give me a lot of sperm.
Did you put it in?
Yes, I did.
It feels good.
It's going to be great.
Yeah.
Ah!
It feels good.
My sperm is still in me.
Ah!
I felt a lot yesterday, too.
Yeah.
It feels good today.
It feels good.
I vomited this morning, too.
You're a pervert.
It feels good.
What?
Ah!
It feels good.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm so tired.
You slept a lot.
Is it good?
It's a little sweet.
Did you feel empty?
I felt great.
Come to my house secretly again.
Okay.
It's a secret.
Ayame, did you come back?
No.
I invited you.
Shinichi invited me.
No.
I taught you how to have sex.
I don't know how to do it.
I didn't say that.
What are you going to do?
I feel sorry for you.
I didn't say that.
You're crying.
It's Shinichi's fault.
You made me cry.
You made my sister cry.
You're the worst.
Apologize to her.
You can't do that.
I'm glad you made up.
Let's have a drink next time.
That's good.
Let's do it again.
Let's make up again.
Please subscribe to our channel.