He suffered a traffic accident on the way to school.
I had to live in the hospital for three months.
I didn’t go to school, I was lucky.
I cry in this situation, it’s too hard.
But you can get the best of it in three months.
If I could.
Sorry to.
Yes, how about you?
This street.
A little border.
Sorry, I move a little.
is okay.
Yes, a little
Oh no no
No to
by
Oh oh oh
Oh oh oh oh oh.
Oh yeah
Another week.
In a week, I will finally be the owner.
No matter of course.
Video of Ivy.
Go in.
Oh yeah
How is it? how is it?
Oh yeah yeah
Yes
Such a person?
Oh, and here
See also Mr.
thanks
Yes
You at this time.
I thought it was what.
In fact, my father
I married again.
Oh is?
It is too hasty, right?
In fact, I decided before.
Do not talk, sorry.
From now on, we are all family.
Let’s do it together.
Welcome to.
My father’s fucking, when I suffer.
I was so happy with such a beautiful person.
But well
Leaving the hospital in three days.
I am sure I will get out.
What are your uses.
Asked by Mr. Kazuo to take care of him.
and Kazuo?
Oh Mr Tove.
But otherwise.
If you care.
Especially to
He is opposed.
I will fix it a little.
Can I help you dress up?
Okay, otherwise
Okay okay okay okay.
Do not be careful.
It is family.
No no no
All right so well.
If you move.
The wounds will get bad.
Well, no, I am okay now.
Sorry, but it smells a bit.
I didn’t have a bath for a while.
It is not easy.
Oh, no, this is the
I am okay, why can I get you home?
Are you okay though?
It is OK now.
What did you do?
No, it is okay.
What this?
Are you visiting?
I was back home, so it is okay.
Can I start the meeting?
Please please.
Please give me.
Yes, I am sorry.
Do you hurt?
It’s okay, let’s see it afterwards.
Yes, thank you very much.
Okay, I will sleep.
Good morning
If you are wrong, you will clean it immediately.
Oh yeah
Clean up or anything else is okay.
Don’t worry, you are your family.
No, that is okay.
I will try to call her mom soon.
Is there something?
No, no, nothing else
Glad you got out of the hospital.
well
Can you be able to get along with your mother?
With your mother? no
Make it look more happy.
You are really a shameful person.
Even if they say so.
Do you talk to girls in school?
Oh well
Drinking too much.
It is already late.
Time to sleep.
It is such time.
to sleep.
Yes, let us sleep.
I drank a lot.
Yes, in fact, I cannot.
I was drunk though.
I got drunk.
I will get out of the video of Ivy.
The first voice.
First of all.
It is noisy.
Earn to Earn.
Oh, oh oh
Continue to A.
Oh yeah, no but
At that age.
Oh, do it
Do not continue?
Do not do.
Chen, is it okay?
A little
Can I get her up?
What are you doing?
I struck the tea.
Oh is?
Okay is it?
Is it okay?
Oh is?
He was drunk and had fallen asleep.
Oh yeah yeah yeah, but
Oh, a little
Maybe the first time?
I have never done that.
What do you mean?
What happened, I get angry.
is okay.
He said he was drunk and slept well.
I will not wake up until morning.
What did you just watch and chew?
What is wrong? we don't have blood.
But it is dirty.
Is it dirty?
Oh, it is hot.
Oh well, can’t you?
Okay okay.
Do you touch?
He was in hospital for three months.
It was boring.
Oh well well
Do you like here?
Feel good
well
well is
What happened? did you feel better?
I felt better.
well
Good to imitate.
Give it up.
Here is the D.
Can you endure?
So, this is moving on its own.
Has your back moved?
A little bit different.
I am not going to do it.
Is it okay?
Prep is not.
greatly
More and more, no.
Something gets tough.
It is going great.
I will tell you all the good things.
Like smoking my breasts.
You are kidding something.
No, I will go out.
It seemed to have gone out.
Not yet not.
Have you ever seen a better woman?
No is.
When you do this, it feels good.
What can I do about this?
Has your face?
The puppy is becoming a pin.
Try the Peru.
Try a gentle perforation.
Go out.
I just licked it a little.
Oh, and no
It becomes a cue.
Oh, I will go out.
No to no.
No to
OK is OK.
What do you like to do? - I love to cheat.
Go to the shark up.
Do you like this?
No to
You want to feel more comfortable.
A little
Yes, it is okay
No to no.
Just wipe it.
It feels good, right?
I want to be nirvana.
It feels good.
A little, a little, a little
No, no is no.
I just entered the front.
must be out.
It is okay, just the front.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
I vomited everything.
This is not to be, at all.
But...
I said I would help.
I went in to the back.
A little base.
What happened?
will go out.
Go out.
Sorry to
I will go out.
behind it.
Do not leave.
greatly
Put it deep.
Do a little more?
by TATA
You can more.
Oh, and I have to be wet.
More soft?
You have to be wet.
Yes, it has to be wet.
by
I understand
I will help you.
No to No.
here and here.
Very hardly
here here
I will go out again.
A little
Going out again.
I am going out again.
No longer
Please say so.
Even if you want to get out.
I get into it and cannot get out.
It went out.
Oh well great.
Viewing is out.
has slipped
I went out.
I have to cry anymore.
must be removed.
I have to get out a little.
Please take out.
Let’s get out a little.
greatly
The sperm is hot.
The shit closed.
Oh...
A lot of stuff.
by M.
I haven’t been around here for a long time, so I’ll leave.
You will go out, you will go out.
Very cute.
He is moving fast.
Oh, there, there is a lot of back.
No, no, it’s good for someone else.
It is moving, but it is moving down.
Oh, it is a lot inside.
Oh oh oh oh oh
Full of, without any.
Nice is
No to
The Pleasure
I put it out.
He is hungry.
Oh awesome.
hardly
Okay, because it is still hard here.
I take out.
Get more out.
Get out of
Take out a lot.
Will you follow yourself behind?
Hold the ass.
Yes is
specifically
made it
No to
Oh yeah yeah yeah
th th
by
greatly
He has come so far.
really
It doesn’t seem like my first chicken.
So a little bit.
Very hardly
W is
Oh oh oh oh!
No to final.
Oh is
Very good w
A cup of w
Another cup.
Oh to!
Going to Plus.
as
Oh is
This man
A cup
Three months ago?
Sorry to
Oh but
Well, so well already.
A little
But still hard.
No, but
Not well done.
Okay okay okay.
It took 3 months.
Is this OK?
Yes to?
I do as I saw in the video.
Is it so?
well is
Have you studied?
greatly
Here is the occupation of the heat with the women of God.
You can no longer.
No more can.
Still easy.
can can can.
A little
No more not.
already easy thing.
Is it okay?
No more out.
Then you will go.
Be careful, first of all.
Yes I am going.
I am going.
Come to go.
First of all, forget something.
Oh is?
What is it?
Come on, I just said.
Oh I understood.
Oh is?
What is forgotten?
First, yesterday was great.
Not enough yet, right?
have to go to school.
Not just hard yet.
If you rest a little, it will be okay.
A little
I brought it well.
It is a bit painful to leave school.
But not to be worn, this.
No to
That is different.
What is different?
A little
Just a little.
I like my ass.
I hit his ass.
No to no.
Can not be?
Yes
No to no.
Can you not stand it? here.
I want to go out.
You are a pinch, right?
Give it such.
Because it
Yes, no to
Oh, it is being.
No is no.
It is being.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Stop the scratch, you
They split revenge.
Oh yeah
here and here.
Yes
Which are they imitating?
Feel good
Improve something.
I do not know.
It is now 40 that I am doing.
This is OK.
Let’s make your chest together.
Then, my husband and I stole my father’s eyes and did it.
The Rabbit’s Obligations
You have become pure.
I will be sick.
Colin is coming back, right?
It’s okay, I’m not back yet.
No to.
I really love your ass.
I love this ass.
Have you been unable to endure?
The ass pulled out.
Colony
He is hungry.
See so much.
Can not take medication?
See what you are doing?
It is cold.
Dad, come back and what do you do?
Somehow it is okay.
I think he will not come home yet.
This feeling.
I can no longer endure.
Do not enter.
Wait a little.
Yes
Oh is
Just now
You saw me here.
He was cleaning.
The food
I ate outside.
From tomorrow now.
You are on a trip and you can prepare a lot.
Oh yeah yeah yeah?
Would you like to put it in your suitcase or clothes?
Yes, thank you
How many days?
So, until Sunday, it is three days.
Three days?
I asked for a plate first.
is OK.
Will we enter?
Come in here.
Come in slowly.
It is travel.
Come in here.
Dad has come.
Sit and sit.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
No to
and
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Yes
Oh yeah
No to
I can once more.
But not here.
Let us go back.
Oh, here
I understand
No to
Oh well...
From tomorrow...
You can do nothing without worrying.
Yes is.
by
Okay okay thank you.
Forgetting is okay?
Yes, it is okay
First of all, school?
Yes, it is time to go.
So I will go.
Come to go.
You are not wearing it.
I wear the pants.
Have you always been dressed like this?
Yes, I did not notice.
I did not notice at all.
Three days from today.
Not a coward?
I could not wait.
Was it like this when you ate?
Yes is.
Not sleeping much.
I was thinking about my mother.
Show me.
Like a chocolate.
Brazil is bad.
Will you enter now?
Just being stuck.
It is even big.
If I were so much.
Maybe be there.
Maybe it will be.
Hardly
Something was gathering.
Are you looking forward to the morning?
Yes is.
Yes
Then then
I am not going to school.
I did it with Simeon.
Yes
Oh yeah
No to
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah
say a little.
2nd
Fuck look
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah yeah
here
I will try to do.
Oh yeah yeah
really
What about skate.
Oh yeah yeah
Slowly, slowly and slowly.
Oh, oh
Oh yeah yeah
Feels good.
Feels good?
Yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes...
Yes yes yes...
Good morning
Can you give me a washing medicine?
Oh yeah yeah
Oh well sir.
What about washing?
I’m more concerned about her face here.
When I see this.
From morning
I will sleep.
Did you clean it?
Sorry to sorry.
Are you worried about your ass?
Oh no, did you blow?
It just became.
Where are you touching?
Is it so wet?
Oh yeah yeah
Oh yeah
No, no no
Labra 1 and
No to
Greedy
Gigas is
Oh, and can’t I?
Getting bigger.
Since when has it been like this?
You are a whore when you see it.
Why are you not opening your pants?
I forgot to vomit.
Really?
I forgot to go.
It’s especially easy to lick, isn’t it?
What are you saying?
Really to
When did you become such a shy child?
Sorry, I have been in the box since this morning.
Not every day.
Dad, you can still do a lot of things without coming home.
Oh that is.
Yes is
It is pulp.
Cake is too good.
Cake is good?
Oh yeah
Yes
This is
It is A.
Oh is
Yes
Yes is
No to
Oh yeah yeah
Oh, and now this.
Entered on the way.
Oh yeah yeah
Oh Oh Oh
Oh oh oh
I will close it here.
No, I have not closed anything.
Really a ass.
I like it.
and evidence.
Restrained by Ruth.
It hurt?
It is crazy.
Without a shirt.
Who is?
here is
Surprisingly surprising
Please rest.
Go to Cloth
Sit to
Oh yeah yeah yeah
K is
Oh that, that is shit.
This is
I just do business.
mother
Feels good?
Will it feel better?
Kitty and bored.
Feels good?
by Inger
Oh yeah
It is picky.
The ranks are picking up.
Mr Lancaster is.
became
sweetly
It hurt again.
I slowly slow you.
Feels good?
Feels good to?
No to anything?
Not because you are going out.
go out.
Take it out and go out.
Nick, Nick and Nick
It hurts.
What is!
by
Oh is
No to No.
Another one.
It feels so good, it turns around.
Feel good
Oh yeah
No to
Because I taught you a lot.
Yes
No to
Who is better with me and your father?
Which of them?
I went away.
This means contractors.
Which one is.
Feels good.
I said the wind blows.
Oh yeah yeah
I am losing my mother.
by
Oh yeah
once
Revered
Oh yeah
......
Dad until you come home.
Still a lot of time.
And do more.
Yes
A little
Yes is
by
by Mama Mama
Let him rest.
Oh to
still enough
Ma is
No to
WON
by
None to None
Do you really feel better than my dad?
Smile, I am going in.
Wait a little.