Once?
ouch, ouch, ouch
ouch
ugh
Aoi! Aoi! What's wrong?
What's wrong? Do you have a stomachache?
Ah, no...
You look like you're in pain.
No, it's really nothing.
I wonder if Aoi-kun is okay.
Aoi-kun?
What are you doing here?
Do you still have a stomachache?
Ah, no...
It's really nothing.
You're here at this hour and you're in pain.
There's no way it's nothing, right?
It's really nothing.
Then, I'll go to your house.
No, it's really nothing.
It's really nothing.
You can't leave your student outside at this hour.
Let's go.
But...
But it's really nothing.
It's really nothing.
You'll have a stomachache.
Are you okay?
Yes.
If you don't call your parents,
they'll be worried if you're out this late.
So, what's wrong?
I'm...
I'm a playboy, aren't I?
Well...
My friend...
This...
It's a stomach medicine.
She made me drink it.
Then,
I couldn't swallow it.
At this rate,
I won't be able to go home.
Well...
Don't you feel bad that I made you drink it?
No, I don't.
It's an important student.
Miss...
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Hello?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't see you today.
I had something to do with my student.
I'm sorry.
Which is more important, me or work?
It can't be helped.
That's not what I meant.
By the way, you canceled the other day.
Hello?
Are you listening?
I thought I could do it after a long time.
Miss...
Because of me,
you couldn't see your boyfriend today?
You don't have to worry about that.
I'm sorry.
Ouch!
It still hurts.
Are you okay?
Actually,
I took it out of the toilet.
But it didn't heal at all.
It's still hard.
If you can do something, please tell me.
Miss...
Show me your bra.
What are you talking about?
Please.
It hurts.
I want to take it out more.
But...
I can't do it alone.
So, please.
But...
Please show me your bra.
It hurts.
It might be easier if you show me.
Okay.
Just a moment.
I'm just taking it out.
Miss...
It's amazing.
It's so big.
Can I do it here?
It's too big.
Please.
It's amazing.
Miss, what size is it?
It's too big.
It might be more exciting.
It's H size.
H size?
It's amazing.
It's so close.
I want to see your boobs.
I can't do it alone.
It's so close.
I'm just looking at it.
Please finish it soon.
I'm embarrassed.
What are you going to do?
Do you have a boyfriend?
I haven't seen him for a long time.
It's amazing.
Can I look at it closely?
I'm just looking at it.
It's amazing.
Can you do it?
It's just a little more.
Can I look at your panties?
It's amazing.
It might be more exciting.
I'm just looking at it.
Is this okay?
It's amazing.
Does it still take?
I see.
Can you take off your panties?
I can't do that.
I'm just looking at it.
Can you do it?
Don't look too close.
It's embarrassing.
Come a little closer.
I think I can do it.
It's good.
It's amazing.
I think I can do it.
Did you feel better?
I didn't feel so good.
I see.
I want you to be a little stronger.
But I did it.
I did it, but I still want to do it.
I see.
I can't do it alone.
Please touch me.
You?
Just once.
Please touch me.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's amazing.
Can you do it?
A little more.
Can I touch you?
You said you were just looking at it.
Look at this.
It's very painful.
Just a little.
Just touch my chest.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
If you do it with your mouth, you may be able to live a little faster.
With my mouth?
With my mouth.
I want you to do it with your mouth.
Please.
You may be able to do it faster with your mouth.
You're tired, aren't you?
Just once.
Just now.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's painful.
It's out.
That's a lot.
It's still like this.
I want you to play with my boobs.
You want me to play with your boobs?
But you said it with your mouth.
But I can't stop it.
What should I do?
I can't go home like this.
But I'll just pinch you with my boobs.
Pinch me with my boobs?
I'll just pinch you.
What should I do?
I'll pinch you.
Come here.
Pinch me.
I'll just pinch you.
Is this okay?
It's amazing.
It's still hard.
Is this okay?
It's amazing.
It's a little wet.
Give me a toothpick.
Toothpick?
It's a little wet.
I'm sorry.
Give me a kiss.
I don't think it's a good idea.
Why?
I was about to kiss you.
I don't think it's a good idea.
If you give me a kiss, I'll be fine.
But we're teachers and students.
Please give me a kiss.
I don't think I can go home.
But I think I can do something else for you.
Give me a kiss.
Just a little.
You pinched me with your boobs.
But I can't go home.
I'm sorry about that.
Give me a kiss.
I'm sorry.
You have a nice boob.
You're saying it's okay.
Give me a kiss.
You have a nice boob.
What's wrong with you?
I can't go home.
Can you go home?
I can't.
I can't go home.
Wait a minute.
You helped me earlier.
That's right.
You have a nice boob.
I'm not a doctor.
I'm a teacher.
You're a teacher.
You said it was for the students.
That's right.
Just a little.
Aren't you wet?
I don't know.
You're wet.
I'm not wet.
Just a little.
What's wrong with you?
Why?
I think I can go home.
Why were you surprised?
I don't care about the teacher.
I just licked you.
You're very wet.
It's very wet inside.
It's very wet.
I'm sorry.
What?
Why?
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
It's nothing.
I'm fine.
I can't stand it.
If you can go, you should go.
It makes it easier for me to go.
It's okay.
You can't go.
Why not?
You can go.
No.
It's painful.
I can't do it.
Look at this.
It's like this.
It's painful.
I can see it.
I can't do it.
It's painful.
I'm scared.
It's warm.
It doesn't feel good at all.
I didn't do anything.
Did you say something?
It's warm.
It's painful.
I'm scared.
I can't do it.
It's painful.
It doesn't feel good at all.
I can't do it.
Did you say something?
I did.
I can't do it.
I'm going to do it.
You should do it.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I can do it.
Thank you.
But it doesn't feel good at all.
What should I do?
You should do it.
I can't do it.
Is this the end?
Hang in there.
It's deep.
Next time, you should do it outside.
Tell me when you go out.
I can't do it.
You can do it.
Why can't you do it?
I can't do it.
You said you can't do it.
I said I can do it.
It's too late.
Can I do it alone?
Alone?
Turn your legs.
I'll move.
Wait a minute.
I'm not alone.
I can't do it.
Why don't you do it?
I haven't done it in a long time.
I can't do it.
I can do it.
I have a lot of hair.
I can't do it.
I'll do it one last time.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I have a lot of hair.
I'll take a shower.
I can't do it.
Look at this.
I want to take a shower.
Can I come in?
Wait a minute.
Let me drink more.
But...
You have a lot of hair.
I didn't say that.
Huh?
Can I kiss you?
I'm sorry.
Stand up.
Stand up?
What should I do?
Do you want to go to the toilet?
Huh?
What should I do?
No!
Huh?
No?
No.
Then let me lick you.
No, you can't do that.
You can lick me.
No, you can't.
You can't do that.
Huh?
Why?
I don't know.
Huh?
Should I go to the bathroom?
I'm really sleepy.
I haven't slept in a long time.
I haven't slept in a long time, so I'm really sleepy.
I'm really sleepy.
I haven't slept in a long time.
I haven't slept in a long time, so I'm really sleepy.
I'm really sleepy.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
A little more.
Please lick me.
Do you want to lick me?
I can't do it.
It's still hard.
Do you want to do it again?
Let's do it with your boobs.
Does it feel good?
It's still big.
How is it?
It's hot.
I want you to stand up and do it.
Stand up.
Does it feel good?
I can't reach you.
If you can do it, you can do it.
You're sweating a lot.
You ran, didn't you?
That's not true.
Ahh
Oh
Sensei
Hmm
Your were so anxious
That is
Oh
Huh?
You don't do anything with her?
Miss, I kissed her...
Yeah.
I don't want to do it yet
I want to do it again
That doesn't fit at all
I feel great
Ahhhh!
That feels good!
Ah!
That hurts!
It's coming out again!
Ah!
Sensei!
I can still do it!
Ah!
Sensei, that's it.
Oh no.
Aoi-kun, you're sleeping, aren't you?
I'll do it again.
I can do it as many times as I want.
I'll do it as many times as I want.
I'm sleepy.
Here you are.
I made only that, so you have to eat a little.
But...
Right?
I'll eat it.
I'm happy to be called a teacher in this situation.
What are you talking about?
Because you are beautiful and kind.
You are my admirer.
The effect of the medicine hasn't been reduced at all.
Maybe it's not just because of the medicine.
I'm sleepy.
You still want to do it, don't you?
Come here.
Can you sleep?
You look happy.
I can't help it.
Does it feel good?
It's hard.
It's a little hard.
I'm not dissatisfied with the teacher.
I thought about Aoi.
Show me.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
It's hard.
Can you sit down?
Does the teacher's bath feel good?
I'll give you a boob.
Does it feel good?
Teacher.
Make a sound.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Do you feel better?
Wait a minute.
Are you okay?
I can't do this anymore.
A little more.
Just a little more.
I can't do this anymore.
What did it tell me?
It's coming again.
I can't stop laughing.
Ouch!
Kotani, can you continue?
It was too hard.
Ouch!
Aoi-kun's grandpa...
Sensei will feel better too.
Don't.
I'm sorry.
Let me see.
It feels good.
It's itchy.
It hurts!
It hurts.
My stomach hurts.
What's wrong?
Sensei.
I can still do it.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Not yet.
I can still do it.
It's hard.
I can't breathe.
It's funny.
It's hard.
It's hot.
I'm sweating.
I can still do it.
It's still hard.
Do you want to do it a little more?
It hurts.
Can I use the floor?
Yes.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I can still do it.
Let me out.
It's hot.
It's messed up.
Does it feel good?
A little more.
I can still do it.
You can still do it.
Let me out.
It's hot.
I can still do it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Let's go.
It hurts.
It's hot.
There's a lot.
It's still hard.
It's dirty.
You're amazing.
It's still hard.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Let's go.
It's hot.
It feels good.
More.
Let's go.
Let's go again.
Me too.
It's hot.
I put out a lot again.
It hurts.
It's clean.
It's still big.
It's okay.
It's still hard.
But...
My friend said...
I'll feel better tomorrow morning.
Is that so?
Doctor.
If the effect of the medicine is gone...
Can I have sex?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
It smells like shit.
Fighting with birth control.
FAIL
Doctor, I'm in trouble. I can't sleep at all.
What? You haven't taken your medicine at all.
Doctor, I can't sleep at all.
But I have to go to school.
What? Please.
I'll be late.
But...
Don't say but. You'll be late.
I'll be late.
No, you can't.
I have to go to school.
Doctor...
No, you can't.
I have to go to school.
I don't want you to do that.
I don't want it.
You want it, don't you?
No, I don't.
No.
You want it, don't you?
She won't!
Please!
You can't do that to her!
Hey...
It makes me want to do something!
You're strong, Sensei.
Your nipples are so long, Sensei.
I'm going to do something naughty.
I'm not going to do anything naughty, Sensei.
I've been doing this since this morning.
It feels good.
I'm going to do it again.
My finger.
It's already wet.
It feels good.
I'm going to do it again.
It feels good, Sensei.
It feels good.
My arms are shaking.
I'm going to sit down.
It's hot.
I'm going to eat.
It's hard.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'm going to do it again.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
It feels good.
Don't you want to put it in?
Okay.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I wanted to put it in.
Okay.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Put it in.
It's hard.
You can still do it.
It's hot.
I want to do it more.
From behind.
Give it to me.
It's hot.
I'll do it slowly.
Slowly?
It feels good.
I'm nervous.
I'm going.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I'm going.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I'm going.
It's hot.
It hurts.
I want to do it more.
It's still hard.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Do it.
It hurts.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Do it.
I'm going.
It's not enough, is it?
It's not enough.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
It's still big.
Touch me a lot.
I don't want to.
It's leaking inside.
It feels good.
It's wet.
Wait a minute.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's hard.
I can't stop.
It feels good.
Let's go together.
You want to go out, don't you?
It's still wet.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's still wet.
Let's do more.
Let me out.
You want to go out again, don't you?
It feels good.
A lot of blood is coming out of your back.
Look at me.
It doesn't heal at all.
Are you excited?
Do you want to play with me?
Can I skip school today?