and yeah.
by ?
Can I go in?
What happened? come in.
The train arrived.
What happened? what happened?
I want to come to Tokyo,
Leaving the local university.
I came here.
Is it okay?
I will call your mother now.
Please do anything, please let me do anything, please.
I used to dance with a tree that I could not express my opinion.
When I came to Tokyo, I was a little happy that I was the only one who could keep the dance.
Go home to.
Soon to go home today.
Go home sister.
I will present.
Join my boyfriend.
I am pleased.
Oh yeah
Then
Go to.
Buying here?
Let’s go buy this.
Go to see?
Let’s be small.
well is
Choose which one is good.
The next Saturday.
I told you to go shopping.
Sorry to.
That day, I had a date.
I could not go.
Sorry to
Sorry to sorry.
I was the only one who brought my boyfriend.
You should have known everything about the SG.
A smile in front of a loved one.
It was a whore I didn’t know.
Something was regrettable.
Is it style?
Go out... are you out?
What? what? what? what? what? what? what?
Is it fucking?
Fuck it.
Ears are right.
Stop a little?
No, no is
You did it yourself too.
Sorry to
I want to eat candy.
The candy?
Can you fly?
No, just jump.
Just now.
Just now
Go home to.
I have my boyfriend here today.
Sorry, I have disturbed you.
Do not care so much.
Yes, I bought a drink, so we all drink.
I went to celebrate with my boyfriend.
not difficult
Sorry to
They are really good together, not really.
No, I did not say that.
Are there no good people?
and me?
I am not.
Oh, the accident
It is surprising.
I think I will have a boyfriend.
I am good.
But what type of person is he?
Oh yeah
Not a type.
Yes
So, the reverse is the opposite.
What do you like about the Spark?
Tell me right.
I want to hear.
I am ashamed to meet myself.
Can you say correctly?
No, no, I can say it.
No, a little embarrassing, just too bad.
No, but he is the drunkest.
Yes, I am concerned.
No, it is not your fault.
Maybe a little sleep.
Sleeping to?
seem to sleep.
I have not yet slept.
It looks delicious.
I am here. - I am getting a cold.
Is it okay?
Is it always like this?
I have never seen this.
Oh yeah yeah.
Let me take the room.
is good.
Have you already slept?
You have slept.
Oh, how far have you gone?
How far?
and date.
Really?
Just that?
What does that mean?
Have you kissed?
Oh, that is what you mean?
Because it is good, I am not yet here.
Yes is
I thought it wasn’t going too far.
No, that
Ordinary and ordinary.
What is normal?
But, I love you, you are a child, you are cute and you like it.
You are a cute boy, but that’s not enough.
What do you mean?
My child’s kiss, Manny and my adult, which one do you like?
No, I don’t know if I’m expected.
Have you ever kissed an adult?
A kiss for adults?
Yes, I think I probably never did.
Do you want to try it?
Oh is?
hurtly
The adult kiss.
No, but
It doesn’t mean doing it now.
How about.
No, that
No, but
by Mick
It is okay, I am sleeping.
No, but
Not that problem.
Wait a little and please stop.
Maybe he will wake up soon.
Really?
No to.
Do you care at all?
Are you drinking too much? – OK.
Have you understood a little?
Oh yeah yeah yeah?
Will you bring water?
OK is OK.
Is it okay?
What are you doing with the SG?
No but normal.
That normal couple.
Just normal again.
Sorry to tomorrow.
No, but too much.
Have you experienced?
Or go to a different place to play.
Not done yet.
Not to play.
Because you are not a high school student.
Yes is
I am an adult and can drink.
Do you want to kiss adults?
How about dance?
Sorry to
A little, a little, it’s okay.
I am too drunk, too drunk.
No to
Please please
Stop it anymore.
Stop the evening.
Wait a little.
in front of your eyes.
So do not voice.
Get it there.
Get it down.
Eat easily
well
Maybe I wake up a little.
Feels good?
Make you feel good.
No so is.
I go to the toilet.
I will buy a drink.
Would you like to eat Garlic Butter Chips?
That is delicious.
Then I will go.
Come to go.
Why did you run away yesterday?
said to escape.
Too much joke.
I will say.
I didn’t taste the Garry.
You are increasingly influenced.
No to
cannot forgive
Yes
Oh well
by Shrine
No to no.
So much bingo.
Yes to?
Feel good
The stone?
Yes
I am very shocked.
It feels like.
Yes
I have done something nirvana.
You will not do such a shit.
No is
Yes
You are fun.
No to no.
It is higher to save.
You must feel good.
Feels good?
No, I am going out.
A lot of out.
I’ll show you this before now.
Please stop for a moment.
If you want to keep quiet, have fun again.
Go home to.
I bought candy.
Do you smell something strange?
Yes to?
Thanks, now is it.
Yes, we will eat them all.
Really, they are very close together.
Yes, it is
This is good.
Yes, of course
I was surprised to say that he would not go.
I really envy.
Okay to be.
But she can’t get a boyfriend too soon.
Is it because you have no boyfriend for a long time?
I guess so.
Sometimes, borrow from your ex.
I am sure. – Definitely not.
It is Maya.
is delicious?
It is delicious.
Are you not well?
No is so.
What is drunk?
A little.
seem to sleep.
I drank a lot.
Both are not too strong.
Not that way.
Oh yes yes
You have become weaker, right?
No to?
Oh yeah, a little today.
A bit early.
OK is OK.
You were drinking.
It is so, right?
It is still enough.
You both have to follow.
Good morning
Do not eat this.
Do not eat?
Yes I eat.
You will sleep while you eat.
It is baby.
You look like a child.
Oh yeah yes.
But that is cute too.
No to?
and Damn.
Congratulations to.
A little bit, my sister.
Please see.
Is there a cane?
by
Oh is?
You’re going to have fun again, right?
Not because I am there.
It is broken, so it is okay.
It is not okay.
No to no.
Are you sleeping well?
No to.
You will find out.
So do not voice.
What is?
Is it OK?
Touch me too.
No to no.
See also, can you see.
Yes but
I touch it too.
Touch more of it.
See also.
He is very standing.
Feels good?
well well.
Be happy and make it work.
stretch your ass.
It feels bad to go to Scotland.
From below here.
Okay, I cannot see it.
Be careful.
hurtly
But I think that they are looking at such adults.
Say you are doing this.
Because that is.
No to
Oh yeah
Feel good
It feels good.
Doing something good.
What is it.
You will be found here a little before.
Sit for a moment.
Know what feels good.
Oh yeah
No to
Yes is
well
Oh is
Yes
No longer bad.
No more no
No longer
Let us eat.
Can you endure?
What are you doing?
say no
A little, a little.
It is OK.
It feels good.
Is it okay? is it good?
Please wait.
No, I will not wait.
Because it might wake up.
It is broken, so it is okay.
I do not know.
Your eyebrows will not wake up.
His back is shaken.
If so do.
not see it.
You entered in.
Okay is.
You want to return.
Have you felt better?
I will find out.
be so tough.
Will you go?
You can get it out.
I pulled in.
What happened.
Oh well okay.
Oh no no.
What happened.
No to you.
You are full of stomach.
So, when I came to Tokyo,
You have been messing all the time, right?
Don’t tell me, it was very difficult at the time.
I had only my sister to rely on.
Now I can rely on you.
Okay is.
So, did you find what you wanted?
Yes, I want to be a neonist, so I am now online.
If I am a NEO, I am the best guest.
Okay, so there will be a lot of it.
Stop to stop.
What is good?
I like French Nile.
Do it do?
Yes I understand.
What happened?
No, no is anything.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
I need to log in, because it’s remote.
Can I do it here?
Yes, well well
Oh, my food, I’ll clean it up.
Really thank you.
Then I will help too.
Yes please
Sorry to.
Please stop being a man.
Can you tell me about mayonnaise?
It is not.
A little before my eyes.
be patient.
No to No.
Be kind to me too.
Please keep it in mind, touch Halloween.
Go straight to the center.
Is it okay?
I am concentrating in secret so I don’t have to speak out.
and halloween.
Yes to.
Do not bear.
I will be patient to not speak too.
But that
From that
from above
No to
Yes
I am focused on your eyebrows, so it’s okay.
Why do the eyebrows rise?
It feels good, you know.
I will rub on the eyebrows.
Oh is
well is
here here?
Oh, I have done it.
They are always blowing candy.
Sorry to
Feels good?
But you are there right now, I am scared.
Then okay.
Caroline and Caroline.
Oh go out.
Go out.
Stop doing something strange to you.
What is strange?
You are joking.
There is something about your sister.
Yuzhou remained silent.
Even a little light.
I mean, you haven’t been hit at all lately.
I do not know.
This is my home.
It’s just that you want to get your boyfriend in, right?
Oh yeah?
Anyway
I will be home tonight for a long time.
Come home as late as possible.
It was my only treasure.
My heart is moving to her boyfriend.
cannot forgive
Such a persistent man.
His heart and progress.
I will manage it.
Oh my sister.
I said I won’t come home today.
You’re going to stay in the room today, right?
Yes is
You are going to go ahead, right?
No, it is
Oh, a little
Yes
Oh yeah
hurtly
well is
by Doddodod
This is my first night today.
Yes yes
Something is shameful.
Yes is.
So I have a room first.
Oh yeah, I understand.
Yes, I hope you come home.
My sister is also very funny.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
I have always admired your sister.
I wrote about her sister.
It is so.
What happened? what happened?
You are not well today.
What to do?
Do it?
Sorry to
Something is wrong.
by
I understand
Stop by.
Good night.
Anyway I am sorry.
He is sleeping there.
Do not voice.
by Rush
My sister
her sister though.
My sister is sleeping next to me.
Think of which place.
Make it feel good.
So I feel good.
Feel good
No to
I need to turn the voice quickly.
cannot
I will find your eyebrows.
Oh that is.
by DON
It is hard.
win together.
You were thinking about me, you were mocking me.
You can touch it as you like.
Oh yeah
Okay is
Think of me.
You wanted to do it.
Sorry to
It was full.
Feels good?
Feel good
Great choices
Feels good?
Oh yeah
If you feel good.
Yes is
Oh yeah
Yes
be hard.
Can I drop it?
drop it
Come soon.
Feeled
Feel badly
I have to endure.
is hot?
Feel badly
Didn’t you get blood?
It is a secret in your hands.
Yes is