Adding a layer mask
You have to recover back to 8 m to enter the VIP room.
프
Today's mozaik deployment is so hard.
I thought it would be a great idea to sleep in this camp all the night.
We must complete the military base!
You don't look so good. Are you okay?
It feels so good.
I'm fine.
Good work, everyone.
Good work.
I'm starting to sweat.
Oh, I see.
You guys.
I'm sorry.
It's tough.
By the way.
Yuki-senpai.
She's the only girl in this training camp, right?
Yeah.
She's a strength trainer.
Coach told her to participate in this training camp.
Yuki-senpai is amazing.
She's amazing.
Yeah.
Well.
Let's do our best to not embarrass her.
Let's do our best.
You're sweating a lot.
Yuki-senpai.
Are you okay?
Everyone is doing their best.
I don't want to be a hindrance.
I told you.
It's useless to collapse.
I'm okay.
I'm feeling better.
I'm going back to practice.
Are you sure?
I'm okay.
Don't make a mistake in your room.
If you rest in your seniors' room,
you'll be scolded.
I know.
Be careful.
Ah.
What?
Aizawa-kun?
Ah.
Eh?
Yuki-senpai?
Ah.
I'm sorry, Yuki-senpai.
I made a mistake in my room.
Aizawa-kun, are you okay?
Yes.
I just brought your luggage.
Take a rest.
Are you sure?
Then,
I'll talk to you.
Ah.
I made a mistake in Yuki-senpai's room.
I fell asleep.
Ah.
I did a bad thing to Yuki-senpai.
I'll apologize to her later.
Ah.
Yuki-senpai's
Amazing.
Yuki-senpai.
Aizawa-kun, what are you doing?
Ah.
Yuki-senpai.
That's my bra, isn't it?
Ah.
This is...
I didn't know you were such a pervert.
Ah.
You always looked at my bra, didn't you?
That's...
Um...
Ah.
After practice,
you always
took it off.
Like my brother.
Eh?
That's...
Ah.
Amazing.
Good.
Ah.
Amazing.
I've always wanted to touch you.
Yes.
Ah.
I've always wanted to touch you.
Yuki-senpai.
You're very soft.
Ah.
It's not what I thought, is it?
I didn't know you were so soft.
Ah.
You can touch me now.
Can I?
Can I touch you more?
Ah.
Amazing.
It feels good.
Ah.
I like being hugged.
Here?
Ah.
Amazing.
It feels so good.
Ah.
Can I touch you on your arm?
No.
Ah.
Can I touch you directly?
Amazing.
Ah.
I wanted to see you.
I wanted to see you directly.
Ah.
Can I touch you on your ear?
Amazing.
It's totally different.
Ah.
It feels so good.
Is it different from when I hug you on my arm?
It's totally different.
Ah.
Can I hug you tighter?
It feels so good.
Ah.
I feel good, too.
Senpai.
Ah.
Can I touch your nipple?
Yes.
Ah.
It feels so good.
Senpai.
Your nipple is so stiff.
Ah.
It feels so good.
When I practice,
my nipple gets stiff.
Ah.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Ah.
It feels so good.
Your nipple is so stiff.
Ah.
I want you to lick my nipple.
I want to lick your nipple.
Lick my nipple.
Ah.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
Can I lick your nipple?
Yes.
Ah.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
Ah.
I want to lick your nipple.
It feels so good.
Ah.
It tickles.
Ah, it feels good.
Your neck is harder than before.
Because my chest feels good.
Are you so excited?
It's always like this after practice.
Like this?
I want you to relax here.
Here?
Yes.
This is the hottest spot.
I'll touch it.
Wow, it's true.
It's hot.
Ah...
Senpai...
It's really hot.
It feels good.
Hmm...
Can you touch it directly?
Yes.
Wow, Senpai...
Wow...
It's embarrassing to see you like that.
Yuki Senpai...
It's really nice to touch you.
Yes.
Make yourself comfortable.
Wow...
It's amazing.
It's really soft.
Ah, it feels good.
It's really hot.
Ah...
Do it more.
It's comfortable.
Ah...
It's amazing.
Ah, it feels good.
Senpai...
Wow...
It's really open.
Ah...
I'll rub it with my fingers.
Is it okay?
Yes.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah...
It's amazing.
Ah, there.
Ah...
Ah, there. It feels good.
Ah, do it more.
More.
Ah...
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it's amazing.
I'll do it.
Ah...
Ah, it's amazing.
I'll do it.
Ah...
Senpai...
Ah, it's amazing.
It's amazing.
Ah...
It's really open.
It feels good.
Ah...
Is it okay?
Do you want to lick it?
No, I don't want to.
I want to lick it.
Ah...
Lick it and make it feel good.
Yes.
Ah...
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it feels really good.
Ah...
Ah, it feels good.
It's good to be done with you.
Ah...
I want to drink more.
I feel good.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
I'm going to throw up.
I feel very good.
Aisawa seems to suffer every day.
I'm suffering.
It's getting bigger and bigger.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
It's hard, isn't it?
Yes.
I'm going to put you to sleep.
I'm going to sleep.
You're very energetic.
You're not feeling well, are you?
I'm fine now.
Why are you fine?
Your breasts are too pleasant.
I feel better when I touch your breasts.
Yes.
What happens when you touch my breasts?
I feel better.
I'm fine.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
It's getting harder and harder.
I feel good.
Can I lick you?
Yes.
I want you to lick me.
I haven't taken a bath yet.
So I may be sweaty.
I love the smell of sweat.
I feel good.
It's amazing.
I feel good when you lick me.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I love you.
What's wrong?
I can't stand up because I feel good.
Did you feel good?
Yes.
It's amazing.
If you feel good with your mouth,
I'll pinch your breasts.
What will happen?
Breasts?
It's amazing.
Don't you want to pinch me?
I want you to pinch me.
I'll pinch your breasts.
It's amazing.
I pinched your breasts.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
It's amazing.
I feel good.
I feel good in my breasts.
It's amazing.
I feel stiff in my breasts.
I can't do it.
I can do it.
Can I do it now?
I want to do it more.
Let's do it.
Look at me.
It's amazing.
Don't do it now.
I'm nervous.
I feel good.
It's amazing.
I can't do it.
I feel stiff.
I feel good.
It's amazing.
I can't do it.
I feel good.
It's amazing.
I can't do it.
I feel good.
It's amazing.
I can't do it.
I'm soaked.
Why did you do it?
I feel good.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
It's amazing.
Come here.
I can move while licking your boobs.
I feel good.
I can't do it.
Come here.
It's amazing.
I feel good.
Do it more.
I can move while licking your boobs.
I want you to hug me.
I understand.
Do it more.
I feel good.
I can't do it.
I want you to hug me from behind.
Is it here?
Yes.
I can't do it.
It's amazing.
I feel good.
Let's go.
I want you to hug me more.
I feel good.
It's amazing.
Let's go.
I can't do it.
I want to move more.
I feel good.
I want to hug you more.
It's amazing.
I feel good.
Look at my face.
I can't believe you were sleeping.
I can't do it.
Thanks to you, I'm fine.
I feel good.
I'm going to sleep.
Okay.
I feel good.
It's amazing.
Look at me.
I can't do it.
Did you look at me?
Yes, I did.
I can't do it.
I'm going to sleep.
Okay.
I can't do it.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm so sleepy.
I slept a lot.
I'm going to clean your ears.
I feel good.
I feel good, too.
Let's do this again.
Okay.
I feel good.
Yuuki.
I had a hard practice.
So, I feel great now.
Wait a minute.
I feel good.
My neck is stiff.
It's not a finger.
It's a nail.
I feel good.
I feel good with this gentle stimulation.
I'm sorry.
I'm strong like this.
My neck is stiff.
I feel good doing this.
I feel good.
My neck is big.
Do you feel good only with your fingers?
What do you want me to do?
Does it feel good to be licked?
Look at me.
You look very comfortable.
Are you embarrassed?
Do you want me to touch you?
You're too energetic.
You like to be with me, don't you?
Does it feel good to be with me?
Your face is funny.
My right hand is slimy.
I'll lick you clean.
Does it feel good to be licked?
Do you want me to brush your breasts again?
Yes.
Well, then, I'll be mean to you.
I can't see your boobs, but they're in there.
You're in a pinch.
Are you excited?
I'm excited.
Are you excited because you can't see your boobs?
It feels good inside my boobs.
It's amazing.
Can I not see your boobs?
No, I want to see your boobs.
Do you want me to hug you directly?
Yes, I want you to hug me directly.
Yes.
Look at me.
It's not that different from before, is it?
It feels good to hug you directly.
I'm excited because I can't see my boobs.
It's not that different from before, is it?
Did you feel like you were going to go now?
It feels good.
You can't do that.
Besides, I haven't felt good yet.
It's not that different from before, is it?
Make me feel good.
Hug me.
I like to be hugged.
It feels good.
Hug me more.
It's not that different from before, is it?
It feels good.
How's my boobs?
It's hard.
It's because my boobs feel good.
It feels good.
I want you to touch me a lot from behind.
Touch me a lot from behind.
It feels good.
I'm touching your neck.
You have to touch my boobs.
It feels good.
You can't stop me.
How's my boobs?
It's messed up.
It's messed up because my boobs feel good.
Can you make me feel good?
It feels good.
It's messed up.
Make it faster.
It feels good.
It's messed up.
What are you doing?
Touch me.
It feels good.
Make my boobs feel good.
I feel like I'm going to puke.
Look at the microphone.
I'm going to puke.
I want to puke.
You want to puke, don't you?
I'm going to puke.
I want to feel good even if I puke.
It's good, isn't it?
Look at me.
It's hard.
It's hard again.
It feels good.
My legs move on their own.
Look at my face when I go home.
It's hard.
One more time.
Did you look at my face?
Make me feel good.
It feels good.
It's on my face.
I'm going to puke.
It feels good.
I'm sweating a lot.
Can you see my boobs moving?
It feels good.
Look at my face when I go home.
One more time.
It feels good.
Can you see my boobs moving?
It's hard.
One more time.
My butt hurts.
It feels good.
Look at my butt.
I'm going to puke.
Come here.
Look at my face.
I'm going to puke.
Look at our faces.
It feels good.
One more time.
They were watching us.
My face didn't look weird when I went to bed.
I'm embarrassed to be seen.
I'll do it from behind.
It feels good.
I'm going to puke.
One more time.
It feels good.
I'm going to puke.
This is amazing.
It feels good.
I'm going to puke.
I'm going to clean up.
It felt good.
I'm going to puke.
I'm sweating again.
Let's take a shower together.
It's cold.
Why are you taking a shower?
Because I'm cold.
I'll give it back to you.
It's cold.
Is it cold?
It's okay.
It's cold.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What?
You like boobs, don't you?
Yes.
You can look at them a lot.
I like them.
Are you excited about your bare boobs?
Yes.
I'm excited.
I like them.
It's amazing.
Look at them closer.
Okay.
I'm going to stick to them.
Do you like them that much?
Yes, I'm excited.
It's amazing.
Are you satisfied just by looking at them?
No, I'm not satisfied.
I want to enjoy them more.
What do you want to do?
I want to touch them.
Do you want to touch them?
It's amazing.
The water sticks to me.
Your nipples are transparent.
It's more embarrassing for me.
It's amazing.
Your nipples are transparent.
I like to touch them.
It's amazing.
You'll catch a cold, won't you?
I'll wipe your sweat.
It's amazing.
Your sweat is dripping.
Can I touch your nipples?
Yes, you can.
It's amazing.
I'll wipe your sweat.
I'm going to wipe this side, too.
Can I wipe this side, too?
I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
Do you get excited while drinking tea?
I'm not excited.
You can drink a lot.
How do you feel when I hug you tightly?
You're getting sleepy again.
I'm so nervous.
Do you want me to lick you?
Then I'll lick you.
I'm touching your boobs.
I'm going to wipe this side, too.
It's so full of juice.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to put it in your mouth?
No, I'm going to hold it.
I'm going to hold it.
I'm going to put it in my mouth.
Do you want to put it in your mouth?
Yes, I want to put it in my mouth.
Then you can put it in your mouth.
I'm going to put it in my mouth.
It's getting really hard.
I'm so sleepy.
It's full of juice.
I'm going to put it in my mouth.
I'm sorry.
You have a lot of juice.
How much juice do you have?
I'll clean it up for you.
I'm going to take a shower.
I can't believe I'm doing this with you.
It's getting harder.
I like to be petted.
It's full of juice.
Did you skip practice?
Yuki.
You can't skip practice alone.
You're not feeling well, are you?
I'm sorry.
You skipped practice, didn't you?
You have to punish me as a senior.
Are you in pain?
This is a punishment.
I'm in pain.
Are you in pain?
Do you want more punishment?
I'll give you more punishment.
Are you in pain?
Everyone else is practicing harder.
I can't breathe.
Why are you wearing a swimsuit?
I was training in the pool.
I see.
Do you want more punishment?
Think about something else.
I'm in pain, but I feel good.
Do you want more punishment?
I don't want more punishment.
I'll punish you directly.
I'm in pain, but I feel good.
I can't breathe.
I'll punish you directly.
Do you want more punishment?
I'm in pain, but I feel good.
I'll punish you directly.
What are you doing?
I'm in pain, but I feel good.
I'm sorry.
You can't drink this.
It's hard.
I can't help it.
Look at me.
It's hot.
You have a lot of hair.
What are you putting in your mouth?
I can't eat anything.
What is this?
Is it really hot?
It's hot.
It's not a bottle.
I can't open it.
Is this a bottle?
Show me.
It's hot.
I can't open it.
It's harder than yesterday, isn't it?
It's too hot.
It's hard.
You're very energetic.
It's getting harder and harder.
It's hot.
You really like my boobs.
I like your boobs.
Do you want me to touch you?
I want you to touch me.
I want you to touch my boobs.
I like your boobs.
You keep looking at my boobs.
It feels good.
Do you get excited when you look at my boobs?
I get excited.
Can I touch you again?
Yes.
It's getting harder.
Can I touch your opposite boobs?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's getting harder.
My hands are frozen.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
My palms feel good all day long.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Do you want me to touch your boobs again?
Yes.
It feels good.
You're sleeping.
I can't sleep.
You're getting bigger.
It feels good.
Do you want me to touch your boobs again?
Yes, I want you to touch my boobs.
You were very fast last time.
It felt good.
Please be patient today.
I'll do my best.
It feels good.
Your boobs feel good.
Please be patient.
You're getting bigger.
You're doing better than last time.
It feels good.
Please let me touch your boobs.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
You're getting bigger.
You were patient last time.
Yes, I was patient.
It felt good.
You're still fast.
I'll clean your boobs.
It feels good.
Don't slack off and practice.
Yes.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
See you in the next video.
Bye bye.
I'm tired.
I'm tired from today's practice.
Is he my senpai?
How long have you been practicing?
You're sweating a lot.
It's been a while.
Today is the last day of the training camp.
I want to do my best.
Senpai.
It's the last day.
I'll do my best.
Will you go out with me?
Yes.
Senpai.
Why?
Yes.
I'll do my best.
Touch me more.
Senpai.
I'll do my best.
Touch me more.
It feels good.
More.
Touch me more.
It feels good.
Senpai.
It's hot, isn't it?
It feels good.
It's hot here, too.
It's hot.
Make it hotter.
It feels good.
Touch me more.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Make it hotter.
Let's go.
It feels good.
Touch me more.
Let's go.
It feels good.
Touch me more.
Let's go.
It feels good.
I'll make you feel good, too.
It's hot.
It's getting hotter.
Why is it so hot?
It's sour.
It's hot.
Make it hotter.
It feels good.
It's getting harder.
Touch me.
I really like you.
It feels good.
I want to lick you.
I want you to lick me.
It feels good.
Do you like this?
I like it very much.
It feels good.
It's getting harder.
I'll put it in your boob.
I want to put it in your boob.
Not yet.
I'll put it in your boob.
Do you want to put it in my boob?
It feels good.
If I move it quickly, it will come out.
I'll put it in your boob.
Can you bear it?
I'll bear it.
It's getting hard.
It feels good.
I'll put it in your boob.
Can you bear it?
I'll bear it.
You can't.
It feels good.
I'll put it in your boob.
Come here.
Look at my face and put it in your boob.
It's warm.
It feels good.
It's the hardest so far.
There's a lot of it.
It feels good.
One more time.
There's a lot of it.
It feels good.
Do more.
Why did you stop?
It feels good.
One more time.
Let's do something more pleasant.
It's hot.
It feels good.
There's a lot of it.
One more time.
It feels good.
It's hot.
My neck is itching.
It feels good.
Let me lick your teeth.
It's hot.
It feels good.
One more time.
Give me more.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Give me more.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Let me lick your teeth.
It hurts.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Give me more.
One more time.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Let me lick your teeth.
Give me more.
It feels good.
I want to do more.
Do your best.
It's hot.
I'm about to throw up.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Let me lick your teeth one more time.
One more time.
It feels good.
I can't do it anymore.
You can do it.
I can do it.
It feels good.
Let me lick your mouth.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It hurts a lot.
You have a lot of it.
Yes, I have a lot of it.
Did it feel good?
Yes, it did.
It felt good.
Thank you.
Why do you look like you're done?
I'm done.
You said you'd be with me until the end.
Yes, I did.
But it's not enough.
What?
It hurts.
I can't do it.