I don't want to live in a world where I have to live alone.
I want to live in a world where I don't have to live alone.
Recently, a new stimulus has been born in my unhappy daily life.
I used to do it every day, but now there are so many things that excite me.
I want to live in a world where I don't have to live alone.
You are cute.
I'm sure you're imagining a lot just by doing this.
Look at me and imagine more.
I can't stop.
Don't leave me alone today.
I want to pee.
Look at me.
Don't leave me alone today.
I want to pee.
I can't do it.
See you tomorrow.
At the same time.
I'm already 34 years old.
I'm trying to make a comeback as a woman.
I want someone to look at me as a woman.
My husband is no longer.
I still want to be a woman.
Really?
That's crazy.
I want to be a woman.
I feel very good.
See you tomorrow.
Bye bye.
I'm sorry.
I was trying to show my body.
I was trying to feel refreshing.
I felt very good.
I'm sorry.
I feel like I'm going to faint.
I want to hurry up.
I can't stop laughing.
I'm whispering as I think.
I want to hurry up.
Oh, I feel good.
I'm about to cry.
I don't know what's going on in my mind.
I'm thinking about you.
I want to see you.
I love you from the bottom of my heart.
It's been a long time.
I can't stand it anymore.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm going to die.
I feel so good.
Akari.
You're going on a business trip for two days.
Are you all right?
I'm all right.
Good luck with your work.
I'm not lonely even if I'm alone.
A few days later.
I'm here.
Touch me.
Are you all right?
You've been through a lot, haven't you?
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Are you all right?
I'm all right.
I love you.
It was delicious, wasn't it?
I feel so good.
I do this every day.
Every day?
I feel so good.
I'm looking at you.
I love you.
What were you thinking about?
I was thinking about having sex with you.
I love you.
I'm going to have a drink.
I'm sorry.
I wanted you to touch me.
I feel so good.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm sorry.
I'm looking at you.
I'm so excited.
I've always wanted to see you.
I'm so happy to see you.
I feel so good.
How are you feeling?
I'm so excited.
I feel so good.
I feel so hot.
Do you feel hot?
I feel so good.
I'm so excited.
I'm so hot.
Let me get in the middle.
I feel so good.
Collect.
I really collect.
I don't collect anymore.
I've been watching you all the time.
I've always wanted to taste it.
It feels good.
It feels better than I imagined.
I can't do it anymore.
Stay still.
It feels good.
Show me your face.
From this side.
It feels so good.
I'm getting a lot of energy.
More, more, more.
To the back.
I can't.
It hurts.
Stop it.
It feels so good.
One more time.
It's been a while.
It's been a while for me, too.
It feels so good.
Stop it.
It's amazing.
It feels so good.
I want to do more.
My name is Akari.
Akari?
Call me Akari.
Okay.
What's your name?
I'm Chiaki.
Chiaki?
Do more over there.
Okay.
Is it okay here?
Yes.
Is it okay?
Let's do it.
You're always late.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
I'm on a business trip.
I won't be back for two days.
Really?
So,
I can do more.
Okay.
I'll do more today.
It's painful.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't stop it.
I can't do it.
It's painful.
Okay.
Go ahead.
I gotta pee...
I smell bad.
I can't do this anymore.
Hey, let me do it this time, okay?
Okay.
Here you go.
That's right.
See?
It's rubbing here. It feels good.
It feels good.
It's rubbing here.
Here you go.
Wow.
It feels good.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Open your mouth.
It feels good.
Is it good?
Feel it.
It tickles.
It feels good.
No, it feels good.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
It's rubbing.
Wow.
It tickles.
It's rubbing here.
Wow.
Can I rub here?
Yes, you can.
I'll rub here.
Wow.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I'll rub here more.
Wow.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
What's wrong?
Your butt?
Do you like your butt?
It's rubbing.
It's rubbing a lot.
Wow.
Does it feel good?
Do you want to rub more?
Wow.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Do your best.
Wow.
It feels good.
Oh, I can't do it.
Don't hit yourself.
It feels good.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, I feel great, ah, ah, ah!
My legs...
Ah, really!
Ah, I feel great!
Oh, it's so good.
Come here.
Hey, Jack.
Take me to that creepy room you always used to go to.
Let's go.
Oh, it's so good.
Is this your room?
Yes.
Did you pee in this room all the time?
Yes, I did.
Oh, did you?
It smells so good.
Oh, it's so good.
Let's touch each other.
Does it feel good when I touch you?
Oh, it's so good.
I think so, too.
Oh, I want to stop.
Oh, it's so good.
You love me, don't you?
Oh, it feels good.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow!
Feel good!
Ah! It feels good!
Ah, touch me.
Touch me, touch me, touch me.
Ah, I feel good!
Ah, I feel good...
Ah, I feel good.
Ah, it's amazing!
Oh, great! Great!
Oh, it feels good!
Oh, great!
Oh, the horse is messed up.
The horse is messed up.
Oh, it was a failure to make a record.
Oh, great! Great!
Oh, great! It feels good!
Oh, more!
Oh, break the horse more!
Oh, it feels good!
Oh, great! Great!
Oh, great! Money!
Oh, great!
Oh, oh, oh, it feels so good!
Oh, it feels good!
Oh, it hurts!
Oh, I had a bad dream.
Oh, you did, too.
What's up?
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
You're young, aren't you?
You're young.
Let me feel you more.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
Are you going to do it again?
It's the best.
It feels good.
It feels good here, too.
It's all getting better.
It feels good.
Don't do that.
What are you doing?
It's hot.
It feels good.
Put it in.
Put a lot of it in.
It feels good.
Don't do that.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Don't do that.
It's amazing.
Oh, it feels good.
Do more.
Oh, it's amazing.
You can't do this anymore, can you?
Don't do this anymore.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
I'm going to have a lot of sex for the next two days.
I'm going to have a lot of sex.
I want you to threaten me.
Oh, it's amazing.
It's been a long time since I've done this.
It's totally different from what I'm used to.
Oh, it's amazing.
Don't make me cry.
Please.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it feels good.
It's been a long time since I've done this.
Oh, it's amazing.
I can't get away from you.
Oh, it feels good.
This is pleasant.
Ouch.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Oh, that feels good.
Let me see your face.
Does it feel good?
If it feels good, let's go to bed.
No, let me go.
Oh, that feels good.
You gave me so much.
Hey, let's do whatever we want today.
Oh, that feels good.
What was I doing?
I'm so sleepy.
Why am I so sleepy?
Oh, that feels good.
You gave me so much.
That feels good.
Oh, that feels good.
Let me go.
I'm so sorry.
We still have 24 hours.
Can you still do it?
I'll do it.
I have to do it.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it.
Let me go.
I feel sick.
I'm sorry.
Let me go.
It's so hot.
Really?
I can't do it.
It feels good.
I'm going crazy.
It's so hot.
I'm hungry again today.
I want to do it more.
It's so hot.
I'm hungry again today.
I have to do it more.
Let's do it more.
I don't want to do it anymore.
It's so hot.
Let's do it again.
I don't know what to do.
I've been noticing that you and your
One bite.
Don't make that face.
I feel like throwing up.
Ah...
I'm going to put this in.
Oh, no.
I feel sick.
I'm going to throw up.
I'm going to leave a lot of urine at the end.
I feel sick.
I don't have time to take care of him.
I'm sorry for being late.
I'm sorry.
She is in the same movement as before
I can't't stop nyuu nyaa
My arms and legs are super confused
You are amazing
and I have to keep doing my best
Yes, I am doing my best
I can't do it.
I don't want to say goodbye to you.
But my husband will come back.
Can I do it one more time?
Really?
Yes.
I can't help it.
Can I take a video as a memento?
What?
A video of us having sex?
That's right.
I'm a pervert.
That's okay.
Thank you.
Can I do it?
Yes.
I can't do it.
I can eat dinner with this.
Yes.
I'll do it when you're not here.
That's great.
I wish I could do it.
You're so close to me.
I'm happy to see you.
I'm excited.
I'm scared.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
You wanted to be close to me.
Yes.
I imagined it.
I can't do it.
I want to kiss you.
I've done it many times.
You're still young, aren't you?
Yes.
How old are you?
I'm 20 years old.
You can do a lot by yourself.
Yes.
I can do it because you're the best.
Really?
Yes.
I can't do it.
I'll do it more.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
My feet are itchy.
It's soft.
I'll tickle you.
I'm tickling you.
It's soft, so it feels good.
I'll tickle you.
It feels good.
It's soft.
It tickles.
It feels good.
Do you feel ticklish?
It tickles.
It's soft.
Ahh...
It's hot.
It's hot...
Ahh...
You were tickling me, as I told you today.
Yes.
You were very cute.
Oh, I'm happy.
I'll tickle you.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, I can't take it anymore.
I can't take it anymore.
I want to tickle you.
Ah, I can't take it anymore.
It feels good.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, I can't take it anymore.
I'll tickle you.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, I can't take it anymore.
Ah, no, no.
Ah, it feels good.
It feels good, right?
I can't take it anymore.
I'll tickle you.
Can I tickle you?
Let me tickle you, please.
I want to tickle you.
Look at me when I tickle you.
Ah, it's getting hard.
Ah, it's there.
Don't tickle there.
Ah, it feels good.
Slowly.
Lay down slowly.
I want to tickle you a lot at last.
I'll tickle you slowly.
Ah, it feels good.
It feels good.
It feels good, Asou-kun.
Look at me a lot.
Don't forget.
Look at me closely.
Ah, it feels good.
It feels good.
Wow, that's great.
It's getting harder and harder.
Ah, it feels good.
It feels good.
Ah, Asou-kun.
Comfy
Nobody, come here
She dropped tons of cocoon
No, no, come back
Comfy
Comfy, Don't
Don't pc
Picch
Drop it
Kukuku
I feel so good
I wanna experience hypnotism
Let me do it, too.
Oh, no.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, I can't see anything when it's in there.
Can you see it?
Oh, it feels good.
I feel like I'm going to feel nauseous.
No, no, no.
Oh, it feels good.
I love you so much!
I can't hold it anymore.
I love this point.
I love here.
It feels good.
It feels good here.
It tickles.
It feels good.
I love here.
Do you love my neck?
I'll massage it a lot.
Not good not good
Ah, it feels good
Feels good
This is really crazy
This feels good
Ah this feels good
This feels crazy
It feels so good!
Ouch!
It's still not enough yet.
It still doesn't feel good.
I think you're cheating right away.
Are you cheating?
Cicadas.
But Aiki, it felt good.
It felt good!
My back hurts.
The scissors...
Ah, it feels so good.
I can't do it anymore!
So gross!
Itch! Itch!
It hurts!
So gross!
Oh, it feels so good.
It feels so good.
Do you want me to do more?
I'll do more for you.
It feels so good.
I'm about to puke.
Hang in there.
It feels so good.
I'm about to puke.
Hang in there.
Look at me.
Look at my butt.
It feels so good.
I'm about to puke.
Wow!
It's so white!
This is amazing!
Wow!
Look!
Let's do it.
Feels good!
Feels really good!
Wow!
Feels good!
I feel...
I feel awful.
It keeps happening.
It's killing me.
So painful.
Ouch!
It hurts here too.
Ot's painful.
So painful.
No-no-no.
Don't make it to feel good,
Put theToday'slove here,
Put a lot of dough here,
Oh my god.
It feels awesome.
It feels so great.
It feels great.
Oh no, it feels great.
Oh no.
I'm going to cry.
It's so great.
It feels so great.
It's still wet.
Wow.
It's comfortable.
There.
I love the entrance.
I love that.
I'm going to get caught.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Rub it a lot.
It feels good.
Rub it hard.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Oh, my God.
I can't do anything.
I'm tired.
Look at me.
Oh my gosh.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Boy, it feels good.
Rokucking on one arm, feeling great.
This is great.
This feels so good.
They are growing!!
Great!
It feels so good.
I'm stressed out.
Do you feel okay?
Yep.
It feels great.
I felt so good!
It's itchy!!
Oh, darn it.
Feel painful,
oh, I feel pain.
Oh,
she's sweaty like scared child.
She's scary,
angry kid.
What?
She's scary, when she's angry.
Hm.
T Umm.
It's scary kind of kid.
Hey, she's a scary kid.
You can be a scarier one to her,
as long as you symptom her.
You gave me a lot, so I have to squeeze it all out at the end, right?
Oh, it feels good.
I really want to give you a lot more.
Oh, really?
Oh, I want to give you a lot.
Give me the last one.
Oh, I want to taste it.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
I'll give you more.
You like this, don't you?
Oh, it feels good.
You'll give it to me, won't you?
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, my hands are shaking.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it's amazing, isn't it?
It's the first time I've ever felt so good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Oh, it feels good.
Ma-kun, do you feel good, too?
Ma-kun, does it feel good?
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it's nice.
It feels so good.
Oh, it's not good.
Oh, I'm not good.
Ah, this feels nice.
Oh, it feels so nice.
Ah, this feels so good.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah.
No! No! Are you sick now?
You can't take it anymore ?
Please, really?
It feels so good.
Wow.
I like it.
It feels so good.
Did you pee with this hand?
Did you pee?
It feels so good.
I feel so good.
Wow!
It feels so good.
I love it.
Wow, it feels so good.
Tickle me!
My back hurts
oh my god
that's feels good
feels so good
Oh no... i have to finish this
i have to finish this
I feel completely  storage space!
in this cloth, too.
no!No!No!
I feel it, I feel
it, I feel it!
no! I feel it!
no! No!
No, it's bad.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it feels good.
I can't do this.
Oh, it's gonna break.
I'm so scared.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't do this.
Please, I can't do this.
Oh, I'm full of blood.
Oh, it's so good.
I'll smell you with all my heart.
Please!
It's so good!
I love it!
It's a good feeling!
Good feeling!
No! No! No!
Tall!
no! no!
What a beautiful feeling!
ahhhhh~~
oh!
!
Urghhhhhhhh!
ohhhhhhh
oh.
oh my god
oh
Ahhhh
**ugh
**glare
**sarcasting
You realy called me
Good
So you panicked all of them?
Nice
Then, from tomorrow, let's do the same thing at the same time again.
Yes, I will.