next it's a high-speed this time
it's a joke
Iriha, you're younger than me, aren't you?
Hey, say that again.
What?
Hey, wait.
You have something to say, don't you?
Say it.
I love you, brother.
I can't stand it anymore.
Oh, I see.
By the way, what do you like about a guy like me?
Oh, your face.
I see.
Your face is important.
I thought you were a quiet guy, but you're quite bold.
I don't know what a woman is thinking.
You've been sweet to me since I was a kid, but you don't confess to me.
We're brothers.
I love you, brother.
Are you still up?
Yes, I am.
Are you stupid?
You're disgusting.
You're younger than me.
Can I sleep with you?
Are you asleep?
I'm still awake.
Come here.
When I was a kid, I used to watch scary TV and sleep with you.
It doesn't mean anything.
Look at me.
I can sleep like this.
You smell so good.
You smell like a woman.
You're so erotic.
When did you become like this?
Don't kiss me.
What are you doing to my sister?
Don't.
Look at me.
Do you like me?
I don't hate you.
Do you want to have sex with me?
I know I'm not a good man.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
If I comfort her just once, she'll surely return to her usual quiet little sister.
She'll notice that it was a misunderstanding just because there was a strange switch.
Just once.
And then, I'm sure...
She'll notice that it was a misunderstanding just because there was a strange switch.
Boy junkie...
I think... he's making fun of us.
I love you.
Does it hurt?
You're beautiful.
Painful, the wound has to be healed.
It's done.
Big brother...
Let's go home.
It feel astonishing!
Bro, it feels!
Ah!
Ah! So cool!!
Catch
Do you like me, too?
I love you, too.
I love you.
I don't have a condom.
I can't.
Put the condom in.
It's all my fault.
Please.
Put the condom in.
You have a long neck.
It doesn't hurt.
I know how you feel.
It's all right.
I'm still in a bad mood.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I'm always happy.
I love you.
I love you, too.
It's all my fault.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sorry.
I was in a bad mood.
I can't go back to the way we used to be.
Where's grandpa?
He's gone to the field.
I'm sorry.
Good morning.
Hiroshi, you should learn to be a good boy.
I know.
Hey, Hiroshi.
Yeah?
Did you say anything to mom and dad?
No, I didn't.
I said,
Thank you for giving me such a wonderful brother.
I feel like I'm still in your body.
Hey, Hiroshi.
Grandpa and grandma went to the field.
They won't be back for a while.
Hey, Hiroshi.
Yeah?
Why am I losing to temptation?
I love you, Hiroshi.
I love you, too.
Give me more kisses.
Hey, Hiroshi.
Give me your wings.
Wings?
Okay.
I love you, Hiroshi.
I love you, too.
You're getting harder.
I can't help it.
Do you want me to hold you?
Yes, I do.
I bought this for you.
Oh, thank you.
You'll be able to play with this.
Yes, I will.
So wear this and play.
Okay.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm sorry.
Let's play a lot.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Get on my back.
I'll get on your back and move.
Wait a minute.
I'll lick you first.
Where should I lick you?
Here.
I'm embarrassed.
Get off me.
I don't care.
I'm embarrassed.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
I'm embarrassed.
I feel good when you lick me like that.
I feel good.
I'm embarrassed.
I'll make you feel better.
I'll lick you.
I'm embarrassed.
I'll make you feel better.
Do you feel good?
I can't stand it.
I'll put you in.
I feel good.
It's moving.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
I want you to feel good.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I feel good.
I'll put you in.
I can't stand it.
I love you.
Why are you coming here?
Shut up!
I'm sorry.
I was cleaning the room.
I can hear you because the wall is thin.
It's hard for you to stay like this.
I can do it quietly with my mouth.
I'll put you in.
It's hard for you.
Don't push yourself.
It's the first time I've done it with my mouth.
I don't know what to do.
How do you feel?
You're getting bigger.
I'm going to sleep.
You're so cute.
How do you feel?
You look like you like this.
You look like you're in pain.
You're in pain.
It's all right.
Watch out!
It's delicious.
Can I do this one more time?
It's hot.
Thank you for the meal.
Hiroshi.
We decided to make a rule.
It's not going to rain today, is it?
No.
I'm going to be late for school.
It's hot.
Hiroshi.
Kiss me more.
It's hot.
Can I touch you a lot?
Touch me a lot.
Okay.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Can I touch you directly?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Does it hurt?
It feels good.
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
Can I lick you a lot?
It's hot.
Did you want to be with me forever?
That's right.
It's hot.
I wanted to lick you a lot.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I have no choice but to lick you.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Thank you.
Do you want to feel better?
Look behind you.
I'll lick you, too.
Behind me?
I'm embarrassed.
It's okay.
It's hot.
Please stick out your butt more.
More?
It's hot.
I'm embarrassed.
It's okay.
It's hot.
I'm embarrassed.
You want to feel better, don't you?
It's hot.
I want to feel better.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
It's okay.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I feel good when I see you.
I can't see your face in this costume.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Please show me your face.
I want to put you in the costume.
I'll put you in the costume.
I want you to put me in the costume.
It's hot.
Do you have a fever?
I'm fine.
My grandparents are not here.
I want you to put me in the costume.
I don't want to.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I want you to put me in the costume.
It feels good.
Give me a kiss.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I like you.
I want you to be closer to me.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Do you want me to hold you like this?
I'll make you more nervous.
It feels good.
I can't do this.
It hurts.
Don't get too excited.
You can hear me if I get too excited.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I like you.
I can't do this.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I can't do this.
I can't stand up.
Give me a kiss.
It hurts.
It felt good.
But I don't want to see your face.
You're so naive.
My face?
Am I that good-looking?
Weather forecast.
Next week, Japan will be hit by a strong typhoon.
Heavy rain and strong winds are expected in various places.
It is expected to be careful when going out.
The typhoon is very big.
The air pressure in the center is 930 hPa.
The maximum wind speed near the center is 50 meters.
The maximum wind speed at the moment is 70 meters.
It's 50 meters per hour.
I can't do this.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I can't do this.
I feel good.
How do you feel?
I can't do this.
I love being petted.
I love being petted, too.
Look at me.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I'm so tired.
I can't do this.
I love you.
It's all right.
I'm sorry.
You're amazing, Kikuchi.
Shut up.
I'll get you some water.
Kikuchi...
No, no.
No.
Kikuchi...
You're amazing, Kikuchi.
You're amazing...
Kikuchi...
You're amazing.
Take it.
It seems like you should go more deeper.
Look at the stairs.
I'm so happy.
Big brother, what's this?
Big brother...
I'll do it again.
It's okay.
Let me see.
Okay.
Ouch!
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
It's so hot.
Did you get a fever?
It's okay.
I'll clean your feet.
What?
Clean my feet?
I didn't do it on purpose.
You're so energetic.
I'm sorry.
It's so hot.
Big brother, do you love me?
Yes, I love you.
It's so hot.
You're so energetic.
It feels so good.
Big brother, do you feel good?
Yes, I do.
It feels so good.
Big brother, do you feel good?
Yes, I do.
It's so hot.
I want to see you feel better.
Let me see.
It's so hot.
Big brother, you're amazing.
You're sweating a lot.
It feels so good.
You're so energetic.
It's so hot.
Let me see.
Do you want me to let you see?
It's so hot.
I love you.
I love you, too.
It's so hot.
I'm hungry.
Let's do it again.
Take off the rubber band.
This is the last one.
You have to cherish it.
Do you want to kiss me?
Yes, I do.
Do you really want to kiss me?
I love you.
I love you, too.
Can I kiss you from behind?
I don't want to wear that.
You wore it a lot the other day.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Don't wear that.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're sweating a lot.
Don't wear that.
You're so mean.
It hurts.
You're sweating a lot.
Do you want to kiss me from behind?
I'm sorry.
I want to wipe your face.
I like this posture the most.
I love you.
It hurts.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I love you.
Say it while looking at me.
Can I look at you?
No, you don't have to.
I love you.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm going to cry.
That was painful, wasn't it?
You don't have to cry.
I love you.
That was painful, wasn't it?
That aoyage...
I don't like this...
Enough
Here, take this
Damn, this is bad
I love it
Big Brother, can you hold on?
I love this
Big Brother
Ouch!
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
I love you.
I love you too.
It's okay.
I love you.
I love you too.
Oh, my gosh.
It's so hot.
It felt so good.
I love you.
I love you too.
The typhoon has passed.
I can't move anymore.
By the way, what do you like about me?
Well...
Don't mess with me. Answer me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
We've been together since we were born.
But...
I want to protect you.
I want to look after you forever.
Do you think so?
You're so cool.
Right? You can praise me more.
I like your face.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
Am I that handsome?
I don't think it's that bad.
Right?
No, it's not that.
Dad and Mom died in an accident.
You must have had a hard time, too.
You've been watching over me all the time.
I love your kind face.
I see.
We're similar.
Good morning.
Do you want to eat bread today?
I think so.
I'll bring some bread.
You just woke up.
It's okay.
I'm going.
I...
I don't regret it anymore.
No matter what happens, I'll always be with her.
Always.
I love you.