Tomo-kun, welcome back.
Good evening.
Are you going out?
Yes, I'm going to buy dinner.
See you later.
Yes.
He is happy because his son is running around.
Well...
I'm still in the middle of cleaning up.
I want to lick her boobs and nipples.
I want to suck them.
I want to pat her butt.
I want to have sex with her.
I want to get her pregnant.
She's out.
My husband is jealous.
Why don't you have kids?
It's been 3 years since you got married.
Maybe you didn't get along with your husband.
I don't care.
Tomo-kun.
You're just in time.
Yes.
Can you do me a favor?
A favor?
I forgot to ask my husband to record this.
I'm not good at glasses.
I'm just going to put the program on the screen and choose.
You can do it easily.
Ma'am.
You knew it.
What?
You knew Tomo-kun was looking at you.
Ouch.
Come on.
You have to lick more.
Yes.
Ouch.
Welcome.
Your boobs are in front of me.
I don't want you to record this.
Tomo-kun was the target from the beginning.
Look.
Tomo-kun was looking at my boobs every day.
You can do whatever you want.
Your boobs are in front of me.
But my husband...
It's okay.
He doesn't care about me at all.
He's working today.
Don't worry.
Ma'am.
I'm sorry, Tomo-kun.
I'm sorry.
What do you think of this side?
What?
This is the butt of an old lady I used to watch on Iaraseam every day.
You have a lot of power.
Are you sleepy?
You're about to puke.
Let's put you to sleep.
Come on, take it off.
You're so young, but you're so slender.
Let's get started.
You're amazing.
You're so young, but you're so slender.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's okay, Tomo.
You're amazing.
You're so young, but you're so slender.
Let's continue in bed.
Tomo.
Is this the first time you've seen a woman?
Yes, it's the first time I've seen a woman.
I'll show you.
Take a closer look.
It's a dangerous day today, so please do this for me.
I'm sorry.
Then, please sleep there.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to be afraid.
I'll gently brush your hair.
Are you ready?
I'll start.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't reach you.
You were wrapped up in me.
This is sex.
You're amazing.
You're so cute.
I'm sorry.
Congratulations on your graduation.
You're wrapped up in me.
You're so beautiful.
Look at the inside.
You're wrapped up in me.
Tomo.
We're just getting started.
It's been a while since I had sex.
I'm going to skip a little bit.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I didn't move that much.
Wait.
I can feel the force of your body.
I can feel it even through the rubber.
You have a great voice.
Did you feel good inside?
If you didn't have a rubber band, you could have done it in one go.
You have a great voice.
Did you come back to life?
I haven't told you yet.
You can still enjoy it.
I want to have sex with you.
I want to have real sex with you.
You said it earlier.
Of course, I want to enjoy it.
I want to have sex with you.
You are a bad boy.
You can have sex with me.
Really?
If you feel like it, you should go out.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can still feel it.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
I want to put you in the bath.
I can't.
I want to make you angry.
Please get pregnant.
I can't.
What are you saying?
Wait.
Please get on my back.
I can't.
Masaharu.
It's hot.
I can't.
Masa.
I can still do it.
I just got out of the bath.
I want to make you angry.
I told you.
It's a dangerous day.
But I can't stand it anymore.
It's hot.
I'm going to puke.
I'm going to make Masaharu puke.
It's hot.
I can't calm down.
I'm going to make Masaharu puke.
It's hot.
You're a great warrior.
You can do this.
I can still do it.
I'm going to make Masaharu puke.
It's hot.
I didn't know sex was such a pleasant thing.
No!
It's hot.
I'm going to make Masaharu puke.
No!
It's hot.
I'm going to make Masaharu puke.
What are you doing?
Mom, what are you doing?
Today is the only day I don't see my husband.
I want to have more sex with you.
No, you had a lot of sex a while ago.
It's not enough yet.
Hey, you can't do that.
Hey, let me go.
You don't feel good, do you?
I didn't ask you to do that.
I want to have more sex with you.
Hey, listen to me.
Say to him, please let me go.
Hey, please listen to me.
Stop it.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Hey, look at me in the mirror.
Please…
I don't know what to do.
I'm tired.
You did a lot of exercises.
I'm tired, so please let me go.
I'm tired.
I understand. I'll give you a mouthful.
Is that okay?
Yes.
I'll give you a mouthful.
I feel good when you give me a mouthful.
I understand.
I'll give you a mouthful.
Why are you so energetic?
I've always wanted to do this with you.
I feel good when you give me a mouthful.
I understand.
What are you doing all of a sudden?
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Don't hit me so hard.
Wait a minute.
You just hit me, didn't you?
You hit me too hard.
Wait a minute.
Don't hit me so hard.
Why is it so hard?
Because I like you.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
Wait a minute.
It feels good.
Don't do that.
It's annoying.
Did you make a lot of money?
I want to make more money.
Do you want to make more money?
Don't do that.
It feels good.
I want to make more money.
Don't do that.
It's annoying.
It feels good.
Don't do that.
It's annoying.
I can't stop thinking about you.
You were such a good girl.
You've been healthy all the time.
Let's take a bath.
You're so dirty.
What should I do?
Wait a minute.
Don't do that.
I'm lonely.
Can I get up?
I'm in the bath.
Wait a minute.
Don't do that.
Oh, I see.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
I'm human.
I can't believe I'm a human.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
My breast feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's cold.
It's hot.
My breast is twitching.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
My breast is twitching.
are frustrated and can't control their boredom.
Boredom to you?
No!
Leave it...
Some water.
Better.
Why!?
New toy?
You're checking on her, aren't you?
Right.
The day will come,
so hurry and say
you want to go to an even moores,
so she won't be lonely.
Roman-kun.
Please.
Let's go home today.
Why do you think
Well, I can't go, can I?
Miwa-san, your shoulders are stiff.
I'll give you a massage.
Hey!
It's okay.
I don't need it.
You must be tired.
I don't need it. You should go home.
It's okay.
I'll give you a little more massage.
Hey, Tomo-kun.
Don't you need a massage?
I'll give you a little more.
Hey.
Hey, what are you doing?
I don't need it.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
I want to do it again with you.
What?
I'm begging you.
You said you were begging me, but you did a lot.
I was thinking about you.
My heart...
I can't hold it.
I want to do more with you.
I want you to be satisfied with me.
I said I don't need it.
Hey, Tomo-kun.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
I'll give you a little more.
I said I don't need it.
You want to do more, don't you?
I'm sorry.
I said I don't need it.
You feel better, don't you?
I'll make you feel better.
I'm sorry.
I want to sleep with you.
I said I don't need it.
I can't help it.
Did you do this because you wanted to sleep with me?
You're a bad boy.
Does your mouth feel good?
If you think it feels good, I can't help it.
Is that so?
It feels so good.
You're shivering.
Do you like this?
No, not yet.
No.
I want to get out of here.
Then you have to put up with it.
No, don't do that.
I'm going to put up with it.
You were able to put up with it.
I want to put you in my arms.
It's the best.
It's amazing.
I'll never forget this.
I'll make you feel better.
It's the best.
I'm going to get out of here.
It tickles.
I'm going to make you feel better.
No, no, no.
I can't stand it anymore.
It tickles.
Here?
It's twitching.
It tickles.
I'm going to make you feel better.
Show me your butt.
You want me to do something, don't you?
It's all in my butt.
It tickles.
You want me to make you feel better, don't you?
I can't do it.
I'll make you angry.
Wait a minute.
Give birth to my child.
Don't say that.
I can't do it.
I'll get angry.
Let's go to the bedroom.
I can't do it.
Wait a minute.
Let's go to the bedroom.
I can't do it.
I want to see your face.
Let's go!
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to throw up all of a sudden.
How much did you throw up?
Do you still have a fever?
I'm sorry.
That's great.
You threw up a lot.
Do you throw up a lot?
That's great.
I'm sorry.
You still have a fever.
You're a healthy baby.
Don't do that.
Welcome back, Tomo.
I'm back.