Announcement by Mr.
Announcement by Staff.
by Mr.
Sorry to call in suddenly.
Actually
Always
I am interested in your work.
I love you and I love you, please come with me.
Look at it, Mimi, she is still in the process.
My class number one is, of course, a big deal.
Mimiya, I’m not going to make a boyfriend at all, if I were my boyfriend, I’t have to get that breast first.
Do not stop saying bad things.
No, I said that.
What kind of cup of breast do you think?
I do not know that.
G or H is said.
How about it.
I want to sell your breast now.
I am back in class, so I will start.
Then is
Sorry to
What I just heard was that...
Forget it.
Oh, I am so fucking attracted.
I did it.
But if I look again.
You are a cute idol.
In addition, the first memory of that teaching milk, the popularity of dance is incredible.
The breast?
Why do you get your breasts off?
Oh, oh, the crap is getting bigger.
Their breasts are pink and full.
and Elo
Only the last one, 2.
Oh yeah
Break it in 3.
Not to see.
I cannot take my eyes.
About the numbers.
Serious knowledge.
Let me tell you.
Oh, the camel
Say the correct six-digit number.
Is it six numbers?
2 and 3, 6.
No camouflage
My number is zero.
Now zero is not zero.
1 3 5
I told you that you would break up with them three.
But not broken.
I just said that I can break by six.
If I get this number, I will break it by 6.
So, whether it will break by 7 or not, this is already difficult, so please split it straight.
If it is broken by eight, or if it is broken by eight of the three digits of the Lord, it is broken by eight.
If you divide this by 8 to 7 and up to 72 by 8, this number is divided by 8.
Q. I broke it, and I broke it.
The Q broke in this, I believe in it.
Yes, I am doing this too.
Dump and get it.
Yes to.
You are always coming somewhere.
So I made class care for students.
Production is comfortable.
Both are class members.
It is easy with Mimi.
Welcome to
I have no time, so I will do it sooner.
More than!
Do you take care?
Wait a moment, sir.
So suddenly
A little
Not just you and two of you.
I can’t think of Lessing at all.
Whatever it is.
It is too much, sir.
What is so great.
That cat is so cute.
It is a cat, right?
Sorry to sorry.
well was
Yesterday was a mistake.
Forget to
Let us do.
by you
What is it? 😂😂
How was it?
My breast.
Oh well
About what?
Excited... was it?
Did you see it? did you see it?
Oh that?
He said he was excited.
I am ashamed to say I have not taken it out.
Is it different?
Oh, oh, that is
Was it annoying?
No so is.
I was fucking excited.
Honestly, I want to see it again!
So see it?
yet another time.
Oh, Mr. What is it?
No, not in this place.
No, no, it is near.
Oh sorry!
Hardly
I want to see, it wasn’t a lie.
Okay, no to no.
In my case, what?
Can I argue?
Okay, it is not going to decrease.
Can I really touch it?
What about my breasts?
Oh, it is big and tight, but it is very soft.
The colour of chickens.
is beautiful.
Elo
Oh yeah
I think that is very attractive.
Here and here.
It is
It is clean.
by Mr. O.
I touched my breasts.
Oh yeah
Is it so?
A little bit, Mr.
A little, it is
Not to be shrimp.
Hardly
It looks soft and soft first.
It is fun.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Do you prefer to be wet?
Okay, but I’m dressed here.
Good here, well here.
A little more wet.
I will wet it a little.
Full of stomach.
The bread bread.
The breadmaker.
such an erratic appearance.
They are touched.
As a front.
becomes more and more hard.
Do it faster.
Look at a little.
Oh yeah yeah.
Tyson’s approach is bad.
It is bad, stay away.
was
by Heat
It is time.
You brought out.
No, but paint this part.
Yes I understand.
No to
I cannot concentrate at all.
They are both alone.
I don’t, but I remember yesterday.
Oh Oh Oh
Reduced
My shit.
thanks to
A little
See also Mr.
So that.
If you are so tightly attached.
Oh...
by Pite
But...
Or to put it inside.
Okay, go in and go out.
Sorry, that...
I like to do it.
No good though.
I like to do it myself too.
End this now.
No to
A cute face.
Show me more.
I don’t know if you see.
I missed it.
Come, come and come
very much
Suffering and Suffering.
Great
Oh guys.
Next is the top.
Are you still there?
by Rush
Because I did it with the desire to live.
It has become tragic.
Sorry to
It is my fault.
No, it is because of your own.
Yes, even before that.
Why is it that you are, not Evan?
Will you do these things?
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry
I am in a hurry, sorry.
Okay, I am too big.
I am late in class.
OK is OK.
I would rather leave someone in trouble.
It is harder late.
First, you can say I was hit.
That is too much.
Wait a little, I’ll open it now.
Secretly
with the previous time.
How to get revenge in mathematics?
Do you remember the square?
What was it?
The Square Root.
Route 4 is
2nd
You know it.
Then
What is Route 3?
Route 3
If I opened.
See also
See also Mr.
Route 3
Bad to know.
In positive numbers?
1.5 is
is appropriate.
Route 3 is
5 is
by Mr.
No to no.
Route 2 is
1 is
4 is
A little bit.
Sleeping is bad.
I don’t know, I don’t know.
What is
Oh yeah yeah
Oh is
Be calmly.
Definitely
Meaning not doing.
Before and What?
Oh,
Can’t you guys?
Try it here.
Not enough study.
No, it is hard to help.
So, can’t you be with them?
No, this is no.
So I will study.
Well guys.
Really really
guys a little.
Two or two, though.
Stand by
Next week in Taiwan.
Now announce it.
Oh yeah
Please, if you
Come to warm up.
Is it delicious?
coldly
Strongly
Do not do so hard.
Oh yeah...
Hahahahah...
No, it...
Ha ha ha...
I stopped a little.
Oh well rack!
Ariana is dead.
Sorry to sorry.
Are you listening to a lesson?
Oh is
Do you listen to the concierge?
Yes, I am sorry
Where did you go? where did you go?
Oh, and so on.
Where did you go?
See also Mr.
Yes Yes
Did Chris get out of it?
No problem, he too.
So, right and right answers.
Please go.
Yes, I am sorry
How do you exercise?
What to exercise?
2, 3, 4
and here
5, 4, 3, 4, 1, 4, 1 and 5
3, 4, 1, 4, 1 and 5
1.2 The
by
A little guys.
Gentlemen are
by
Oh well
Professor something.
The curry is broken and I will take you to the health room.
The decoding?
Something already...
Are you okay, Mimi?
Mimi, I won’t be studying this.
I am disturbing...
No, it is not a hassle.
I am a little sick now.
If someone sees you, I know.
We sleep warm, guys.
Feels good?
Very good feeling.
greatly
Sorry to
Oh yeah yeah
Oh well
greatly
Would it be dirty?
Get out.
Yes
It is attached there.
Ladies and gentlemen, from here.
Can I sit again?
Oh, oh, oh oh oh oh oh
Not yet can.
I will sleep in my pants again.
Do not sleep, this.
Do not sleep, fast.
Go to go.
Because I do this.
and ECH
Mr. Khatcher is pretty much a bitch.
Because you do this.
Yes
Oh yeah
sweetly
Oh is
by
Oh, and push it up.
No to
Here, here is
Yes
What do you do.
You love this, you love the meat.
I like it.
How is?
It is soft.
be big.
I have a hold.
Have it in hand.
See me too?
First of all...
Eat it yesterday.
To Heck?
Oh well...
If you have...
What kind of girl?
by Kareem
Not yet, I am going in.
Oh yeah
This is FU.
Late to be struck.
I am in the wicked.
Yes is
I will do it to you too.
Oh yeah
I will give you more.
This is
What will happen?
I cannot endure.
Can you endure?
You have to be patient.
No to no.
Oh, oh...
The knee sound.
No...
Oh oh...
No to...
Oh to!
Oh well...
by
by JJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJJ
Oh
Not yet
↑ to ↑
↑ is ↑
that 🙂
is ↓
↑ to ↑
No to?
Oh
It comes
No to
Do you want to get out of me?
and so
You want to go out.
But
Someone really comes.
So somehow.
within this
You can be spotted.
No to
I get in.
Feels good?
Totally
Now this way.
Yes
I went in.
Gee
No to say.
No, if it is so hard, I will say.
Not yet
Oh well go.
by Dude
Oh yeah
Kind like yet.
Dad has gone.
Dad was playing.
See also
Great is
O O O O O O O O O O O O
See also
It is great.
Where to go.
Oh, oh oh
Oh to!
No flowers yet.
Without doing anything.
go out
Oh to!
I slept a lot.
Wait for me, Mimi.
Sensitive
Oh yeah
by
by Mr.
Come to
Come here and here.
See also
Great is
I was a hit.
You can lick.
Oh yeah
Oh yeah, I was gone.
Fuck it.
Do you want to enter?
I want to enter.
Yes
Then
Put it in.
Yes
Oh is
I like these things.
well well.
I too
Yes to?
Liked it
He is hungry.
Oh well fucking.
Reed to me.
Yes
I am feeling bad.
What we did.
Because of me.
Is it my fault?
Okay okay.
That is my fault.
Oh well I will.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh.
Sorry to sorry.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Wait a little, wait a little.
Yes is.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
I will enter.
I’ll give it again, it’s not too fast.
Oh no no no.
Oh oh oh
No to
Why is?
What to do?
It feels good in your house.
I want to see your face.
I want to stand.
together with us.
No more
Already together.
together from now on.
It tastes good.
Good night I will give you.
Come to
Oh well!
Oh yeah...
Oh well...
No, no sir...
How to do?
Oh is?
No to?
Oh well sir...
No to no.
No longer...
I have to go home.
Everyone...
I will find out.
by Rush
Oh yeah!? to
Oh to!? to
See also Mr.
I will hinder.
No matter
My house and his room are like this.
Something strange?
Yes, something
I think she looks like a girl.
All of you take a picture.
Yes
by
This is the girl’s room.
Oh yeah yeah
This is
Oh my sister.
Oh, my dear, I use this.
Oh yeah
Oh yeah yeah?
Oh no, this one.
Sorry, I fell here.
I left it as I used it yesterday.
This and this?
Yes
Do you use this?
Yes, it is mine.
Yes
Sorry, but I used this.
Will you try this too?
Oh is?
You care about it, right?
I care, but what?
Oh, a little
Oh is?
How do you think to use this?
Family medication
do this here.
I am interested.
Yes
How is?
I mean difficult.
Let’s check out a little more?
Oh yeah
Does not hurt?
It actually doesn’t hurt.
Do you like that?
Go to?
See also
I see this letter.
This is?
Then
Oh yeah
How is?
I always use this.
Because I am...
Mimi is very much a bit of a bitch.
Yes to.
I honestly don’t know so much about Mimi.
There is such a side.
Are you happy?
A little pleased.
I will make you stronger.
Or it is better to be weak.
Mimi is a mutant.
Something I care about a little.
Break a bit.
I will leave it in the room.
Okay is?
Oh, no can
Really got out.
Gentlemen are
A little, it happened.
Do not go.
Have you been?
Do not be merciful.
How was this?
Do it again.
No to
No to?
Is it okay?
Because I stood up.
smelled
Why is it smelling?
It smells.
Can you bring it to the cake again?
A little around.
Just got out now.
See it?
A little, I see it.
It is awesome.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
It has become increasingly tough.
Is it so?
See also
Painted on my finger.
How is?
No to
Yes is
Oh is?
Awaken a little.
Next, do you want me to feel good?
You are not white, you like it.
Oh, I like you.
Then good.
This, which
It feels good.
Wherever you are, it feels good.
here and here.
here here?
Feel good
Yes
by Mimi
You are saying an enormous voice.
But you like it, right?
So really.
Yes
Do you always do this?
It is doing.
Yes
Yes, it feels good.
More...
More strongly?
Yes
What do you think and do these things?
Why not?
No to
I want to know about you and yours.
I always know.
Feel good
It is so.
Oh yeah yeah
Oh,
and well
Oh, oh
Yes
hardly
by M.
Oh, oh
Oh, you are a lot of picky.
More to more.
More of?
Not enough though.
Can I guess directly?
First from here.
Yes
Oh oh oh oh oh
Path prevention and direct, which one to do.
Feel good
Directly
Oh oh oh oh oh
Oh oh oh
If it were a crystal.
What will happen.
Will break up.
Can I guess?
guess it.
Not to be scared.
I will stop now.
The Cat Voice.
It is shit.
Feel good
It feels good.
Stay there, he is cute.
About the cat.
not stop.
Feel good
Back to the cat.
Oh yeah yeah
Oh well, oh well
by YHWH
Stay still on.
I go, I go, I go
Oh to!
Oh is
greatly
Great time is.
Yes
Oh yeah
More and more.
Look in here.
You are a big shit today.
Are you excited?
Oh yeah
Two people in private with Mr. Mackey.
by Tatarata
Soon to
Suddenly tough.
Is it hard?
But you can’t go yet.
Oh well...
Great is
Feeled...
Mrs Paris...
More than usual...
I am doing it.
Yes
hurtly
Are you deliberately closing it?
Did you find out?
If you kill...
Can you go up?
Oh...
A little...
Great is
Beautifully on the other side.
Paris is too much.
You can feel so much on your face.
It feels good if you are no longer moving.
Fuck it, Fuck it.
A little, a little
sweetly
You guys, I can’t resist.
cute is
A cute face.
Do not say that.
I am ashamed.
Oh, a little
A little more.
A little
Oh, oh
Why so much... today?
Will you hate?
I will not hate.
Then bye!
It is great!
It is different when you are in class.
What is
I can only see such faces.
Such a cook.
If you are active.
Yes is.
Oh that.
Oh well, awesome
Great Grigory.
Feel good
It feels good tooth.
is bad
bad bad bad bad bad
Can not anymore?
Great is now.
I have never seen such a man.
I like to get that messy too.
What do you want?
I want to start from the top, I want to get tired.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh oh oh oh
They are doing one.
But it is awesome here too.
such a face.
No to?
by M.
Oh a little.
A little
Oh oh oh oh
It will break down in the synth.
Can not break?
Oh, oh
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
I like a lot.
Mrs. Mimi is a big guy.
I think it will expand.
I am very happy.
When they live, no one can return.
Full of Mimi.
Touched a lot.
Only me.
by Big
Do you like me too?
I like it.
really is?
Do you like the breast?
Do not happen.
I also like my breasts.
The one I love.
It is Miss.
pleased
How is?
OK is
I love you.
I love
The Cat
touching it once.
Put it out within me.
This is FU.
OK is OK.
Go, go, go and go.
I want spirit.
That and more.
I want more.
What to do.
here here
Love me.
About us
Because you already know.
What do you think?
How about?
Focus on me now.
I like the quick.
I have confessed to many people.
You will love me the most.
I am not interested in anything except Quicksilver.
OK is OK.
It is Berry.
Only me, Mr Raven.
I love it too! I love it too! I love it too!
I go, because I will go.
Go, go, go and go
Very awesome.
Really like it.
of body.
than what
I love you and me like this.
Full of.
Liked it
pleased
It feels bad.
You may feel it, it is cute.
He is cute too.
I am ashamed to say that.
Full of stomach.
I am hungry, I am going.
Feel better.
Full of stomach.
something is great.
It is biking.
Daddy
by
No so because.
I think you are feeling bad already.
are together.
Daddy
Dad, let’s get upset.
That is FU.
This way you can feel better.
Come to
Liked it
by Phuo
by
Oh yeah
Let us go here.
I really want to make you feel good.
Come to
Yes yes
No see.
by
How about.
I like to put on my clothes.
Yes
No, it is the best.
I am in PAH.
Great is
See also
How is?
I love going in.
My only breasts.
Yes is it.
Oh well, here is it.
Try to keep curry.
Let me be crap.
It slips very well.
It looks like a mango.
Moving a lot.
Happy is
I am so happy to be able to do this with someone I like.
I am pleased.
I like it.
I like too.
Wait, wait, wait, I said I should feel better, but I didn’t say I should.
I want to go out.
No, no, no more no longer no longer.
But you don’t work hard.
Still, I will tell you in your mouth.
In the mouth?
All of you, your mouth, your breasts, and the middle, are fine.
You are great body.
Oh yeah yeah
Oh oh oh oh
Oh well heavily.
Oh yeah
I want to go out again.
Then
empty again.
More than your mouth or chest.
Better inside.
well inside.
Put more behind.
Looking at a lot.
How about.
More full of.
I understand
It is increasingly filled.
by Mr. and Mr.
More and more.
I love it.
I want to feel more comfortable with yours.
I will cry.
My loved one is crying.
See also Mr.
I love too.
It hurts!
not enough
Still not enough.
Mr and Mrs.
There was a great Earl.
coldly
Yes
Strength to.
Eat inside again.
Yes
You are ready.
Do it.
mutantly
Yes
Liked it
Why is cute.
Yes
Once again, once more.
I will go.
Let us go again.
Oh go go go.
Oh yeah
Really
I really want.
Yes
But I too.
If you eat.
It really did.
I really want.
Woo
Today I have a mom and dad.
Oh yeah
What happened to.
What should I do?
Then
Go to wait?
Congratulations to you.