I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to die if I don't do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it
I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to die if I don't do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something
about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about
it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it, so I'm going to do something about it
.
There is a secret that my husband can never tell me about my relationship with my son, so
what are you doing
?
Isn't it that I was studying?
I couldn't concentrate on my studies because I had a headache.
You took it out once before dinner, didn't you?
No, but I don't think I took it out enough.
I'll give it to you again, so concentrate on your studies.
Yeah.
Well, please.
I feel sick.
Yeah.
Please take it out soon.
I don't want to do it anymore.
I'm in trouble.
My son seems to be hiding under the bed, but there are so many that I can see it.
You're an old man who's interested in that kind of thing.
Yeah.
He seems to be hiding in his room at night and doing naughty things.
I see.
Yeah.
This year is the year of the entrance exam, so I'm worried if I can study properly.
Is your family like this, Ma-kun?
My family?
My family is...
Well, let's see.
What should I do?
This is the only story.
Well...
What?
Are you processing your son's sexual desire?
Hey, you're too loud.
I'm sorry.
Well, I was surprised when I first heard it from people.
But when I actually processed my son's sexual desire, my grades went up.
Is that so?
By the way, Ma-kun.
You said that your grades suddenly went up recently.
Yeah.
My mother said that if I processed my son's sexual desire, I could concentrate on studying and my grades would go up.
It's quite famous among my friends.
It seems that Mr. Yoshida is also processing it.
Mr. Yoshida's house?
I'm sure it's the top of the year.
It's not a big deal at first, but once you get used to it, it's no big deal.
It's like a mother's job to process her son's sexual desire.
And if you give it to him, he'll be happy.
If you like, try it.
What?
Well...
I don't know about my family.
Yeah.
It's a mother's job to process her son's sexual desire.
I'm used to it now and I do it every day.
Hurry up and take it off.
You'll be late.
I know.
Ah...
It doesn't come out.
How about this?
What?
Ah...
You'll be sensitive if you hold your eyes down like this, right?
Come on, don't move.
My body moves on its own.
Ah...
How about this?
It's harder than before.
Ah...
You can't get it out with this, can you?
I'll do it like this.
Ah...
Hurry up and take it off.
How about this?
Ah...
What is that?
Sure.
What about me then?
Your heart
is getting very warm.
What are you doing?
Wow, you have a lot of gold.
What's that?
If you're so full, you can't go fast.
Wow, it's hard.
Does this feel good?
Yeah.
You haven't been able to go fast lately, have you?
I can go fast if I have a sore throat.
If you have a sore throat every time, your mother will get tired.
Can I touch your boobs?
I can't help it because I do it every day.
You like boobs, don't you?
Yes.
I'll continue.
Just do it as it is today.
You said you wanted to drink.
I want to drink.
I never thought I'd have to sit next to you again.
I'm sorry.
Don't suck so hard.
If you do that, you won't be able to continue.
I'm sorry.
You'll be late.
Get up.
Let's do it with your mother's boobs today.
That's a little fresher, isn't it?
With my boobs?
Get on my lap.
How is it?
This side, too.
You have blood on your neck.
How about this?
It's in your boobs.
How is it?
It's getting hotter.
How about this?
It feels good.
How does it feel?
I'll pinch your boobs.
Pinch?
How about this?
Is this right?
It feels good.
This feels good?
I'll pinch your boobs.
How does it feel?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll pinch harder.
Harder?
It's hard.
It feels good.
I can't see your boobs.
How is it?
Slowly.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's really hard.
Does your boobs excite you that much?
It feels good.
How is it?
I think you can breathe easier.
I'm a little tired.
I'm going to sleep.
Lean on me.
Use your boobs as you like.
Move them as you like.
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
Your boobs are really soft and it feels good.
Really?
Move them as you like.
I'm going to sleep.
Mom.
You look really sad.
Don't look at your mom's face.
If you look at her face too much, you'll be embarrassed.
I'm going to sleep.
It's amazing.
I can see that your boobs are moving.
It's like I'm touching your mom's boobs.
I'm going to sleep.
Use your boobs as you like.
Is this okay?
It feels good.
Move them as you like.
I'm going to hold you.
I'm going to sleep.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
It's amazing.
Use your boobs as you like.
I'm going to sleep.
It's amazing.
Don't move your face.
It's hard to wash your face.
I'm sorry.
I have to go to school.
I'm going to be late.
See you later.
Mom.
Please.
Can't I do it now?
I'm doing laundry.
I have a lot of housework.
Can't I do it tomorrow?
I haven't done anything since this morning.
So, I'm nervous.
So, please.
I'm going to be late.
Please.
I can't do it today.
I have to do it tomorrow.
Please.
I can't do it.
Hey.
I'm going to be late.
I can't do it.
Please.
You can do it, right?
I can't do it.
I told you I can't do it.
If you can't do it, you can't concentrate on your study.
Hey.
Please.
I got it.
What?
I'm going to take it out with my mouth.
Really?
I feel sorry for you if I don't do it.
Do you feel better if I do it once?
I'm going to study hard tonight.
I can't do it.
Are you okay?
I want to lick the tip of my tongue.
I can't help it.
I can't do it.
Do you like it?
I feel good.
I'm drooling.
Do you want me to do it?
Yes.
I feel good.
Don't you go out yet?
Mom.
Can I sleep with you?
We had sex yesterday.
I want to sleep with you.
Okay.
Do you have a condom?
Wait a minute.
I can't help it.
I brought it.
Put it on.
I put it on.
Sleep here.
I'll put it on you.
You are very big.
I put it on.
I feel good.
You are very hard.
I've been shaking all the time.
I can't help it.
I feel good.
If you want to go, take it out.
Mom.
I want to shake more.
You are selfish.
I can't help it.
I feel good.
You are harder than before.
Does it feel better to do it live?
What are you talking about?
You can't.
Do you understand?
I feel good.
You are very big.
I can't help it.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Which one do you feel good?
I forgot that I had sex with you.
You haven't done it for a long time.
Show me more.
Like this?
Look at me.
I feel more than before.
I feel good.
Why?
This is hard.
This is like your ass.
I understand.
You like your mother's legs, don't you?
I'm going to sleep.
Look at me.
I like your mother's legs.
If you study hard, I'll let you use it as much as you want.
It's amazing.
There's a lot of light in there.
Hurry up and take it out.
There's a lot of light in there, isn't there?
I'm going to sleep.
I'm sleepy.
I feel good.
I'm going to sleep.
You're sleeping, aren't you?
Oh no, oh no!
Help us!
Feels acrophobous, doesn't it?
It feels so good.
Take out the painkillers.
I know, but...
Mom, does it feel good?
It feels so good.
I'm going to puke.
You can see the hole in my butt well, right?
It's so bad.
I can't breathe properly.
I'm going to puke.
Look closely.
It's so intense.
It's so hard.
How do I move this?
You haven't taken it out yet.
I'm going to puke.
You should take it out, too.
It feels so good.
It feels so good, right?
I'm going to call my dad.
Dad?
Hello? Dad?
What's wrong?
Stop it.
Hello?
It's nothing.
Work?
It's already over?
You said you'd be late today, didn't you?
I see.
Thank you for your hard work.
Dinner?
You said you'd be late.
I didn't make it.
What do you want to eat?
I'll make something easy for you.
It's nothing.
I'll make you a drink.
I'm sorry.
It's nothing.
I was a little nervous.
Be careful on your way home.
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
I didn't do it on purpose.
Are you coming home?
I'll be home soon.
What should I do?
I heard you finished work early.
I have to go out soon.
What should I do?
What?
Why?
It can't be helped.
It's special today.
Drink it raw.
Are you sure?
You wanted to drink it raw.
You can drink it raw.
What?
What are you going to do?
Are you going to quit?
If you don't do it soon, your father will come home.
I'll do it.
Oh, my God.
It's disgusting.
My mom's body is...
It's slimy.
It's not good.
It's very hard.
It's warm.
It feels good.
Don't let it out.
It's hot.
It's different from when I put on rubber.
It feels good.
What's wrong?
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
It's disgusting.
It's hot.
Your father will come home.
You should go home soon.
It feels so good that I can't do anything.
Don't do it.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good that I can't do anything.
Don't do it.
Go home soon.
It feels good.
I can't do anything.
Don't do it.
If you keep doing it, you'll get sick.
I'll do everything for you.
It feels good.
But I'll do it only today.
Ah...
It's so intense...
It's like my belly is gonna pop out...
Give me a hand...
No, it's a special power...
We can't save him.
Help me!
Help!
Slowly!
I'm glad I was able to do it today thanks to my mother.
Instead, study hard.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Then I'll go study.
You've been studying hard lately.
You seem to be motivated.
If I keep going like this, I might be able to pass the entrance exam.
The entrance exam?
Yes.
I'm going.
Dad.
I wanted to throw out the trash.
It was just right.
Can you throw out the trash?
Mom.
I have a mock exam today.
But I can't concentrate because I'm silent.
Can you take it off?
I have a rubber band.
I can't have sex because my mother's period has begun.
Come on.
Take it out.
If you don't hurry, you'll be late.
I know.
You're still big.
Hurry up and take it out.
Wait a minute.
You'll be late.
I know.
Sakura.
What?
Can you touch my nipples?
Nipples?
Why?
Because it feels good.
Is that so?
Nipples.
Here?
There.
Is this okay?
Your nipples are twitching.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
I didn't know you felt my nipples.
Ah.
Does this feel good?
Yes.
Ah.
It feels good.
Your nipples are twitching.
Yes.
Ah.
You like it when I touch your nipples.
Your nipples are twitching.
Ah.
Does this feel good?
Your nipples are twitching even more.
Ah.
Wow.
Your nipples are twitching even more.
Ah.
Hey.
What?
Your nipples.
I want you to lick them.
Eh.
Do you want me to lick them?
No?
It can't be helped.
Ah.
Does this feel good?
It feels good.
Really?
Ah.
Ah, I'm sorry.
I made your ears more and more crispy.
Let me appliances you.
Oh no!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Yeah
I'll lick your favorite nipple.
I feel sick.
How do you feel?
You're getting better and better.
I'll touch both of your nipples.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I feel sick.
I'm too nervous.
Don't do that.
What's this?
It's food.
It's hot.
You're getting hotter and hotter.
I feel sick.
Don't do that.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
I feel sick.
It's hot.
I'll make you wet.
Do you feel better?
Mom.
What?
I want you to lick my nipple.
I feel sick.
I can't help it.
Is this okay?
I feel sick.
It's hard.
Don't do that.
It's hot.
I want you to lick my nipple.
Don't do that.
Just touch my nipple.
It's hot.
I can't help it.
Open your mouth.
I'll lick your nipple.
How about this?
It's hot.
Mom.
What?
Show me your nipple.
My nipple?
Is this okay?
Show me more.
It's hot.
Is this okay?
I feel sick.
Show me your nipple.
It's hot.
How about this?
It's soft.
I feel sick.
It's hot.
It's soft, isn't it?
Your nipple is very hot.
It's hot.
I feel sick.
Is this okay?
It's hot.
Show me your nipple.
I feel sick.
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot today.
I'll give you some water.
It's hot.
Thank you.
If you don't hurry up, you'll be late.
I know.
You're late today, aren't you?
It's hot.
I'll get the garbage bag.
Okay.
See you later.
I'm going to do the laundry.
What's this?
Your grades are very low.
Your grades are not good enough to pass the entrance exam.
I can't concentrate on studying.
You have three months left until the exam.
I know.
Go to your room and study.
I want to pass the exam before that.
I know.
You were taking care of your son's sexual desire.
Hirano, you're talking too loud.
I'm sorry.
I see.
I thought you were a good person.
But...
My grades are getting better.
But, I was taking care of my sexual desire every day.
My grades started to drop again.
Every day?
Almost every day.
My son asks me to do it three times a day.
Don't do it too much.
Don't do it three times a day.
Do it once or twice a month as a reward.
Other mothers do it, too.
You're right.
Maybe I did it too much.
I'm home.
Are you studying hard?
I can't concentrate on studying.
Can I tell you something today?
Did you buy a book?
No, I didn't.
Why?
I'll think about it if I get good grades.
I won't do it until I get good grades.
Can I return it to its original state?
Yes.
I see.
I don't need it now.
I'll keep it.
I'm home.
That's great.
Your grades are going up again.
You did your best.
I've been studying hard for a month.
I see.
Keep up the good work.
Mom, do you remember our promise?
I remember it.
Mom...
I'm home.
Welcome home.
I'm tired.
Do you want to take a bath?
I'm hungry, so I'll eat first.
Then take a bath first.
I'm tired.
I'll prepare dinner.
Mom!
I'll wash your back.
Where's Dad?
He's eating dinner and watching TV.
Turn around.
Mom...
I'll wash your back.
What?
Why are you washing my back?
Don't you like it?
It feels good.
I'll wash your back.
How do you feel?
It's warm.
It's warm, isn't it?
Mom...
Turn around.
I'll wash your back.
You're sweating a lot.
I'll wash your back, too.
Mom...
Turn around.
I'll wash your back.
I'll wash your neck.
No.
Mom...
You're sweating a lot.
I'll put a lot of water on your back.
You've been holding back for a month.
That's why you're sweating a lot.
I'll clean your back.
You're sweating a lot.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll clean your back.
I'll put a lot of water on your back.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll put a lot of water on your back.
You're getting bigger and bigger.
Mom, look at me.
Do you like this?
It's hot.
I'm getting excited.
You're sweating a lot.
I'll wash your back.
I'll give you a bath as promised.
It feels good.
I haven't had a bath in a long time.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's been a month since I had a bath.
It feels good.
You're sweating a lot.
I'll do something more pleasant for you.
What are you doing?
Your buttocks are twitching.
What's wrong with you?
How do you feel?
It feels good, but I feel strange.
It's not good.
It's really not good.
You're very sensitive.
It's not good.
I'll lick you a lot.
You're sweating a lot again.
It's not good.
You're making a lot of noise.
It's embarrassing.
Mom, are you in there?
It's me.
How are you studying?
You're getting better at studying.
Yes, it's easy.
I heard from a doctor
that you were not scared.
What?
What about you?
I'll do my best.
I'm counting on you.
Mom, Dad is here.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
It hurts, doesn't it?
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You don't have a bath.
You can't take a bath today.
I can't?
Instead,
I'll make you feel better
I'll make you feel better.
I'm hitting my hips.
Mom.
What?
This feels good.
Let's take a bath.
No.
I told you.
You can't take a bath today.
You don't have a bath.
I can't?
Your hips feel good, don't they?
It feels good, but I want to take a bath.
Mom.
It feels good to rub my body.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'll rub your body.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
You like my hips, don't you?
I love your hips.
It feels good.
I'll rub your body harder.
You have a lot of sperm.
It feels good.
You should take the exam again.
But, that's difficult.
If you pass the exam,
you can have sex with me.
Do you really want to do that?
I'll do my best.
Do your best.
Mom.
I got a message from the university.
How did it go?
I'll open it now.
I'm nervous.
Oh!
I did it!
I got it!
Congratulations!
I did it!
I got it!
I did my best.
I'm so happy.
Mom.
Do you remember our promise?
Of course I remember.
Dad is not on a business trip today.
Mom.
It's hot.
Is there a lot of semen here?
I can't stand it anymore.
It's hot.
It's the first time to kiss you.
I'm so happy.
I want you to kiss me directly.
Look at me.
You have a lot of semen.
I can't stand it anymore.
I can feel your nipples.
I'm glad.
You like it, don't you?
Do you feel good?
Yes.
You're selfish.
I can't stand it anymore.
You have a lot of semen.
Look at me.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's hot.
It's hard.
It's big.
It's bigger than before, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Touch me a lot.
I love you.
It's soft.
Is it big?
You can do whatever you want.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's good.
Touch me a lot.
I can feel it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Touch me.
You're good at it.
It feels good.
Really?
It's hot.
Touch me.
It's okay.
It's hot.
Do you feel it?
You touched me.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It's getting hotter.
Touch me more.
More.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Can I touch you a lot?
Touch me.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Touch me.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Touch me.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's warm.
It feels good.
It's hot.
You did a good job.
Do you want to touch me more?
Let me touch you.
Let's do it together.
It's hot.
Do you want to touch me more?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'll do it more.
Make it harder.
It's hot.
It looks painful.
Do it more.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Do you want to touch me more?
It's hot.
It feels good.
Do you want to touch me more?
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'll do it more.
I'm so nervous.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'll do it more.
Feel it.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'll lick you.
You like this, don't you?
I like this.
I'll lick you.
It feels good.
I'll do it more.
Don't do that.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
What?
Today, I'm going to give you a pacifier.
I don't want to.
I want to.
It's okay.
Give me a pacifier.
I'm going to give you a pacifier.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's slimy inside.
I know.
It's slimy.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I know.
It feels good.
I'm going to give you a pacifier.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Give me more.
I'm going to give you a pacifier.
It's hot.
Give me a pacifier.
It feels good.
I can't.
I'm going to give you a pacifier.
I'm sorry.
It's the best.
It feels so good.
I'm so happy.
It tickles.
It feels so good.
More.
Give up already.
There, there, are you all right there?
You're all right....
This must end soon.
Hey, hey, don't do that.
I don't want to hurt you.
Aaaaaaaah...
Haa...
Aaaaah, I don't like this.
What should I do?
Aaaaah, my chest hurts a lot.
Aaaaargh...
...this is awful.
Aaaaaachk, it feels good.
Aaaaaaah!
This is needless.
Oh how cute!
It's amazing-
Don't press that part again!
Don't press this-
I want to do it more.
I'm going to sleep.
It feels good.
Let's go.
I'm going to sleep.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm so tired.
I've never felt so much sex.
It's my first time.
You can still do it.
Let me stand up.
I'm going to sleep.
You can still do it.
Please.
I'm hungry.
Let me stand up.
Let's do it again.
It's hot.
I fell asleep again.
If you want to do it again, tell me.
Thank you for watching.