I'm not sure if it's a good thing or a bad thing, but I'm glad that I was able to do it.
I'm glad that I was able to do it.
,
Yes, please.
I think you've cleared all the parts I talked about on the phone last time.
How is it?
I see.
This may be difficult.
By the way, what kind of place is it?
Well, I've heard that other companies have better ones than this Mitsumori.
I think this is a little difficult at the moment.
Is that so?
It's not like that.
I told you to look it up.
But you didn't say you'd look it up all.
Of course.
It's natural to do it even if you don't tell me.
Why do I have to tell you everything?
No way.
I'm really sorry.
I'll tell you often.
Is that so?
Yes.
Then, please come to Mitsumori again.
Yes, I will.
I'm sorry for today.
I'll come to Mitsumori again.
Thank you for today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Please come again.
Yes, please.
Excuse me.
Do you know what went wrong?
I made the documents as instructed.
As instructed?
I told you many times.
I told the president to look it up because Mitsumori is important.
I gave him the past data.
I see.
What do you mean?
You used the past data, didn't you?
Didn't you use it?
I used it until last year.
What about this year?
This woman who has been preaching since a while ago is Yuri Sasahara, my boss.
Since she joined the company, she has been working hard for Sasahara.
She is a very strict boss.
But I always think about Sasahara.
Do you want to go home?
This is a speed game.
I'll make it for the professor and send it to him again.
All right.
I'll go home early today.
Let's go.
Are you sure you don't want to go home?
Of course I don't want to go home.
Come early in the morning.
Why?
It's 1 o'clock in the morning.
What are you talking about?
I missed the drama.
You shouldn't make such a lie.
That's why the consultation went wrong.
Is it my fault?
Of course.
You made it.
It's a lie, isn't it?
I'll bring it tomorrow.
What do you mean tomorrow?
Tomorrow is Saturday.
So what?
I don't have a day off because of your mistake.
I'm sorry.
But it's already late.
Sasahara, let's go home.
I've booked a room for you.
You can't go home until this is over.
Do I have to stay overnight again?
I can't go home because of you.
Yes.
Let's go home.
1.5.
0.5.
Okay.
I made it.
Sasahara, what do you think of this?
It's fine.
Sasahara, buy me a drink at the convenience store.
Okay.
So, this is the end of today.
Yes.
Buy me a drink at the convenience store.
I'll buy it right away.
Okay.
1.5.
0.5.
I feel like I'm alive for this.
Sasahara, you drink a lot.
Do I?
Well, I don't want you to get tired.
I won't let you get tired.
What are you talking about?
Seriously.
Why can't you work?
It's not a big deal.
I'm not complimenting you.
I'm not?
Sasahara, you laugh a lot.
I didn't know you laughed a lot.
I laugh a lot, too.
I get nervous because of you who can't work.
I'm glad.
Sasahara, you're always angry.
What did you say?
Did you say that I'm an angry old man?
No, I didn't say that.
I don't care.
If you say that to a girl, she'll hate you.
Is that so?
I don't want to be hated only by you.
I'm sorry.
It's 100 years early to hate me.
What?
Did you say that seriously?
It's not a big deal.
You're still young.
I...
Don't get drunk.
I'm out of alcohol.
I'm going to buy it.
I'll buy it.
Don't get drunk.
Wait.
I'm fine.
Sasahara, please go.
I don't want you to get drunk.
I can't bother you anymore.
What's this?
Is it a blackout?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I...
I can't go out.
Are you really okay?
Yes.
I'll check the breaker.
No, don't go.
I...
Are you okay?
I'll turn on the light.
I...
Thank you.
Okay.
This is...
Oh.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
No.
I'm sorry to have disturbed you.
But I'm glad you're back.
Yes.
Sasahara.
Yes?
I'm sorry.
Are you free today?
Yes, I am.
I'm going to check the bathroom.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
All the other rooms are shared.
This is the only room you can sleep in.
I can sleep in the shared room, so I'm fine.
I see.
It can't be helped.
We can share this room.
Let's sleep here.
I can sleep on this chair.
You can use the bed.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Saji.
I hugged you.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
Saji.
Can I sleep next to you?
I can't get tired.
Can I?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Don't go.
What?
What's going on?
This is...
What did you say?
I thought you said my name.
No, I didn't.
I'm sorry.
I won't forgive you if you tell anyone about this.
Yes.
Okay?
This is a mouth-to-mouth conversation.
Yes.
Don't tell anyone about me.
I'm sorry.
I see.
Um, don't tell anyone at work, okay?
Okay.
Ms. Sasahara.
I have a new idea.
Oh, I see.
Ms. Sasahara.
Let's go to the beach today.
Today?
Okay, but think of a place to invite me.
I'm sorry.
But it's okay, right?
It's okay, but...
I'll book a restaurant.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
Welcome.
I'll have the usual.
Okay.
What do you want to drink?
I can drink anything.
Anything?
Yes.
I'll have a brandy, please.
Okay.
I'll have a brandy.
You can't drink brandy, right?
Yes.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Let's have a toast.
Okay.
Here you are.
Cheers.
Are you okay?
This liquor is very strong.
What?
Have you ever drunk brandy?
Actually, I'm not used to this kind of place.
Is that so?
Why did you drink brandy?
I thought it sounded cool.
You're funny.
Am I?
I'm getting hot.
What?
It's like a dream to be with you like this.
Are you really okay with me?
There are many young people.
I love you, Sasahara-san.
Walk carefully.
I'm sorry.
You're drunk.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I can walk on my own.
I want to walk with you.
I'm getting hot.
I'm sorry.
Walk more.
I'll do my best.
Are you okay?
It's heavy.
Yes.
I'm okay.
I'm getting hot.
Yes.
Do you have a necktie?
Where am I?
It's my house.
It's your house.
It's a big house.
It's fashionable.
Thank you.
I can't.
Can I lie down?
Yes.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
I'm going to drink brandy.
Are you okay?
Do you have water?
Yes.
I'm okay.
I can't.
I'll sleep.
Yes.
I'll wake you up.
Thank you.
It's amazing.
It's painful.
It looks painful.
Right?
It's painful.
It's painfu.
painful.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
Sasahara-san.
You look beautiful.
What?
Sasahara-san.
I can't stand it.
You look beautiful.
Sasahara-san.
I want to see you.
You look beautiful.
Sasahara-san.
You have a weak neck.
It's hot.
It's so soft.
No.
It's getting cold.
It's so hot.
Let me see.
The color hasn't changed.
It's so hot.
You haven't taken a bath yet.
You can't do that.
I want to see your face.
You are so beautiful.
Ah!
No, no, no.
I didn't take a bath.
You are dirty.
No, no, no.
Rin-chan.
That's not good.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it
hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts,
it hurts, do it, it hurts,
it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it
I'm sorry...
What are you doing?
Don't do that.
Help me.
I'm sorry.
It's been a while.
It's been a while since I felt like this.
No, no.
No, no, no.
It's okay, it's okay.
Do it one more time, one more time.
It hurts.
What should I do?
I'm hungry.
I love you.
Delicious.
I want you to see me lying on the floor.
It's good.
I feel so good.
Then I'll die
Let go of me
Wait! Wait wait Wait no no no no no no wait, isn't it guys!
I found this wall for the first time
I don't feel good
I can't get up
Stop it
There you are...
I'm sorry...
Aah!
This is good!
Ah, this is greasy.
No, no, no.
This isn't good.
No good.
Does it feel good?
Is it fresh?
Crap.
No good!
Please!
Let's go!
Itch! Itch!
Go!
Oh, no!
I feel sick!
Ah, don't do that!
You're dirty!
Stop! Stop it!
Don't do this to me
It's done.
Where should I stand?
Around your waist?
No, only your waist.
Okay...
Turn one knee together.
For the T-bone surgery.
Give me your hand.
Oh...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Method acting
Examples
I feel so good.
I'm going to die.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
ah ah
ah ah ah
I love you too.
Me too.
Sachi-kun.
What are we going to do today?
What are we going to do?
I want to be with you.
But...
I'm going home.
I know.
Okay.
Sachi-kun.
I love you.
Good morning.
Oh, Shichizaji-kun.
Yeah.
Good morning.
I had a lot of fun yesterday.
Oh, yeah.
Me too.
I'm happy to be with you every day.
What are you talking about?
Sasahara-san, you are surprisingly shy.
What?
Don't make fun of me.
Hurry up and get to work.
What should I do?
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm...
This is the office.
But...
I don't think I can stand it.
Just a little.
I can't stand it.
Hey, what are you doing?
Just a little.
I can't stand it.
Wait.
Not there.
I can't stand it.
Wait.
It smells good.
Don't do it yourself.
Don't do it.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Pretty noisy.
Wow, amazing
Okay, okay, okay.
It feels good.
Oh, it feels so good.
It feels so good.
It's so good.
Oh, it's so good.
Oh, it feels so good.
The way you take off your glasses is so nice.
It feels so good.
Oh, it feels so good.
Okey, okey.
Okay, okay, okay, oka...
Just so you know...
Who is it?
Who's there?
Who are you?
Wow...
You can sleep now.
You did a good job!
DRY
Embarrassing...
I'm gonna cry.
Embarrassing carcass.
Hey hey hey!
Uh-huh
ugly
That's awesome
No way
My condition got too bad
They have to clean this to get the egg out
It's okay, it's okay.
I can't do it either.
I can't do it.
It's delicious.
It's really good.
I can't do it.
You can't let it out yet.
It's so soft.
It's so hot.
It feels so good.
I'll put it in your mouth.
You like it, don't you?
I can't.
What's next?
Let's use this.
What's that?
Why do you have this?
You have a lot, don't you?
What's wrong with this?
I was forced to wear this at the wedding.
Really?
I left it in my bag.
You bought it yourself, didn't you?
I didn't buy it.
You left it in your bag, didn't you?
I left it in my bag.
Make me feel better.
Do you know how to use it?
Do you feel good?
I love you.
I love you so much.
If you feel good,
Do you feel good?
Ahhh~!
Ahh! I'm going, I'm going, I'm going!
It's not over yet, I'm going, I'm going!
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going!
I think he's gone
Wonderful.
You're gorgeous.
Are you okay?
Do you feel good?
Do you want to feel better?
What happens if you go inside?
It's okay.
It's amazing.
I didn't know it was this big.
Do you feel good?
It's amazing.
I'm happy.
Do you feel good?
It's amazing.
It's okay, it's okay.
I feel so good.
I'm out of breath.
It hurts.
I'm okay.
No.
Agh!
Huh?
It hurts...
It hurts!
It'll all go away...
Really?
Th-they're coming!
They're here!
Help me, help me!
Help me!
I feel sick, I feel sick!
I'm in pain, I'm in pain!
I'm in pain!
I feel sick, I feel sick!
I'm in pain, I'm in pain!
Help me, help me!
I feel sick, I feel sick!
Di-san.
I-I know you're in there.
We're in cat trouble!
I won't let you in!
If we can't get him in...
we're losing all hope!
I-I'm there, I'm there!
Come here I'm here I'm here!
I'm here, I'm here, I'm...
You're here?
I need to take care of you like a man.
Yeah.
I will revenge for you
to give you a puberty.
I promise.
Okay.
Ihate...
take my shoulder.
What?
I hate when
It's veryitutional.
I'm very tired.
My near panda is very daunting.
I'm exhausted.
Go, Go, go.
I'm leaving.
Off go, go, go.
C-c-c-c-cutie!
Huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, huff, h
Huh?
What shall I do?
The urge to work is gone.
Yes, indeed.
What shall I do
Shall I give it another go
Faster, faster
Go on, go on, go on, go on, go on, go on, go on
I'll do it again.
Yes, I'm sorry.
What's this?
You're being chased again.
You really don't grow up.
I'm not eating at the desk.
I'm going to the bathroom.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Sashi.
What is it?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Are you going to stay at my house tonight?
Yes.
Thank you for watching.