......I'm sorry. I didn't mean to make you angry.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to make you angry.
I've been staying at my brother's house for 3 months.
I'm Minami, my brother's wife.
I thought she was beautiful when I first saw her.
I went to her home once or twice a year.
She was so kind to me.
I might have fallen in love with her if I hadn't met her.
I was happy and nervous every day to live with such a person.
But it was hard for every one of us to take care of her.
This is the story of my habit that always helped me make a choice.
I wonder what it is.
Hey, what's wrong?
I can't move this.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Let's have a look.
Oh, really?
Can I have a look?
Yes.
Oh, really?
I see.
It's just a little bit of a freeze.
Oh, really?
Yes. It will be fixed soon.
Yes.
Thank you.
Here.
Yes.
I think I can fix this.
I see.
I will fix it soon.
Thank you.
I see.
My brother is also an analog person, so he is not good at computers.
Yes.
But my sister is not good at computers.
I see.
I'm surprised.
Are you?
Yes.
But I can fix this.
Oh, thank you.
I should have asked you earlier.
It's not a big deal.
I see.
Until now, I had a normal life.
When I was in elementary school, I became an adult without knowing that I was dating a man.
I met my father's daughter and got married to my husband.
In the daytime, I spent a lot of time alone and had a normal life.
At that time, my brother and I decided to live together.
It was a little fresh and I was a little excited about a different life than before.
Let's eat.
It looks delicious.
Really?
Yes.
I'm glad.
Can I eat this?
Yes.
How is it? Is it delicious?
Yes, it's delicious.
I'm glad.
You are good at cooking.
Really?
Yes.
I'm glad.
Let's eat this, too.
Yes.
It looks delicious.
I often go to work at night and stay at home during the day.
So, I had lunch with Minami.
We had a casual conversation, but we had a lot of fun.
She enjoyed listening to my brother's complaints.
It looks delicious.
I'm glad.
I love pasta.
Really?
It looks delicious.
Do you have any other dishes you can cook?
Well, I'm better at cooking Western food than Japanese food.
Really?
Yes.
Do you have hamburgers?
Yes, I do.
I can make hamburgers, too.
I want to eat hamburgers you make.
I'll make hamburgers next time.
Can I?
Yes.
I'm glad.
You are good at cooking.
Really?
I didn't expect it to be delicious.
I'm glad.
I'll eat this, too.
I think I made it delicious.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Yes.
I'm proud of myself.
I agree.
It's delicious.
Yes.
There was a time when my brother's complaints were like a night's story.
I was not satisfied with my brother's complaints.
It's delicious.
Yes.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I do.
I feel good, too.
I'm glad to hear that.
Yes.
Ahhhh
Itch, Itch, Itch
More on the side
Itch
Ahhhh
Wait a minute
It's a little weird.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. It's a little weird.
Are you tired from work?
It's a little weird.
Do you want me to do it for you?
Are you okay?
It feels good.
It's a little weird.
I'm glad you're a kind wife.
It's getting deeper.
Do you want me to do it again?
It's okay. I'll make you feel better.
It feels good.
It's a little weird.
Thank you.
I have to get up early tomorrow.
Good night.
I'm going to the bathroom.
What's wrong?
I need to go to the bathroom.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Tsuyoshi is so strong.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's hot.
I usually come back in the morning.
I was about to finish early.
I cut it off in time for the last train.
I didn't hear that.
My brother is not on a business trip this day.
I came home early.
It hurts in the middle of shoes.
I don't want to go back to the way it was.
Never mind.
My cheeks hurt, they sting!
I can't wave.
Go.
I'm home.
Why did you kiss me?
Aren't you going to come home soon?
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
Chiyoshi.
Yes?
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Yes.
You came home early today, didn't you?
I happened to be home early.
I see.
You saw me earlier, didn't you?
What?
I didn't see anything.
Is that so?
Yes.
Especially.
I saw you.
I want you to keep it a secret.
Yes.
Of course.
I won't tell you.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I won't tell you.
Thank you.
I saw you earlier.
You saw me earlier.
What do you mean?
Well, I mean...
My sister is not a bad person at all.
Is that so?
I'm sorry, but...
I can't satisfy my sister.
Did I say something wrong?
Don't look down on me.
Don't do that.
No, I didn't mean that.
Well...
I mean...
My sister...
I didn't expect her to do such a thing.
I was so nervous.
But, a woman who does such a thing...
She must be despised.
No, she isn't.
Actually...
Well...
I...
When I saw her for the first time...
When you saw her for the first time?
Well...
So...
So?
Well...
I like her.
What?
Well...
I've liked her for a long time.
When I saw her for the first time...
I thought she was a beautiful woman.
I've liked her for a long time.
I've admired her.
I've...
I've liked her for a long time.
Wait a minute.
I see.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
Well...
I just wanted to tell you how I feel.
I'm glad.
Please keep this a secret from my brother.
I see.
Well...
It's a secret between us.
I see.
Well...
Sister.
Yes?
Well...
Just for now...
Will you be mine?
What?
Sister.
Well...
Just for now...
No?
Is this also a secret between us?
Yes.
Well...
Your lips are very soft.
I'm embarrassed.
You're very good at kissing.
I feel very happy.
I'm so happy.
I feel so happy.
I've always wanted to kiss you.
I'm so happy.
mmm
awesome
mmmm
mmm
I'm really happy
so
Is this okay?
It's very beautiful
What's wrong?
It's painful
It feels good
Does it feel good?
It's painful
What's wrong?
It's very beautiful
It's painful
It feels good
It's embarrassing
Let me see
It's very beautiful
It's embarrassing
It doesn't hurt
It feels good
It hurts
Ah
I have a favor to ask you, but I want you to lick me.
Are you okay?
Does it feel good?
It feels really good.
You do such a great thing.
I do.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Help me.
It's my first time.
Me too, sis.
Again.
One more time.
I love you.
I love you too.
It was very exciting.
I thought they were real siblings.
I had sex with Giri's brother.
Until the next morning.
The next morning.
Hey, sis.
Did I wake you up?
What are you doing?
You've grown up.
I love you.
Does it feel good?
It feels really good.
I love you.
You were so small yesterday.
You've grown up so much.
It's amazing.
You're so attractive.
I love you.
Do you like this?
I love it.
I'll do more for you.
I love you.
Do you like it faster?
I love it faster.
I love you.
You're so big.
What do you like?
You're good at everything.
I feel good when you touch me.
I'll give you a boob.
Can I?
Yes.
Thank you.
You have a lot of boobs.
Really?
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Do you like this?
I love you.
I'll give you a boob again.
I feel good.
You're so big.
But you're still fine.
I feel good.
You're amazing.
I can't do it anymore.
I feel good.
I love you.
I'll give you a boob again.
I feel good.
I love you.
I've been in love with Tsuyoshi since that day.
I feel good.
You're the best.
You should go home early.
I want to be with you.
You're the best.
You're so beautiful.
I feel good.
I want more.
I'm not okay yet.
I feel good.
I'm not okay.
I want more.
I feel good.
I'm not okay.
I want more.
I feel good.
I really loved you.
I thought I should stop time.
I can't believe I'm going back to Tokyo.
I'm sorry I kept you waiting.
Don't mention it.
Thank you.
I hope to see you again.
I'll come back again.
I'm going to go.
Take care of yourself.
Let's go.
I'm lonely.
When can I see you again?
I can't stand it anymore.
You're very wet.
I'll come back again.
How do you feel?
I'm going to go.
I don't feel good.
You don't seem to be in a good mood lately.
Is that so?
Are you sick?
I see.
By the way, I'm going on a business trip tomorrow.
So I will not see you again.
It's lonely.
Do you have a day off?
Yes,I have one day off.
Let's do something amazing.
Sister.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
when
Where did you come from?
When can I participate?
Yes, yes, then
That's fine.
You're doing really well there.
I know, I can feel it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
✖️
with
Yeah.
Huh?
I missed it so much.
I'm so happy for you.
Yeah, of course.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Yeah, uh, uh, uh
Oh
Ah ah ah ah
Okay.
There...
It feels good.
It definitely does.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ash Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Good
Aha
Ah! Ahhhh!
Oh…
Wah!
Wah Wah!
Oh...
Ahhh…
Ah...
Don't! No!
No!
Come on, Angel!
I'm a teacher ...
Oh...
Oh!
Er!
Itchy!
Itch!!!
It hurts.
No, no, no.
I'm going, I'm going.
It hurts.
Show me your face.
I hate you so much.
I'm going, I'm going.
It hurts.
It's so hot.
I'm going, I'm going.
I'm glad you're so excited.
My pants are tight.
It's hot.
It's so hot.
I've always wanted you to do this.
I've always wanted to do this.
I'm going, I'm going.
I'm looking at your face.
My jaw is getting hard.
You're getting really excited.
You need to sleep a little more.
I want you to put it in.
I can't stand it anymore.
It hurts.
I want you to put it in.
My hands are shaking.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I want you to put it in.
It's embarrassing.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It still hurts.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
I can't do it.
I'll come to your house again next month.
This time, I'll stay with Minami for half a year.
It's very exciting to have sex with him for the first time.
I didn't tell my husband about this.
I'm very excited.
It feels good.
But from now on, Minami...
Let's have a lot of sex.
Thank you for watching my video.