Good morning.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm going to go to the doctor's office today.
Okay.
Thank you for your hard work.
Please forgive me.
Okay.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
I made breakfast for you.
It looks delicious.
Does it?
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
What's wrong with this wine?
Don't you remember this?
You drank it in Yokohama before you got married.
Did I?
I don't remember.
I found the same one as the one you drank at that time.
I don't remember well.
You don't remember, do you?
I'll pour it for you.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'll pour it for you.
Cheers.
Where are you going tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
I'm going to work tomorrow.
I told you to take a day off because it's your wedding anniversary tomorrow.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
But I can't go to work tomorrow.
I have to go to work on the weekend.
I was looking forward to it.
I'm sorry.
Let's go to work together when you get back.
Okay.
I'll make you a sandwich.
Do you want to eat it?
Yes.
It's delicious.
I'll make you a sandwich.
Hello, is this Sasano?
Yes.
Get ready for this project that I mentioned last time.
I will.
Get some materials.
Well, I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Oh, you're taking a day off today, aren't you?
Yes, I have something to do.
Oh, you've got all the documents you asked for.
Oh, yes.
These are the documents you asked for.
Thank you.
Oh, can I talk to you for a moment?
You know the project I'm working on, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I'm going to ask you to help me with it.
What?
It's a project I've been working on for a long time, so I'll ask you to back it up.
Yes.
Read all of this. I'll explain what I'm going to do later.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Good luck.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, I'll leave it to you.
Director, how did you make this graph?
Well, I think this one is better than that one.
Is that so?
Yes, thank you.
Well, this one is good, but I think this one is better.
What do you think, SANA?
Are you listening?
Oh, yes.
Oh, this one?
No, this one.
Oh, yes. I'm sorry.
Yes, yes.
Keep up the good work.
Yes.
Director, are you all right?
Are you all right?
You can work, but you're missing out on this kind of thing, aren't you?
It's just a coincidence, isn't it?
Uh, please get in.
What?
It's onbu, onbu.
I don't think I can do that.
But, you know, I'm a bit nervous.
I'm a bit nervous, too.
I'm a bit nervous.
No, I don't think so.
I'm telling the truth.
I'm fine.
I'm strong.
That's not what I mean.
I'm not that kind of person.
Here we go.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
This is a popular product in our company.
Is it?
Yes.
I hope you can use this app.
It seems to be popular among young people.
That's right.
Is this a pen?
This is a ballpoint pen.
This is the most popular product among the products I brought today.
Is that so?
Yes.
It has a cute shape.
That's right.
You are amazing.
What is this?
This is a present for you.
I'll give you whatever you want.
That's my job.
I see.
Let's go to the next place.
Is your leg okay?
Yes.
I think you should go back to the office.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Let's go.
Okay.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm okay.
Does it hurt?
No.
Do you want to go to the convenience store again?
I'm okay.
It's faster this way.
It's time for you to take care of your health.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Please wait a moment.
I'll call you later.
Okay.
I just bought this.
I got it.
Excuse me.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
I don't know where to go.
That's bad.
Do your best.
I'm going home.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
I'm working on the exhibition.
I see.
Is it okay?
Yes, it's okay.
I'm glad to hear that.
How was the exhibition?
It's almost over.
The president there is strict, so it's almost over.
Is that so?
That's great.
I felt good when I went to talk to him.
But, it can't be helped.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Does your leg still hurt?
Thank you.
How long are you going to do this?
I'm sorry.
By the way, I like you.
What?
Thank you.
As a person, as a boss.
I know.
I'm going to the convenience store.
Okay.
Thank you.
Sena is small, but he has a strong chest.
He is manly.
I'm sorry.
Hello, Sena?
What's up?
Okay.
I see.
I'll show you the material tomorrow.
Okay.
Thank you.
What's this?
You'll know when you see it.
It's a lunch box.
Thank you.
You always go to the convenience store, don't you?
No.
I made it for you.
Thank you.
Eat it gratefully.
Okay.
Thank you.
It's a miracle that I passed the project to that company.
But I have to write a proposal now.
It can't be helped.
Let's do our best.
Yes, I'll do my best.
I'm sorry.
It's almost closing time.
Please excuse me.
I see.
I understand.
What are you going to do?
It's not over yet.
My house is close, so I'll do it there.
I see.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
My house is close, so I'll do it there.
At your house?
Yes.
I'll be back soon.
Okay.
Thank you.
Manager.
I got a letter from C to D.
Do you want to read it?
Yes.
It's good.
You're good.
Thank you.
Let's do our best.
Yes.
It's done.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's perfect.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't say anything.
Here you are.
Manager.
I like you.
As a boss?
No.
As a woman.
I really like you.
You're beautiful.
Thank you.
I really like you.
I'm sorry.
You're beautiful.
I like you.
I'm sorry.
I can't help you.
Do you wanna lie and talk to Yukari-sama?
It's nothing important.
Now...
Come here.
Show me your back.
It's soft.
It's beautiful.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Show me your back.
It smells good.
It's soft.
It's soft, isn't it?
Show me your back.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Can I see you up close?
It's beautiful.
Show me your back.
You're feeling better, aren't you?
It's beautiful.
Show me your back.
You're feeling better, aren't you?
I can't.
I love you so much.
It's beautiful.
I can't.
You're feeling better, aren't you?
You're beautiful.
I can't.
Stop it.
Feels so good...
Mom, help me.
Hmm
Ha ha ha ha
I'm sorry.
I wonder if I'm a bad wife.
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
All right.
Manager.
I did it.
The contract is OK.
You did it.
Yes.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Let's make a contract.
OK.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I wonder if I'm a bad wife.
You are beautiful.
I admire you.
I feel good.
You are beautiful.
I admire you.
I feel good.
I adore you.
I admire you.
It has finally came into my life...
good morning
Good morning.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Why are you embarrassed?
It's me, isn't it?
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for beating you up, especially when you care about your friends.
Because I'm embarrassed.
Don't worry, I'm not mad at you.
It's just that you made fun of me, so I'm a little embarrassed.
Alright, let's get this straight,
have you everysics with someone?
Yes, I did.
He also said irrelevant information.
What did he say?
Slowly
Please stick out your lips slightly
Can I touch you?
I'm so happy
I want to touch you more
Does it feel good here?
It feels good
I want to touch you more
Does it feel good?
It feels good
Give me a kiss
It hurts
I can't open my mouth
Can I touch you?
It hurts
Does it feel good here?
It feels good
I want to touch you more
It hurts
Can I touch you more?
I can't open my mouth
It hurts
Can I touch you more?
Can I look at you?
It's beautiful
Don't look at me
It's okay
It's really beautiful
Can I touch you more?
It hurts
I can't hold it anymore
I want to stop
Stop it
It feels good
It hurts
Can I touch you more?
Does it feel good?
It hurts
Give me a kiss
Can I touch you now?
Please
It hurts
Can I look at you?
Can I touch you more?
It hurts
It feels good
Does it feel good?
It hurts
Can I touch you?
It feels good
It hurts
Did I say too much?
It feels good
Can I hug you?
Yes
It hurts
It feels good
Please eat this carefully
It hurts
It feels good
Please hug me
It hurts
It feels good
Ok, I'm done.
Enough?
Yes...
It's crazy
I-
I can't believe what happened...
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I can't do it anymore.
You can't do it anymore?
It feels good.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It feels good.
I can't do it anymore.
It's okay.
Help me.
I can't do it anymore.
It's okay.
Help me.
It hurts.
It's embarrassing.
I can't do it anymore.
It's okay.
It hurts.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sorry.
She wanna cry.
It's not a war, not a war at all.
I don't know what to do.
It felt good, didn't it?
It was good.
I'm really going to be late.
Would you like to take a break today?
No.
I have to bring a plan.
I can't do it.
Go ahead.
I'm going to take a shower later.
I see.
I'm going to bed.
Good morning, Tama.
Please subscribe to my channel!