Midnight, Chiharu Miyazawa
Hello?
Ah
Were you working?
Yeah, I was working. What's up?
Well...
Did you have a day off today?
Yeah, I was working, but I'm at the office now.
I just went to the bathroom.
Oh, you went to the bathroom.
I just went to the stairs.
Stairs? What about work?
I just took a shower, so I'm fine.
Oh, did you smoke?
No, I don't smoke.
Oh, really?
What are you doing on the stairs?
Oh, are you tired?
You said you've been busy lately.
Yeah.
Actually...
It's a little sudden, but...
Yeah, what is it?
I want to break up with you.
What? Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Why? Do you hate me?
No, it's not like that.
I still like you, but we haven't met lately.
We're both busy with work.
Yeah.
But...
But even if you tell me forever, I can't accept it.
I know it's very sudden, but...
I still like you, but...
If we don't break up, we...
I'm sorry, too.
I don't think it's good.
I think there are better people.
Why are you sorry?
I...
I like you.
I still like you.
You like me, don't you?
I don't want to break up with you.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize. I don't want to break up with you.
Really.
I...
I love you.
Don't say that.
I don't want to break up with you, but...
But...
What?
I...
I still like you.
I like your kindness.
I like everything about you.
I made a lot of memories with you.
I remember that, too.
I said I'd be with you forever.
I know.
But...
I really have to meet Naoko.
Please.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Don't say that.
I know.
I don't know.
You don't know?
I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
It's okay.
We have to work.
Please comfort me when we meet again.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I was worried.
Let's meet soon.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about me.
It's okay.
I'll call you again.
Okay.
See you.
Good luck with your work.
Thank you.
See you.
Chiharu.
Are you crying again?
Yes.
Thanks to you, I was able to make up with him.
You're a good actress.
They say a woman's tears are the strongest.
I think so, too.
But when I cry, he cringes.
That's cute.
You're a scary woman.
I'm glad I didn't understand you.
I heard that one person will come in today.
Have you seen it?
I haven't seen it yet.
I'm talking to the staff.
Our department will come later.
Are you curious?
No.
I thought it would be nice if I could work.
I see.
Do you know there's a restaurant near the office?
Pasta restaurant?
I haven't been there.
Let's go next time.
Let's go.
It looks delicious.
It's fashionable.
I'm having lunch.
Let's go.
I'm looking forward to it.
What?
Do you want to go to the restaurant for lunch today?
Let's go.
It's a little crowded because there's no restaurant around here.
I see.
Do you have to make a reservation?
Let's do it.
It's lunch time.
I don't want to be late.
I don't know.
Excuse me.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Let's introduce ourselves.
I'm Asakura, and I'm going to work in this department from today.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Chibisho.
I'm Asada.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Sure.
I'm a little older than you, but I have no experience in this field, so I'll leave it to you.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Asada.
I don't know anything, but thank you.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
I'll leave the seat to you.
Okay.
I'll leave it to you.
I'll tell you how to use the computer.
Okay.
First, set the password in the company.
I've set it up.
Okay.
Is it okay?
Yes, it's okay.
You don't have to be so smart.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm 30 years old, but this is my first time in Tokyo.
I don't know anything about work or private life, so I'm sorry to bother you.
No problem.
Thank you.
I'm a little older than you, but I have no experience in this field, so I'll leave it to you.
Okay.
How old are you?
I'm 26 years old.
Oh, I see.
Nice to meet you.
Enter your name here.
Okay.
And you're done.
Oh, this is how you set it up?
Yes.
Oh, thank you.
You're welcome.
Chiharu, you're doing a good job, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
No, but the manager said you were very good at it.
Oh, he said I was good at it because I was easy to use.
Oh.
Well, let's practice together.
Oh, yes, I understand.
Also, this company has a lot of overtime, so be careful of your health.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Then.
Thank you.
Chiharu Miyadaro
Chiharu Miyadaro in the middle of the night.
This is the third volume of the CVC.
Oh.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
This is.
This is the second volume.
Oh, here it is.
Yes.
Also, there is a document that I mentioned.
It's written here, so it contains the documents I mentioned.
Oh.
This is the back seat.
Yes.
What should I do with the documents that are not here?
The documents that are not here are written in the PDF file of the computer, so please print them and submit them.
Oh, I see.
Yes.
Oh, there were a lot of PDFs.
Yes, there were.
There were.
Yes.
Are you okay with anything else?
Well, for now, yes, I'm okay.
Yes.
Thank you.
Then, it's like this.
Please do your best.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Asada-kun.
What is this training?
You always make mistakes in the numbers.
Oh, yes.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
You're just bothering the customers with this.
Huh?
Yes.
You're not an amateur, are you?
You have experience, so you should be able to do this.
Oh, yes.
You're a good age, but you make so many mistakes.
I'll be careful.
You're a kid.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Well, Asada-kun, you make a lot of mistakes.
Is Chiharu-kun teaching you properly?
Yes, I'm teaching him properly.
Then, you make a lot of mistakes.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You're just bothering the customers with this.
Then, I'll teach him properly.
Yes, you should.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Huh?
Asada-kun.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Yes.
Where?
Here and here.
I made a mistake with the numbers.
Oh, two places?
Yes.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I have experience, too.
Oh, really?
Yes.
It's dangerous.
It's okay if you make a mistake.
Let's do it together.
Oh, yes.
It's about 200 yen.
Yes, it's about 200 yen.
I'm really glad that the manager noticed it before I sent an e-mail to the dealer.
That's good.
It's dangerous.
I'm sorry.
It's done.
Can I have a look at this?
Yes.
Yes, yes.
It's right.
It's perfect.
Perfect?
Yes, it's great.
Oh, really?
Yes.
It's done.
The manager will forgive you.
Yes.
To be honest, I was about to cry when the manager scolded me.
Oh, really?
But, I thought it was impossible for a man to cry at work, so I held it in.
But, I'm glad.
I also cry a lot, so I know how you feel.
Do you?
Yes, I cry a lot.
At work?
Yes, at work.
Oh, really?
You're really strong, so I don't think so.
No, I'm not.
But, let's do our best.
Yes.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
Midnight.
Chiharu Miyuzawa.
I'm sorry to interrupt your work.
No, it's okay.
I've heard about it, so I'm not sure if I can help.
You don't have to.
I'm glad that you help me.
We don't have any plans.
It's enough.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thanks to you, it's almost over.
Okay, I'll do my best.
Let's do our best.
Chiharu Miyuzawa.
Excuse me, I have to make a phone call.
Okay.
I'll leave it to you.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Yes, I'm on my way.
Hello, what's up?
I'm on my way to work.
What happened?
I've been thinking about it.
Let's break up.
What?
I want to prioritize my work now.
I think Chiharu and I will spend less time together.
So...
Let's break up.
No.
Why are you saying that again?
We've been doing well.
I'm sorry.
I want to spend more time with Chiharu.
I think I like Chiharu more and more.
I'm sorry.
No.
I like you.
I love you.
I always think about you when I can't see you.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I can't give Chiharu an answer.
I'm sorry.
I'll finish the document after this final check.
It's done.
Please check it.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm going home.
I'll check it tomorrow.
Wait a minute.
Please use this.
Thank you.
This is all I can do.
I'm sorry.
I'm going home.
Thank you.
I can see you, Chiharu.
Good morning.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
Thank you for this.
It's okay.
I'm glad you like it.
I put the data in the shared folder yesterday.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm okay.
If you don't mind, I'd like to talk to you.
Please tell me anything.
It's not a big deal.
Don't worry about it.
Is that so?
By the way, I'd like to thank you for yesterday.
Would you like to go out for a drink tonight?
Thanks to the gunpowder yesterday, there seems to be no overtime today.
That's good.
If you're about to run out of energy, let's run away with all our might.
Yes.
Let's run away with all our might.
I'm sorry.
I called you, but it didn't work.
I see.
You broke up with him, didn't you?
That's right.
He dumped me.
How long have you been dating?
It's been about four years since I was in college.
Four years?
That's a long time.
I haven't seen him since I became a social worker.
I haven't been in touch with him, and I've been in trouble many times.
I've been lying to him every time.
Did you lie to him?
I'm good at lying.
I lied to him to make him feel selfish.
That's amazing.
Did you lie to him yesterday, too?
Yesterday...
I lied to him.
I'm not good at lying.
I thought I'd become a strong woman enough to wipe away my tears.
I was dumped by a man and cried.
It's okay.
You can cry when you want to.
But I know how you feel.
If I were you, I'd like to see him.
I wanted to see him so much.
But I'm afraid I can't see him.
I'm sorry.
Chiharu, are you okay?
I'm sorry. Did I say anything wrong?
No, it's okay.
Here.
Please use this.
Thank you.
It's warm.
It's warm, isn't it?
Yes.
It's warm.
Can we go somewhere just the two of us?
Yes.
At midnight, Chiharu Miyazawa.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I got carried away.
Are you okay?
I didn't think the kiss would feel this good.
You're crying again.
I'm sorry.
Are you embarrassed?
Yes, I am.
But you're not crying.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. It must have hurt.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
It's very beautiful.
Really.
I'm sorry.
I'll continue to make you feel good.
I feel good when you lick me.
Really?
I'm sorry.
It's very soft.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
Don't do it.
Hey.
Stop it.
Don't do it!
Come here!
It's cute, isn't it?
I'm embarrassed.
You may think it's strange, but I think your face when you cry is cute and wonderful.
Really?
I'm happy.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
It's cute.
I feel good.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm more surprised.
But, it's cute.
Really?
But, I'm embarrassed because I'm naked.
Leave it to me.
Please take it off.
Okay.
I'll take it off.
Why are you hiding it?
I'm embarrassed.
I feel good.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's because I feel good.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm happy.
I feel good.
I'm embarrassed.
You're good.
You're too good.
You're in a hurry.
Really?
What should I do with this?
Should I put it in?
Is it okay?
But, I don't have a rubber band.
I may have a rubber band.
I'm embarrassed.
Then...
Okay.
I'm embarrassed.
I want to sleep.
I feel good.
I'm embarrassed.
What is it?
What?
I'm embarrassed.
Here.
OK, let's start!
Yyhhhhhhhhh
Stay there
I'm sorry
Ugh
Woooow
Waah
You get it now
Here
I'm going to sleep.
That's good.
That's great.
I'm going to sleep.
That's good.
She's crying again.
I'm sorry.
That's good.
I'm so...
I also feel so good!
I love you so much.
I love you.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't help it.
I'm glad.
It's amazing.
Tissue?
Thank you.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Thank you.
I love you so much.
I love you.
It was really pleasant.
It was pleasant.
Every second was just beautiful.
I had a happy day.
I hope you had a relaxed time this whole time.
Just try your best until you get back to your senses and move on.
One more bite
Midnight
The next morning
Thank you.
Good morning.
Why are you in a hurry?
The director called me.
I see.
Good luck.
OK.
It's almost over.
Yes.
The director forced me to work overtime.
I'm sorry to help you.
You're too kind.
But it's OK.
I'm glad.
Besides,
we can live here together.
It's OK.
It's over.
Good job.
Thank you.
I was patient.
Me, too.
We did bad things.
Yes, we did.
It's hot.
I'm getting tired.
Can I touch you?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's getting harder.
It feels good.
Nobody's coming, right?
I guess it's going to be okay.
Yeah.
I feel like I can't go any further.
But it's exciting to work at a company like this.
I feel good.
My voice is loud.
I see.
I feel good.
I'm fine.
But I feel like I'm in pain.
I feel good because I'm in pain.
I'm scared.
I'm in pain.
I'm worried.
You feel good, don't you?
I feel good.
Wait a minute.
I'm in pain.
Are you okay?
There's no one here.
I was surprised to hear that from the office.
I feel good.
I'm in pain.
You're playing with me, aren't you?
You have a cute reaction.
I'm in pain.
It was good.
I felt great.
I'm glad.
I don't feel bad at all.
Do you want to sit here?
Can I sit here?
What should I do?
I see.
You can sit here.
Wait a minute.
I haven't done anything yet.
Today...
I don't have any plans.
I have to go home.
Is that so?
I'm sorry.
I'll call you next time.
Okay.
See you tomorrow.
In the middle of the night...
I woke up.
Good morning.
What's wrong?
You haven't slept for three days.
That's right.
If you had a cold, you would have gone to see a doctor.
Thank you.
Did you sleep well?
Yes, I slept well.
I want to sleep.
I was worried about you.
What should I do?
I'm sorry.
I was talking to you.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Yes, I know.
When will you sleep?
I don't know.
At first, I thought it was better to have a girl.
I thought so, too.
It's easier to raise a girl.
I see.
Do you understand?
Yes.
I see.
So, are you going to move?
Are you going to move to a place where you live?
Yes.
Well, it's a little narrow now.
I don't have to live there.
I don't have to move to a place where I live.
I see.
If you move to a place where you live, it will be a little wider.
So, it's better to move.
Yes.
I have a son who I love.
I see.
If you can do this, you can do your best at work.
Yes.
I'm looking forward to your future.
Thank you very much.
Do your best.
Yes.
Do your best to raise your salary.
I see.
Yes.
I have a son who I love.
Do you have a son who you love?
Yes.
I see.
Do you have a son who you love?
I have.
It's been 3 years.
I have a son who I love.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I think it's a good idea.
Why didn't you tell me you were getting married?
I'm sorry.
Why?
I was going to break up with my wife.
My wife and I have been married for five years.
Our relationship hasn't been going well at all.
We were talking about getting a divorce.
I took off my ring when I joined the company.
I'm sorry.
Did you get that call from your wife?
Yes.
It's been four months.
That long?
What are you going to do?
What am I going to do?
I'll choose you.
I'll cut off my wife and child and be with you.
No.
Don't say that.
But you said you'd break up with your wife.
I can't be happy.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Thank you.
This is all I can do for you.
You're so kind.
Thank you.
This is the last time.
I don't want to say goodbye.
I love you.
This is the last time.
I love you, too.
I love you.
I'm not sure if it's a good thing or a bad thing, but I think it's a good thing.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
I'll put it on right away.
I love you.
Why did you marry me?
I don't want to.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I still love you.
This is the end.
I'm sorry.
I'm happy, but...
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
But I love you.
I love you.
You're about to go.
It's over when you go.
Could you do it more?
Hey...
Please help me.
Don't go.
You can go to your favorite place.
I'm sorry.
Don't go.
Go.
It's over, isn't it?
Don't tell me it's over.
I'm sorry.
Let's say goodbye here.
I'm fine.
I lied to you.