It's going to be a great feeling during sleeping in a midnight.
no.
done.
Excuse me.
Yes?
....
Oh.
Good evening.
I'm Misaki, I'll be working at Shigena swingu today.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Have a seat, Mom.
You don't have to be so formal with me.
Have a drink.
Thank you.
Is this your first time working late at night like this?
Yes, it is.
I see.
There aren't many customers at this time of the day.
So you don't have to be so formal with me.
I see.
Well...
I work to replenish my products.
And I also work to distribute newspapers and magazines.
That's what I do.
I see.
You often think about that, don't you?
Yes.
I'm getting old.
My back hurts a lot.
Is your back okay?
I think it's okay now.
That's what you're thinking about now, isn't it?
No, it's not.
I'm just saying this because I'm worried about you.
I see.
This is the bread I put in the disposal earlier.
You can eat it while it's open.
I see.
I'll eat it.
No, you can't.
You can't eat this.
It's noisy.
If Misaki wants to eat something else, will you be careful?
I see.
And this is your uniform and nametag.
Thank you very much.
Can you come to the cash register?
Yes.
Put the money here.
And...
Rokka, use this.
Yes.
When you're ready, come to the cash register.
I see.
Thank you.
Okay.
Then, I'll introduce your part-time job.
Uemura-kun.
Yes.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
I'm Misaki, and I'll be working here from today.
Nice to meet you.
How long have you been working here?
It's been five years.
That's a long time.
So, you remember everything, right?
Yes, I do.
If there's anything you don't understand, ask him.
Okay.
Then, I'll leave now.
Nice to meet you.
Have you ever had a part-time job before?
I worked at a supermarket.
Oh, did you?
Yes.
Then, you can be my customer.
Okay.
Have you ever worked at a cash register?
No, I haven't.
I see.
Yes.
Most customers don't come to this shop.
But, sometimes they do.
So, I don't have to be polite to them.
I just try to remember everything.
I see.
I haven't changed that much.
Then, I'll leave it here.
I'll leave it as it is.
Here's the name of the product and the price.
I'll leave it here.
Cash registers are like this.
I see.
Recently, many customers use IC.
So, you can press this button and it'll light up.
I see.
Well, it's okay.
You'll get used to it soon.
Yes.
I'll try it.
I'm here, too.
I see.
There are more items below.
You can put them in order.
You can put all items below.
I see.
Some items are scattered.
Well, the shelves above are...
Yes.
Today, they are neatly arranged.
But, they are arranged in four rows.
Four rows.
Sometimes, there are customers who put them in order.
Yes.
So, you should put them in order.
I see.
I'll put them in order around here.
I'll leave it to you.
It's okay.
Please.
Okay.
Please call me if you need anything.
I'll leave it to you.
Okay.
It's 520 yen.
I see.
Thank you.
I'll put it in a bag.
Please.
Okay.
It's 580 yen.
I'll put it in a bag.
Please.
Okay.
Thank you.
Are you nervous?
Yes.
Do you get used to it quickly?
I'm a little confused.
Because you don't know what to do?
Yes.
You did a good job.
Did I?
Yes.
It feels good to do it quickly.
It feels good.
Almost no one comes at this time.
Let's take a break.
Is it okay?
You'll get tired even if you stand still all the time.
It's okay because you'll get tired when customers come.
I see.
Let's take a break in the back.
Okay.
Are you okay with your legs?
I'm okay.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Let's take a break.
Okay.
It's like this.
It's good to work slowly.
I have a newspaper to do.
I always have a fight with my eyes.
I thought it was this time.
Oh, this.
What is it?
Do you eat this?
No, I don't.
The manager told me not to eat the waste.
I think it's okay.
You eat it every time.
And the camera over there.
If you don't like it, you've already been warned.
It's good.
I think it's okay.
You must be hungry.
There is a lot of food.
Then, I'll eat it.
Okay.
Oh, it's the same one.
It's good.
How is it?
It's good to eat at this time.
That's right.
How old are you, Misaki?
I'm 33 years old.
33 years old?
Yes.
You're over 10 years old.
You're an adult.
Are you a student?
I'm a professional student.
I want to compose songs.
Do you know DTM?
Yes.
I'm editing videos.
But it doesn't work at all.
It's a great world.
My dream is to produce an idol and make a world debut.
Dream?
Don't you have a dream?
I don't have a dream since I got married.
I see.
Marriage is a dream for me, too.
I admire you.
You're a good person, aren't you?
I was a good person at first.
It's a common thing.
I see.
It depends on the timing.
I don't know.
That's right.
It's packed.
I can't take it.
Welcome.
Midnight.
Kanna Misaki.
Wash your hands.
I'm hungry.
I'll get going.
It's been a while since I've done this, so I'm going to clean up the mess I've made in the past few days.
I'm going to clean up the mess I've made in the past few days.
I would love to be able to say that way to you.
Oh, good work.
Good work.
I get into the habit of trimming the protective clothes while running errands.
I always make sure to put the protective clothes on in before I leave.
This is the first time I've seen such a large room in my life.
I'm not sure if it's because I've lived here for a long time,
or if it's because I've lived here for a long time,
but I think it's because I've lived here for a long time.
I'm not sure if it's because I've lived here for a long time,
Is there a problem?
I also thought about this a while ago.
You sometimes look angry or sad.
Really?
No.
Is that so?
Well, it's a late-night part-time job, so I think it's okay to be polite.
Misaki, you should definitely smile.
I understand.
Also, I've been working here for a long time, but I'm younger than you, so it's hard for me to use honorifics.
Well, I understand.
That's good. I like that smile.
Shall we go?
Yes.
Oh, you're using honorifics again.
I'm counting on you.
Hey!
Midnight.
Kanna Misaki.
Oh, you're fast.
I'm going to check the fridge.
Yes.
Could you leave it to me?
No problem.
Thank you.
Misaki.
Yes?
I have a client who wants to apply for a job.
I can't do it, so could you do it for me?
Oh, I understand.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
What are you going to do?
I'm sorry.
You dropped this, didn't you?
Yes.
And this plate is the last one.
Thank you for waiting.
What happened to the client?
Look at this.
It's a mess.
I'm sorry.
And this is the last one.
I only drink this coffee.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm going to look for that plate again.
Could you wait a moment?
Do you have it?
I'm sorry.
Hurry up.
It's terrible.
I can't give this to the client.
I only drink this coffee.
Oh, I see.
And I don't have a place to put this.
This is the last one.
I'm sorry.
Please be careful.
This is the same product as the last one.
Please look at this.
If you don't have a wound, I'll give it to you.
That's fine.
I'll give it to you.
Okay.
Be careful.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad you came back.
I was a little impatient.
I was surprised when you said that.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was on the way.
It was almost over.
You work fast.
I learned it.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
I'm sorry.
Were you awake?
Yes.
I was thirsty.
There was nothing in the refrigerator.
But we have to work together.
I can't help it.
If we don't work together, we won't be able to live.
What do you mean?
You want me to work harder?
That's not what I mean.
Let's talk about that at home.
It's 1,010 yen.
It's a little cheap.
I can't do that.
I have to pay for it.
You can pretend to sell it.
I can't do that.
You can.
It's a part-time job.
Sir.
This is a product.
Please buy it.
What is it?
It's not a part-time job.
It's a part-time job.
If that's the case, let's talk in the back.
How much is it?
I'll pay for it.
Thank you.
How much is it?
It's 1,010 yen.
Do you want me to put it in a bag?
No, it's okay.
It's 1,010 yen.
Thank you.
What's the receipt?
I don't know.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Thank you for helping me the other day.
Is he your current husband?
Yes.
I don't know.
I think it's hard to get married.
I think so, too.
It's better not to marry someone you really want to marry.
What?
Did you think so?
I did.
At that time.
What's that?
I don't know.
Are you laughing?
No.
At midnight.
Kanna Misaki.
It's quiet.
Yes.
I'll do it today.
You two can go ahead.
What?
You've been standing for a long time, and your back hurts, right?
Yes.
Then, you go ahead.
Thank you for your hard work.
Excuse me.
See you tomorrow.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm tired.
I'm tired, too.
Did something happen?
Yes.
You got up at a strange time.
Yes, I did.
Are you hungry?
I'm a little hungry.
There's a ramen restaurant nearby that serves ramen until late. Do you want to go there?
Ramen?
What?
Are you worried about calories?
Is the ramen there using tuna broth?
It's really good.
It's healthy.
What do you think?
Then, I'll go.
Will you go?
Yes.
Then, I'll wait for you in front of the restaurant.
All right.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
I'll go.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Here you are.
Thank you.
It's all right. I bought it.
I didn't pay for it.
Really?
Yes.
Then, I'll go.
It was really good. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I invited you, but you treated me to a meal.
It's all right. You're my senior in life.
But, I'm your senior in part-time job.
You're right.
Pay me.
I don't want to.
After all, you're my senior.
By the way,
you live close to my house, don't you?
Yes, but why?
You know, there's no train at this time.
It's hard to go home because it's far away.
You're right.
If you don't mind,
let's go to the park.
I want to talk to you.
All right.
Just a moment.
Thank you.
Isn't it nice here?
Yes, it is.
Thank you.
Misaki, you're a good teacher, aren't you?
You learn quickly and you're very helpful.
Really?
I'm good at teaching.
I'm glad to hear that.
By the way,
do you have sexual harassment?
Yes, I do.
What is sexual harassment?
I see.
I had it before.
It's when a pretty girl does sexual harassment to a cute girl at work.
I see.
I wish I didn't have it.
You're beautiful.
Maybe.
What?
Am I beautiful?
Yes.
I think you're very beautiful.
You have the charm of an adult.
Really?
I'm glad to hear that.
I mean it.
What?
It's nice.
It's quiet in the park at night.
Yes, it is.
It's been a while since I said that.
Hey.
Misaki.
Can I kiss you?
Sure.
I was thinking the same thing.
What?
How about this?
It's good.
I like it.
We still have time until the departure.
It's cold.
Why don't we go to a warm place?
Let's go.
I'll go next.
Okay.
Let's sit down and talk.
Why did you kiss me?
Because you're beautiful.
That's why I wanted to kiss you.
I'm glad to hear that.
But...
I know you're married.
So...
I don't know why I didn't meet you earlier.
I'm frustrated.
I'm sorry for kissing you.
I'm sorry.
I know it's not good.
Let's go home.
Wait.
I...
I wanted to kiss you.
I kissed you because I felt the same way.
That's why I came to the hotel.
Can I kiss you?
I'm glad to hear that.
I...
You're beautiful.
I'm good.
I'm fine.
Okay.
This is what I like.
Very good.
I'm glad.
I'm so happy.
I'm happy.
Thank you.
So beautiful...
Really?
What?
What's up?
He is very sleepy.
He is sleeping.
You are making it difficult.
I'm sorry.
I'll never forgive you.
I'm going to give you a massage.
Are you nervous?
Can I eat this?
I want to eat this.
Why?
Why are you frowning?
It's cold and I'm freezing.
Really?
Can I touch you?
I see.
It's been a while, so I don't know what to do.
Can I touch you?
It's okay.
You don't like it?
Can I touch you?
It's okay.
You don't like it?
Can I touch you?
Do you like me now?
Thank you.
I don't have such a thing.
I don't mean I don't like you.
I see.
I think it's right.
Yes.
It's difficult.
My hands are slippery.
Your hands are slippery?
Yes.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Does it hurt?
Not at all.
I'm fine.
Thank you.
It's very beautiful.
Yes.
I'll do this.
I'm fine.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sleepy.
...
What do you mean?
What you mean is…
I mean…
Ouch!
She's trembling.
He's so strong.
It's cold.
Good.
Please treat me nicely just for this weekday.
They are so close to each other.
This is bad.
I'm going to cry.
Please move as you like.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
It's a little strong.
I'm going to cry.
I'm embarrassed.
I can't do this.
It's ok.
Do you know how much time I've been waiting for you replacement so far?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It does, doesn't it?
I want to do it more.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It does, doesn't it?
It tickles.
Wait a minute.
Thank you.
It's a little embarrassing.
You did it.
I did it.
Do you regret it?
No, I don't.
Are you cold?
You look so cute.
Do I?
You said it for the first time.
It was very beautiful.
It was beautiful.
It tickles.
It's been a while, but I think I did it.
You can do it, can't you?
I may not be able to do it.
That's not true.
I don't think so.
This is the most exciting thing I've ever done.
Do you want me to teach you?
No, I don't.
What is it?
You're staring at me.
It's beautiful.
That's all I can say.
What is it?
Do you want to take a shower together?
Together?
No.
I'm nervous.
Because...
Don't you feel embarrassed to be in the shower?
Now?
No.
I'm going to take a shower.
I don't want to.
I'm going to fall asleep.
I'll be back.
What day is your next part-time job?
My part-time job?
Shift.
I'm Yosuke Sui.
Really?
Why is it so real all of a sudden?
I remembered.
It's good for a part-time job.
Why?
I met you because of my part-time job.
You're right.
It's Wednesday.
What?
Midnight.
Kanna Misaki.
I remembered.
Do you often do that?
What do you mean?
Like one night?
I don't do that.
I see.
Hey.
You're thinking about something erotic, aren't you?
What?
Yes.
Do you want to do it here?
No.
I don't want to do it here.
Then, come here.
Come here.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Midnight.
It's hot.
You're excited, aren't you?
I want to do many things with you.
I want to do it, too.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It's hot.
Your lower back is moving.
Welcome.
Thank you.
It's hot.
You're excited, aren't you?
I thought my heart would pop out.
It didn't pop out.
Midnight.
Kanna Misaki.
It's hot.
You have to be quiet.
Do you want to try it?
It's hot.
Try it.
It's hot here.
I'm going to give you a massage
It feels good
It's hot
I'm going to give you a massage
Give me a massage
It feels good
It's hot
Give me a massage
Are you okay?
It's hot
I drank it
Really?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry
I'm going to sleep
In the middle of the night
You have time today
That's right
Don't you get sleepy?
Not that sleepy
Why?
Just a little
Why do you have a free time
I see.
Hey, can I borrow this?
Oh, sure.
Here you are.
Thank you.
That'll be 1,200 yen.
Here's your phone number.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Can I leave it like this?
Sure.
Hey,
since no one's coming,
how about
buying this?
Sure.
Are you sure?
I bought it for you.
I'll go to the back.
Okay.
Here you are.
I'll go to the back.
Thank you.
Here you are.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I'll go to the back.
Here you are.
Thank you.
It's hot.
I did as you said.
I'll put this on you.
I can't do it well.
How do you want me to put this on you?
From the back.
Like this?
No.
It's hot.
It's hard to put this on you.
You have to hold your voice.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Your voice is coming out.
I'll compress it.
It's hot.
Welcome.
Please wait a moment.
Thank you for waiting.
It's 108 yen.
I'll pay it.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Is it okay?
Thank you very much.
I was very impatient.
I was careless because I thought no one would come.
Can I see your hair?
Where?
I was impatient.
Your hair is white.
I was very excited.
I'll do it again.
Midnight.
I'll put this in your hair.
What?
Your hair.
I'll put this in your hair.
Did you bring it?
It's amazing, isn't it?
Here?
Please bear with me.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I feel like I'm going to fall asleep.
Can I help you?
No.
I can't do it.
I'll help you.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
It's midnight.
I'm going to bed.
It's a nice day, isn't it?
That's right.
Good morning.
Did you have any problems?
No problem at all.
Then you two can meet.
Thank you for your hard work.
Let's go.
Can I have some water?
No.
Are you going to school after this?
Is that so?
Don't you come to my house?
Misaki's house?
Yes.
What about your husband?
I have something to tell you.
My husband leaves in the morning.
I'm fine.
Is that so?
Really?
I'll text you his address later.
Okay.
I'll call you when he leaves.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Thank you for your hard work.
The seasoning is a little thin.
I'll be careful.
The rice is a little hard.
The rice is too soft.
I'm sorry.
Can you add more meat?
I can't wait until lunch.
Why don't you make it yourself?
I work every day until morning.
I'm tired.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to work.
Excuse me.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I...
I'm thinking of quitting my current job.
I'm sorry.
Actually, I work at a supermarket during the day.
If I work at night, my body will break.
Don't push yourself.
I'm sorry.
I thought my heart would also be broken.
I've done a lot of exciting things in the store.
I'm a little happy.
But I couldn't forget it right away, so I read it.
I'm sorry.
That's why I read it.
This is...
I think it's a kejime.
Can I do it?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'll make you feel better.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's a bit intense today, isn't it?
It's the last one, isn't it?
It's a bit...
It's getting intense, isn't it?
Would you like me to apply it like this?
It's okay.
Like this.
It's a bit...
It's a bit sad to think that I can't do it anymore.
Please don't forget me.
No.
I'm doing it to forget you.
It's okay.
I'll do my best not to have any regrets.
It feels good.
It's okay.
Can you do it?
I have to forget you.
It's painful if I don't forget you.
It's okay.
What's wrong?
I don't want to end this.
But it'll end someday.
I have to end this.
I don't want to end this.
No.
We can't continue this forever.
Let's end this.
It's painful.
I'm sorry.
Where is the tissue?
Over there.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Are you crying?
I won't cry.
You look like you're crying.
Did you get used to it?
I can't forget it.
I'm sorry.
Midnight.
Kanna Misaki.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's been a while.
What's wrong?
I thought I'd go shopping.
I see.
Thank you.
There are no customers as usual.
It doesn't change at all.
It's always like this.
How is Misaki?
Well.
It's normal.
I see.
How about you?
I'm fine.
I see.
That's good.
Actually,
I came here because I wanted to see your face.
Hey.
There are no customers now.
Thank you for your hard work.