I'm going to paint Niiano's nails!
What?
Cheers!
It's the end of the year!
Akari, Toma, are you going home tomorrow?
I'm going to work a part-time job tomorrow, so what about the day after tomorrow?
Ah, that's right!
For Me, it's around the end of the year ...
New Year's?
You're lucky, Suzuka.
You're in Hawaii with your family.
You're so rich.
I'm so lucky to live in a place like this.
Are you going to Hawaii with me?
I'm looking forward to your wedding.
No, I'm not going.
I have a part-time job.
I see.
I'm nervous when I'm with my parents.
You should come with me.
You're in Hawaii.
I'm nervous when I'm with my parents.
They're rich.
Don't say that.
Saito, you're serious.
You're working hard on your part-time job.
Say hello to them.
Okay.
Saito, when are you going home?
I can't go home yet.
I have a part-time job.
When the New Year's holiday is over, let's go on a trip together.
That's a good idea.
Where do you want to go?
I want to go to a hot spring.
Do you want to go to a hot spring?
That's a good idea.
Let's go to a hot spring.
Let's rent a car and drive for two hours.
I can't drive.
I don't want to drive.
That's not good.
You can't drive.
You have a driver's license, right?
I have a driver's license, but I can't drive.
Have you gained weight recently?
No.
You used to be thinner.
That's true.
I like you more.
You used to be thinner.
Why did you gain so much weight?
I don't know.
You're a happy fat person.
I used to like being thinner.
I think I'm better off being fat.
If you say that, I'll get fat.
It's better to be a little chubby.
I don't want to be chubby.
I feel safe.
I want you to lose more weight.
I'll be careful.
Don't eat too much rice.
You almost ate Takoyaki.
Toma, let's talk.
Why are you alone?
I don't know.
Are you drunk?
I'm not drunk, but I'm a little drunk.
Let's talk.
Are you okay?
To be honest, I'm a little drunk.
Really?
I'm a little drunk.
Did you drink that much?
Two glasses.
Isn't that weak?
You're weak.
I can't drink a single glass.
Really?
I drink with my friends on my birthday.
I see.
I thought you were a strong drinker.
I'm sorry.
I bought a lot of alcohol.
You like alcohol, too.
I'm a strong drinker.
You don't get drunk at all.
I'm worried.
Pizza is delicious.
Yoshida can't come today.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'll call you later.
Okay.
I'm home.
Are you okay?
Did you drink too much?
Do you want to kiss me?
No.
Why?
Because I like you.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
I'm here.
Calm down.
Do you want to kiss me?
No.
No?
I'm sorry.
Do you want to drink water?
I'll be back.
Wait a minute.
I'm home.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm going to run out of battery.
Really?
I'm going home.
What about Akari?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I can't run because I'm dizzy.
I don't have enough battery.
Do you want me to stay here?
It's dangerous.
It's not dangerous.
I'm not drunk.
It's not my house.
I'll stay here.
I'll be home early tomorrow.
Really?
Thank you.
You helped me a lot.
I'm going home.
Have a happy new year.
Thank you.
I didn't bring my pajamas.
I'll bring it.
Really? Thank you.
You helped me a lot.
Everyone left.
I'm going to take a break.
Suzuka was drunk.
I don't want to kiss you.
I'm sorry.
Don't you sleep?
Did I wake you up?
No.
Let's drink.
I'll drink this.
Cheers.
What's wrong?
I didn't do anything.
Who did you go out with?
I didn't tell you?
It's a customer who comes to my part-time job first.
So I went out with him.
I see.
I thought you confessed to Saito.
No.
Didn't you like Suzuka?
At first.
I won't tell you.
What did you like about Suzuka?
I don't know.
After all.
I'm grateful that you like me.
I see.
What if I told you that I like you?
What?
I was really curious.
I'm glad you told me.
It's a long time ago.
I see.
Do you like me?
What?
No.
Aren't you interested in me?
Aren't you my type?
What?
What's wrong with you?
Don't be so serious.
I'm sorry.
Were you really interested in me?
Yes.
What?
You're popular.
You're cool.
No.
Why?
I'm fat.
Don't you cheat on me?
I'm not good at it.
Suzuka?
Yes.
I see.
Aren't you good at it?
I'm not good at it.
I see.
Hey.
What?
I'm not good at it.
What's wrong with you?
You're funny.
It's just a touch.
You're drinking too much.
I don't think so.
You're cute.
I like people like you.
Calm down.
I'm calm.
If you make a fuss, I'll wake up.
Yes.
What do you mean?
I have to go back.
I can't sleep if I drink this.
If you drink this?
Then I'll make you drink it.
You've been thinking about it since you kissed me.
You wanted to kiss me more.
I don't think so.
You'll be fine.
I'm sleeping, so I won't wake up for a while.
Just be quiet.
Your eyes are getting bigger.
I'm sorry.
You made your eyes bigger.
I just kissed you.
You wanted to kiss me, didn't you?
You're naughty.
I'm going crazy.
What is it?
I don't think I can go any further.
Why?
Because you'll be found out?
I can't stop it.
What do you want to do?
You wanted to do it, didn't you?
I thought you wanted to do it because you'd be found out.
You want to do it, don't you?
I can't do it.
You can't do it?
I'll put a nail in your boob.
It hurts, doesn't it?
You want to touch me, don't you?
Wait a minute.
Come on.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You want me to come?
No.
Look at me.
I made a sound.
What do you mean?
It's weird.
That's not true.
I've been thinking about it.
I love people like you.
Don't say that.
Why?
I can't do it.
Because you're shaking.
You just touched me, didn't you?
I touched you.
How was it?
It's weird.
I love you.
Wait a minute.
It's weird.
What?
You're shaking.
What do you mean?
I'm going to seduce you.
You're shaking.
I can't touch you.
You can't touch me?
Then I'll touch you.
You don't touch me, do you?
That's not true.
Do you want to be with me?
Of course.
When was the last time you touched me?
It's been a week.
I see.
You want to touch me more, don't you?
You're so quiet.
You won't do this to me, will you?
If I touch you, you'll find out.
I'm afraid you'll find out.
Of course.
It's dangerous.
Does it feel good?
No, it's not like that.
That's right.
It's ticklish.
It doesn't feel good.
Let it out.
It's ticklish.
How do you feel about me?
It's normal.
What do you mean?
It's not normal for me.
I don't do that.
I see.
But you wanted me to do this, didn't you?
That's not true.
You're so scared.
You didn't want me to do this.
I see.
You can feel it so much.
Do you kiss Saito-kun?
Do you feel good?
I'm just kissing you.
You're so big.
You weren't expecting this, were you?
It's okay.
You won't wake up if you're quiet.
What?
You don't want to wake up, do you?
You don't want to?
You've never kissed me, have you?
I've never kissed you.
You're serious.
Why are you hiding it?
Show me.
I can't.
Saito-kun has a lot of pimples.
I don't have pimples.
You don't have pimples?
Isn't it good if you don't have pimples?
You're not excited, are you?
You're lying.
Do you think so?
Have you ever been touched?
No.
It's a strange feeling, isn't it?
You can't say it out loud.
You'll be noticed.
By your favorite Suzuka.
Oh.
Does it feel good?
It's good.
Wash your hands and move.
I can't do it here.
Why?
Did you lick Suzuka, too?
That's right.
What?
Don't you want me to lick you?
To me.
I don't want you to lick me.
Why do you say that?
I can't do it.
You're squinting.
Didn't you want to see me again?
That's not true.
I see.
Then...
I'll make you feel better.
How does Suzuka lick you?
Or...
I'll do this for you.
You're squinting.
That's my heart.
It felt good.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
So I can't do it.
Why?
I'm scared.
But I'm telling you to do it more.
Don't you want me to do it more?
Because it's bad for Suzuka?
That's right.
Then you don't have to do it.
That's...
I can't do it.
You can't do it?
Why?
You said it felt good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You can't do it?
I can't do it.
Why?
You're holding back because it feels good.
If it feels good,
I'll do it.
You can't do it?
Me?
I can't do it.
Why are you kissing me?
I haven't done it yet.
You did it on your own.
Me?
That's right.
I did it on my own.
You're wearing Suzuka's pajamas.
What are you doing?
You can do it on your own.
I did it on my own.
You don't have to lick me.
I'm just licking you on my own.
Have you ever done this with Suzuka?
I haven't.
You haven't.
Have you ever licked Suzuka?
I haven't.
Okay.
But did you want to lick me?
Yes.
Why don't you put your tongue out?
Does it feel good?
I'm just licking you on my own.
What's wrong?
I'm going.
Are you going?
Yes.
Do you always throw away the garbage when you have sex with Suzuka?
I do.
Do you?
I see.
I'm going to put it in.
No.
You can't.
Wait a minute.
Don't you want to put your tongue out?
That's...
I see.
You're already like this.
I can't.
Why?
Is it cheating when you have sex?
No.
I don't know.
Is it cheating when you kiss?
Is it cheating when you rub each other like this?
That's...
I haven't done anything.
That's right.
You haven't done anything yet.
You haven't done anything yet, so it's not cheating.
Do you feel good?
You feel so good that you can't speak.
It's all the way in.
Look at me.
You did it.
You haven't done anything yet, so it's not cheating.
Do you feel good?
Do you feel better than I thought?
Don't ask me that.
Why?
Because it's true.
If you talk too much, you'll wake up.
Why are you holding your breath?
Look at me.
You haven't done anything yet, so it's not cheating.
Did I say it's amazing?
What's amazing?
What's different?
Your hips are moving.
Isn't it amazing?
You want to kiss me, don't you?
Isn't it?
It's not cheating.
You're cheating.
It's all my fault.
You can't do that.
What's wrong?
If you do that, I'll go out.
You can't go out?
You can't do that.
Then you have to go out.
What's wrong?
I'm going crazy.
You can't go out?
I can't.
Because I have you.
If you don't do anything, it's not cheating.
You can't do anything.
I don't know.
Does it feel good?
Are you going to go out?
It's all my fault.
You didn't do anything.
Look at me.
I can't.
You can't?
Why can't you?
If I go out, I'll do it.
What's that?
I'm letting you go out.
I'm doing everything.
It's not cheating, is it?
It's my fault that you feel good.
It's my fault that the player goes out.
Maya wants to act hot on you, but she's having fun!
You are crying.
Just a minute.
It will be okay soon.
Don't do this.
I'm doing all this by myself.
There's no swearing.
Why?
If you speak out loud, they' ll hear all about it.
Do you want me to kiss you?
Do you want me to kiss you to make you feel good?
No, no, no.
No?
Who makes you feel good?
No, no, no.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It looks painful.
Ah!
I covered your voice with a kiss.
You're a bad person.
Isn't it cheating to kiss?
Hey.
I didn't mean that.
Huh?
I kissed you, didn't I?
It's enough, isn't it?
Why?
You haven't kissed me yet.
Hey.
What?
Let's end this.
Why?
You haven't kissed me yet.
No.
You wanted to touch me, didn't you?
You're not a monster because I let you touch me, aren't you?
You wanted to touch me.
Have you ever touched my breast?
Yes, I have.
Yes, you have.
How was my breast?
It was a little small, but it doesn't matter now.
I love you.
I love you, too.
You're a bad person.
What?
I'll make it.
You can't make it?
Yes.
All right.
It's hard to be found out by Suzuko, isn't it?
But you have to be found out by Suzuko.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
You're getting warmer.
What?
Am I getting warmer?
Yes.
Why?
I don't know why, but I feel good.
My voice comes out.
I feel good and my voice comes out.
What?
You kissed me.
You kissed me, so I left.
That's enough.
Why?
I'm at my limit.
What?
Why?
You don't have to put up with it.
Why can't I stop?
Of course.
I can't.
You have to put up with it.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
Why?
So you don't have to put up with it?
No, that's not what I meant.
If you put up with it, you'll find out.
I'm sorry.
Don't be mad at me.
I'm doing this on my own, so I'm not mad at you.
I'm sorry.
It's delicious.
It's a secret.
I'm sorry.
Akari.
Akari, wake up.
I don't have time, so I'm going.
I'm sorry.
I'll be back in three days, so look forward to the souvenirs.
Yeah, be careful.
I'll be back.
I'm sorry.
Good morning.
What are you doing?
I'm making breakfast.
I see.
Did Suzuko go already?
Yeah, she said it's time to fly, so she went.
I see.
What are you making?
I don't know.
I'm eating.
I know you want to eat more.
Look over there.
Let's kiss.
I'm sorry.
You're hitting me.
Hey, Asadachi.
Are you excited to be with me?
I remembered what happened yesterday.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to do.
Are you okay?
I can't tell you
When will it be my turn?
powder
I can't tell you
I'm sorry.
Are you happy?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You want to go out, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
I said it too soon.
I want to do more.
Come here.
Do you want to sleep?
I'm sleepy.
What should I do?
I can't help it.
Hang in there.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
I'm sleepy.
Don't tickle me.
I don't want to.
Come here.
I'm sleepy.
Touch me.
You were waiting for me, weren't you?
I'm sleepy.
Are you sleepy?
I'll put you to sleep.
I'm sleepy.
Do you feel good?
I can't help it.
I'll put you to sleep.
Do you want more?
I can't help it.
I'm sleepy.
I'll put you to sleep.
Do you like it?
Do you want more?
I can't help it.
Are you okay?
I'm sleepy.
Can you see me?
Do you feel good?
I can't help it.
Do you want to sleep?
I'm sleepy.
You were thinking about yesterday, weren't you?
Do you feel good?
I'm sleepy.
Do you want to sleep?
I can't help it.
Who do you want to sleep with?
I want to sleep with you.
Good job.
I can't help it.
Do you feel good?
I'm sleepy.
I can't help it.
Do you feel good?
I've never done this before.
I can't help it.
It's okay.
I'll give you a bath.
I can't help it.
It feels so good.
I'm getting sleepy.
You've seen a lot of them, haven't you?
Why are you still standing?
Because I'm sleepy.
I want to eat it.
Wait, wait.
I'm going to eat it now.
Oh, no.
I'm sleepy.
Help me.
It feels so good.
I'm getting sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
It feels so good.
My back won't stop.
Me, too.
I'm sleepy.
It's okay.
Let me out of your stomach one more time.
I can't.
You can't, can you?
If you let me out of your stomach, I'll kill you.
I'm sleepy.
I'm getting sleepy.
I'm out of my stomach.
I'm still out of my stomach.
That's not fair, Akari.
Why?
I'm out of my stomach.
It's your fault, Akari.
Is it my fault?
I'm sleepy.
It's refreshing.
Don't you take a lot of pictures?
I don't usually take pictures.
Why?
I'm a little embarrassed.
What?
You look excited.
I'm having fun.
I'm glad to hear that.
It's a little cold, isn't it?
You're right.
I'm glad the weather is nice.
It's better than a date.
You're right.
It's been a year.
That's right.
It's almost New Year's Day.
Do you eat soba?
I do.
Really?
I like warm soba.
Don't you eat soba?
I don't eat soba.
Let's eat soba together.
You're taking a lot of pictures.
My arms are getting tired.
Do you want to take a picture?
I'll bring it to you.
You're tired, aren't you?
Do you like taking pictures?
I do.
I see.
I don't usually take pictures.
Do you have any plans for next year?
I don't know.
Next year...
Don't you have any plans?
Me?
I'm going to lose weight.
Why?
I'm going to lose weight next year.
You're cute and I like you.
That's too much.
I think it's okay to be cute.
What should I do to lose weight?
Diet?
I don't think so.
Do you usually eat too much?
I don't think I'm eating.
But when I think about it,
I feel like I'm on a diet.
What's that?
I don't eat much.
I know.
I feel like I'm not eating.
You eat a lot.
I eat a lot.
What's your favorite food?
I like sweets.
Me too.
I like custard.
Do you like custard cream?
I know.
I like whipped cream more than custard.
I like whipped cream and chocolate.
I'm home.
Did you walk a lot?
I'm sorry I made you walk a lot.
It was fun.
Did you take a picture?
Yes.
Let's go home.
It's warm.
It was a little cold.
I didn't change my clothes.
I borrowed it from Suzuka.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Does it look good on me?
Yes.
Which do you think is cuter?
What?
I don't know.
Don't push yourself.
I'm not pushing myself.
Really?
I didn't change my clothes.
So I didn't put on underwear.
Did you notice?
Don't tease me.
I'm not teasing you.
Why are you embarrassed?
I'm sorry.
Who is it?
Suzuka.
I'm sorry.
I'll call you back.
Okay.
Hello.
Yes.
I'm fine.
Did you arrive safely?
That's good.
Are you lonely?
I see.
It's warm.
I'm fine.
I see.
It's nothing.
Yes.
I see.
I'll do it.
Did you get on the plane?
Yes.
Really?
I'm fine.
Yes.
I see.
It's nothing.
Yes.
I see.
What?
It's been two days.
I'm fine.
Yes.
I have to be careful.
What?
I drank a lot yesterday.
Yes.
I have to do the laundry.
I'll do it.
I have to be careful.
Yes.
I see.
It's nothing.
Yes.
What?
It's nothing.
Don't worry.
I see.
Yes.
It's nothing.
I see.
I'll do it.
I can't do it.
I'm on the phone.
It's boring.
But you didn't find out.
I was suspicious.
Really?
You didn't find out.
I felt good.
Yes.
I can't do it.
Do you feel good?
Are you excited to see me naked?
No.
You've been like this since you took off your clothes.
I'm not excited.
Do you feel good?
I like your kiss.
You slept a lot.
I can't do that.
Are you angry?
Let's go.
What?
You tried to touch me.
I didn't.
Did you want me to touch you?
What's that?
Do you feel good?
Do you want me to do it again?
I'll do it again.
Did you take it off again?
You're just kissing me.
You're so cute.
Have you been standing like this for a long time?
You're doing it because you want to, right?
I love you.
Thank you for the drink!
Despite the pain and difficulty, thank you for leaving.
It's all thanks to you and everyone who has moved in with us through this difficult time.
But for everyone here in this time,
we're thankful to you and everyone who still has hope when times harsh.
This is crystal clear.
I don't really want to be the one with the negative image.
I wish I could only do my best to give her a smile.
I couldn't stop myself.
It's so hot.
Can you drink it quietly?
I'm sorry, Ishimaru.
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
Do you like it?
Give me your hand.
Did you feel it just by kissing me?
It's so hot.
Who are you comparing me with?
I want you to drink it.
It's so hot.
Do you feel good?
I'm glad.
I hope you feel better.
It's so hot.
I'm sorry.
I'm the only one who feels good.
Why?
You don't like it?
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
I'm glad.
Can you drink it?
It's so hot.
Yes.
I'm going to fall down.
It's so hot.
It's a little painful.
Do you want to sleep?
Yes.
It's so hot.
I love you.
I love you, too.
It's so hot.
Do you always sleep here?
Yes.
Do you want to sleep?
It's so hot.
You're good at sleeping.
I love you.
It's so hot.
You're sweating.
Is it not enough?
It's not enough at all.
It's so hot.
I can feel it, too.
You're sweating a lot.
It's so hot.
Isn't it cold?
It's a little cold.
I'll warm you up.
It's so hot.
It feels good.
Do you feel better?
It's so hot.
It feels good.
It's a little embarrassing.
It's so hot.
Does it feel good?
Do you want to sleep?
Who do you want to sleep with?
I want to sleep with you.
Look at me.
I can't reach you.
I'm right here.
It feels good.
Who do you like?
I'll scratch you.
Do you understand?
Did you feel good?
I did.
It feels good.
Did you feel good?
You fell asleep.
Do you want to go?
Are you still standing?
I'm tired.
Did you fall asleep?
Are you still standing?
I'm tired.
I want to do more.
I'll do my best when I'm tired.
I'm glad you're in a good mood.
What's your name?
My name is Masa.
Can I call you Masa?
Are you sleepy?
Masa.
Are you still standing?
I want you to feel good.
Do you feel good?
Are you still standing?
Your body is warm.
Do you feel good?
Get up!
This feels good.
Have you ever had such a pleasant sex?
Ah, my...
Feels good.
You can still do it, right?
Do you want to do it again?
Yes, I do.
Ah, my...
Why do you keep standing?
It's okay, it's okay.
Ah, my...
I'm addicted to it.
Can you still do it?
Ah, my...
I love you.
Do you want to do it again?
Yes.
I'm full.
I'm so full that I can't believe it.
I love you.
Ah, my...
It hurts.
Ah, it hurts.
Ah, I want to do it again.
I can't.
I can't do it yet.
Ah, it hurts.