Prepare Soda
Soda
It is missing sesame oil.
I put in half a teaspoon of sugar because I like sweet salty taste.
It's hot.
Kazuo, are you back?
I'm back.
I'm back, dad.
It's still hot here.
That's right.
There is no air conditioner in this house.
Let me introduce you.
Hey!
What?
Nice to meet you. I'm Reia.
It's hot.
What's wrong, Kazuo?
Say hello to her.
I'm sorry.
I'm Kazuo. Nice to meet you.
I'm getting old, but I'll be a mother.
Nice to meet you.
I'm coming in.
It's hot.
I didn't expect my dad to remarry.
You're good at cooking, and I envy you.
I know.
I didn't expect to meet such a good wife.
I'm so happy.
It's hot.
What are you looking at?
What?
Are you interested in my mother?
No, I'm not.
You can look at my butt.
It's hot.
I'm going to take a rest.
I haven't done anything for a long time.
I'm bored.
Is there anything to do?
It's hot.
Excuse me.
My dad is so mean.
I don't know what to do.
It's hot.
What's going on?
Can I wash your back?
No.
I can't come back.
My dad will get mad at me.
We're family.
We need to be close to each other.
But...
I'm scared.
Just my back?
Yes.
Please.
My legs?
How do you feel?
I feel good.
I'll wash your feet.
No, please don't.
What's wrong?
What?
Did you take it off?
No, no, no.
I didn't take it off.
You're cute.
Rei-san, it's hot.
My head is hot.
You should stay away from me.
Should I stay away from you?
It's hot.
My head is hot.
I'm touching your neck.
Should I stay away from you?
That's a little...
It's hot.
I forgot to take it off.
I'm going.
Don't you have to wash it?
It's okay.
I'm so excited that I can't sleep.
It's hot.
I had breakfast.
I'm going to work.
Are you going to work today?
Yes.
I had a problem.
I have no choice.
Good luck, Koichi.
I'll do my best.
See you.
I'm going to work.
Are you going out today?
I'm going shopping later.
I see.
I have to wash the dishes.
I'm going to wash the dishes.
Do you know where the medicine for insect bites is?
Do you mean insect bites?
I think...
I think it's around here.
I found it.
This is it.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, but can you apply it to my butt?
Your butt?
My hands are wet.
Okay.
Thank you.
Where is it?
It's around here.
Excuse me.
Is it around here?
No, it's deeper.
Is it deeper?
Is it around here?
It's a little deeper.
Is it deeper?
Yes.
I found something red.
Do you want to apply it?
Yes.
I applied it.
Thank you.
I feel better.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm going to go shopping.
It's hot.
Why isn't it working?
Would you like to drink beer with me?
Yes, please.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
I'm sorry.
You spilled it.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'll bring another one.
What's wrong?
I'm at my limit.
You're seducing me, aren't you?
Seducing you?
I'm going crazy.
You're seducing me.
I can't do this.
Calm down.
I've been watching you.
My father will be angry.
I know.
But I can't stand it.
I'm sorry.
I can't do that.
Why not?
You're seducing me, aren't you?
You're seducing me.
I'm sorry.
It's so soft.
How is it?
Do you like boobs?
I like boobs.
I'm sorry.
It's so soft.
You've been watching me, haven't you?
Did I show you?
It's getting harder.
You've been watching me, haven't you?
You showed me.
So I watched you.
Did I show you?
You did.
I'm sorry.
Calm down.
Are you excited?
I'm sorry.
Show me your boobs.
Please.
Does it hurt?
Yes.
Please.
Are you done?
More.
It's so soft.
Thank you.
I've been curious about you.
Have you?
Did you know me when we first met?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
Like this?
Yes.
Look at me.
What's this?
Don't suck so much.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
I'm getting better.
Really?
I'm sorry.
I want to see this side, too.
This side?
It hurts.
I can't stand it.
Just a little.
Just a little?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Can I see it?
You've seen it, haven't you?
I haven't seen it.
Please.
Don't suck so much.
It's amazing.
It's so beautiful.
Just a little.
Just a little?
It's amazing.
Please open your legs.
It's okay.
Please.
It's amazing.
Just a little more.
Can I take this off?
Please open your legs.
It's amazing.
It's getting harder.
Does it feel good?
It's too sexy.
It's amazing.
It's so sexy.
Can I see it again?
Just a little more.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Can I do more?
I want to see you feel better.
I don't want to be found out.
It's okay.
I don't want to be found out by my father.
I don't want to go home yet.
I have to work.
I know.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
I want to see your buttocks.
What?
I can't move.
It's amazing.
Please come here.
Please be careful.
She is crying.
It's so hot.
What are you wearing?
Can I touch you a little more?
I can't.
I'll make you feel better.
What did you do to me?
It's hot.
Is it hot?
Please look at me.
It's amazing.
It's so beautiful.
I can't stand it anymore.
Let me sleep.
Do you want me to let you sleep?
Please.
I can't sleep.
It hurts.
It feels good.
You like being strong, don't you?
Please look at me.
Why?
Don't open your eyes.
Please hurry up.
It's amazing.
Please look at me.
It feels good.
It's beautiful.
Your eyes are beautiful.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's amazing.
Please look at me.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm sweating.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I want you to hug me more.
I can't stand it anymore.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
I'm rubbing my family's pee in your boob.
Don't say that.
It feels even better.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm going to pee.
Are you going to pee?
Can I pee here?
It's amazing.
Please look at me.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's warm inside.
Did you want to be here all the time?
Please look at me.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Can I rub your butt?
Does it feel good?
It's warm.
Chin up.
with my
Do it more
Does that feel good?
Does it feel good?
That's amazing
Can I move?
Do it more
That's amazing
Does that feel good?
Can I move?
That's amazing
This is a secret between us
Beer on a hot day is good
Hey, Katsuo
What are you doing?
Did you hear what I said?
Sorry, what?
Beer on a hot day is good
That's right
It's good
I'm sweating
I'm going to take a bath
I see
It was really hot today
I'm going back to my room
I see
Hold on
Thank you
What's wrong?
I can't hold it anymore
Can I?
Thank you
I'm scared
I can't hold it anymore
Can I?
Don't do that
My mom will get mad
I'll try not to be noticed
Please
Just a little
I'm going to take a nap
Okay
I'm going to take a bath
It feels good
That's good
I'm going to take a bath
What was that?
It's hot
How do you feel?
It feels good
I'm going to take a bath
Please
It's hot
It's warm
My dad will get mad
I'm going to take a bath
I can't hold it
Please
Yeah
Let's go
Wait, I can't keep up
Good job
You were so embarrassed
You look so scary
Yeah...
It's going away.
Here...
Yeah...
I'm sorry.
I'm holding you so tight.
Don't say that.
You're so cute.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
You're about to come out.
You can come out.
I'm sorry.
You have a lot of hair.
I'm scared.
It stinks.
Wait a minute.
It feels so good.
What's wrong?
More.
My hand is stuck somewhere.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
What is it?
Didn't you see Rei?
I went shopping.
Did you go shopping?
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Are you cooking?
I'll help you.
What are you doing?
Hey.
Don't you want me to help you?
I want you to help me.
But my father will come back.
Are you scared?
No.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
I can't see.
Isn't it more fun to be with you?
It's more fun to be with you.
It's painful.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
I'm going to have a stomachache.
Do you want to see your stomach?
No.
I don't want to put vegetables in my stomach.
It's too much.
My stomach is growling.
Do you want to see my stomach?
I want to see it.
Your stomach is growling.
I'm sorry.
Let me see your stomach.
My stomach is growling.
Your stomach is growling.
Let me see your stomach.
Okay.
Your stomach is growling.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It hurts.
Why did you go?
It's beautiful.
Is it really beautiful?
Can you help me?
Put it in your mouth.
It's hot.
Hold my hand.
Look at me.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
I can't hold it anymore.
I want to hug you.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I still have a stomachache.
I want you to get well soon.
I'm sick.
I can't hold it anymore.
I want you to get well soon.
Your father may come back.
But, I can't hug you anymore.
She's sick, so I want to do something.
Too hot!
Oh, it's hot.
Give me a kiss.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to suck on my dick.
You want me to suck on your dick?
Say it.
I want you to suck on my dick.
Okay.
Oh, it's hot.
Give me a kiss.
Do you want me to suck on your dick?
I want you to suck on my dick.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, my god.
My parents are coming home.
I know.
I'm so erotic.
Hello.
Yes.
Oh, Travolta?
Okay.
I'll be back tomorrow at 4 o'clock.
Yes.
Excuse me.
I can't do it.
I'm so erotic.
It's the worst.
My job is the worst.
Oh, yeah.
I can't go home tomorrow because of my job.
I'm lonely.
I can't help it.
I'll go home sooner or later.
It's a shame that we got along so well.
That's right.
Oh, it's hot.
Kou-ichi, you drank too much.
Don't sleep here.
Get up.
Come on.
Don't sleep here.
Get up.
I'm lonely.
I'll be lonely from tomorrow.
We're just getting started.
Yes.
I can't help it.
You shouldn't sleep here.
If I sleep here, I'll get drunk.
But I can't help it.
I can't help it.
Dad is sleeping.
Are you okay?
What if he finds out?
I can't go home.
I love you.
I can't help it.
Can I kiss you?
Yes.
I'll lick you more.
It's nice.
I'll kiss you a little more.
I'll kiss you more.
I'll get your belly curled...
Oh, no...
I'm going to go home tomorrow.
I want to make it a memory.
I miss you.
I can't forget you.
Get a hold of yourself.
I miss you.
Does it feel good?
It feels great.
I love you.
Don't cry.
It feels good.
I love you.
Look at me.
It feels good.
I want to hug you.
Really?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I love you.
Don't cry.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I love you.
It's the last one.
I want to eat a lot.
I love you.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Can I take a picture of you?
I'll take a picture of you, too.
It's the last one.
Can I lick you more?
I love you.
I want to see you more.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I love you.
I'm at my limit.
Look at me.
I love you.
Everyone, move.
I'll tuck you.
One, two.
Can I give you a kiss?
How do you feel?
It feels so good.
You look cute.
You look beautiful.
Look at me.
Look at my face.
How do you feel?
It feels so good.
Can I touch your back?
How do you feel?
It feels so good.
Your neck is warm.
How do you feel?
You can come back anytime.