Sorry for the late. sorry.
Just stay here.
Sorry to say goodbye.
Sorry to.
First of all, I am a little uncomfortable, but
Can you please introduce yourself a little?
Can I ask your name and your profession?
Oh yes yes.
Fujitsu is out.
Yes, her profession is actress.
It is right?
Yes yes yes.
The actress AV.
You are a shy guy, right?
How long will you be in Dallas?
Debut for a year, a year or so.
A year a little.
How many shows did you feel?
Oh, how many are they?
Maybe six or seven books.
7 Pope, I know.
and photographing?
Yes to.
You are a photographer, you are an actor?
The actor, is it?
How is sex with an actor?
I did take the picture, so I didn’t have the opportunity at first.
I’ve gotten used to it more and more recently, and it’s a little, a little, surprising.
Is he feeling good?
Oh yeah, it is great.
Thank you very much. thank you.
Even if it is private, including photographing.
Who do you like to attack if you attack?
I think I was more likely to be attacked at first.
If you were to attack or even work, it was surprisingly fun, and I recently realized a bit of fun.
It also makes it a bit fun to attack.
I am enjoying the reaction of the other.
I feel more and more open than I was a year ago.
You ask me what I’m doing today?
Maybe you didn’t listen.
Today, I think I should be able to talk to the amateur.
Talk about the amateur.
Amateur or general?
Yes, the general people.
Are you interested in talking about trouble?
Private
Is it different sex?
Other than same sex.
But maybe they didn’t step in.
No one stepped in.
by Lia
There have been some nice people lately.
I hear such stories.
What should I do about it?
Talk a little bit of anxiety and anxiety together.
A fun conversation between the girls.
Do you mean to talk to you?
Oh no is.
No is.
Yes, no is not.
So this is the first?
Oh, so is the first time.
The first time?
Is it true?
Great, something new again.
Mr. Schroots, I have a place to wait for you, so I’m going to go down there for a while, but what about it?
From now on?
I am not prepared for a little bit, but is it okay to be excited?
I’m waiting, can I go and try it a little?
Are you waiting?
Yes, let’s try it a little.
So leave me from here.
Yes to.
Sorry to.
So here here.
Yes, so let’s go.
So let’s try to go quickly.
I think there’s a little staircase there, but can I go up the stairs?
Yes to.
I’ll be here, can I knock you a little?
Hi to.
Hi to you.
So please go.
Okay okay?
Sorry to.
Yes to.
Please go.
Thanks to.
Please sit here.
How about?
Have you ever been to such places?
Is it like a studio?
It feels like that.
There is something, light.
I understood.
I would like to talk to someone who wants to talk to you from now on, but
Can I call you?
Yes to.
So please please.
Please please.
That was the one you just called.
He is a little worried and I hope he can talk to you.
It is the first time I see him that I don’t know who he is.
Yes is it.
Yes is.
So, please introduce yourself and ask for your name and age.
Yes, I say a workforce.
Yes, the master
I am 20 years old and I am a second grade student.
is college student.
Yes is
20 years old, mental or mental.
Yes is.
Do you have a chance to talk to college students?
No, no is not.
Is it not?
Great, meet for a long time.
I’m getting older, recently.
No, is it often said?
How old are you and your pretending?
Okay, well, but more than one time.
It is he, but Mr. Fujitsu has a special feeling, but can I ask him for a little bit?
Oh yes, what is it?
I am also a fan of Fujitsu.
Did you see something from me?
I am so happy, how long have you watched it?
I see it all, check it out.
All of it?
I am surprised to be here with you now.
Is there a lot of communication with such fans?
I am not, because I have a little history.
Or even an event?
I didn’t even go to the event, I thought I wanted to do a little.
First time I met your fans, how about?
I am glad to hear a lot of great voice.
I am glad, and I too.
Well, he has a real problem, and I think he wants to solve it with Mr. Fosaki, but can you listen to that problem?
If you want to be me, listen to me.
I have no girlfriends.
A girl’s friend?
Are you not in a movie school?
It’s not a school for men, right?
The university is different, but the high school is a male school.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Oh, but something like that.
Are there any good kids in the first job?
What do you say, pretty?
I can’t talk, from old.
You want a girlfriend, right?
I mean female friends.
Oh, but what is it.
Do you want to be able to talk?
How about that?
Is there a ZEIT?
Planning with everyone.
Try to make a wave with everyone.
Let’s do summer camp together.
Is Summer Camp a bit?
Take the harddrive down and make the barbecue together.
Please come here.
Or, in other words, what do you mean by being with a woman?
Without it.
It is not.
In other words, they didn’t meet.
with women.
That means doing something echoing.
Your experience is
No, not the
Oh no is?
No is
Not so much, right?
I do not tie hands.
What do you mean to continue?
is virgin.
The virginity?
I saw a virgin for the first time.
No, something unexpected.
Something is normal.
Ordinary
Usually it seemed like they were playing well.
You are not playing at all, right?
I mean you, Mr Fujitsu.
In fact, he has a real problem with virginity.
We want to resolve it somehow, too.
Mr. Tushman, I have a request.
Can you ask for his loss of virginity?
Sorry, did you say me?
I cannot be.
A little more.
You are far away.
That is absolutely.
Mr. Tushika, I like to be messy.
Is it true?
Yes to.
I think that’s good for a child of the same age.
I think I’m a little older than my mother, but I think she’s younger than my mother.
Probably is.
You are good at pretending.
Sorry, but it will be the first time.
No, it is the first time.
Okay is?
I was looking forward.
Is it true?
So, will you do it?
Okay then
Yes, if it is okay.
really
So a little.
I will come if I disturb you.
So, a little I
Once I let them go away.
A little bit of you two.
I think I should go there.
Sorry, I am sorry.
I was really happy to say I am a fan too.
Is it really more beautiful than you see it live?
Or actually more?
In fact more.
really is?
I wanted to ask for a moment.
Oh well
My own
Wait and wait.
What did you teach me the name?
It is Shantou.
Mr Shane is
Maybe you want to shake.
I will give you the shade.
Mr Shane is
My own
What body parts do you like?
A little bit
Let me hear.
The face.
Oh, it is a face.
Oh yeah yeah.
Are your feet beautiful?
It is a foot fetch.
Oh yeah yeah.
Feet of Feet.
What do you want to do with your foot?
by foot
I just watch, but I act.
Just touching it.
Just touching it?
I want to touch you, I want to look at you.
I am doing something with my own.
It is so soft inside, but it is my own.
Try to touch this one.
Okay okay.
Yes is
Oh here
is true?
You are fucking sweaty.
Is it true?
Oh what to do.
I should have painted it a little more.
Oh at all.
Totally different from me.
It is a bit soft.
and patin.
Thanks to.
Can I touch her a little?
Is it yes?
I have to touch it a little.
Something awesome.
And Harry is.
I sweat it.
A little bit.
Oh awesome.
I feel like a hiccups.
Do you know?
something like this.
I can’t touch this hand so slowly.
Sorry, but I touched it earlier.
No, I am pleased.
I am glad that this is not the case.
Oh yeah yes.
I guess you’re going to be touched here.
From the foot of Feth.
The feet are beautiful, yes.
really
Yes, thank you
You really won’t do it.
I want to kiss.
and kissing.
This is my first kiss.
It was my first kiss.
Yes is it.
Do you want to kiss or something?
No, I am a fan, I don’t want to do anything at all.
Really?
Yes to.
So, is it really okay?
Please please.
Which one? from which one?
Also soft.
Is it true?
It was cute.
thanks to
It is more beautiful when you get nearer.
Very embarrassingly
I would be ashamed if you saw a hole.
No, not at all.
Can I try it down?
Oh I don’t like.
Oh no no
I am pleased.
How to do it?
I will try to put it in first.
Yes please please.
The best.
It is like this.
What do you want next?
I want to see my breasts.
The breast?
Yes is
I will sleep a little.
Oh well.
This too hurts a lot.
These too
Can I try it?
Oh thank you.
Maybe a fox 3.
Okay, how to photograph.
Oh this.
The last one is a bit difficult.
Oh, I photographed it.
It is awesome.
by
It was a dream to photograph.
Really?
Yes, if someone else is taking a third shot, it seems.
Oh yeah yeah?
such a way.
You are already beautiful.
I hid it.
Oh, really, it was a little different.
Oh, it is a shabby tree.
and so on.
Why do I want to see.
Is it a tree?
Which one is better from the front to the back?
What should you think?
But from the back, it may feel like a man is being forced out of the body.
I want to be quoted.
by Qin?
Yes to.
Oh, yes, no, but what do you want?
No, this image was already.
Oh that is.
So, will you try both?
Oh yes yes.
No, but this at all.
Oh no no.
It seems to drink.
Oh it soft.
Oh yeah, it is awesome.
It is like this, right?
Oh well
Are there any quarrels?
A good fight?
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
This is great too, but.
Yes is
So, in this way.
It feels good to be like this or to be licked.
I want to lick.
Oh really?
Is it OK?
So feel it.
It feels good.
Look, I got up in my breast.
I stood up feeling good.
Do you feel good?
Yes
Oh is
Stop, I say it. 😊
I am happy.
This is the first time this voice.
Yes is it.
Is it okay?
No, I am pleased.
Shamefully
Totally
Skin is beautiful.
Do you hate this?
I am happy.
Is it okay?
What about Max?
really is?
How is it?
Is this good?
It may feel good.
Oh really?
The football.
Do you usually do it yourself?
No, I do not do.
Oh yeah yeah.
It is awesome.
No, it feels good enough.
Here and below,
Oh here?
It will hurt.
Yes is it.
Is it OK?
Yes
Sorry to
Is it okay?
greatly
Looks like looking.
here here?
Yes is
I will see a little.
greatly
I may have sweated too.
Is it true?
Okay, you are sweating.
really is?
Looking in?
I want to see.
It is like this.
Very very beautiful.
It seems more open.
Can I paint it?
In this?
The Paka?
It feels puppy.
See it?
Very pink.
Shamefully
I am excited to see you all the time.
Great
It seems to touch.
and kind?
What is good?
Yes is it.
by here.
Do you know the Eclid or the place?
But somehow it is here.
You can’t see the mosaic.
A little around here.
This side
A little bit gentle.
difficulty
Because it is very sensitive.
Oh yes so much.
If it is not wet, it will hurt.
Sorry, I have to do this.
Sorry to sorry.
Sorry, but I should be a little wet.
I am pleased.
When to touch.
Sorry, but try this one more time.
Oh feelings.
Feels good there.
Feel good
Are you like this?
greatly
Oh well well.
I want to put my fingers in.
Oh inside?
Yes is
I know?
I know
Where are you?
It was just when I just touched it.
Yes is
Open it, here, there are two.
here here here here here
In the meantime, here.
You know here?
Try putting it in there.
Because it is okay.
It is fucking hot.
It was warm.
It’s okay, a little back.
to the back?
OK is OK.
This is?
If you put your finger in, try touching it a little higher.
Up and up?
Oh there there.
It feels good there.
I am different from everyone else, but I feel good.
I feel like something is messing up.
Are you wasting?
Yes, it is a bobo.
The bobo?
It is Zarza.
Oh, yes, I’ve never heard of anything like that, yes.
Is this good?
Oh, oh, that’s so good, that’s that mess.
Are you in Sarasota?
Sarah is yes.
I have never seen my feet inside, I have never seen my feet inside.
It feels good.
Just a little, just a little kind.
and kindly.
Sorry about now.
about this.
It feels good.
If you want to try another finger.
Another one.
This is?
Maybe it’s easier with the middle finger.
Which one is easy.
Fingers and middle fingers.
What if I do people.
Which of them.
Let us try a little.
2nd
Going in?
Because it is bigger.
Yes is it.
Wait a little.
Better to be wet.
Can I get wet?
greatly
Change it okay.
What is easy?
This is a handshake, okay?
Oh no, no, it is okay.
Do you feel good?
It feels good, you just touched it and you were getting upset?
Oh, and so, Sally is good.
Oh...
Oh, it feels good now.
Let me sit for a while.
At this speed...
This is cute.
I waited for the day.
Oh cute!
We can go with you!
Tagged discussion
I was surprised once.
Great! I am pleased
It was really great, really, really the first time.
The first time.
Yes, I felt something good.
What will I try?
I want to lick.
really is?
Is it OK?
It feels good.
Where can I lick?
The Great
just just
around and together.
Do not rub it too hard.
It was very hard.
But feel good.
I did not feel.
Drinking a cup of individual.
It felt good, can I return it?
Yes please please.
Do you hate this?
Such as this?
What do you think?
Let me drink it.
Was it already a binary?
A bit embarrassed.
Show me and show me.
It is awesome.
You are okay.
I am fasting in the stomach.
Is it okay?
It feels good.
Feels good?
It is awesome.
Such as this?
I will Zack.
The Zaccha?
Is it okay?
If you feel bad, tell me.
It feels good.
Is it good to both up and up?
Which of them feels good?
All feel good.
Everything feels good.
I can lick it a little.
Please please.
Feel good
Oh, great
darkly
Can I cap?
Yes is
Oh is
Very warm.
Is it warm?
It is also warm.
Feel good
It feels great.
So this is?
Not yet
Yes
I want to enter.
Would you want to get in?
Okay is?
by me
Please please.
Then then
I want to get gum.
Is there here too?
Do you have this?
Why is it in the clothes?
Do you always have it?
Always in the pocket.
I thought maybe today.
Is it so?
Isn’t it good to carry it?
Can you put it on?
Of course, of course
Oh well wait.
See this, it is written on the male side.
It is.
Yes, it’s on the male side, so you go.
It is spoon.
This is fine, right?
It is here.
Hold it a little.
Wait, down a little bit.
Sorry, wait a while, take it up.
Okay, yes, I have arrived
No to
I just left because I was wet.
Tastefully
This is OK.
It is very wet.
Look at it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh to!
It feels good.
Heat is
Oh yeah!
Oh to!
Warmly
It is warm.
Great, hard and warm.
Feels good?
Do you feel good about this?
Very good feeling.
Can I move a little more?
These are these.
Oh well bad.
Not a little.
Because it is heavy and hard.
pleased
Oh yeah
Khatchik
Yes
Can I remember it too?
Fuck that.
Oh yeah
I want to go in from behind.
From the back?
Wait a little.
The voice is beautiful.
How high is it?
It fits here.
Is it match?
He touches my eyes.
A little there.
A little entrance.
Or there.
So then that.
and stay
That is
Oh yeah yeah
Oh, oh
Uzi is middle.
and Bach
by T
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Voodoo
to
My stomach hurt.
Please turn here.
Great, feel good
Oh, it feels good.
Oh Oh Oh
Loosen the Magistrate
Oh oh oh! Steam is Dangerous
Is it okay? Are you OK?
I want to get gum.
You can use gum.
So get close.
Okay is it?
OK is OK.
Oh yeah
Oh is
Feels good.
See also
It was Tintin.
It felt good.
really is?
Great, I got a lot out.
I came to Gandhi.
What is completely different.
It was great, I felt good, I said it a few times.
I am pleased.
Really agreeing?
is identified
Thanks to.
I felt good at all.
Hi to.
Oh sorry to.
I am here. sorry.
Both of them are naked.
No no, yes is.
Mr. Fukushima, how far has this gone?
Yes, until the end, yes.
Did you do it to the end?
Yes, it is yes.
Maybe it is in his right hand?
Yes, yes, I was in charge.
It feels like you are being released like this.
Sorry to.
What did he mean, what happened to him?
Oh no, it is great.
Great thing, what happened?
I graduated, maybe four years.
Congratulations to you.
Thanks to.
Is this the first time that you feel like you’re in contact with Virgo?
Yes, yes, it was so.
But, I felt good.
Was it good?
It felt great, it was amazing.
I am glad you are.
Was it good? was it good.
How about by the way?
Is this one shot in the man, and is it satisfying?
No yet yet.
Still yet?
Do you say you are not going out yet?
Not yet out.
I’m not saying it’s not yet, but the camera.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah.
How do you think of him?
It is great, be well.
You are well, I am.
It is me, because I am.
thanks to.
It is him, but he doesn’t want to go out.
I don’t think I will have such an opportunity either.
I want him to fulfill his wishes.
Why can’t you, Mr. Fukushima, spend a night with him today?
Is it one night?
Oh yeah?
Oh, oh, oh, but is it not bad?
Yes, please now.
Is the schedule tomorrow okay?
Well, now it is empty.
Are you empty?
Why, please, please, please please, please please, please please, please please, please please, please please, please please, please please, please please, please please.
Yes is
I think I want to help someone, please.
Is it okay? really.
I am okay.
Okay is it?
Thanks to.
Even if I am still hindering you,
I am here, sorry, sorry.
Please be pleased for a night.
Thanks to.
Sorry, I am sorry.
Sorry, good morning
Good morning.
Suddenly
I am glad, sorry
Do you shower?
Yes, let’s take a bath.
Each of them or together?
I will remove it from here.
Really thank you.
It is beautiful.
here is
Please here.
The bathroom is strange.
This is?
Yes, this
To touch it?
I touched it, but I touched it with my hands, so I have a lot of hands.
Can you touch me?
Yes
Did you wash because you were hungry?
Oh this.
Oh, and so on.
Do not be sick.
Can I wash it here?
It was warm.
Oh, and so on.
I have felt better.
OK is OK.
Something strange sounded.
Really beautiful is.
I feel it is getting tough.
When you touch the bubble, you feel better.
Is it true?
I do not.
I wanted to see it already.
I just said.
Is it like that?
Feel good
greatly
Oh Oh Oh
It is hard.
Oh, it has become hard.
You are so cute.
and ass.
Go to the person you like.
It is really beautiful, even with your ass.
Can you tell me what your favorite parts are?
The ass is rancid.
touched me.
A strange daughter.
One minute more!
Be hungry.
Oh yeah yeah.
Laughing
You are interested.
Oh Oh Oh
Oh, so cute
Yes is
Oh Oh Oh
It feels good.
Oh well fuck.
Oh Oh Oh
Feels good.
A little
hurtly
If you get used to this, you may not be able to do it now.
Maybe it is hard.
He is hard, hard.
You can even lick or lick.
The Yellow?
Feel good
Such as this?
My friend’s melody is good.
really is?
Yes is
there there
He is hungry.
Oh, I feel bad.
Oh yeah yeah
Oh, oh
Feel good
Feel a bit good.
Oh a little.
That is very difficult.
Love and Parkour is great.
appear to be.
Oh is
No to
See also
I went out like this again.
If you get that, I will go out.
You are very well.
Can you put it on the screen?
When I left this way, I was tired.
Yes, I am sorry.
Do you sleep?
Sleep well.
Can you sleep with me?
Yes I don’t know.
It is one bed.
Go to sleep together.
So then no.
Look, something happened in this house.
It is very nice.
really is?
I thought he was not there because he was gone.
So, I mean, you have to repair it a little, or you have to repair it?
No, it is cute.
by
Is the silk cute?
No, it is very beautiful.
You have been awakened.
I awoke.
Have you awakened?
It is exciting, there.
Yes is.
I am going home now.
So is it.
thanks to
But when I saw this, I wanted to do it again.
Did you want to?
Yes is
No problem, because he is fine.
So well okay.
It is soft.
You are also very soft.
Oh yeah
I do a little.
really is?
happy to
Do you feel good?
You are standing, right?
Why are you so touched?
No to
by
Oh is
Oh yeah
You are happy.
Has it collapsed?
Oh, that feels like this.
Oh yeah
This is?
Is this feeling good?
Yes
I will just rub it a little.
by
No to
Oh yeah
This is so.
I am strong.
Sadly already.
No to
No, it is nice to be in touch.
Oh is
and AR
Do you smell?
They will bite you all the time.
really is?
Remember my smell.
Can I lick?
The shit is open.
Feels good?
Even if you feel good.
Oh yeah
No to
Oh yeah yeah yeah
by BoB
No to
th th
Are you well in the morning?
Very beautiful.
I want to see that too.
Put it on the first.
Yes is
No to
Can I drink?
here is
greatly
Drink from below.
Yes to? Yes to? Yes to? Yes to? Yes to? Yes to? Yes to? Yes to? Yes to? Yes to? Yes to?
The staff’s clothes are very wet.
Yes
What did you do to Bishop?
No to
Yeong
Oh yeah!
What to do next?
It hurts.
It hurt?
Then
Let’s live.
by NIV
Okay is it?
OK is OK.
If your face is large.
I want to enter.
Wait to wait.
I am fucking hot.
Will you go in with a little bit?
I want to enter.
Very good feeling.
not move.
They are attacking here.
Oh well great.
Oh is
It looks like you are in.
I am watching the toothbrush.
Oh well.
It hurts.
So that.
Oh, he was here.
Oh...
Oh yeah...
The Irvine’s Mock.
Especially good feeling.
Mr is
Oh is
The last 30 minutes.
very much
I spent it.
He again.
Look at you.
Please stop for a moment.
I want to stand up and try.
You look well, right?
Yes, I look well.
Feel badly
Very good
Posse is
My hand hurt.
really
It is safe.
Oh oh
This is
Full of stomach.
The highest
Feel good
The face is cute.
Feels good?
It feels good.
I want to drink.
First, you will already go.
Anyway, you can get in.
Something, something is not okay.
OK is OK.
I want to know how difficult the child is and how he feels.
I feel better in my mango.
Okay is it?
I am going.
It feels good.
Oh, it is awesome.
I got out once.
It is true, the highest.
Please go on.
Is that not another problem?
I missed it.
Hathaway, you are well.
Yes is.
No, but Mr. Fukushima did this.
You don’t like Fujitsu anymore.
I won’t go home anymore, kid.
I miss you.
OK is OK.
Hanoi has found a great man.
Make this man happy.
I found it.
Do not hurry.
It was very fun.
Really thank you.
I have to go home.
promise to
Find your favorite child.
promise
I will strive.
You are supporting.
Have a good luck.