The next day
Where is Hajime's room?
Here it is.
There he is.
Hajime, your sister is here.
Hajime.
Hey.
Oh, you're here too.
You look well.
I'm fine.
It must have been tough for your mom.
You know, baseball can cause injuries.
That's right.
I really didn't have enough attention.
I see.
Well, you're good at baseball.
Even if you get hurt, it can't be helped.
Well, it's a sport that's easy to get hurt.
How is your life in the hospital?
I'm really bored.
Aren't you bored?
I'm getting married.
You're doing WBC.
That's right.
I won the WBC final ticket.
Really?
That's amazing.
It was a little expensive.
I'm going to watch Hajime's play.
Wow.
Please.
If you get better, let's go watch the play.
I'm going to watch it on a weekly basis.
That's a little...
Practice, practice, practice, practice.
That's good.
By the way, I met my sister at the entrance.
That's right.
I gave her sweets.
If you get better, eat it.
By the way, what were you looking at on your smartphone earlier?
I didn't notice you came.
That's right.
This is normal.
Look, it's not in Korea.
I see.
Oh, it's in Korea.
It's very flashy.
Yes, it's cute.
What is it?
Is the girl in front of you coming?
I'm scared.
Only my mother comes.
Only your mother comes.
I'm lonely that I can't meet a girl.
I don't want to meet a girl.
You like flashy girls, don't you?
Well, I like you.
I'm sorry.
What?
Your aunt is very beautiful.
What are you talking about?
You don't have to be so careful.
I'm sorry.
Don't be like that.
Can you show me?
Look.
Show me.
This.
It's flashy.
It's really flashy.
I like you.
I like you, but it's flashy.
Your aunt is so beautiful.
What are you talking about?
I'm lonely that I can't meet a girl.
I got a call.
Is there anything I can do?
I'm not allowed to use my cell phone in the hospital.
So I have to go out once.
Go out?
I want to go out.
It's really annoying.
Your aunt is really beautiful.
Why are you talking like that?
He's always like that.
That's terrible.
I'm really nervous now.
I wish he was more fashionable.
He's so fashionable.
If your aunt wears an idol-like outfit, it's flashy.
I can't wear it anymore.
That's not true.
Your aunt has a beautiful face.
I can't wear it anymore.
If your aunt wears an idol-like outfit, it's flashy.
That's embarrassing.
You can't wear it anymore?
I can't wear it anymore.
I don't know what I'm going to say to him.
He looks like an idol-like outfit.
Stop it.
Your aunt is an idol for me.
Don't say that.
I'm so nervous.
My blood pressure is going up.
Your aunt is so cute.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Does it hurt?
No, it doesn't hurt.
Are you feeling better?
No, I'm not.
It's not like that.
What's wrong?
I'll be right back.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Shall I call the nurse?
It's not like that.
What's wrong?
I'm just happy that your aunt is here.
Please close the curtain.
Curtain?
What's wrong?
I closed the curtain.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
I closed the curtain.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
It's hard to say.
Can you listen to me?
What is it?
I really like your aunt.
You said you liked her.
But it's a joke.
I really like your aunt.
What are you talking about?
I want to kiss your aunt.
It's impossible.
I really like your aunt.
I've been in the hospital for a long time.
I haven't been able to do that for a month.
Please calm down.
Please.
I want to kiss you just once.
That's not good.
Please.
Please calm down.
I know you're bored.
I really like your aunt.
Please.
Please be quiet.
I like you.
I can't do that.
Please.
No.
I've known you since I was a baby.
I can't do that.
I really like your aunt.
I want to kiss you just once.
Please.
I really like your aunt.
I want to kiss you just once.
I'm lonely.
I can't do that.
Why are you saying that?
I really like your aunt.
I want to kiss you just once.
That's all.
That was just for a moment.
That wasn't a kiss. It was a kiss.
It doesn't matter.
That's all.
Let me do it again.
One more time.
No.
You did it right.
I'm not satisfied.
No.
Come here.
I told you not to do that.
I told you to kiss me just once.
That was a kiss.
It doesn't matter.
One more time.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
I love you.
It's over.
No.
It's only for a moment.
It's not good.
It's just a little bit.
Give me a little bit more.
That's right.
That person will be back soon.
It's all right.
This hospital is really far away.
It's near the entrance.
He's not going back yet.
Give me a little bit more.
I'm not sure if I can do it or not, but I'm sure I can do it.
He's sleeping in the hospital now.
I don't think he can do it.
No, no, no.
It's hot.
No.
Just a little.
It's hot.
No, no.
Just a little.
No one's coming.
No.
What's going on?
It's hot.
Just a little.
I like you.
No.
Just a little.
The curtains are closed.
No, no.
No.
Come here.
You're so cute.
No.
I can hear you.
It feels good, doesn't it?
No.
You're still alive, aren't you?
Hey, Oppa.
I can't speak, but I feel the cave like I'm in heaven.
Nya demás?
I'm feeling good!
Sooooo good!
I'm scared.
Uncle,
please.
Please, wait a little longer.
You're so strong.
Please keep it a secret from him.
I'll keep it a secret.
I'm scared.
Please keep it a secret from him.
I don't know what it is but it feels empty.
It's wonderful
It's wonderful?
I'm ok
Ah.
Be good, my dear.
Here you go.
You want me to lick your
It's the best if you can stop it.
You want me to stop it, don't you?
You were bored, weren't you?
I'm so glad you stopped it.
Does it feel good?
It's so good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You were dissatisfied, weren't you?
You're smiling so well.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're getting better.
Are you surprised?
I'm actually a very scary person.
Come here.
Do you need surgery?
It's a simple pain in the neck, isn't it?
It feels so good.
It feels so good, right?
I'm happy.
It feels so good.
It's hot.
I want to run away.
It's getting cold.
I don't have a blanket.
It's okay.
It's cold.
I'm sorry.
It feels so good.
It's cold.
It's the best.
It feels so good.
Can you call me Mimika just for now?
Mimika.
It feels so good.
Can you call me Mimika?
I love you.
It feels so good.
Ah...
If you don't keep your voice down,
people will hear you.
I'm so sleepy.
Ah...
Show me your butt.
I feel so good.
Ah...
Show me your butt.
I feel so good.
Ah...
Show me your butt.
I feel so good.
Ah...
Show me your butt.
I feel so good.
Ah...
Show me your butt.
I feel so good.
Ah...
It hurts.
I feel so good.
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
It doesn't hurt at all.
I can't stand it.
Let's do more.
Okay.
Ah...
It's rubbing.
I feel so good.
Can you hear it?
It's rubbing.
Ah...
I feel so good.
I'm scared.
Hama-san, I'm going to have a stomachache.
Are you going to have a stomachache?
I'm so tired.
I want to move more.
I'm going to have a stomachache.
Move slowly.
I'm so tired.
I'm so scared.
That's good.
That next one doesn't feel right.
That's too old.
I don't know anymore.
I'm so tired.
I want to go again.
What?
Hajime.
I'll open the curtain.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
I'm wiping Hajime's body.
Really?
Why are you wiping your ears?
It's okay.
How long will it take?
It's going to take a while.
Can you smoke in the smoking room downstairs?
I see.
Okay.
I'll smoke downstairs.
See you.
You'll find out.
It's okay.
I'll do it again.
It feels good.
It's going to hurt.
It's okay.
It hurts.
If you smoke so fast, you'll hurt yourself.
It's okay.
It feels good.
Hajime, do you like me?
Tell me you like me.
It's obvious that you like me.
It's good.
I like you.
It feels good.
It's getting bigger inside.
Do you want to go?
I want to go, but...
What should I do?
I want to go.
I want to go inside.
I like you.
It feels good.
I want to go inside.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It hurts.
I can't help it.
Do you want to go?
Will you let me go inside?
Let me out.
It hurts.
It's okay.
I did a lot.
It felt good.
I'm happy I was able to do this.
It's good.
Will you visit me again?
Will you keep it a secret from him?
I'll keep it a secret.
I'll come again.
Did you feel good?
It felt really good.
It hurts.
Thank you.
Are you satisfied now?
Yes.
I feel refreshed.
I want you to visit me again.
Of course I will.
But...
Yes?
Was it okay to let you out?
It was okay.
I felt good too.
I'm glad you said that.
It was pretty intense.
Didn't it hurt?
Not at all.
It was hot and soft.
Didn't it get worse?
Not at all.
I think I got better.
If you find out,
the teachers will be mad at you.
That's right.
You have to be careful.
I'm sorry.
That's right.
You have to keep it a secret.
Yes.
I didn't know you were this good.
I'll make sure you don't catch a cold.
Thank you.
Just a kiss...
I thought you were going to throw it at me.
But you threw it at me.
I know.
It's been a long time
since I threw it at a woman.
You don't do that to me.
I don't want to.
It's a secret.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It was a good and happy time.
Please fix it until the next time.
Yes.
How was it?
It felt really good.
It was the best.
You did a good job.
It felt really good.
It was my first time
but the switch just went off.
You scared me.
I'm sorry.
I was surprised
that you were closing the door.
I'm sorry.
I have to go now.
I know.
I'm lonely.
Thank you.
I'll come again, so please fix it.
I'll come again.
Bye.
See you.
I'm sorry.
Hi.
Hello.
How are you doing?
Good.
How long is the training?
It's next week.
Oh, I see.
It's good for your skin.
I hope the results are good.
I think so, too.
But I think it's okay because I'm in good shape.
Yeah, that's right.
You're getting better little by little.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I can't tell at all when I see it.
Your face color is getting better.
Yeah.
It smells better than before.
What's wrong with you all of a sudden?
I was so close to work.
Oh, really?
Thank you for coming.
Don't worry about me.
Thank you.
I'm sorry I came all of a sudden.
No, it's okay.
I'm so happy.
I didn't have any souvenirs or anything.
I didn't feel good at all.
You just came.
I'm happy, too.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I'm so glad.
How's your life at the hospital?
Well, the food is a little...
Oh, I see.
It's not good.
The taste is a little light.
The amount is just right.
No, that's not enough.
It's not enough.
The taste is...
It's not that sick.
The taste is good, but the taste is light.
That's right.
It's a little...
It's not enough.
It might make you hungry.
My grandfather used to say the same thing when he was hospitalized a long time ago.
Oh, I see.
The taste is light.
That's right.
He used to say the same thing.
It's going to be crispy when you get discharged.
What?
But I don't think I've lost that much weight.
But you've lost about 4kg.
Oh, really?
On the contrary, I feel like I'm going to get fat because I'm not exercising.
Oh, you're right.
I don't think I've lost that much weight.
It's more than 4kg.
What?
You haven't eaten much food, have you?
Well, the amount is not enough.
That's right.
It's about an apple.
Oh, that's right.
I was just looking at the apple right now.
Thank you.
If it's a fruit, it's good for your health.
That's right.
It's good for digestion, too.
It's easy to eat.
What do you want to eat when you retire?
What should I eat?
Ramen.
I can't eat ramen anymore.
I want to eat it, but I can't.
I'm sure you can't eat ramen after retirement.
I want something with a strong taste.
Something with a strong taste.
Then, I'll try the boiled one.
No, no, no.
That's not it.
Is it different?
No.
You've eaten thin sweet potatoes so far, haven't you?
Ramen is delicious.
It's delicious, but it's not good.
Oh, I'll go and wash the dishes.
Can you watch me?
Oh, yeah.
Shall I go?
Oh, it's okay.
I thought so.
I'll wash the dishes.
I'll do it.
I'll do it a lot.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
This is Ikeda-san in charge of this.
Hello.
I'm Obanosumire.
Oh, my.
Is that your younger sister?
Yes.
You look like her.
I thought you were her brother.
I'm not her brother.
Your hair is beautiful.
Yes.
I'm not her brother.
I'm in the laundry room.
It's a little crowded in and out right now.
It might take a little time.
I see.
I think it might be faster to do the laundry outside.
Oh, really?
Oh, the laundry outside.
Let's do that.
Yeah, I think so.
You can't read it, can you?
It's a little crowded, isn't it?
That's right.
Is the laundry outside pretty close?
It's a little far away.
Oh, it's a little far away.
But I don't think it's that far away.
I think it's about 15 minutes away.
But I can walk at all.
You're working out now, aren't you?
You're not working out, are you?
It's a serious matter, isn't it?
I'm busy.
I don't think so.
I don't think it's suitable for you.
I was thinking of asking you to do it.
Shall we go?
I'll wait for the result.
Oh, thank you very much.
Then I'll go.
Have a good night.
Be careful.
Oh, oh.
What do you really want to eat when you get discharged?
I want to eat only the ones that have left.
Oh, oh.
That's right.
What's wrong?
Oh, oh.
Are you sick?
Oh, I'm totally fine.
Oh?
Tell me if there's anything.
Oh, yes.
Are you really okay?
Oh, I'm totally fine.
Oh, oh.
Don't you feel hot or cold?
I don't think so.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Yes?
My mom told me to drop my laundry.
Can you check my bedding?
Oh, really?
Yes.
My sister's house is pretty messy.
You have a bed under your bed, right?
I used to have a bed under my bed.
Oh.
I don't think so.
Oh, really?
Yes.
My mom always forgets to put her underwear under her bed.
I'd be happy if you could take a closer look.
Oh, really?
I don't think so.
Can you check my bedding a little bit more?
Oh.
I don't think so.
Do you have anything to say?
No.
Oh.
I don't think so.
Oh, really?
Yes.
I don't think so.
I think it's okay to say something here.
Then,
I will tell you my story after we get discharged.
I see.
Do you like it better today?
Ma'am.
Yes?
Can you close the curtain?
Oh.
Oh, right.
The curtain.
Shall I close it?
Sure.
I see.
If you close the curtain,
it looks like a living room.
Yes.
Is this okay?
Thank you.
Why? Is it hard to talk?
Oh, but tell me.
I'll ask you anything.
Anything?
Yes.
Actually,
after I became pregnant,
I couldn't take care of myself at all.
So I wanted you to touch me.
Here.
What?
Are you talking about being quiet or not crying?
Well, that's a little...
You said you'd do anything.
Ma'am.
Yes.
If I could do something for you,
I'd do anything.
Well,
when I went to your house,
I fell down.
What?
Your house?
Oh, no.
Wait a minute.
Did you just
touch me?
Yes.
You were looking at me, weren't you?
I was looking at you.
Ma'am,
it's painful.
If you touch me,
I think I'll calm down.
I see.
Ma'am, please.
Just a little.
No.
No, I can't do that.
I'm serious.
Look at me.
It's very...
painful.
I can't do that.
I can't touch you.
Well,
Ma'am,
I want to see your buttocks.
What?
I'll do it myself.
Show me your buttocks.
Well,
I can't do that.
I'll just look at you.
Just look at me.
I want you to look at me more.
I'm sorry.
I feel like I'm looking at you.
I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
You like my butt so much?
I think your butt is erotic.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Your shape is beautiful.
Your bottom is transparent.
It's a great color.
Is it transparent?
The color of your face is transparent.
I don't know.
I didn't notice it was transparent.
Your butt is erotic.
It's not erotic.
Can I do it a little more?
Wait a minute.
I didn't notice it was transparent.
I touched your butt too much.
Wait a minute.
I can feel your lower body.
It's okay.
This is the first time I've ever seen it.
I've never seen it before.
Your thumb is tired.
Touch with your thumb.
Come on.
I want to see more.
A little bit more.
Can you do it?
What?
A skirt?
Can you do it?
Now...
Hey...
Can you...
Can you tie the skirt and stand confronted by the skirt?
Did you get angry?
Now...
It would be nice if you could stick it out this way.
Please do it as it is.
Do you want me to help you?
It's hard to do it alone, isn't it?
I'll do it for you.
Please do it as it is.
Does it hurt?
I'm glad.
Please do it as it is.
It's okay.
I'm glad you can see it.
Please do it as it is.
It's hard to do it alone, isn't it?
What?
What are you doing?
You can't do that.
Wait a minute.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You can't do that.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
You can't do that.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
You can't do that.
Hey, you can't do that.
Kiss me.
This is the first time for me to do this
This is...
Wait...
No...
Don't do it...
I can't do this...
No...
No, I can't do that.
I can't do that.
No.
No, I can't do that.
What's wrong?
The hospital's food is not good, so it's really helpful.
Right?
Ouch!
It's not healed yet.
That's right, but I've been living in the hospital for a long time.
I have a cramp.
It's really helpful.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Did you lose weight?
Really?
I haven't been able to do it for three days.
I see.
It's been about three days.
It's been three days.
I feel like I've lost weight.
Really?
Are you doing something?
I'm doing a face massage.
Really?
Tell me.
Your face is really bad lately.
No, it's not like that.
How much is left?
It hurts a lot.
But you're fine.
That's right.
If you don't lose weight like this, you'll be more energetic.
How many times?
387 times.
No way.
I'm fine.
Ouch!
It hurts a lot.
I can't do a futon match anymore.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You're a good boy.
You're doing a good job.
Today...
Yeah?
Your mom isn't here, but are you asking her something?
Yeah.
Huh?
I didn't ask her anything, but she's not here?
No, I said she'd come over the day before yesterday.
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, I see.
I'll ask her later.
Ah, yeah.
Do you have something to tell her?
I just want to ask her to change her clothes.
I didn't change my clothes?
You didn't bring it?
Well...
I brought it the other day.
What day did you come?
3 days ago?
Does it stink?
It's okay.
What?
Wait a minute.
It stinks.
Is there a bath in it?
Not yet.
That's why.
Wait a minute.
No, no, no.
No?
No.
Why isn't there a bath in it?
That's because...
The nurse...
Ike-chan?
Well...
What?
It's not good for your skin.
I'm a patient.
Isn't it good?
It's not good if there's no bath in it.
Is that so?
It stinks.
It stinks?
It's better to wipe your body.
I'll wipe it.
Who?
It's okay.
Why?
You're not wiping it.
Isn't it better to be wiped by your mother?
Well...
I'm used to it.
Isn't it better to be wiped by your mother
than by your aunt?
Isn't it?
No, no, no.
It's okay.
It stinks.
Let me wipe it.
I'll wipe it.
It's okay.
Be quiet.
Wait a minute.
I'll wipe it.
It's embarrassing to wipe it.
Where?
Where did you get it?
Over there.
It was over there.
Wait a minute.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
Be quiet.
I can do it myself.
But you're still a child.
Don't say that.
It's okay.
Why?
Over here.
Over here?
Thank you.
Good boy.
Is it cold?
It's okay.
It's okay?
I'll wipe it over here.
I'll wipe it in front of you.
Excuse me.
What?
Your back smells, too.
Wait a minute.
I didn't wipe it over here.
You used to change your clothes when you were little.
Do you remember?
When I was little...
You remember.
Really?
What's wrong?
It's okay.
It's nothing.
Wait a minute.
I'll wipe it again.
What?
If you wipe it, it'll get hot.
Wait a minute.
I'll wipe it like this.
What?
Don't you see?
It's embarrassing.
No.
What is it?
You look like an old lady.
Are you embarrassed?
No.
What?
It's...
It's been a long time.
What?
You know,
I've been living in a house for a long time.
I don't have time to be a woman.
If you wipe it,
if you wipe it,
it'll react.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
I'm not looking at it.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
It's your fault.
What?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
You're talking like a man.
I don't like it.
What do you want?
What do you want me to do?
No, I don't want you to be so mean to me.
No, because...
If you're like that, I'll have to apologize.
Seriously.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
What should I do to forgive you?
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
I don't know.
What?
What did you do?
Is it okay to do anything?
I don't know.
I wish I could do something.
Tell me.
I don't know.
You can do something, right?
I wish I could do something.
I'm sure you can do it.
Tell me.
Can you touch me?
I see.
That?
Please.
I can't do that.
Why not?
I don't think I can do that.
No, I can't.
You can do anything.
Didn't you say you could do anything?
I did.
But...
We're relatives, right?
I don't think it's good.
Because I can do anything for you.
If I can't do anything, I've decided.
Please.
I can't.
No one's watching.
But...
No one else is watching?
It's your fault.
I'm sorry.
Please.
What should I do?
Can you touch me?
Just once?
I can't do that.
I don't know.
Can I touch you for now?
Yes.
Don't touch me.
I can't.
More like this.
I touched you.
I haven't touched you yet.
More.
Like this?
Yes.
More.
More like this.
Yes.
Don't touch me.
I don't think it's good.
Yes.
Is that all?
No.
Please.
Just once.
Just this.
Yes.
Please.
Is that all?
Yes.
More like this.
I touched you.
I knew it.
If you didn't touch me,
I wouldn't be like this.
Yes.
I'm taking responsibility for this.
More.
Please hold me.
Yes.
Is that all?
Like this.
Touch me.
Yes.
More.
What?
I didn't tell you to touch me.
I just told you to touch me.
Move it.
Why are you touching me?
Please.
Wait.
No.
Please.
Where are you touching me?
Don't touch me.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay if you don't make a loud voice.
Yes.
It's not like that.
Please don't do that.
Move it.
No.
I'm going to hit you.
You're going to hit me?
You're going to hit me.
No.
I'm going to hit you.
Shut up.
No.
I'm going to hit you.
Move it.
I'm so sorry.
Hey.
You can't do that.
Don't do that.
I'm going to hit you.
No.
You can't do that.
I'm going to hit you.
It's over.
I'm so sorry.
You can't do that.
I'm sorry.
Be quiet.
Here.
No.
I'm your uncle.
Do you know?
No.
You know what?
What?
You can't do that.
Show me your butt.
What? My butt?
I don't want to.
Please.
Show me your butt.
Just looking?
Please.
Just a little?
What?
Show me more.
What's going on?
What's this?
A tea bag?
What? It's a tea bag.
What? It's not good?
It's not good?
You don't want it?
It's embarrassing.
That's it.
Show me more.
Don't stare at me like that.
It's embarrassing.
Is that enough?
Just a little more.
You're too selfish.
You don't want to?
I don't want to.
Just a little?
It's not a little.
I can see it.
Where?
Don't tell me.
Can't you see it?
For example?
What?
Here?
I can see it.
That's it.
Stay like that.
Don't stare at me.
If you do that, I want to see more.
Hurry up.
It's over.
It's not fun to look at your butt.
It's embarrassing.
Just a little.
I can see it.
Don't open your eyes too much.
It's over.
Just a little more.
It's okay.
Don't be stubborn.
Hurry up.
Let's do this.
It's okay.
Are you going to sleep?
No.
Hurry up.
Don't say that.
Don't do that.
Why?
I can't go.
Then what?
If you lick me.
Then I'll go.
Are you going to sleep?
I might go.
What do you mean?
I'll go.
Really?
Are you really going to sleep?
Yes.
I'll go.
Hurry up.
It takes too much time.
But
If you lick me.
Isn't it big?
Really?
It's really big.
I think it's big.
I don't know.
I've never seen it before.
It's the biggest.
Really?
I can't get in.
It's big.
I'm not sure if this is the right way to eat it.
I'll try it.
It's a little spicy.
It's spicy.
I'll try it.
Is it spicy?
I think I can do it better than my hands.
I'm glad.
How do you want me to lick it?
A lot.
A lot?
I want you to lick it for me.
Does it feel good?
Yeah.
It feels good?
Does it feel good?
Yeah.
Do your best.
Really?
Yeah.
Do your best.
Hurry up.
Yeah.
Are you still eating?
Just a little more.
Yeah.
Hey, Kou-chan.
What?
Yeah.
Can you do it?
Now, I want to try.
No.
I think you can do it in an instant.
What's wrong with you?
All right.
In an instant.
Can you do it?
Yeah.
In an instant.
You can do it right away.
Yeah.
I don't want to get spooked by you.
Oh, no.
Is it okay?
It's a secret to my sister.
Of course.
If you get mixed up, you'll be scolded.
It's okay.
It's in.
It's all in.
If it's this, you can go fast, right?
Yeah.
It's all in.
What?
Does this feel good?
It's amazing.
I'm going to go.
How is it?
A little more.
What should I do?
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Are you going to the toilet?
Are you going to pee?
I thought you were going to pee.
Wow.
What is it?
It feels good.
I'm going to pee.
Do you like this?
It feels good.
I'm going to pee.
You're good at one minute.
It feels good.
Do you like your buttocks?
My buttocks?
You're biting a lot.
It smells good. Touch it a lot.
Do you like your buttocks?
Do you want to put it in while looking at your buttocks?
I want to look at my buttocks.
It's good. Wait a minute.
It's good.
Look at your buttocks.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Be quiet.
Are you still not going?
It feels good.
Do you like this?
Do you feel good?
It feels good.
I'm not going yet.
Let me do it.
It feels good.
This way.
You're not going yet, right?
It feels good.
If it commodity, it'll be more comfortable.
I'm tired.
Yes, I'm also tired.
Stop.
I'm coming to you.
It's okay.
I'm coming to you first.
Come on.
I'm coming to you.
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
I've been patient enough.
You can be friends with me.
What?
Let's go out like this.
I'm nervous.
I'm scared.
Do you want to give birth too?
Cream.
Come out.
Love of Automobile.
Ah!
Hehehe
Ah, all of it?
Ah
Ah, I'm sorry
Hehehe
I put a lot
Ah
Hehehe
How much did you put in?
Ah
Hehehe
Come on
Ah
Hehehe
I put a lot
Ah
Hehehe
Yes, wait
Which one?
Ah
Do you put the clothes on by yourself?
Yes
Okay
Please put the clothes on yourself
Hehehe
Is it safe to put them in?
I don't know
But it's all good
Eh?
Apparently.
Despite my soaked in water.
If you're tired
...I want to see...
...傳 somewhere.
subsidized?
Yeah.
Ehhhhh?
Hey.
Can I play with you?
Can I?
Yeah.
I think I can go to the hospital in a little while.
Really?
Yeah.
I think I'm going to get a headache.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ouch.
Does it hurt?
Yeah.
But I have a reason to go to the hospital when I'm back.
See?
Oh!
Ah, I'm tired, Grandma.
Can I eat this?
Ah, yeah.
You want this?
Which one should I choose?
This one, this one is better.
Ah, that's not good.
Yeah.
It's good.
Excuse me.
I'm here to measure your weight.
Oh, auntie.
Oh.
Here you go.
You're so energetic.
I'm so sorry about the test.
It can't be helped.
If the test goes well,
the time might be faster.
Really?
Yeah.
I'll tell the doctor to be nice to you.
It's not good.
How are you feeling?
I'm totally fine.
You don't have a fever, so you're fine.
Yeah, I think I'm fine.
Here you go.
Hello, Mr. Kawaguchi.
Hello.
How are you feeling?
My back has been hurting since yesterday.
I see.
Let's measure your weight.
Here you go.
Is there any other part that's not good?
No, just that part.
No, there isn't.
Here you go.
Excuse me.
Can I have a minute?
I see.
Tatsuya, can I talk to you for a minute?
Huh?
I have something to tell you.
Really?
Yeah.
Tatsuya, can I talk to you for a minute?
What is it?
Actually,
I have something to tell you
I was wondering if Tatsuya-kun was doing that at night.
What do you mean by that?
I heard an AV sound coming from Tatsuya-kun's bed at night.
I was wondering what he was doing.
It's been a while, so I understand how you feel.
Are you really doing it?
I heard it every night, so I'm sorry I was told to tell you.
I see.
I understand how you feel, Tatsuya-kun, but what do you think?
I'm sorry. I was sleeping.
I see.
When I do it by myself, my hip joints and waist hurt.
I can't do it until the end.
That's why it was hard every day.
Tatsuya-kun?
My teeth hurt a lot.
I see it every night.
I'm so embarrassed. I'm sorry I was told to tell you.
No, it's okay.
I see.
But it's hard, isn't it?
When I do it by myself, my heart hurts a lot.
I wonder if I can do it.
You don't have to put too much pressure on your body.
I'm sorry.
I'll be careful.
Tatsuya-kun.
Please be patient tonight.
Be patient?
I'll do something.
Something?
I'll think about it.
Anyway, rest in peace until then.
See you again.
Tatsuya-kun.
Are you awake?
Auntie?
I'll go in for a moment.
What?
I'm sorry I'm late.
Tatsuya-kun.
I understand
Are you getting dirty today?
I see
but I can't
I'm sorry, I can't do it by myself
No, it will be painful if you do it by yourself
I wonder if you can't do it by yourself
What?
Why?
I want to do something for you because it will be painful
But...
I'm sorry
Right?
What?
It's embarrassing
I'm sorry
Is it okay?
Wait
Please be patient
It's getting harder
I'm not doing anything
Are you okay?
I'm okay
I'm sorry
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
Please tell me if it hurts
It's getting harder
It's okay, it's just a normal sound
It's painful
It's okay
I'm sorry
I'll be gentle
Natsuya-kun
Does it feel good to be pushed away?
What?
It's okay, you can say anything
I'm sorry
Does it feel good?
It's okay
Is it painful?
You can say anything
It's okay
Does it feel good?
Natsuya
I want to touch you
What?
If you touch me
I think you'll be able to get out soon
It's okay
Is it okay?
It's painful
It's okay
This is better
Touch me gently
I'm sorry
You're getting better
It's embarrassing
It was painful, right?
It's okay
It's better to look more
The person next to you is sleeping
It's okay
I think you should be a little more gentle
Doesn't it hurt?
It's okay
What should I do?
I think I'm going to cry
I have to endure
It's okay
I want to look down
What?
Look down
It's okay
Really?
Why isn't it okay?
This too?
It's okay
It's a little wet
It's embarrassing
What?
It's okay
It's embarrassing
Tatsuya-kun
Don't make a sound
If you touch it, it will make a sound
I'm busy with work
I haven't been touched in a long time
It's okay
Yes.
It feel like we have high blood pressure.
Take it easy.
Can you also knead it?
Is that ok?
Huh...
It's good.
It feels so good.
Shima is using the
I will massage your ears.
It's cold.
Are you okay?
It feels good.
I can't take it anymore.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
It feels good.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Are you okay?
It's really hard.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
It feels good.
I'm happy that you're getting better.
Wait a minute.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
Don't hold back.
It's okay.
It's amazing.
It got a lot on my skin.
The Battle of Tofu.
It was a lot, wasn't it?
Here you go.
Will you come tomorrow?
What?
Tomorrow?
I can't come tomorrow.
But when you retire,
let's go somewhere to celebrate together.
Really?
Let's go somewhere we can relax.
It's a promise, auntie.
You'll get better, right?
I'll definitely come.
It's a promise.
If you don't sleep well, you won't get better.
Let's go.
I won't go back.
What?
It's okay.
I'll stay with you until Tatsuya-kun goes to bed.
Really?
Good night.