Kohinata Shouichi, 30 years old
A kind but boring man.
That's what people often say.
My wife, who had just gotten married and had gone out with another man, said the same thing.
I'm still living in my home, which I bought on my own, for my wife, who was a single mother, and my husband, who was a single father.
I'm still living in my home, which I bought on my own, for my wife, who was a single mother, and my husband.
It looks like a state-owned property in the company.
I'm a man who was abandoned by my wife, who left a lot of loans until her retirement.
What did I leave behind?
Welcome home, Shouichi.
Big brother.
I'm home, you two.
Thank you for your hard work today.
Mom, you're cheating.
It's a new marriage life for two people who are much better than their wives.
A year ago
Damn it.
Damn her.
Shoichi, are you going to break your body like this?
I brought you some water.
Drink it.
Shut up!
Who do you think you are?
Your daughter ran away pretending to be a man.
It's boring to be a gentle man.
I've been doing my best for your daughter.
I'm sorry.
I ignored you because your daughter didn't want to change her name.
I forced her to go to Shinjuku.
I suggested Tokyo.
I decided to pay for Akari's tuition.
But your daughter...
I'm sorry, Shoichi.
I'm really sorry.
Why?
I really loved her.
I really wanted to make her happy.
That's what I thought.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I was really happy that you married my daughter.
I was really happy that such a kind and wonderful person came to my daughter.
I'm sorry.
I can't forgive you.
I'm really sorry.
I'll do anything.
I'm sorry.
I'll take her place.
Take off your clothes.
What?
You'll take her place, won't you?
If it were true, you would have been married every night.
But your daughter ran away.
So you have a lot of money, don't you?
If you're a mother, take responsibility.
What are you talking about?
I'm your wife's mother.
You think it's okay to apologize, don't you?
After all, you and your daughter are the same.
Do you think someone will forgive you if you apologize?
No.
I understand.
If that's how you're going to save your heart...
I'm sorry.
You can't do this to me, can you?
That's right.
I don't have any feelings for women.
I don't have any manners or etiquette.
I don't give a damn about that.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
If you make such a loud noise, you'll wake up Sakaguchi.
You can't do this to me, can you?
It hurts.
What is it? Do you have a problem with me?
Please forgive me.
I did it.
It's the first time I've done it with a woman.
It's the first time I've done it with my daughter.
I've never done it with your daughter.
I've never done it with my ex-husband.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
It's the best.
I'll do my best.
Good morning, Akari.
Where's mom?
Mom?
She's here.
Good morning, Akari.
I'm sorry I didn't notice.
I spilled some milk on my pants.
My mom cleaned it up.
That's right.
If you don't wipe it right away, it'll stain.
It was a good idea, wasn't it?
If you don't mind, let's...
It's okay.
That's gross.
Akari, don't say that to your brother.
Mom, it's okay.
I don't care.
I have morning practice today, so I'm going, too.
Good luck.
You told me to go home in front of Akari.
You can do whatever you want with me.
That's...
I'm sorry.
Besides, you wanted your mom, didn't you?
No, you can't.
I can't?
No, that's not what I meant.
That's what you mean, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
Akari, please get ready to go home.
Yes.
Please come here.
Oh, my God.
This is it.
I'm sorry.
The first and the next night.
Hi.
Or shall we go to the bath?
Let me do it.
What?
Here.
Damn it.
She must have been thinking about you.
Maru-e accepted the rape as a natural process.
Shunichi-san.
Akari is going to be late.
Akari is going to be late, too.
I have to be at home.
You're studying hard, aren't you?
Don't worry.
I have to make a loud noise.
I'm sorry.
You're the best.
You're so weak.
You're so weak, aren't you?
I'm going to do a lot of things to you.
I'm sorry.
Shunichi-san.
You're the best.
When you were with him, you were bullied a lot.
I'm sorry.
Apologize to him.
I'm sorry, Shunichi-san.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for everything.
Mom.
How can I make you happy?
Like this?
Do you want me to make you stronger?
Or do you want me to twist you?
You're saying no, but you're getting stronger.
I'm sorry.
Please make up for what your daughter did.
Did you just lick your nipples?
I'm sorry.
You're always here when you comfort yourself, aren't you?
You're a real helper.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
I'm sorry for this body.
It's true.
Please reflect on yourself.
I'm sorry.
You're doing a great job.
You're so excited.
I'm sorry.
Akari.
How's your study going?
Are you doing well?
Have you learned anything?
Not really.
You're in the bathroom, aren't you?
I'm sorry.
I'm cleaning now.
I'll be done soon.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for you to have three shots in the morning.
I'll be back soon.
That's because your mother touches you all the time.
Because...
I thought it would be hard for me to be like this.
It's very hard because of your mother.
Can you do something about it?
Yes.
Then, see you later.
That's great.
I'll do something about it.
First of all, it's my order.
Can you feel good with your hands?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
How do you feel?
I feel very good.
I want to thank you.
You can do whatever you want.
Yes.
What's wrong?
You're going to have a stomachache.
Yes.
Please drink a lot of water.
Oh, my God.
It's time to go to work.
I have to hurry.
It's so good!
I want to see Syonichi a lot.
His parents are my life's target.
Syonichi, you'll be fine.
Syonichi, I'm here.
What is it?
You look like a newlywed.
If you don't like it, don't say that.
Come to my room when you sleep tonight.
In the bedroom of the couple.
Is that okay, Sayuri?
Yes.
I'm going to bed.
You're awake.
Thank you for waiting.
I'm going to bed.
Good night.
I'm embarrassed.
I look old.
No.
You look good.
I'm your daughter, Yoko.
No.
I'm sorry.
Shoichi.
Please do it again tonight.
I'm sorry.
Sora-chan.
I'll take care of you.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
You're the best.
I knew it.
Mom?
That's...
That's your underwear, isn't it?
You look like that when you see me.
I know you've been seeing each other lately.
I'm sorry.
I want to make you feel better.
Then I'll do it.
I'm sorry.
It's warm.
Your ears...
Shoichi-san, you're getting really warm.
Your mother's body is really warm, too.
Because I'm touching Shoichi-san.
Your head is full of Chimpanzee stuff.
That's right.
Shoichi-san, isn't this a little bad?
Shoichi-san, you're getting really warm.
Shoichi-san, that's all Chimpanzee stuff.
Mother, please do that.
Here you go.
Take it off.
It's the best.
Does it feel good?
It feels great to be wrapped in my mother's delicate breasts.
Look, it's hard again.
Shoichi-san, you're getting really warm.
You're really going to mess it up, aren't you?
That's all you're thinking about, isn't it?
Please take care of my child.
I'll do it.
I'll take care of Shoichi-san's child.
Let me take care of him.
Shoichi-san, you're getting really warm.
I'll make up for it with a lot of care.
You don't have to do that.
I won't let you go.
Please put the box here.
I'm sorry.
Please spread your hips.
Please put Shoichi-san's picture in my box.
Please enjoy it.
Shoichi-san...
Sayuri...
What do you think of my baby?
Don't ask me that.
I don't know.
If you don't tell me, I'll tell you.
I don't want to.
Shoichi-san's picture is the best.
We're a couple.
Shoichi-san...
Sayuri...
It feels so good.
I can't stop.
I can see your mouth.
It hurts.
Look, Shoichi-san.
Shoichi-san...
I can't move.
I can't move either.
Shoichi-san...
I want you.
It's okay.
I'm going to make you cry forever.
Shoichi-san...
I'm sorry.
Shoichi...
Please, Shoichi.
Please.
Shoichi...
Shoichi, I can't move.
You've worked hard.
Brother...
Aichi! Aichi!
Aichi, wait!
Aichi, are you in there?
Aichi, hurry up!
I can see you!
I can see everything!
Aichi!
Aichi, are you in there?
Aichi, hurry up!
He has a runny nose.
He looks like he's about to die.
Ayumu!
I've helped you so much.
It was my fault...
It hurts.
Calm down.
Don't cry.
It's my fault.
It hurts.
Until the end...
Give it to me.
Sayuri.
If you give it to me again...
I'll give you more.
No.
Umeko's ginseng is delicious.
Mom and she...
They say such a vulgar thing.
They do such a terrible thing.
They are the mother of Giri and Umeko.
No matter how much she went out...
It's disgusting.
Well, Shoichi.
I'm going to go to the party.
Please take care of Akari.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's a long vacation.
I can't ask you to take care of me.
I have a cold.
And today is just a vacation.
But you don't have to worry about the cost of living.
No.
I'm sorry to have you take care of everything.
Sayuri is my wife.
Shoichi.
I'm sorry.
I know it was hard to be abandoned by my sister.
But I didn't think I'd do that to my mom.
I thought we were a real family.
The first impression I had of him was...
He was a kind-looking man.
Actually, Shoichi is a kind person.
He came to my company to take care of my sister.
Even after they got married and got divorced...
His kindness didn't change.
I lost my father when I was young.
His kindness was a strange feeling that I wasn't used to.
Every time Shoichi was kind to me,
Shoichi, I'm sorry.
If you want to take my sister's place,
Thank you for watching.