I don't know why, but I don't think it's a good idea to do that.
This is good.
This is the best.
There is a lot of food in the pot, so please eat a lot.
Thank you.
This is good.
You are a genius in cooking.
No, I'm not.
You are.
Please put this in the lunch box.
This is the best.
This is really good.
I'm going to work hard today.
I'm glad to hear that.
I put a lot of delicious food in the lunch box.
Thank you.
I'm going to be late today.
I see.
You've been particularly busy lately.
The sale of a large apartment has begun.
And I'm going to sign a contract with a large land in SUMOTA.
Please don't work too hard.
I think I'll be able to do it if I overcome this obstacle.
Do you want anything?
No, I don't want anything in particular.
But if I can get a day off, I want to relax with you.
I'm going.
See you later.
Is it warm?
It's hot.
All right.
Hello.
Yes.
Haruki in the east is my husband.
What?
Haruki had a car accident?
Yes.
Haruki.
I'm glad you didn't get hurt.
You said you had an accident at work.
I told you I was fine.
I'm sorry.
If I hadn't driven...
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'm going to be hospitalized for a week from today.
What should I do with my clothes?
It's okay.
We'll follow you.
Take a break.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
Let me know if you need anything.
You're right.
They say hospital food is tasteless.
I'm from Kyushu.
I don't like tasteless food.
I see.
Hello.
Take a break.
Yes.
He's really busy, isn't he?
I think so.
I'm sorry.
Let me know if you need anything.
You don't have to apologize.
If it's an accident, it's a smartphone accident.
Can you buy it for me?
Okay.
And...
Do you know?
It doesn't matter what you think.
It accumulates on its own.
Accumulate?
Yes.
Even if I'm injured, I'm honest.
When I see a nurse, I feel dizzy.
What should I do?
Well...
I'm going to call my husband.
I almost forgot.
I'm not the one who was driving.
When you had an accident, you were depressed.
What if the company finds out?
I'm still young.
I did it.
What should I do?
I see.
Yes.
Okay.
I'll explain it to you.
If I really do it,
I won't have to tell the company about my accident.
Yes.
Are you still there?
My senior is coming back.
I'm sorry for bothering you because of my husband.
I'm sorry.
Well...
What?
Until when?
Until I'm satisfied.
What?
Well...
I'm excited when I see you.
Don't look away.
What?
I'm sorry.
It's close.
Well...
I'm sorry.
Boss.
What?
It's close.
Don't look away.
What?
Don't hide your face.
Look at me.
What?
Don't hide your face.
Look at me.
What?
I'm excited when I see you.
Don't look away.
Let me hold your hand.
No.
Well...
I feel good.
Let me go.
No.
I'm not satisfied yet.
But...
Until now...
I haven't been able to do this since the accident.
What?
Well...
Do you know how hard my body is?
I have a lot of hair.
Look at me.
What?
I'm in trouble.
I might come back.
You'll be fine.
What?
Let me hold your hand.
Well...
What?
It's amazing.
Your hands are warm.
No.
What?
It's amazing.
Well...
I might come back.
You'll be fine.
This is more important than that.
No.
This feels good.
Stand up.
Show me your belly.
Well...
Will you keep it a secret?
Keep it a secret?
I'm in trouble.
What?
I might come back.
Wait.
What?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Shiori.
I'll be busy from tomorrow.
I want you to visit Kazama.
What?
I want you to cook for him.
He doesn't like hospital food.
No.
I...
I'm sorry.
Let me cook for you.
I want you to eat good food.
Thank you.
What do you like?
Well...
I like pork.
That's great.
Thank you.
Well...
Is this all?
What?
I won't tell you.
I'm not good at cooking.
I won't make you sad.
Do you think I'll do that?
Well...
Please don't.
I'm not good at cooking.
I won't tell you.
Please don't.
Well...
I'm not good at cooking.
You have soft breasts.
Have you been touched by your senior?
How do you feel?
I touched you.
It's hard here.
Please don't.
If you don't, I'll tell you.
I'll press here.
Please don't.
Can I open my eyes?
Do you feel this?
You've been acting strange.
Please don't.
Can I lick this?
You look like you're in a good mood.
I told you not to put up with this.
Do you feel good?
Please don't.
You don't look like you're in a good mood.
I can't help it.
Look at this.
Hurry up.
You didn't take a bath yesterday.
How does it taste?
Is it good?
You're good at licking.
Look at me.
Don't look so sad.
Lick me.
It's easier for you to lick me.
You're a good boy.
Is that all you can do?
You can lick me more.
I want you to clean up there, too.
Lick me more.
Lick the back of my hand, too.
Why are you licking me?
Are you excited?
Don't be sad.
Look at me and lick me.
It feels good.
It's hot.
What's wrong with you?
It's dirty.
Drink all the water.
Drink it.
Show me your tongue.
Wow.
Stop it.
It's okay.
It's slippery.
Stop it.
Is it your hobby?
I wonder if you like this.
How do you feel?
Stop it.
I have to thank you.
How do you feel?
Stop it.
Is it here?
What are you drooling?
It's getting narrow.
Stop it.
How do you feel?
Did you drool?
Did you feel good?
Do you feel better?
Stop it.
Do you feel good?
I'm sure you feel better.
Can I go out?
No.
Don't go out.
Stop it.
Please let me go.
I don't have time.
Stop it.
Let me kiss you.
Please.
Stop it.
You feel good, don't you?
If you cry too much, the hospital will find out.
Hold it in.
You feel good, don't you?
Stop it.
Your bed is dirty.
I'm sorry.
I want you to apologize.
Stop it.
You're too weak.
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
You're going to sleep.
My bed is dirty.
Stop it.
You're going to sleep.
I'll do it again.
Stop it.
Can I go home now?
Okay.
Thank you.
Haru-san.
About Kazama-san...
Yes?
Can I ask someone else to replace him?
Wait a minute.
Thank you.
I see.
The woman president.
I'm looking for a replacement.
Today?
I think I can do it.
I'll check.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you for waiting.
What did Kazama-san say?
Nothing.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm leaving.
I have to finish it.
Hello, Kazama-san.
I didn't expect you to come today.
Kazama-san.
I don't think this is good.
I don't want to do anything more to betray him.
I looked it up.
It's a crime to replace a victim.
It's a hidden crime.
Then...
Arrest him.
No.
It's okay.
If you satisfy my desire,
I'll never let you go.
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
Please.
No.
You're wearing something cute.
Did you choose it to show me?
No.
No?
But you knew I'd do this.
No.
Stop it.
I'll make you more embarrassed.
No.
Stop it.
Show me your bottom.
No.
Stop it.
Don't touch me.
I don't want you to touch me.
Stop it.
What did you bring?
I brought a lunch box.
Can I go home today?
Let me in today.
No.
You can't.
I can't have sex anymore.
You can't?
Then...
It's not fair to your wife.
Open your mouth.
No.
But...
Stop it.
I was just about to say that.
You're a good wife.
Stop it.
It feels good.
Did your senior teach you that?
Stop it.
Look at me.
How deep are you going to go?
Go as deep as you can.
It's good.
That felt good.
Stop it.
It's hard to stand up.
Lean on me.
It feels so good.
Are you trying to make me go faster?
I appreciate it.
Stop it.
I've been holding back because you've been doing a lot of pleasant things.
That's right.
That's good.
I wonder what kind of food I'll make tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
I don't need dinner.
It's been hard lately.
I know.
A woman's name?
I'm sorry. I have to make a call.
I'm sorry.
Please don't look at me like that.
You're so cute.
Stop it.
I can't look at you like that.
You're more excited when you're embarrassed like that.
How do you feel?
You're so nervous.
Please don't look at me like that.
What are you doing?
You're so dirty.
I'm sorry.
You have to be serious.
I told you not to get dirty, but you did it again.
I'm sorry.
You can't do that.
You have to apologize properly.
I'm sorry.
The hand I'm touching now has a lot of salt on it.
It's my hand, so it's fine.
You should take off your bra.
I'm sorry.
Please don't do that.
Your breasts are very warm.
Is this right?
I want you to drool.
It feels good.
It feels great.
You're good at this.
It feels good.
You can take it out like this.
I want to take it out.
Come here.
What do you mean?
You can sleep for a long time with this.
I'm sorry.
Oh no I drank too much
Is it okay isn't your belly aching more?
Hey do you think your belly is catching on fire
It's more worse if you spit it out
Your belly hurts
Why are you taking so long
This is bad.
I'm gonna puke.
Well, then.
Oh, right.
I was going to ask you.
Are you busy as usual?
Yes.
I have a call from work at home.
Really?
What?
You said you wanted to take care of your wife.
No matter how busy you are, you can't take your work home.
That's impossible.
Have you been coming home late lately?
Come to think of it,
I always come home after the date has changed.
It's my own feeling, but...
Maybe that phone call...
Maybe.
Is it from another woman?
I'm going home.
Maybe that phone call...
No.
It's just my imagination.
Maybe.
Haru-san.
Um...
What's wrong?
I see.
I haven't done it lately.
I'm sorry.
I have to go to bed early tomorrow.
Um...
Lately...
You seem to call me a lot at home.
Who are you really talking to?
It's work.
I see.
I'm sorry.
You have to go to work tomorrow.
Yes.
Is this all you can eat?
It was delicious.
Um...
About the accident...
I know.
I won't tell anyone, so don't worry.
Thank you for the meal.
I'm sorry.
Look at me.
This is the last time.
I'm sorry.
You're very honest today.
That's not true.
It's hot.
Why are you always sweating?
That's not true.
Maybe you were expecting something like this.
No.
I'm sorry.
You have a beautiful wife.
Why?
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
What?
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
It's easy for you to get a fever.
Are you so excited today?
I'm sorry.
You want to drink more, don't you?
What?
Come on.
I'm sorry.
You've been hospitalized.
You have a wonderful wife.
I'm sorry.
What?
You want to drink more, don't you?
I'm sorry.
What?
This.
Please put this on at least.
Do you want me to do it?
Come here.
I'll put this on you.
Did you really put this on me?
Yes, I did.
You have a wonderful wife.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
You look like you're in a good mood.
It hurts.
Have you already left?
That's amazing.
There are a lot of people.
Let's talk on the phone.
Please don't do that.
Hello, good morning.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I'm going to be hospitalized tomorrow.
Really?
Congratulations on your promotion.
Is that your wife?
I can't let go of your hand.
Your wife's food was the best.
I'm eating it now.
Your wife is really good.
I'm proud of you.
Excuse me.
Mr. Kazama.
What is it?
You promised you wouldn't let go of my hand.
I said I wouldn't let go of your hand.
I didn't promise I wouldn't let go of your hand.
This is not cheating.
This is cheating.
Mr. Kazama.
I said I wouldn't let go of your hand.
Please cry.
This is a condom.
You said you put it on.
It didn't fit.
I didn't put it on from the beginning.
Please cry.
Stop it.
Please stop it.
I'm going to cry.
Please don't make me cry.
I'll do anything.
Don't make me cry.
Don't you want to cry?
Stop it.
Did you say you would do anything?
You don't want me to take it out on you, do you?
Don't take it out on me.
Come on.
Get up and make yourself comfortable.
Don't take it out on me.
I promise.
Please stop it.
It's disgusting.
I didn't know you were so good at moving on your own.
I should have done it with you the other day.
It's disgusting.
I'm getting goosebumps.
Do you feel good?
No.
Don't you feel good?
I'm just trying not to make you angry.
Stop it.
You're the worst.
You're the worst person who's crying and feeling so good.
Stop it.
Please tell me when you're about to leave.
I know.
I don't want you to make me angry.
What are you doing?
I'm getting goosebumps.
Don't do that.
Please.
Stop it.
Don't take it out on me.
I'm not forcing you to do it.
Stop it.
Please.
We made a promise.
Stop it.
I'm not forcing you to do it.
Please.
I'm in danger.
I might be able to have a baby.
I don't want to do it.
Please.
I can't do it.
Stop it.
Take it out on me.
I'm in danger.
Please take it out on me.
Stop it.
Can you cook for me after you get discharged?
I love you.
Mr. Kazuma.
I'm sorry that I couldn't protect you.
What do you love?
Thank you for watching!