Are you going to help me with my interior design.
Ok.
Good morning.
Today, I'm going to show you how to make a simple and delicious breakfast.
I'm going to show you how to make a simple and delicious breakfast.
Honey, eat it quickly because it will cool down.
What? Is there something on it?
No, nothing.
I'm going.
See you.
I don't know what's going on with Yuichi lately.
Is it a problem?
So, I'll be back on Monday.
I understand.
I'm going.
See you.
Good morning.
Is your father on a business trip?
Yes, he's in Hokkaido.
I'm looking forward to the souvenirs.
What?
If anything happens to your father, I'll protect you.
I'm just kidding.
Go wash your face.
Why is my mother so cute?
I can't hold it anymore.
It's finished.
I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to die if I don't do something about it.
Mom, you're such a cutie.
You're a good girl.
I'm in amazement.
I can't wake up at all.
Mother's breast.
It's soft.
I can't wake up at all.
Mother's breast.
Mother's breast is cute.
I can't wake up at all.
It's delicious.
Mother's breast.
I can't wake up at all.
And Mother's breast.
thound
wow
A throat is opened
trembling
sound of mother
movements of mother
This is...
This is my mom's pussy.
Awesome.
I wonder if I can put two fingers in it.
It's in.
Awesome.
Mom.
I can't stand it.
Awesome.
This is my mom's pussy.
Mom.
I feel so good.
Awesome.
Mom.
Yuichi.
What are you doing?
Mom.
Calm down.
I can't stop.
Mom.
Wait.
Please.
I...
I have to be your mom.
Mom.
I feel so good.
Awesome.
Wait, Yui.
I feel so good.
Is that so?
You shouldn't go outside.
Go outside.
Mom.
No!
What happened to you?
What are you doing?
You can't do that.
I have to go wash you.
Get up.
Mom, are you okay?
Mom.
Just one more time.
Stop it.
No!
What are you doing?
Just one more time.
You have to do it.
Stop it.
Mom.
Don't look at me.
You have to do it.
You can't do this.
Stop it.
Mom.
Please.
Just one more time.
No!
I'll take you outside.
That's not the problem.
It is.
Stop it.
It's hot.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
The son's kiss was poor.
I don't know why.
I don't remember.
Yes, this is Takahara.
Oh, Yubiko. It's me.
Oh, it's you.
I just got home, but I bought too many souvenirs.
I'm sorry, but could you pick me up at the station by car?
Are you listening?
Yes, pick me up.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
It's been about a month since I crossed the line with my son.
There were some rules between us parents.
Mom, I need to go to the bathroom.
Oh, sorry.
Dad, you're still here, aren't you?
Yes.
Rule No. 1. Don't do anything when your father is around.
I'm going.
Okay.
I'll be a little late today.
Bye.
Oh, hurry up and go to school.
Make sure you wear a rubber band.
Rule No. 2. Be sure to deny it.
You don't have to do that.
If you're going to put it in, hurry up and put it in.
You're going to be late.
It's okay.
Mom, you feel good, don't you?
No, I don't.
I'll hurry up.
You're going to be late.
Mom, I'm going to put it in.
No, I'm not.
Mom, you're going to be late.
You're going to be late.
Mom, you're wet.
Mom, look.
It's like this.
Stop it.
Hurry up.
School.
Mom, give me a kiss.
Mom, come here.
Sit down.
What are you doing?
Mom, you feel better, don't you?
No, I don't.
It's okay.
Hurry up and put it in.
What are you going to do?
I'm scared.
Mom, you feel better, don't you?
You feel better, don't you?
I'm scared.
You want to do more, don't you?
Don't be late.
I'm scared.
Mom, come here.
Mom, did you go now?
Rule No. 3.
Buy a doll within the scope of your allowance.
I'll sign it.
I'm scared.
Mom, you feel better, don't you?
Hurry up and go.
I can't help it.
Mom, you feel better, don't you?
You feel better, don't you?
I'm scared.
Mom, you feel better, don't you?
You can go home.
Mom...
Aba, go inside the room.
Mom, I'm scared.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh
mhm
mar
w
tan
I can't do it anymore.
What do you mean you can't do it anymore?
You have to go to the hospital as soon as possible.
I can't do it yet.
Look at me.
I can't do it anymore.
You have to go to the hospital as soon as possible.
You still have a long way to go.
Still?
Still.
You feel great, don't you?
No.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, routine
Oh....
you were first
Oh...
I've been scared
Don't...
Man
I slept a lot.
You feel better, don't you?
You should go to school.
Mom.
I'm not done yet.
I don't have a rubber band.
Put it in your mouth.
I'm going to be late.
Rule 4.
When you don't have a rubber band,
you have to put up with it with your hands and mouth.
You have to put up with it.
I don't have a rubber band.
Put up with it.
You have to put up with it.
hear the knock sound
Mom, let's get out of here
An accident occurs
yes
Let's go
I'm sorry.
I'm exhausted.
Oh, I feel refreshed.
Oh, no.
I told you not to put it on paper because it's hard to wash.
Oh, no. I'm late.
I'm going to go.
Mom, I'm going.
I won't do it anymore.
Rule No.5. You should never put a sanitary napkin on paper.
Mom, please.
Just once. I'll take it outside.
No, you have to wait until you get the allowance.
Then, please do it with your mouth.
After that, the young sexual impulse didn't stop.
I can't help it.
With my chest and butt.
I used every part of my body to clean my son.
Oh, no.
Please drink a lot.
Mom, I feel good.
Oh, no.
Please lick my head, too.
Please drink a lot.
Oh, no.
Mom, please drink a lot.
Please drink a lot.
Oh, no.
I'm going to vomit.
Mom, please use your feet.
Please use your feet.
Mom, I feel good.
Oh, no.
Please use your feet.
Mom, I feel good.
I feel good.
I don't want to be a mother.
I'm going to vomit.
Hey, mom.
According to the Internet, there is something called kamikoki.
It's nothing.
Let's finish it quickly.
I'm going to vomit.
Mom, I feel good.
Mom, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Do you want me to rub more?
Mom, I'm sorry.
Mom, look at this.
It's totally different from when you move by yourself.
It's so soft.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Does it feel good to rub your head?
Hey, mom.
It's like you're panting.
Mom, your butt.
I'm so excited to rub your butt.
You have to be a mom.
I'm so excited.
I can't stand it.
Hey, mom.
I want you to rub my armpits.
Mom, your armpits are so beautiful.
Mom.
Mom, aren't you nervous?
I feel weird.
Let me down.
Mom.
I'm going to die.
It feels so good.
Mom's armpits.
Mom.
My armpits are so full.
Mom's armpits.
I'm so excited.
Mom.
Mom, it feels good, doesn't it?
One more time.
Mom.
No.
It's amazing.
Mom, it looks like it's in there.
Mom.
Mom, your armpits are the best.
Mom, I'm going to put a lot on you.
Touch my armpits.
It's amazing.
Mom.
I can't stand it anymore.
Mom's armpits.
I'm going out.
Mom, look at me.
Mom.
You have to make a chest.
Make a soft breast.
Ah.
AH.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
AH.
Oh, it feels so good.
I can't forget it.
Mom.
It feels so good here.
How about this?
Oh, it feels so good.
Mom, I'm here.
Mom, let me down.
Oh, it feels so good.
Let me down a lot.
Like this.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it feels so good.
I can't help it.
Mom.
You have to let me down a lot.
Mom, let me down a lot.
Let me down a lot.
Mom.
Dad, can I ask you something?
What is it?
I have something I want.
It's a little early, but can I get some pocket money?
Here you are.
Don't waste it.
Thank you.
Mom.
He is sleeping.
What are you doing?
Mom.
Mom, I'm home.
What are you doing? It's dangerous.
I bought a rubber band, so let's go to my room.
I have to prepare dinner.
You can do it later.
Let's go.
Mom, hurry up.
Hurry up.
Wait a minute.
I'm sweating because it's hot today, so I'll take a shower first.
What?
Can I?
Here you are.
Mom.
Mom's armpits smell good.
I don't like it.
Mom.
Mom, I don't like it.
I don't like it.
If I don't make him stop doing this for the sake of this child,
I think so, but every time I ask for it, I end up accepting it.
Mom.
Calm down.
I'm so cold.
It's delicious.
You have to be a mother.
Mom.
You're licking me.
I don't like it.
Sit down.
I want you to sit down and lick me.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
I want to fill your mouth.
Lips.
You're moving a lot.
It's hot.
Use your hands.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
Mom, wait a minute.
I'm going to go.
You can go because you want to go.
I want to do more with you.
Show me your butt.
Your butt is the best.
It's hot.
I made you feel better.
I'm tired.
Mom.
I can't stand it.
Wait a minute.
Mom.
It's hot.
I feel good.
Wait a minute.
I can't stand it.
I feel good.
Look at me.
Mom.
It's not mom.
It's hot.
I can't stand it.
Mom.
It's hot.
It's not mom.
I'll fix it.
It's amazing.
Mom.
Get on my back.
I feel good.
Move a lot.
Mom, do you feel good?
I feel good.
I can't stand it.
Show me where it's in.
Mom.
Mom, move a lot.
I can't stand it.
I'll move.
Mom.
You want to take it out, don't you?
Take it out.
Mom.
I want to play with you more.
Wait.
Mom, don't move so much.
Don't touch there.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
I can't stand it.
Mom.
It hurts, doesn't it?
I can't stand it.
I want to play with you more.
Mom, wait.
Wait a minute.
Mom, stop.
Mom.
I want to play with you more.
I can't stand it.
Mom.
I can't stand it without you.
Wait.
I can't stand it.
You've healed, haven't you?
Are you satisfied now?
Mom.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
Calm down.
It's all right.
I can't run away anymore.
Mom.
I can't stand it.
I can't stand it without you.
Mom.
Mom, you're the best.
I can't stand it.
It's all right.
Wait.
I can't stand it anymore.
I can't stand it.
Really.
My father will come back.
It's all right.
Don't fight.
I'm home.
Hey, Yumiko.
Huh? It's pitch black.
Where is she?
Yuichi.
Yeah?
Are you shopping?
I just wanted to study.
Do you know where your mom is?
I don't know.
I think she went to the convenience store.
I see.
I have to go to the office today.
I have to drink again if I get sick.
Take me to my mom.
Okay, I'll tell her.
I'm counting on you.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
She left.
I was almost safe.
What are you talking about?
Oh, no.
I thought you were going to have a heart attack.
I was so excited that I thought you would find out.
I'm tired.
Let me rest.
Oh, no.
Mom.
Hey, Yuichi.
You're here again.
Mom is here.
Wait a minute.
This feeling...
Did you run out of rice?
It's okay.
Wait.
I have some rice.
Take it out.
Mom.
Just a little.
No, no.
I have some rice.
Mom.
Oh, no.
Wait.
Take it out.
I can't take it out.
You've already started moving.
Do you really want to take it out?
I think it's a good day today.
I'll let you do whatever you want.
Mom.
It's okay, right?
I said no.
Wait.
Stop.
I have to take it out.
Wait.
Mom.
It hurts.
I can't do it.
It feels better here.
Come here.
I want to kiss you.
Give me a kiss.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Stop it.
Mom.
You're amazing.
You're totally different.
I'm going to eat it.
Wait.
Mom.
I have to do it.
That night,
as if Yuichi wanted to go back into me,
I'm home.
Welcome home.
It must have been tough.
Yeah, but I managed to get through it.
I'm glad you're okay.
By the way, where were you yesterday?
I had something to give to my neighbors.
Where's your family?
I don't know. I think they're still sleeping.
What do you want for breakfast?
No, I'm sleepy.
Wake me up when it gets cold.
Okay.
Good night.
Sweetheart.
To be continued...