Will you replace coffee?
No, no, I’ll be sure that the call will come soon.
So I will prepare medication.
Yes to.
Sorry, I wrote this before.
Well, it was okay, because it was Kanto, and it was good to eat.
Oh yeah yeah.
Yes, age is not going to take away, and medication is getting more and more every year.
Please take care, you are very busy here.
I have a golf course this week, but it’s hard to run around and hurt my back.
What’s happening, do you still want to wake up?
Oh, so I will wake you up.
I’m not a child, so I don’t need to get up in the morning.
You are the right guy, do not get the job.
What do you usually do during the day?
I look at the website or look for work, but I’m still looking for work.
See the site.
WEB but also directly.
You should have taken the interview and taken it directly from yourself.
Yes to.
In any case, we did not have the internet.
In any case, in the present time, this is not enough for the school.
Telephone or fax.
The fax was in the last century.
It is difficult, right?
I think you’ve been in the past for fax.
I missed Poppy.
You were not a pocket?
Yes to.
Do you say you love Poppy?
Why did you do it? read something.
I love you 14106.
Good morning, not to mention.
Good morning to you.
So much awakening.
Oh well good morning.
I played online games late yesterday.
No, no, that is why.
What about you getting a job?
It is time to get in shape.
Yes, I will try hard.
Mostly of Usha.
You lack the desire.
When your father.
No matter how much I wanted, I tried my best.
What food is it?
Yes I am sorry.
Isn’t it time for you?
Oh yeah yeah.
Yes to.
I will visit you, Visit.
Yes, I will try hard.
I am going.
Come on you.
Come to go.
You are preparing breakfast.
Thanks to.
Can I clean up your room today?
You have to buy cheese.
Sorry thank you.
I go to the toilet.
I will enter.
Can you clean your room?
Sorry thank you.
It is very dispersed.
Sorry to
Can I wash this clothes?
is okay.
What about this magazine?
That is okay too.
Can I throw it away?
Yes is
This is?
Please also please.
This is good too?
Congratulations to Tissot.
It is
Was it chronic?
I have a tick, so I’ll buy it later.
Yes is
Can I get this towel?
This is?
Oh yes please.
1 2 3 4
This is
Oh yeah
There is.
Yes is
Thanks to.
Would you leave this magazine?
Yes, please leave it.
Then a little.
Please please.
Oh sorry to sorry.
Yes is
by Mr.
Going to eat today?
Oh yeah, I will go.
Yes is
How is?
Find a good job?
No, it is quite strict.
Because you are a comic.
No so does.
Be more confident in yourself.
Yes is
If you do not, you will find a good job.
Okay okay okay.
Thanks to.
Okay, so about this.
I will wash you.
Yes, thank you very much.
Yes, I am sorry
Then is.
Yes is
I will be in your room tomorrow.
Yes, you have to rest.
So what happened to the right man?
What time is today?
As usual, I spent the day in my room.
Absolutely, it is a problem.
Take care of everything, please.
I understand you.
Go to sleep.
Oh, it hurts.
Hurt the shoulder?
Oh, a little
Make a light massage.
Oh yeah, sorry to.
well is
Oh yeah
here here?
Do you feel good?
Oh yeah
It feels good.
You recently
It’s a little too hard, isn’t it?
Yes to
touching the body.
So much
Please do not force.
Yes, I understand, thank you
Oh, it has become so much lighter.
well done.
Okay, so I go to sleep.
Good night.
Good night to you.
Yes
Have you already slept?
They clean up the room and are spreading again.
Sorry, this is it.
Oh, and go on.
Students
Oh really not.
Oh, sorry to sorry.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Don’t tell Mr. Tove.
Delighted
The tree.
Wu is
Really sorry.
Sorry to
Because it is okay.
Really sorry.
I will not tell your father.
Please do not say.
OK is OK.
by Mr.
It looks like a cheek.
calmly be
Because it is okay.
Please do not say.
Mr Tove, look at it.
Hore to calm.
Okay okay okay.
Sorry, I am sorry
Is it okay?
by Mr.
Sorry to
How is?
Is it okay?
Take a slow deep breath.
I have calmed up a little.
Have you calmed?
well was
Really sorry.
Do not work anymore.
Such a shameful thing.
I was also in the Department of Education and interviewed with my colleagues.
It’s okay, so be more confident.
Sorry, thank you very much.
Oh, my dear, what happened?
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah
What happened.
What happened, calm down.
Why not.
Calm to be.
What are you saying.
No, if not be calm.
Sorry to
What are you doing, no.
No to
Come away from.
No, do not touch it.
A little, leave it.
Relax and really.
Leave away
Just a little.
No to no.
Do not do this, stop.
You have to deal with everything.
No more, no more
Think about your mother once.
What are you doing?
No to no.
No, not if not
No to!
Everyone is there.
Stop it, stop it.
calmly be
A little
I will there.
by Mr.
What are you doing.
I will there.
A little
Stop to
Leave away
A little
No to
calmly be
A little
No, a little bit of a bit.
No is
No come here.
by Mr.
What are you doing.
by
It is Nabe.
by Mr.
Do not be angry with your father.
You are no longer touched.
It won’t stop anymore.
A little...
A bit exactly.
Stop it now.
No to no.
No to
exactly
Oh oh oh oh
Please be careful, please.
Please please
A huge force came out.
by Tejas
Stop it, please
What are you doing?
Where are you near?
Stop to
Opened again.
No is
Stop to
What is?
I will not stop.
Stop to
Stop it
Opening it again.
I can smell like this, and I smell like this.
Do not mess up something?
I want to see below.
here below, here below
Oh oh oh oh!
Please show me.
Do not look at me.
Show me it.
Oh yeah
A little
Don’t look at me, Mr. Yoshino.
See also.
Oh, a little
Oh yeah
No to
Show it.
not appear.
Oh well
Great is
Stop now, stop now.
Show me it, right.
Wait a little.
Stop laughing and don’t laugh.
Show me properly.
Stop it.
No, I am not, wait.
No, no, no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
Is it here?
No, no to no.
has been in.
Do not enter.
It hurts, the fingers.
My fingers are in me.
Among them
Move it.
Amazing though.
It will be warm and comfortable in your stomach.
My fingers are pleased.
by Ar.
Among them
by ahm
No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No No
Oh is
No to
What that.
My feet do not hurt.
No to!
by Nay
Oh awesome.
The mother’s shit.
by Bishabisha
No to no.
such a place.
by Nay
No to
I cannot endure.
Can I enter?
A little
Drink it.
No more drinking.
Come ahead
No, wait a little.
Only ahead.
Wait a little.
still is
Go ahead, go ahead.
No, please please
No to!
Oh no!
Oh, a little
A little
Oh well, oh well
Wait a moment, I haven’t woke up yet.
Go ahead, go ahead, go ahead.
go to
Go home you.
He was in a bath.
How was the right man today?
Eat well or not.
It seems like I have some rest today.
Absolutely unnecessary, he too.
Yes is
Lunch tomorrow.
I went to golf the day before.
I will avoid this in the car today.
Congratulations to both.
Yes, I understand
What happened, my friend?
I am in the bath now, wait a while.
I’m going to play golf tomorrow morning.
I went in the day before, so I just left.
Oh, my dear, what happened?
Mother, Mother
No to no.
I can no longer endure.
No to
by Nayer
No to no.
by Mr.
Be calm to.
A little
No, no no no no no.
calm and be calm.
by Nirvana
Stop it.
What do you do.
by
calmly be
Be calm to.
Because this cannot be done.
by
Stop it.
Yes
No to
Stop it now.
Stop it.
So stop it.
If you are calm.
by Nirvana
No to
A little
Do not do this.
Please please
We can take courage.
Masha Kiki
So be calm.
Please please
calmly be
This is this
The the
and
Oh yeah
Yippidy yi yippity yay.
I want to enter.
No to
by
In the refrigerator.
I understand
by hand
No to
by
No, no no no no.
not to enter.
No to no.
by Mr.
No, just that.
Oh yeah
Oh oh oh oh oh oh
by
Oh yeah yeah yeah
My own
Also also.
well well
Nam is
Oh yeah yeah yeah
No to no.
Do not come.
No to.
Kilimanjaro
No to
and more.
Oh awesome.
slowly
and more
Oh is
Oh awesome.
by
There are no people.
He has a big voice.
I am ending somewhere.
What am I doing?
Please do not go.
away
Gaw
Oh yeah
Oh yeah yeah
Me is
B is trapped
Oh well
and more
Oh well.
Once once
Ugh
The tongue, the tongue
The tongue
The tongue alone.
Say to me crying.
No, no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
by Mr.
No tooth.
by Brist
by Mr.
This thing
You should never tell your father.
Oh yeah, of course.
It is cold.
So say to.
I received a mail from my father.
We arrived at the Chiba Colf House.
Oh is
Is it a dark day tomorrow?
There is
From what time?
You will eat breakfast.
Thanks to.
Tomorrow from 9 o’clock.
I hope you find a job soon.
Always have confidence.
I failed my exam eight years ago.
I have lost confidence in a lot of things.
And I’m really sorry for doing this to my mother.
No, I am sorry for myself.
I have such a blind face in front of you.
No, but I think it’s a little bit like growing up.
And I was very pleased with it, because it was the first time.
Oh, that was what I just said?
Yes, I have said it a lot of times.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
So many times, I said.
Probably about 50 times.
Oh, it is crazy.
No longer with you.
He has been tight on his back since.
Sorry to
It became stiff again.
Yes is
To your father.
Definitely not telling.
of course is.
Good food interview, and good luck.
Yes, I will try hard.
No problem though.
Heavy
It has become so hard.
Not all of them are large and cannot get in.
Good food you make.
The sweet taste is strong.
Good for sweet food.
Another one.
I came out in my mouth.
hardly
too hard
What is the best feeling?
Is it first?
here here?
It is growing ever greater.
No to
by Tjap
Oh yeah
just just
I got dried up.
Follow it tightly.
by
This summer.
Oh well delicious.
Oh madly
It is tighter than before.
It feels good.
by Rush
by Mom.
I want to make my child.
Okay is.
I fear
Feel good
I was scared.
You will be surprised.
Great, it feels good here.
Oh oh oh
The right yours.
Get the water out.
go out
Oh, the hard
by
Full of voices.
I am used to.
I am lying, mother.
I was dirty with my sperm.
Let me wash it.
Yes is
Please use them.
This here
here here
Let me handle.
thanks to
Mr Alley
Why do I do.
Oh, oh
Oh is
Are you enough?
Just just got out.
Are you okay?
Eat well sir.
I am also a diner.
Oh yeah, so to say.
Oh yes yes
You seem to have interviewed.
I am a doctor, but I will try.
Oh yeah, well done.
You have lost your ex.
Oh you have changed.
Thanks to.
Do you not think so?
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Okay, I am going to go quickly.
Okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay.
I have cleaning.
Oh yes.
Not much too much.
I am going.
Come to go.
Come on you.
Stay hard on.
Thanks to.
Coffee is in place?
Now it is okay.
What happened, Mr Asuka?
I also got the interview and wanted to make my mother feel confident.
My mom is beautiful, too.
This is this.
It is soft.
No to
Feel the food.
Before the food.
I want to get a chicken.
No time is.
But there is no time.
I want to do it anymore, no problem.
No to
You have to prepare, right?
I understand, I understand.
So I will let you relax.
The eye?
Feel good
It feels good.
I like here too.
Feel good
Very good feeling.
Kyle, the big one is back today.
Is it okay?
Very good you.
Not very hard?
Not too hard, very good feeling.
You are kneeling your feet.
Sleep here.
How many times do you do it, Mom?
Okay is.
is beautiful.
Let me guess.
It feels like.
He is a big big bitch.
I will drink more.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
This time
It is not great, I will eat.
well is
It feels too much.
Is it enough?
Strengthen to
OK is OK.
say say say.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Yes
Sorry to sorry.
by Mr.
How is?
Have you relaxed?
It was great feeling.
Are you confident about this?
Yes is
well was
When I come back from food.
I will make you more confident.
Thanks to.
Succeed to.
Yes, let’s open this.
Thanks to.
First job today or not.
Today, I am also listening to new people.
Do not succeed, sir.
Yes, absolutely completely wrong.
You’ve been holding me back for years, so I didn’t have to worry.
I have a car or two, and I don’t know what it is.
It feels like it’s getting bigger. 🙂 Glad.
Oh yeah yeah.
Okay, then it is time for me to come out.
Come out, oh, I’ll send you.
No to no.
Come to go.
I got full of stomach.
Because it is shrinking.
Congratulations to you.
Feel good
Not painting on the face.
Even hungry.
here and here.
Do this so.
The bread
Want to touch more?
I want to touch.
I will flow a little.
If you leave it here.
Very sweaty.
Oh is
by
No to
Oh Oh Oh
Only the Steam Styles.
Drink a lot.
Mother, hold her there.
Take off your ass.
Great to Mom.
I go to sleep.
Feel good
Eat it! eat it!
Would you fuck.
It is closed.
Oh yeah
Sorry to
A little
Oh is
Go to Go.
by
A little
Wait to
by
A little pleasure.
OK is.
Come to
The tree.
I want here.
A very big chip.
Full of it.
It is full in your hands.
My stomach hurt.
Enter full of.
greatly
Feel good
From below to here.
greatly
Oh well! it is cute!
Focused
Oh yeah!
Oh oh oh!
Sleep, sleep and well.
I will die.
Oh the shit!by
Oh yeah...
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Do not go...
Oh oh oh oh oh
Then then then then...
Oh, and so on.
It is inside St. Robert.
Stop to stop.
Touch and move.
This is good.
There is a lot of taste in me.
I love it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, no one has a tongue.
Oh oh oh
Since 11 o’clock.
You still have a little time, right?
You can do it once more.
His voice is so hard.
by
Feel good
from first