I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
omen
Hello?
Ah...
It's you?
How are you?
I'm fine.
That's good. How about you?
I'm getting used to it.
That's good.
Are you eating properly?
I'm eating, but it's just a convenience store bento.
You can't cook, can you?
I want to eat your food.
But I'm sorry I suddenly decided to go on a business trip.
I'm sorry I decided to go on a business trip.
You're the most difficult person to deal with.
That's right.
I can't help it.
But there's been a sudden case in a long time.
I'm in trouble.
My colleague, Yamashita.
Last year, Watanabe-kun.
I think he was sent to the countryside.
I'd like to take care of you, too.
It's hard to get a plane ticket.
I have to do my best to get back to the company as soon as possible.
Do your best.
Come back soon.
It's cold to be alone.
I just got a call.
I'm going out.
See you later.
I'm going.
Yes.
It's Nakanishi.
Excuse me.
I'll open it now.
Hello.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Hello, Nakanishi.
Hello.
I'm Yamashita.
My husband is always with me.
Even though it's a company case,
I'm sorry to bother you.
Not at all.
This time,
I brought your insurance documents.
Is that so?
Thank you.
Please come in.
Excuse me.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Here are your insurance documents.
Please sign here.
I'll come to pick it up.
I see.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Thank you.
It's a nice house.
Is this your house?
Yes.
It's my husband's name.
It's a residential loan.
Is that so?
It must be hard for you.
Yes.
Actually,
I got a report from the HR department
about your husband.
I see.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but the HR department
is not reliable.
At this rate,
we can't avoid
the long term
of the current regional business
I see.
On the other hand,
regarding the
reduction of human rights fees,
your husband's name
is listed
in the list of
early retirement
and so on.
What?
The list?
Well,
can't you do something about it?
It's a residential loan,
and you're working hard
in the countryside.
I'm also
a direct boss with human rights.
I'm working hard
for Tachibana,
who is working hard
in the countryside.
Well,
it's okay.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
It's hard for Tachibana, isn't it?
Even though it's the company's case,
it's a sudden business trip.
By the way,
I deliberately
sent her to the countryside.
What do you mean?
The wife of Tachibana
was a very good woman, wasn't she?
Oh, yes.
I, Suzuki-kun,
don't know what to hide,
but I'm a big fan of Murui.
The head of the department
violated the human rights
and sent her to the countryside
alone.
Yes.
Oh, hello.
Yes, it's okay.
What?
Oh, yes.
Yes,
it's okay.
Oh, yes.
If you look inside,
you can see Suzuki-san
from the same department.
Yes.
It seems that he brought
some insurance documents.
Yes.
Okay.
Yes,
it's okay.
Thank you.
Do your best.
Yes.
I'm doing the laundry.
See you.
Yes.
I'm doing the laundry.
See you.
Bye.
I'm doing the laundry.
See you.
Yes.
Okay.
Bye.
Contact information, personal number,
and the name and age of the person.
Yes, that's right.
I'll leave this document with you.
Thank you.
Um, Mr. Nakanishi.
Yes?
It's about my husband's personal information that I told you about the other day.
Oh, about that?
Actually, my wife...
Actually, the situation isn't that good.
The company's balance of power has been fluctuating.
I'm also working for my husband as his direct superior.
I see.
Can't you do something about it?
My husband doesn't know anything and is working hard in the countryside.
I see.
Ma'am.
You know about internal affairs, right?
As a man, I'll do my best for my husband.
So...
It's more like a give-and-take.
I'd like you to help me for my husband's sake.
Oh, me?
Of course.
What can I do?
Ma'am.
Yes?
You know, right?
What?
Ma'am?
You're a grown-up woman.
Is this a problem?
Please don't.
Then...
I'll do my best for my husband's sake.
I'd like you to help me for my husband's sake.
What?
Please don't.
I'm in trouble.
Are you sure?
Ma'am.
My husband will stay in the countryside as a single man forever.
No!
Ma'am!
Please let me go.
No!
What are you doing?
Please let me go.
You're in good shape, ma'am.
No!
This is Tachibana's rice.
Stop!
Ma'am.
Your butt.
No!
Ma'am.
Stop!
Please let me go.
This is for your husband's sake.
I'll do my best for my husband's sake.
Please let me stay with you.
No!
Ma'am.
You're soaking wet.
Tachibana has been single for a long time.
No!
Are you okay?
I'm tired.
Please let me stay with you.
Ma'am.
No!
Please don't do this anymore.
Are you okay?
My husband will scold me.
You don't have to go back to the company for a long time.
You bought a house in Bunjyo.
You can't live with your husband forever.
I'm sorry.
No!
Ma'am, what are you doing?
I can't do this anymore.
I'll do my best.
Please let me go.
I'll do my best for my husband's sake.
Please do your best, too.
Okay?
Don't cry.
Ma'am.
No!
Are you okay?
It's about time.
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
You know what I'm doing, right?
No!
It's okay.
It's a give and take.
No!
Please don't do this.
What?
No!
It's okay.
Leave it to me.
No!
Please don't do this.
Ma'am, you can't do this.
I can't do this.
I'll do my best.
Yes, it's me.
Are you coming?
The president?
Okay.
I'm going back to the office.
I'll hang up.
That's all for today.
Please think about your husband.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
It's okay.
What can I do for you today?
I heard that Tachibana brought the money home.
So I asked him to keep it.
I haven't heard from him yet.
This is the project document of the Himawari Hill House.
I see.
I'll call him.
Hello?
President Nakanishi came to see you.
He said he came to keep the documents.
Documents?
I didn't say that.
I'm sorry.
Where is he?
He's in the bedroom.
Bedroom?
He's in the chest.
Chest in the bedroom?
Okay, I'll check.
I'm sorry.
Please wait a moment.
Where is he?
Wait a moment.
Is he sleeping?
Is this a big file?
I think so.
Can I use it for a video tour?
Yes, please.
Can you see it?
Yes, I can.
Himawari?
Himawari Hill?
This?
Yes.
Himawari.
This is it.
Thank you.
Is this all?
How is it?
Did you find it?
This is it.
Mr. Tachibana, how are you?
I'm fine.
How about you?
I'm doing my best.
I see.
You should come back soon.
We need more people.
I want to come back soon.
How about you?
Is it hot?
I don't know.
The weather is not good.
Is there a typhoon?
I don't think so.
Be careful.
Don't get hurt.
I'll give this to you.
See you.
Stop it.
I'll give this to you.
Please come back soon.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I was excited the other day.
About my husband...
I don't know what's going on.
It's getting worse.
I'm doing my best.
How about you?
Can you take off your clothes?
How do you feel?
What do you mean?
I can take care of my husband.
But I can't take care of my wife.
I don't know what to do.
But I can't do this.
If my husband finds out...
I don't know if my husband will be able to return to the company.
It's not an exaggeration to say that it's up to me.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I haven't seen my husband for a long time.
I'm sure you have a lot of them.
I'm sorry.
My wife is a really good woman.
I wanted a wife like my wife.
I'm sorry.
Let's do our best for your husband.
I'll do my best.
What a nice boob.
I'm sorry.
Please stop.
I can't.
Is it okay if your husband doesn't come back?
I'm sorry.
You'll be so happy.
I can't.
Please stop.
What's wrong?
It's okay.
I won't tell my husband.
Of course I won't tell anyone.
You have a hard mouth.
I'm sorry.
This is also a secret.
Do you always wear pants like this?
What a nice butt.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
This is for your husband.
What's wrong?
You're so wet.
I'll put my finger here.
I won't let you move.
Your waist is moving.
I'll make it a little tighter.
I'm sorry.
Your wife is sleeping.
I can't stand it.
What are you talking about?
Please forgive me.
I won't do it again.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I want you to kiss me.
I'm sorry.
Please lick my head.
I want to lick my wife's head.
Please push me.
I'm sorry.
Are you satisfied?
You can't be satisfied with just a kiss, can you?
I can't do it.
It's okay.
I have a hard mouth.
This is for your husband.
I'm sorry.
Your wife's pussy is very hard.
It's very hard and unpleasant.
Please stop moving.
I'm sorry.
How do you like my pussy?
Your wife's pussy is very hard.
I'm sorry.
Please stop moving.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sorry.
Thank you ...
Thank you very much ...
Thank you too ...
I'm sorry.
I felt so good that I cried a lot.
Now you can rest assured about your husband.
Please.
I'm sorry.
Hello, wife.
Were you washing your face?
I'm sorry.
I rang the doorbell several times.
The door was open.
It's dangerous.
I see.
It's getting dangerous around here.
You have to be careful.
Yes.
I have a good news for you today.
Your husband has been released from prison.
Really?
I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
This is also thanks to your hard work.
I want you to cooperate with me one more year.
One more year?
Yes.
One more year.
I'm sorry.
I'm in trouble no matter how many times I come.
My husband may come back to me one more year.
Are you sure?
I'm sorry.
It's my husband.
It's okay.
Get out.
It's a video call.
It's okay.
Hello.
Are you okay?
Do you have a document?
I'm fine.
What are you doing now?
I was doing the laundry.
Did you do the laundry?
Yes.
Didn't you get a letter from the bank?
A letter?
Yes.
It's a house loan.
I haven't been able to confirm it yet.
It's coming soon.
Yes.
Tell me now.
Okay.
A house loan?
Yes.
We have a variable interest rate loan.
I see.
The interest rate will probably increase in the long term.
It can't be helped.
I'm sorry.
Do you do the laundry?
Do you dry your hair?
It smells.
I don't have time.
I see.
It's raining.
I have to dry my hair.
It's raining over there.
You...
Don't you use a moisturizer?
Moisturizer?
Yes.
Should I use it?
It smells when you dry your hair.
You should use a moisturizer.
Moisturizer...
Are you okay?
Are you busy?
No, I'm not busy at all.
Are you okay?
Are you sick?
I'm not sick.
Why?
Do you have a fever?
I don't know.
Are you sick?
I may be a little tired.
It's not a big deal.
Thank you.
I'm going to take a bath.
Okay.
Good luck.
Be careful.
You too.
Are you really okay?
I'm fine.
I'll hang up.
Bye-bye.
It's over.
You did your best.
What should I do if he finds out?
You should be patient.
Did you feel good?
I'm sorry.
Give me a hug.
I was also excited.
Please touch me.
I became like this because I was excited about my wife.
You did your best.
Please give me a hug.
It feels good.
Your wife's mouth is the best.
It's hot.
What are you doing?
I'm fine.
Why are you taking a bath?
Please cooperate with me.
I'm scared.
I don't know if your husband will come back to the main office.
It depends on your wife's cooperation.
I'm scared.
Please look at me.
Don't close your eyes.
It's hot.
You did your best.
Let your husband finish his work.
How do you feel about your husband?
Don't ask me such a question.
Your wife...
It doesn't matter if it's a lie.
Please tell me that you like me.
For your husband's sake.
I like you.
One more time.
I'm glad.
It feels good.
Please tell me that you like me.
I like you.
How did it go?
Everything went well.
I see.
I'll ask your wife to like you tonight.
Can I?
Good evening.
I asked Suzuki to come tonight.
Wait a minute.
What are you going to do?
I'm sorry, Suzuki.
I'll ask your wife to like you tonight.
Can I touch you?
Can I touch your beautiful wife?
Please don't.
I like you.
Please.
My heart is pounding.
Wait a minute.
I like you.
I can see that when you take off your apron.
Why?
Isn't it good?
This is also for you.
It's amazing.
You have a soft skin.
I'll massage your face.
Can I?
This is the first time I've massaged your face.
It's amazing.
Please stop.
You have a cute bra today.
That's right.
It's amazing.
Please show me more.
Did you see the video I took the other day?
I thought I'd share the video with everyone in the club.
Please stop.
Is it no good?
At least cheer up SUZUKI.
Do you want to see my breasts?
Yes.
Do you want to try it yourself?
It's amazing.
This will cheer you up.
Please cheer up SUZUKI.
It's amazing.
Please touch here.
Please.
It's amazing.
She told me that she likes me.
Is that so?
I have evidence.
Please show it to SUZUKI.
I thought SUZUKI would cheer up when she saw it.
Please cheer up SUZUKI in another way.
It's amazing.
Please cheer up SUZUKI in my way.
It's all for your husband.
It's up to you whether your husband can return to the company.
Please look at my breasts.
It's amazing.
Please cheer up SUZUKI.
My wife's breasts are soft and warm in my mouth.
I'm excited.
She is the best woman.
Please hold my head.
It's amazing.
You are good.
Please hold my head.
From tomorrow.
It's amazing.
SUZUKI's breasts are so big that I can't put them in my mouth.
Please hold my head.
I want to make my wife feel good.
It's amazing.
Do you feel good?
You are the best.
It's amazing.
Please eat more.
Don't your feet hurt?
You can stand up.
It's amazing.
I can't stand up.
Do you want to sleep?
Please sleep.
I want my wife to sleep with SUZUKI's breasts.
Please.
It's amazing.
Your breasts are so soft.
Your breasts are getting wet.
It's amazing.
What did you do?
I'm sweating.
I got a job offer from TACHIBANA.
Please make SUZUKI feel good.
Please.
Please don't.
I'll spread it to everyone.
Please make SUZUKI feel good.
Or should I send a video to my husband?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I did bad
Blessings
I hope you return to the room soon
Let's do our best more and more.
Why are you crying?
Why?
What?
Why don't you push me every day when you sleep?
Sleep?
I want to be in a good mood today.
You two are getting bigger.
What do you mean?
You are so pretty.
What do you want to say?
I want to talk a lot.
But you can talk when your husband comes back.
Because my husband never comes back.
I'm not satisfied with what I want.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
You are getting bigger.
I want you to love me.
You have a big heart.
You are getting bigger.
I'm excited.
I feel good.
You are getting bigger.
You feel good, right?
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
ah ah ah
Mhm
Barely
Yeah yeah Yeah yeah
nea
Hmm
even
u fireworks
Umm
What?
Oh my god
Oh defines
Ohh
Oh
You're at 30.
Because of you, she's so weak.
She needs you to get better.
You need us.
You're right.
Shall we go back to bed?
Then go back.
OK, let's go back.
I love you.
The dogs make a great sound too.
I'm thirsty!
Here you are.
Let me see your mouth.
You look comfortable.
Thank you.
Please put this on your face.
It's delicious.
If you keep doing that, I'll cut you.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I haven't put anything in my mouth yet.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It hurts so much.
I'll put this on your face.
Please put this on your face.
It hurts.
It's big.
It's big, isn't it?
I'll put this on your face.
It hurts.
It hurts so much.
I'll put this on your face.
It's big.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
It hurts so much.
Look at me.
Don't look at me.
It hurts so much.
I'll put this on your face.
You can't go back to your husband.
I can't go back to my husband.
I'll give you a massage every day.
It hurts so much.
It feels good.
Do you like it?
I like it.
I'll give you more.
I'll give you a massage.
Stop it.
Are you lonely?
I'm lonely.
You have a lot of hair.
Give me a lot.
You can't help me.
I don't know?
I can't help it?
If you don't mind, can I go inside?
I'm going to fall.
It's so big.