P Matte.
Hello.
Please come on in.
Taki-san, looks like he's been here.
Really?
That's a lot of furniture.
You said your chair is cold.
Thank you.
Lunch was great.
It was so busy.
The register was so crowded.
The manager was so mean.
He was always mad at us.
I understand the staff's work,
but I want them to do the register.
I want them to help us.
Taki-san had four hands.
That's how busy he was.
Are you working?
Yes, I am.
Here you are, Taki-san.
Thank you.
You are so busy this year.
How is your shift, Takuma-kun?
It's been a while.
Today is Monday, isn't it?
I see.
I heard that your shift will be changed.
Really?
What should I do?
The manager said that he would do the register again.
Again?
I don't want to do the register.
I don't want to fix it.
I want to do the register,
but I can't do it.
The shift will be changed.
I want someone to do it.
I need someone.
Do you have anyone?
I can't think of anyone.
I want someone to do it with me.
What do you do on your days off?
Recently...
Do you have any friends?
Recently, I started playing volleyball.
Volleyball?
Yes, volleyball.
That one?
Yes, that one.
My friend recommended it to my wife.
You are tall, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
You look like it.
Am I tall?
I'm 173cm tall.
You are taller than me.
How tall are you, Takuma?
I said I'm 170cm tall,
but I'm actually 168cm tall.
Really?
I'm wearing sneakers.
Let's stand in a line.
What?
It's a blind date.
I can't do it anymore.
Let's stand in a line.
What do you think?
You're right.
Am I taller than you?
I know that.
We don't have a chance to stand in a line.
I'm still 20 years old.
Really?
I'm going to be 20 soon.
I believe I'm going to be 20 soon.
You're tall, but you're inexperienced.
Thank you.
You're still inexperienced.
Did you lose weight when you were a student?
I didn't work out much.
That's a shame.
I know.
I have a competition next month.
I always work out on weekends.
Is it around here?
Where?
Is that the gym?
Yes.
You do it?
I go to the gym about three times a week.
Next month?
Let's go.
I have a class.
I can't.
I have a test.
I can't go.
I wanted to see it.
I wanted you to cheer for my team.
What's your team?
Himarigaoka Pink Panthers.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
There are a lot of words mixed up.
Really?
Can I say it again?
Again?
Please say it again.
Himarigaoka Pink Panthers.
Yes.
It's a long name.
I don't know.
Do you call them?
Judges?
It's funny.
Where?
Where should I look?
It's embarrassing.
Is your uniform pink?
Is it flashy?
It's a design.
I didn't see it.
Take a picture of it.
I don't want to.
I want to see it.
It's definitely pink.
I have a test.
I have a test next month.
I have a lot of things to do.
I'm really busy at university.
I see.
That's right.
Are you busy at university?
Yes.
Do you exercise at university?
I'm in a circle, but I play soccer.
I was serious until high school.
I think I went to university.
I want to exercise.
I play soccer.
Soccer is good.
I have a part-time job, soccer, and classes.
I have a test, so I'm busy with classes.
I have a part-time job, too.
It's going to be hard to change shifts again.
I might want to quit soccer.
Are you going to get a job soon?
I'm going to get a job in two years.
I'll get a job in the spring of next year.
I'll get a job at a company.
I see.
You'll get a job next year.
It's too early to get a job.
I agree.
I'll be a supermarket worker for the rest of my life.
You'll be a supermarket worker for the rest of your life.
If I were you, I'd be relieved.
Really?
Yes.
I'll be a supermarket worker for the rest of my life.
You seem to be popular at university.
What?
You're popular, aren't you?
What do you think?
What?
You seem to be popular.
Right?
You're a soccer manager.
You're in the same class as me.
Shun.
What?
Well...
I'm trying to be popular.
I talk a lot.
I've been playing soccer since I was in elementary school and middle school.
I was in a boys' high school.
I didn't get along with my classmates.
It's been a long time.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's hard.
I'm older than you, but I'm easy to talk to.
I'm not a mother, but I'm like an older sister.
I'm easy to talk to.
I'm not good at talking to people who are a little older than me.
I'm not good at it, but I don't know.
I see.
I'm surprised.
Are you older than me?
Well...
I'm easy to talk to.
Do you have anyone you like?
Do you have anyone you're interested in?
I have someone, but...
I'm busy.
You have someone.
Is that person older than you?
Yeah, I think so.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, that's how it is for me.
I don't have a girlfriend, so...
So?
It's like...
I'm a virgin.
Oh, really?
I don't really say it, but...
I don't know.
I didn't know that.
I don't think it's necessary, but...
Well...
Yeah, that's how it is.
Oh, really?
I didn't know that.
Yeah.
I see.
I don't know.
It's difficult.
I think I can get a girlfriend soon.
Really?
I don't know.
You'd think she would, but it's like she just arrives.
Yeah, I think so.
Taki, do you have children?
I don't have any yet.
Oh...
Well, it all depends on the timing.
Oh, there are something like abnormalưng.
An informant?
Yeah, my kids are like informants.
Taki's children are about...
they're about this big.
No, I'm not that big.
In 2 months.
3 months.
4 months.
You're a really big girl.
No, I'm not.
My husband is busy these days.
What does he do?
He works at a pharmaceutical company.
Oh, I see.
Does he go to a doctor and sell medicine?
Yes.
It must be difficult for him.
I think he needs a lot of knowledge.
Do you know a lot about medicine?
No, I don't.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
The bath is ready.
Thank you.
I have a meeting tomorrow morning.
Oh, I see.
Thank you for your hard work every day.
Do you want to get a foot massage tonight?
Sounds good.
I'm counting on you.
I learned how to stretch at Mama's Ballet.
Is it the left side or the panthers?
No, it's the left side or the pink panthers.
Pink panthers?
Yes.
I have a meeting next month.
Oh, I see.
How is your part-time job?
My part-time job?
You must have a lot of part-time jobs.
I'm busy at the store.
I see.
I remember you had a young part-timer.
What was his name?
Takuma.
He comes to my house sometimes, doesn't he?
Yes, he does.
He comes to my house and talks to me when he comes back from work.
I see.
How old was he?
I think he was 20 years old.
I think he was a student.
20 years old?
Yes.
But he was so young.
You can't talk to him.
No, I can't.
Do you want to eat something?
Have you eaten?
No, I haven't.
You're not hungry, are you?
I have curry.
Do you?
Yes, I made it.
Can I eat it after taking a bath?
No, you can't.
What should I do?
Stand in a straight line and stretch your legs like this.
Like this?
Yes, like that.
Are your legs stretched?
I've never done this before.
You haven't?
I learned this stretch from my mom's ballet class.
Really?
Look at this.
Can you see my legs are stretched?
Put your legs back.
Stretch your legs again.
Doesn't it hurt?
No, it feels good.
Like this.
I see.
I'm tired.
You're young.
You get tired easily.
Do you want me to push you?
Yes, please.
You have a lot of work to do.
I'll push you.
Thank you.
Do you want me to do it first?
Doesn't it hurt?
No, it feels good.
It's soft.
Is it?
It's getting softer.
I can stretch my legs now.
Next, this side.
This side?
Yes, this side.
I can stretch my legs.
It's really soft.
Is it?
Was it soft originally?
Yes, it wasn't that hard.
This side, too.
When I visited you the other day,
you said you didn't have a girlfriend.
Yes, I did.
After that, I talked to my friends,
and it became a big deal.
The same-sex relationship.
I see.
What should I do?
Should I graduate?
Can I have a girlfriend?
Yes, you can.
It's a big deal when you're in your 20s.
Yes, it is.
I heard you had an experience.
When was it?
I'm in my 20s now.
You're asking me that?
Your first experience?
I can't tell you that.
I'm sorry.
I'm just curious.
By the way,
was he your current husband?
I'm not sure.
I heard you're going to marry someone you've never met.
I'm not going to comment on that.
I see.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Where's your wife?
She's on her way home.
Is it because you haven't met her?
No, I haven't.
I haven't.
Are you going to wait for her?
Of course not.
We're going to get married.
But what about me?
He's a part-time worker.
Who? Suzuki?
No, no, no.
He's cute and young.
He's older than me, but I don't talk to him much.
I thought he was 25.
You don't talk to him?
No, we meet on weekdays.
I see.
And...
The person I like...
I like you a lot.
What? Me?
Again?
It's weird to say this to a married person, but...
He's very kind and follows me.
We get along well.
I like you a lot.
This isn't a prank, is it?
No, no, no.
I'm married.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I was surprised because it was so sudden.
Yes.
I'm going to the bathroom.
You're back.
I'm back.
Did you eat dinner?
Yes, I did.
I'll bring you some tea.
Okay.
I'm tired.
Are you tired?
Yes.
I'm tired.
I have to get up early tomorrow.
What time is it tomorrow?
I have to leave the house at 6 o'clock tomorrow.
6 o'clock?
You're early.
I've been busy lately.
You have to go to bed.
Yes.
I'm doing well at work.
I'm glad you're doing well.
Thank you.
Don't overdo it.
What's wrong?
Takuma is there, right?
Takuma?
He's my boss.
He's your boss?
Yes.
He said he liked me today.
What?
He said he liked me.
He said he liked you?
Yes.
He said he wouldn't hurt me.
Is that so?
Yes.
Girls of that age are straight.
Girls of that age are delicate.
So, you should tell him not to hurt you.
That's right.
Yes.
I'll try to do that.
You should.
I was surprised to hear that.
I was surprised, too.
You know I'm married, right?
I know.
I'm married, too.
That's not true.
I see.
Why are you here?
I was surprised.
Are you working?
No, I'm at home.
Oh, he's here again.
I see.
I think he'll be conscious of you when you come home.
I don't know.
I know.
I don't think he'll be conscious of me.
He might be serious.
You should tell him not to hurt you.
I'll try to tell him.
I'm going to take a bath.
The bath is ready.
Is it?
Yes.
I'll take a bath.
It's early in the morning.
Okay.
See you.
What?
You must have been busy.
Yes, I was.
The manager didn't do anything.
I was busy, too.
I didn't do anything.
I'm sorry.
I know.
Don't worry about it.
By the way, Takuma.
About the other day.
Yes?
You said you liked me, didn't you?
I have a husband.
I'm glad you said you liked me.
Takuma, you're young.
You're 20 years old.
You can have a lot of girlfriends.
Yes, you're right.
Don't look so sad.
I'm not worried about it.
I hope we can continue to be partners.
Yes.
Don't look so sad.
Do I have to wash this?
Yes.
Let me help you.
It's okay.
I'm almost done.
Okay.
Do you have enough sweets?
Yes.
Are you okay?
Can I hold your hand?
My hand?
Yes.
What's wrong?
I don't mind.
Can I hold your hand?
Yes.
Your hands are warm.
I'm nervous.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Well...
I know you're married.
I know you can't go out with me.
But I like you very much.
Well...
I want to kiss you.
What?
Kiss?
You can't do that.
My husband will be angry.
Can't I do that?
You're married.
You can't do that.
I'll close my eyes.
I won't do that.
Come on.
Just once.
That's all.
What's wrong?
I want to do it again.
You can't do that.
Don't look so sad.
Just 5 seconds.
5 seconds?
Just today.
You'll be angry if I kiss you.
That's all.
You kissed me for 5 seconds.
I want to kiss you more.
Do you?
That's all.
You can't do that.
Drink some tea.
You need to wash your face.
I'm serious.
That's all.
I'm tired.
You did a good job.
You did a good job at work.
You might get a promotion.
Promotion?
That's great.
It's not decided yet.
I see.
How about you?
What?
What happened to your partner?
Takuma?
He rejected me.
But he understood me.
He rejected me and understood me.
I'm fine.
How did he reject you?
Did he hurt you?
He didn't hurt me.
I see.
That's good.
I want to have a better relationship with him.
I hope you find a new partner.
I hope so.
I want to meet a girl of the same age as you.
You are a student.
I may have been asked by an adult.
Anyway, I'm glad to meet you.
Is the bath ready?
It's ready.
I'm going to take a bath.
See you later.
Takuma, what happened to you?
The tea is gone.
I'm sorry.
You can take a rest over there.
I'll help you.
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sorry.
I don't know because I don't do it often.
It's okay.
You were busy today.
Yes, I was.
I had a cramp.
What?
Did you have a cramp?
My neighbor said she didn't have vegetables she wanted.
I see.
Avocado?
Yes.
She wanted to eat it.
She wanted to eat avocado?
She didn't have it.
I was told that.
I'm in trouble.
You are.
You must be tired.
Well, then.
Takishi.
Yes.
The other day...
I'm sorry.
I got carried away.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
By the way...
Did you think about it?
I don't need to think about it.
I have my husband.
Right?
As I said the other day.
I don't care about it.
I'm glad you say so.
Can't I?
No, you can't.
What should I do?
What?
We have a good relationship.
So...
You don't need to kiss me?
No, I don't.
I kissed you the other day.
You said you kissed me the other day.
You don't look so sad.
Can I?
What?
Kiss.
It's over.
Yes.
Hey.
It's over.
I can't.
Don't touch me.
I wanted to touch you.
Don't do that.
Hey.
Calm down.
Don't do that.
You'll be scolded.
Don't say that again.
Don't do that.
It hurts.
You'll be a coward.
Hey.
It's over.
Open your eyes.
Hey.
I'm going to fold the laundry.
Don't do that.
Hey.
Don't push me.
I love you.
Don't do that.
You kissed me a lot.
It's over.
Don't do that.
I've never seen you like that.
I'm disturbed.
You're big.
Don't do that.
Hey.
You can take a rest over there.
I want to take a rest here.
Don't do that.
I'm disturbed.
It's over.
Don't do that.
I'm disturbed.
Wait a minute.
Don't do that.
It's over.
If you show me your face, it's over.
Don't do that.
You'll cheat on me.
No, I won't.
Don't do that.
Wait a minute.
It's over.
I don't want to do that.
I really don't want to do that.
Don't do that.
You'll cheat on me.
Wait a minute.
I really don't want to do that.
Don't do that.
I'm disturbed.
Wait a minute.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't do that.
Wait a minute.
How do you feel?
Don't do that.
I'm sweating.
Like this?
Wait a minute.
I'm excited.
Don't do that.
It's over.
Wait a minute.
Don't do that.
I'm excited.
Wait a minute.
It's over.
Don't do that.
I'm excited.
It's over.
Don't do that.
I'm excited.
It's over.
How do you feel?
I'll be scolded.
I'll be scolded by my husband.
I'll be scolded if I do that.
Don't do that.
It's over.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm excited.
Calm down.
Don't do that.
It's over.
I'm excited.
Someone is here.
Don't do that.
It's over.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
What are you doing?
I'm stretching.
Stretching?
Are you learning ballet?
Yes.
I see.
Yuina.
I might be promoted in the next promotion.
That's great.
I'm glad.
That's good.
You'll have more jobs.
You'll have more business trips.
That's right.
How are you doing?
I'm busy.
What was his name?
Takuma?
Yes.
How is he?
Is he busy with school and work?
Yes.
I see.
I'm tired.
Is the beer ready?
It's in the fridge.
In the fridge?
I'll bring it.
I'm home.
You shouldn't look at me like that.
Look at me.
You're getting bigger, aren't you?
I can't do this anymore.
Why?
I'm going to be a cheat.
Can I kiss you?
Not here.
I can't do this anymore.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm sorry.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Power, ah, no.
Ah, oh, oh.
This is difficult.
No, no, Pakmu, no.
Oh, ah.
Is this stretched?
I can't believe it.
Kaki-san.
I love you.
I can't believe it.
I want to touch you.
Can I touch you?
What's going on?
It's hot.
I can't.
I can't do this anymore.
I'll be like a ghost.
I'll die.
You don't have to do this.
I can't do this.
I must stop thinking about you.
I can't.
Okay breath.
Does that feeling good?
No, no, no.
Give me your hand.
Are you ok?
Stop, stop, stop.
Let's stop here.
Hey.
No more.
No, no.
Hey.
No more.
Stop.
Taki-san.
Why don't you have any hair?
Well, I prefer not to have any hair.
Wow.
Does it feel good?
Taki-san, how do you feel?
Well, well, well.
Oh.
Here?
Yes.
It's fluffy.
Oh.
How do you feel?
There, there.
I want to eat it.
I can't see it.
Oh.
It's hard.
It's embarrassing.
Oh.
I can't, I can't.
I can't.
I have to go.
Is that so?
No.
I'm going to die.
I can't.
Let's do our best.
I can't, I can't.
It's over.
I can't.
I'm going to die.
Please get up.
I can't.
Your buttocks are beautiful.
Is that so?
I can't.
I'm going to die.
Wait.
I can't.
I'll hold this.
No.
I can't.
I'm going to die.
Eh?
Eh? Wait a minute!
Is this okay?
Yes, yes.
I have a runny nose.
Can I just go ahead?
I'll just go ahead.
Can you see my nose?
Can you see my tongue?
Can you see it?
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Wait a minute.
It feels so good.
Feels good?
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Wait a minute.
You said you'd just go ahead.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah!
Wait a minute.
I'm going in.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, I'm so excited.
Wow.
Ah.
My ears.
Ah!
Ah, wow.
Wait a minute.
You said you'd just go ahead.
Ah.
Ah, I'm going in.
I'm going in.
Ah!
Wow, wow.
Ah, oh.
Also.
Ah.
Oh, ah.
Oh, ah, ah.
Ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah I know.
Wow, wow.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, I can't help but do it.
Ah.
I'm so touched by your poor condition.
I didn't know I had such tension over Being Jewish.
I'm unit after being baptized into the Jewish community the body makes welcome wszyhing the hoo-hoo!
A...
Huh?
He wiped me!
He's breathing heavily.
Oh, my!
It came out.
It came out?
It came out a lot.
Wow.
It's tough.
Do you want me to take it off?
Yes.
Wow.
It came out.
I'm sorry.
You graduated as a virgin.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Wow.
You are still strong.
No.
You are very energetic.
I want to do it a little more.
Do you want to do it a little more?
Yes.
Here.
Do you still have it?
Yes.
I got two.
Wow.
It came out.
Yes.
Do you know how to put it on?
Here?
Yes.
That's right.
I don't know how to put it on.
It's big.
Let's do it again.
Yes.
The lower part.
Yes, the lower part.
That's right.
It's hot.
It's dangerous.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
It's intense.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's dangerous.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's dangerous.
It's intense.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
I can't put it on.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm tired.
Are you tired?
I'll put it on your chest.
Really?
Lie down.
Okay.
I'll do it.
I'll put it on your chest.
Can you see it?
It's all in there.
It's amazing.
I can't do it anymore.
Wow.
I can't do it.
You can't do it?
You can't do it again?
My back hurts.
Can I move?
Yes.
Ah.
It feels good.
It's like I worked out.
A bit more.
Ah, that's it.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it's ticklish.
I can't do it.
Ah, it feels good.
It feels good.
Ah, I can't do it.
Ah, it feels good.
I can't do it.
Oh, my...
I want you to look at my buttocks.
You want me to look at your buttocks?
Yes.
Okay.
This way.
Oh, my buttocks.
Look at my buttocks.
What?
Oh, my buttocks.
Can you look at my buttocks?
Yes.
Oh, my buttocks.
I want you to look at my buttocks.
Can you look at my buttocks?
Yes.
Oh, my buttocks.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah, I can't move.
Ah, it's hot.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah, it's so good.
Ah!
Uh!
Ah, I can't get up.
Ah, I can't, I can't.
Ah, it's so hot.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah!
What is this?
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah!
Ah, it hurts, it hurts.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah!
Ah, it tickles.
Ah, I can't get up.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah!
Ah, it hurts, it hurts.
Ah, it tickles.
Ah!
What is it?
There's air in the blanket.
Ah!
Ah, it hurts, it hurts.
Ah, it tickles.
Ah!
How are my feet?
My feet?
Move your hip..
Ah!
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, it tickles.
Ah!
Ah, it hurts so much.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah!
One, one, one, one, one...
Oh, it's going in...
Oh, no, no...
It's hard...
I'm gonna get out of here.
You're gonna get out of here, right?
It hurts, it hurts...
Can I put it on your butt?
My butt?
I'm gonna put it on your butt.
Help me...
Oh, it hurts.
It hurts.
There, there...
She's crying
I'll just take a look
Thank you
She has a lot of hand cream
It's spilling out in front of me.
Wow.
I'm sorry.
It's too much.
It feels so good.
Did it feel good?
Yes.
You graduated.
I did it twice.
You must have had a hard time.
It was my first time.
Yes, it was.
I want to kiss you.
Kiss?
What are you going to do?
Are you going to take a bath?
Yes.
Let's take a bath together.
Let's take this off.
It's bubbling.
You're good at making bubbles.
Why are you twitching?
I'm going to take a bath.
Let's take a bath.
What's wrong?
I'm going to take a bath.
Your butt is amazing.
I like your butt.
It's amazing.
I'm going to take a bath.
Your butt is amazing.
No, it's not.
It's my hand.
Your hand?
Is that so?
Your butt is amazing.
I can see it in the mirror.
What's wrong with you?
Your butt is amazing.
Your butt is hard.
It's amazing.
Your butt is amazing.
Please raise your hand.
Like this?
It's amazing.
I'm going to take a bath.
Thank you.
I feel like I'm wearing a bra.
I'm wearing a bra.
Your butt is amazing.
It's amazing.
I want you to pinch my butt.
Like this?
It's amazing.
Your butt is amazing.
I want you to pinch my butt.
It's amazing.
I'm going to take a bath.
It's not good to touch.
I'm going to wash you.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
I'm going to the bathroom.
The bathroom is very clean.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Wow, it's amazing.
Wait a minute.
Grandpa, it's getting really hard.
It's all because of you.
Wow.
I want to do it one more time.
Do you want to do it one more time?
Because you are energetic.
What do you want to do?
I want to do it with my mouth.
With your mouth?
You have no choice.
Like this?
It's so tight.
It's hard, isn't it?
If you inhale like that.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's amazing, isn't it?
OK
You put in a lot
You have finished
Shall we go?
Towel?
The towel is over there.
Welcome back.
I'm back.
It was a tough day.
Was it?
How's your part-time job?
My part-time job?
I'm busy.
I'm doing well.
I see.
That's good.
By the way,
my brother in the countryside
sent me a message saying he'd send me some vegetables.
I'm glad to hear that.
He said,
it looks a little damaged,
but it's delicious, so he'll send it to me.
I see.
I should thank him.
You should.
By the way,
my junior, Yamashita,
has become single.
It must be tough for him.
Single?
It must be tough.
I don't know when I'll get married.
Me neither.
How's your ballet?
Ballet?
Have you decided your position?
Yes.
I'm an attacker.
An attacker?
Yes.
It must be tough to be an attacker.
I know.
I'm inexperienced.
I don't know what to do.
I see.
By the way,
how's your part-time boyfriend?
Is he doing well?
Yes, he seems to be doing well.
Is his name Takuma?
Yes.
I see.
Let's comfort him
when he comes to our house.
Because he's lost his memory.
Okay.
It's late.
I'm tired.
Let's take a bath and go to bed early.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Let's not see each other anymore.
Takuma,
I'm married.
I don't feel sorry for my husband.
Do you change your mind?
No.
I don't see him anymore.
Do you quit your part-time job?
Yes.
I quit my part-time job.
What?
I feel sorry for him.
You don't have to see him.
Okay.
Can I give you a hug?
A hug?
Yes.
It's the last time.
I'm sorry.
I'm done.
Wait a minute.
It's the last time.
I stood up.
Did you stand up?
That's great.
I'm sorry.
Why are you crying?
Did you stand up?
I'm sorry.
It's the last time.
That's great.
Why are you crying?
I'm sorry.
I can't stand it anymore.
After this, I'm going to have a seminar at the civic gymnasium.
I'm sorry.
They don't appear to be scared of humans.
They're not as wild if they get weak or intimidating.
The questions climax time!
Zaki-san loves your presence due to his soft body.
I'm sorry.
I can't stand up.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I do.
I can't stand up.
You're eating a lot.
I'll take this off.
I can't stand up.
Do you want me to lick your hands?
I'm sorry.
Please sit down.
It's hard.
Thank you.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
Take care of yourself.
Don't look so sad.
But...
You don't have to quit your part-time job.
I'll do my best.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm going home.
I made a phone call.
She often appears in my videos.
Yes.
She is interesting.
By the way, I'm on a business trip from tomorrow.
So, please take care of me while I'm away.
Okay.
This program is interesting.
I know.
Today is a special day.
Are you on a business trip?
I'm not in the countryside, so I think I can see her.
I'm going to take a bath.
Okay.
Rina.
What?
I heard your position is an attacker.
Is that so?
You have a nose.
I know.
I wonder if I can do it well.
What was your team name?
Hibari Gaoka Pink Panthers.
I see.
I'm going to a match.
Don't worry.
Are you going to a match?
Yes, I'm going to a match.
Didn't you say you had a class or a test?
I'm going to take a break.
No, you can't.
I'll do my best to give you a good report.
Okay.
Good luck.
Thank you.
I'm going to take a bath.
Can I stay here for a while?
You can.
My husband is away on a business trip.
A business trip?
Yes.
I see.
Okay.
You can do a lot of things.
I can.
I'm going to take a bath.
It feels good.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I'm going to take a bath.
It feels good.
Look at me.
That's great.
Do that.
I'm going to take a bath.
That's great.
It feels good.
I'm going to take a bath.
I love you.
Do you love me, too?
Do you love me more than your sister?
I love you.
I'm going to take a bath.
Can I take a bath again?
I wanted to take a bath.
That's great.
I'm scared.
I have to get out of here.
Hello?
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
That's right.
I understand.
Which way is the best place?
That's right.
Is the road wide?
I see.
There is a hot spring town called Tochigi.
That's right.
Take your time.
Do you want a souvenir?
I see.
I like strawberries.
I like this.
I don't like baked goods.
I'm going to hang up the phone.
See you.
I'm fine.
I have a sore throat.
I can't take a bath.
I love you.
Your clothes will get dirty.
That's not true.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'll hang up the phone.
I can't take a bath.
I have a sore throat.
I'm going to hang up the phone.
Are you going to hang up the phone?
That's amazing.
I'm going to hang up the phone.
Do you smell something?
Can I break this?
Do you want to break this?
Can I?
I can't help it.
I'm going to hang up the phone.
Hello?
What's wrong?
I'll be careful.
That's natural.
That's only in the living room.
I won't put it in the living room.
Don't worry.
Be careful on your way home.
Be careful of cockroaches.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Go to the bathroom.
Is the food delicious?
There's gyoza in the kitchen.
I'm going to the bathroom.
That's good.
That's right.
I'm not in a bad condition.
Thank you.
I'm in a bad condition.
I want to go slowly.
I'm going to hang up the phone.
Oh, you're here.
Yes, thank you.
See you.
Hey.
You can't do that.
You'll make a noise.
Hey.
I was on the phone.
What if my husband finds out?
Don't make a noise.
I don't feel good.
I can't stand it anymore.
It hurts.
I don't feel good.
Ah.
I can't stand it anymore.
It hurts.
Ah.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's okay.
Ah.
It hurts.
Achoo!
Did it go in your nose?
Did it go in?
Yes!
Oh no, oh no!
You need a bit more.
Hey hey!
Grunt grunt!
Oh that feels so nice
Mmm
So good
Wanna kiss?
Hmm?
Oh my back
Ah ah
Mmm
Good
I'm done.
I feel fascinated by you.
That's all.
The explosion has got me stressed out.
What's going on?
I'm dismissed right now.
You said that?
You're going to give me a think?
I'm gonna do that.
Ouch.
It's fading.
It's obvious.
Tissue.
Shall I take it off?
Okay.
Good.
Thank you.
Ouch!
I don't think I can come today.
You can.
You just have to stay still, and it'll be fine.
Really?
Yes.
I'm going to put it in.
Okay.
Oh, no.
It's in.
Do you want more?
I want more.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's refreshing.
Oh, no.
It's amazing up to here.
It's so painful.
Calm down.
It's the best.
Oh, no.
It's amazing.
It's amazing up to here.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
It's amazing up to here.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
I'm tickled.
I want more.
I love you.
It hurts.
Oh, no.
It's amazing up to here.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
It hurts.
It's painful.
Will you be able to deliver the package by the day after tomorrow?
Yeah.
Will you be able to deliver it by 6 p.m.?
By the day after tomorrow?
Yeah.
That's good. How much should I prepare?
About 5,000 yen?
Oh, I see.
You've already planned it.
I see.
It's a broken one, isn't it?
Okay.
I'll try not to break it.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, but I can't open it.
Oh, the veranda?
Yeah.
Oh, I got it.
Yeah, it's okay.
I'm sorry, but I can't open it.
Yeah, I'll leave it in the storage room.
Yeah, leave it to me.
It's okay.
I'll hang up now.
Yeah, see you later.
Bye.
Oh, I got it.
Oh, I said I can't do it.
I can't do it.
I said I can't do it.
Oh, I can't do it.
I can't do it.
It's intense.
Hang in there.
Oh, it's uncomfortable.
Oh, no.
Oh, I love it.
I love it.
It feels good.
It's all the way in here.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, I love it.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
I love it.
Oh, I love it.
It feels good.
Oh, it feels good.
I love it.
Oh, I love it.
More.
I love it.
Oh, I can't do it.
I can't do it.
Oh, no.
Lie down.
Oh, I love it.
Oh, it feels good.
It's intense.
It feels good.
Lie down.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Oh, it feels good.
I love it.
Oh, it hurts.
It hurts.
Uh!
OK OK
Ah ah!
気持ちいい!
アイスケア!
アイスケアだよ!
ネイベー!
アイスケア!
もっと頂戴!
もっと もっと!
アイスケア ほんなんかい!
ちゃーなー!
アイスケア イイケイケ!
!
OH!
OHH
Ah! Ah!
I'm sorry!
I feel so good!
Ah!
It's so warm!
Ah! I feel so good!
Ah! Ah!
I feel so good!
Ah!
Let's go, let's go.
I'm so tired.
What?
Are you tired?
Yes.
You're going to fall down.
I'm fine.
Look at me.
I'm going to fall down.
I can't do it.
Wait.
I'm going to fall down.
Get up.
I can't do it.
I'm going to fall down.
Oh, my God.
It hurts.
It's not over yet.
I can't do it.
Take your time.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good.
You're amazing.
I love you.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
It hurts.
I love you.
I like you.
I'll go consulting with a doctor at the hospital.
My back is so sore that it hurts like crazy!!
I want to get treatment here.
It feels so good!
You can do whatever you want.
It's amazing!
It feels so good!
Let's do it again!
Let's do it!
It's so good!
It feels so good!
I can't do it!!
I can't do it!
I can't!
It's so good!
No, no, no!
Go, go, go!
Kedo-chan...
No...
Kedo-chan!
I love you!
I love you, too!
I love you so much!
Kedo-chan!
I feel so good!
Kedo-chan, I love you!
I love you so much!
I love you!
No, no, no!
No, no!
I love you!
I love you so much!
I can do it, too.
I can do it.
Let me hold your hand.
I can't.
I can't do it.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I'll do it now.
I can't.
I can't do it.
ugh.
Oh my god.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
I love you.
I'm getting sleepy.
I love you, too.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm sweating, too.
It was fun.
I love you.