INSIDE
There is someone working.
Could I use this carpet, please?
Excuse me.
Why are you getting such ecstasy?
Hey, can we have a cup of tea?
Yes.
I think that's better.
Yes, it is.
Let's try it.
I'm tired.
Let's start from the beginning.
Yes.
I'm sorry, but it's not that big.
It's small.
Yes.
I'm tired.
I'm sleepy.
I'm a little tired.
By the way, you have a shift this week, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I see.
The manager said that he would do it next week.
I have a shift at such a time.
I'm sleepy.
Hey, Misako.
Yes?
I heard that you are on a diet.
This is good for me.
This is good for you, isn't it?
Yes.
When I'm tired, it's good for me.
It's important.
Yes.
Don't get stressed.
I agree.
How do you feel now? Are you used to it?
I'm used to it.
Everyone is a good person.
I think you are quite old.
You don't have a wife, do you?
No, I don't.
I'm sorry.
You have strong muscles.
Do you work out?
I've been playing soccer.
That's why I have strong muscles.
Is that so?
I didn't know that you have strong muscles in soccer.
I do weight training.
I see.
That's great.
Are you a college student?
Yes, I am.
Do you have a job?
I want to work for a foreign company.
I see.
My boss is a public official, so he doesn't allow me to work for a foreign company.
It's hard.
It's hard to find a job, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It's hard to find a job.
It's great that you have a part-time job.
You are studying.
Yes, I am.
How is your family?
My family?
What do you mean?
What does your husband do?
He works in an IT company.
I see.
He comes home late.
He seems to be busy.
So, I spend my free time with my husband.
I earn my own money.
I heard that you went to a fitness club.
Did you?
Yes, I did.
Recently, I started going to a fitness club.
I've been doing stretching and studying.
I've been studying blood flow and bone structure.
I see.
Do you enjoy going to a college?
Yes, I do.
Do you?
You are a college student.
Don't you have a crush on anyone?
I don't hear that from you.
I don't have a crush on anyone.
Do you have a crush on a girl in your class?
No.
Don't you have a crush on someone?
Do you have a girlfriend?
No, I don't.
You don't?
I thought you had a crush on someone.
Do you have a crush on someone?
No, I don't.
Wow, that's great.
You are young.
Do you talk to her?
Sometimes.
I see.
That's great.
Don't you ask her out?
Ask her out?
I can't do that yet.
Recently?
Yes.
I see.
I'm sorry for asking you out.
I don't talk to you about that.
Is it good?
You eat a lot.
Were you hungry?
Yes.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
The bath is ready.
Thank you.
I have a meeting tomorrow morning.
I see.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll give you a massage later.
That's good.
Thank you.
It's a massage for fatigue from fitness club.
That sounds fun.
I want to go to a fitness club.
I think it's good.
I can't recommend it to you.
But, there are only women there.
I think there are more women there.
But, there are a few men there.
They are your fans, right?
I don't think so.
How is your part-time job?
I'm busy at the store.
I'm on a shift.
Who is he?
I think he is YOHEI.
Does he come to your house?
He comes to my house to eat and talk.
How old is he?
I think he is 20 years old.
He is a student.
20 years old?
If he is that young, he won't talk to you.
I don't think so.
It was a good sound.
Stretching feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
I think it's better to stretch your legs like this.
How is it?
It's soft, isn't it?
Yes.
I often play soccer.
I see.
It's softer than mine, isn't it?
Is that so?
It doesn't stick to my legs.
It's amazing.
Try it.
Let's do it together.
It's quite soft.
Stretching feels good, doesn't it?
It's effective.
It's good.
Fitness club members often do this kind of stretching.
Do they?
Yes.
It's good.
You've already stopped.
Yes.
I'll stop.
Thank you.
Stretching feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
Do you want to take a break?
I'm a little tired.
Yes.
By the way, I heard that you have a crush on someone.
How are you doing these days?
Well...
I've never had a girlfriend.
Is that so?
Yes.
I don't know how to approach a girl.
I see.
Does that mean you've never had a girlfriend?
Does that mean...
I'm a virgin.
I see.
I thought you weren't popular.
I'm embarrassed.
Not at all.
I'm sorry for asking you a strange question.
Do you have a crush on someone?
Yes.
Do you have a crush on the same person?
I see.
Do you mean the person I know?
Yes.
Do you know him?
I'm Miyasako Okawa.
Are you playing a prank on me?
No, I'm not.
Did someone tell you that?
I'm serious.
I like Miyasako Okawa.
I see.
I'm sorry for asking you a strange question.
Not at all.
Do you have a crush on someone?
No, I don't.
I see.
Do you really like Miyasako Okawa?
I don't think so.
I see.
I'm sorry for asking you a strange question.
I'm embarrassed.
I was surprised.
I see.
I didn't expect you to do such a thing.
I'm hot.
I'll stretch you.
Okay.
I'll stretch you like this.
Let's do it together.
Okay.
I'll hold your inner thigh.
I'll stretch you.
Okay.
Hey.
Can I ask you a strange question?
What is it?
Go ahead.
In your life, how many times have you been confessed to?
Confessed to?
Yes.
Do you mean I like you or I have a crush on you?
Something like that.
I've heard strange things.
I see.
I don't remember because it was a long time ago.
Do you remember when I proposed to you?
What are you talking about?
It was the anniversary of our marriage.
Yes, it was on the 16th.
You should have come back earlier.
Without overtime.
I see.
What were we talking about?
How many times have you been confessed to?
I don't remember.
Did someone confess to you?
No way.
I see.
I'll give you a bath.
Okay.
Don't forget to wash your face.
I see.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I heard about your shift.
I see.
I'll go to the washroom.
Wait there.
Okay.
I'll be back soon.
I'm so tired because you confessed to me.
I see.
About the other day...
Okay.
I'm sorry.
What?
I'm glad that you confessed to me.
You're still young.
I think you can be a better man.
I'm sorry.
Don't look so sad.
I'm angry.
I'm sorry.
Can you give me a hand?
Give me a hand.
I've always wanted to do this.
Can you stretch your arm?
I want to kiss you just once.
Kiss?
I can't do that.
Please.
Just once.
Don't look so sad.
Just a little.
Just for 5 seconds.
But my husband is here.
He'll get mad at me.
I know.
Just a little.
Please.
Just for 5 seconds.
But...
Please.
Just a little.
Just for 5 seconds.
Just a little more.
I said just a little.
Please.
Just for 5 seconds.
I'm sorry.
Why?
I still have a lot of laundry to do.
I'm sorry.
I'm serious.
Please think about it.
Ah, that feels good
A few days later
Ah, it feels good.
Really?
Yeah, it's great.
By the way, did you have those sweatpants?
These?
Yeah.
I bought them last year, but I never wore them.
Are they stretchy?
Oh, yeah.
I think so, too.
But it's easy to wear.
I think it's good for a day-off.
But you're wearing underwear, aren't you?
What?
Really?
Yeah.
What are you talking about?
You're wearing underwear.
No, I'm not.
Really?
By the way, what did your boyfriend say?
Your boyfriend?
Yeah, I think so.
How's he doing?
I haven't seen him lately.
I don't know because I haven't seen his face.
I see.
I don't have a shifter on me.
Anyway, I'm going to take a bath.
Oh, yeah.
I'm the only one who didn't take a bath, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm going to take a bath.
I'm tired today.
I'm tired, too.
There are a lot of people coming recently.
I think so, too.
Yeah.
You're good at patting.
Really?
It's the first time I've been told that.
You're good at patting.
Yeah.
But I'm not good at it.
I'm not good at it.
Hey, Kamiya-san.
What?
I can't forget what happened the other day.
What happened the other day?
Hey.
I'm fine.
No.
Hey.
I'm patting you now.
I'm fine.
No.
Hey.
I said no.
I can't forget what happened the other day.
No.
Hey.
I'm fine.
I have to fold it.
You can do it later.
No.
I said no.
I'm patting you now.
No.
I said no.
Hey.
I can't forget what happened the other day.
I can't forget.
I'm patting you.
No.
I said no.
I can't forget.
I'm patting you.
Don't do that.
Hey, don't do that.
Why do you want me to sleep?
I'm sleepy.
Stop it.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm sleepy.
Hey, wake up.
I can see you.
No.
Don't smell me.
Hey.
Hey, wake up.
Don't do that.
I'm embarrassed.
I can't do that.
I really like you.
But I forgive you.
I forgive you.
I know.
But I beg you.
I really like you.
Stop it.
No.
Can't I?
I beg you.
Wait.
I'm not Wakami.
Stop it.
I'm glad you said that.
But I forgive you.
Can't I?
No.
I really like you.
I'm glad you said that.
Please be my first love.
I beg you.
Stop it.
Don't say that.
I beg you.
Look at me.
Don't say that.
I beg you.
But...
Just look at me.
Just look at me?
I beg you.
Just look at me.
What should I do?
Well...
How about breast?
Can I take it off?
I've never taken it off.
I'll take it off.
It's beautiful.
Pants.
I beg you.
It's difficult.
I'm ashamed to be eaten.
How about clitoris?
Where is it?
I've seen it a lot.
I just have to look at it.
No...
Here?
Just look at me.
No...
Wait...
This is a pain relief patch.
No...
Wait...
Just look at me.
Wait a minute.
No...
Wait...
Just look at me.
Youhei-kun...
No...
Wait...
Don't touch me.
Don't lick me.
Wait...
No...
Youhei-kun...
Wait...
No...
I'll give you a massage.
I won't do that.
No...
Wait...
What are you doing?
I'm in your arms.
No...
Here?
Someone is here.
I have to get out.
I'm worried.
I'm sorry.
By the way...
Yes?
I'm going on a business trip.
Yes.
You're amazing.
I'll have more work.
Yes.
I'll have more business trips.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Yes.
I'll have more work.
I'll get a house loan.
Yes.
I'll move to a bigger house.
I'll do my best to increase my part-time job.
Your part-time job?
Yes.
You should say hello to the manager.
I don't have to do that.
You don't have to do that.
I see.
Is your part-time job a business trip?
Yes.
How is it?
I don't know because I haven't had a chance to go on a business trip.
I haven't had a chance to go on a business trip.
I see.
I'll take a bath.
Yes.
Hey.
Don't do that.
Please.
You can't do that.
I told you not to do that.
Please be my first person.
I'm sorry.
I'll teach you.
I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
I touched you a lot, didn't I?
More.
I want you to tell me how you feel.
How I feel?
Can I touch you?
But you don't have to touch me.
I want you to tell me everything.
I can't.
Mom.
Hey.
How do you feel?
I'm not strong enough to touch you.
It hurts.
I'll be gentle.
I'm dead.
It's heavy, isn't it?
Hey.
Don't do that.
I told you not to do that.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
I want to touch you.
I'm touching you.
I'm sorry.
I'm...
I'm embarrassed.
I didn't mean to do that.
I'm sorry.
It's the best.
I can't help it.
I'm surprised when you lick me suddenly.
I see.
I'm surprised.
I can't help it.
What should I do?
Take your time.
I'm sorry.
It's warm.
I'm surprised when you move your fingers.
Otherwise, it hurts.
I saw your buttocks.
My buttocks?
It's very beautiful.
It's smooth.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
Take your time.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Take your time.
I want you to lick me.
Do I have to lick you?
Yes.
But...
Please.
Just a little.
I'm sorry.
I'm just licking you.
I'll touch you.
It's amazing.
I put my buttocks in your buttocks.
What?
I don't want to.
You said you'd just lick me.
I put my buttocks in your buttocks.
But...
No.
I can't do that.
Please.
No.
Just a little.
Just a little?
Please.
No.
I can't do that.
Just a little.
Please.
Okay.
Just a little.
Wait a minute.
I don't have a condom.
You don't have a condom?
I can't put it in if I leave it as it is.
I see.
Okay.
You put a condom in your wallet?
Yes.
I didn't know that.
I see.
Can I put a condom on you?
It's the same on the other side.
This side?
Yes.
I'll turn this around.
Okay.
Does it hurt?
It's okay.
Try it yourself.
Okay.
It's okay if it stretches.
Like this?
Yes.
Okay.
Just a little.
Can you feel my shoulder?
I think I put my finger in it.
I see.
Just a little.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Wow.
It stretches.
Wait a minute.
I told you that I put my finger in it.
Wow.
It's strange.
Wait a minute.
Wow.
It stretches.
It stretches a lot.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
Wow.
It stretches a lot.
It's hot.
You are energetic.
I'll do it again.
Do it again.
Next, I'll do it from behind.
From behind?
Can you feel my shoulder?
Wow.
Take your time.
It's very beautiful.
Do you like my butt?
You like my butt, don't you?
Over there.
Wow.
It's hot.
It stretches.
Wow.
What's this?
It feels good.
It's dangerous.
It's hot.
I'm tired.
Can you get on my back?
It's hot.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It's dangerous.
It's hot.
mommy
oh my, so cold
ah, so 선
ah ahh
ah, so
o ka o ka
oh my goo-
so cold
ah ahh
ah, it's cold
ahh
ah, it really hurts
hey, hey, don't overreact
I love you.
I'm glad.
You've loved me for a long time.
I love you.
I feel sick.
I'm sick.
It hurts.
The other day, the manager told me that I was on good terms with you.
He said we were on good terms.
I feel sick.
Wonder what this is...
What is it?
⚆⚆⚆⚆⚆⚆⚆ ......... It so pretty, it's yummy!
『Meng! Not sure if I mentioned it earlier..wait and see. . .
So cute!
Hmm!
Yummm!
Wahahahahaha....
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
My heart was pulling so much.
Was it that good?
Congratulations on your graduation.
Thank you.
It felt good, right?
Yes.
I told you it was just the tip of my tongue.
This is your bag.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'll wash your hair.
Okay.
It's really dry, isn't it?
Yes.
It was less than I expected.
It tickles.
Does it tickle?
It's like a dream.
Is it like a dream?
Yes.
I felt good, too.
Did you feel good?
Yes.
I felt good, too.
Really?
Yes.
I'll give you something.
Really?
Yes.
Yohei-kun.
Yes?
Did you feel good when I gave you a bath for the first time?
Yes.
Really?
I love you.
I'm glad.
You're the best.
Are you washing your hair?
Yes.
Really?
I'll wash your back.
Okay.
I'll wash your legs, too.
It's clean.
I was surprised that there was a condom in my wallet.
I got it for free.
I see.
Do you wash my hair so carefully?
Yes.
You just want to touch my butt, don't you?
I can't touch your butt.
You really love my butt.
Yes.
I want to touch your butt.
I'm wondering if you're washing your hair.
I'm washing my hair.
But...
I just gave you a bath.
I'm sorry.
I've been touching your butt all the time.
I've been watching you naked.
I'm ticklish.
I rubbed it on your butt.
My butt?
You really love my butt.
I'm ticklish.
I thought it would be hot.
Like this?
Yes.
I'm ticklish.
Did you just wash my butt?
Yes.
I think my hair is clean now.
I'm ticklish.
I'm going to take a shower.
I'm going to sleep.
What?
I'm ticklish.
I'm done with the shower.
I'll do it here.
Here?
You did it earlier.
I'll do it one more time.
No, you can't.
No?
You did it earlier.
I'll do it with my mouth.
With your mouth?
I can't help it.
You're amazing.
I'm ticklish.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
Yeah.
Phew...
...
Let me help you rub your cheeks.
Here we go.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Can you feel my chest?
Yes, I can feel it.
But, Youhei-kun, it's a secret to everyone in the supermarket.
Of course.
Can you promise me?
Yes.
It hurts, doesn't it?
You have a lot of pus.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
It's hot.
I'm sweating.
Thank you.
That's all.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
Then, let's go.
By the way.
Yes.
My brother said he would send me vegetables.
Oh, did he?
Yes.
By the way.
It's time to harvest vegetables deliciously.
Oh, is that so?
Yes.
Let's cook together when my brother comes back.
He said that, didn't he?
Yes.
You don't look well.
Do you have a problem?
Do I have a problem?
Yes.
I'm fine.
Are you fine?
I'm fine as usual.
Is that so?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Oh, Hei-kun.
Will you stop seeing me?
What?
I'm married.
I'm sorry for my husband.
So, I won't see you anymore.
No way.
Please understand me.
I like you.
I'm glad to hear that.
I like you very much.
Thank you.
But, I don't think it's good.
Then, let me hug you for the last time.
Okay.
I'm so happy.
I love you.
I've loved you for a long time.
Let's be together for a long time.
Yes.
I'll do my best to be with you.
I love you.
Hey, Yohei-kun, it's not like we won't see each other again.
We'll see each other at the party, right? If we wear the same shirt.
You know, you're going to college.
There are a lot of young and beautiful girls in your class, right?
I want you to find a girlfriend like that.
No, I don't want to.
I don't want to find a girlfriend who doesn't know me.
Look, I'm standing up again.
But I just told you, let's break up.
Hey, please say it at the end.
Then I'll really forget about you.
Okay.
Then this is really the last time.
I don't want to break up with you.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for everything.
It's not like I'm in pain.
Really?
Really.
What have you been up to lately?
It was fun to be in this kind of relationship.
So, let's get along even after work.
It's been a long time since I've been in a relationship, so I'm a little nervous.
Hey, Wakabayashi-san.
What?
I don't have anyone to forget.
Hey.
I'm going to the fitness club today, so I'm a little tired.
I'm sweating, so I can't get dressed.
It's dangerous.
Hey, don't touch me at that time.
It's amazing.
I'm hungry.
I can't do it.
I can't do it here.
I'll do it with my mouth.
Wait a minute.
I can't do it.
Hurry up.
Are you going to get along with your job?
Somehow.
Let me know if you get along.
Don't forget me.
Don't forget me even if you get along with your job and quit your job.
I can't forget you.
I'm glad.
I can't do it.
You've done a lot.
This is the last one.
I can't do it.
Excuse me.
See you later.
I can't do it.
I'm going on a business trip tomorrow.
I'm counting on you.
Be careful.
I'm going to take a bath.
resetting
It's been a while since we were together.
Yes
Stretchy
Very stretchy
I'm going to take a break.
I'm sweating a little.
Is that so?
Let's take a break.
I can see you from a little while ago.
Can you see me?
Don't you feel sick today?
No, I don't.
I don't feel good.
Why?
It's so hot.
My body is warm.
It's hot.
Do you want to sleep?
Yes.
Can I stay here tonight?
I'm going to take a break.
Don't you want to go home?
Yes.
Can I go out?
Hello.
Did you finish your work?
Yes.
Now?
I was sleeping.
It's nothing.
Do you want a souvenir?
Where are you going?
Hokkaido?
I see.
Anything is fine.
You can buy me a snack.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I'll buy you a snack.
I have a friend.
I'll call you back.
See you later.
Hey.
I was talking to you.
But you noticed me.
Why?
You asked me what I was doing.
You're not coming back, are you?
No.
I'm nervous.
I'm sweating.
Calm down.
What?
I'm sorry.
I touched a strange place.
Wait a minute.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
It's dirty.
It's dirty, isn't it?
I'll wipe it off.
No.
It's dirty.
Do you really want to go to Kyoto?
Yes.
You can go to Kyoto until morning.
It's cold.
You're sweating.
I'm sweating.
I'll wipe it off.
It's embarrassing.
It's not that soft.
It's a little different.
It's embarrassing.
It's dirty.
It's dirty, isn't it?
It's cold.
Don't do that.
It's embarrassing.
Hello.
I was watching TV.
Yes.
What?
It doesn't matter what it is.
Yes.
I got it.
There is a famous snack in Hokkaido.
It's a white lover.
Yes.
You've never been to Hokkaido, have you?
It doesn't matter what it is.
It doesn't matter what you want to buy.
It doesn't matter what you want to eat at home.
Yes.
It doesn't matter.
See you.
Yes.
Why?
I'll be found out.
Don't do that.
Are you nervous?
I'm suddenly getting excited.
I'm getting excited.
Why?
You like to be licked, don't you?
I want to spoil you more.
Why?
I want to touch you.
You're getting bigger.
You're the best.
I want you to lick me.
You were a good boy.
You've become a good boy.
I'm done.
I'm going to be a good boy.
I'm tired.
Do you want to go to bed?
I'm fine.
Wait a minute.
Today,
I don't need a rubber band.
Are you sure?
I'm fine today.
I'm tired.
I feel good.
Give me a kiss.
Do you like me?
I like you, too.
I feel good.
I'm tired.
The phone is ringing again.
I'll be quiet this time.
Hello?
What?
How many times are you going to call me today?
Okay.
Are you going to take a break when you get home?
Do you want to go shopping?
Okay.
Do you have something you want to buy?
Do you want to make it at work?
Okay.
I'll leave the door open.
I'll talk to you when I get home.
Okay.
Good luck at work.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
I'm sweating.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
Why do I feel so good?
I'm sorry.
I'm sweating.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
I like you so much...
I love you.
You are so sleepy.
I can hear your voice.
I love you.
It's the first time for me to do it on my own, isn't it?
I always think that it's the first time for me to do it on my own.
I wonder how long I can do it until morning.
I'm not sure if I can do it on my own.
Can I do it?
Yes.
Let's do it a lot.
Thank you for watching.