I said goodbye to dinner.
I will hinder.
Thank you, sit here.
Oh yeah
I will go in now, wait a little.
Thanks to.
A nice house here.
No to?
Something wide.
Yes to.
Can you rent here?
Like a home, your husband.
Meaning you bought it?
Yes Yes Yes
Thanks to.
I will eat.
It is hot today.
It is hot, today.
I want to sir.
The freezer now.
Yes is what.
The freezer turned.
It is hot.
Really, the record was good.
Maybe it would be better to record.
Suddenly I read four books.
Something is there.
Yes is what.
Yes is.
Impossible is impossible.
Wait and sweat.
Summer is hard.
A bit tough.
But it can sell a lot, you know.
Yes yes yes
It is delicious.
A realized feeling.
Yes is it.
Yes yes
Do you do shift there?
It is so.
Yes
Not much recently I got in.
Not a bit.
Do you want to get a lot in?
If you can.
Recently that
Is it Mr. Sato?
He was in, a new man.
The new person?
That boy is already in a lot.
Training along with.
I am glad to go in a little.
Is there no bad day?
A bad day.
The Circle.
Kareena is.
No to Kork?
Caroline has already put it all in place, but not everything.
I am happy to have the afternoon included.
At what time?
Can you do it after 16?
16 to 9 o’clock.
It will finally help.
Then a little.
Photographer is free on Saturday.
Yes yes
But what about Sunday.
Yes, I can do it on Saturday.
Maybe Sunday we’ll have some gathering.
Then on Saturday.
Today is Tuesday, no.
Monday, Wednesday, Saturday and the moon.
Oh, and I think maybe it will be okay.
I am pleased.
It hurts.
No, really really.
Yes, I have to wait.
It is two years, so time is bad.
Yes is it.
In the meantime, I will give you hope.
Yes please please.
It is OK.
Was Mr. Shamir a record?
Yes to record.
It is record.
No, it doesn’t change a little.
When the record is busy, I am busy.
You are also cooking that, right?
Usually a husband.
But
Freeride, it would be fine.
It is a little hot.
Not because of the heat, but because of the technology.
I would rather have a record.
A little freezer.
Oh well, what a senior.
I am afraid to go hard.
A little, I never did.
But Freezer is fun.
Why Why?
Sometimes I get annoyed.
I like to eat.
If you try.
It feels safe.
There are also good working kids.
Yes is what.
to Lusan.
It looks fun.
With Lusan?
They are doing a naget.
I know I dress up or I get dressed.
I like to Lusan.
Are you also doing it in?
kindly
I say you like it there.
I like it, but it feels like it.
What are you letting me do?
Yes is.
Okay, it looks fun.
This is wide enough.
There are children too.
What do you do, Mr?
He is a normal sarabini.
I work in a printing company.
by Printing
I’m looking at it, but I think Tate is a job.
If this is going well, I think it should be a little better.
It is probably.
Okay well.
I don’t know printing or image.
You still don’t know.
Does Todd have a child?
Oh, and kindergarten.
How old are you?
About 5 years old, now.
Old or old?
Yes is.
Go to
Will you go pick me up?
I have to go to you, always around 3 o’clock.
I’ll pick you up, so much.
Do you always go there afterwards?
Yes, it’s part, so you won’t get in for long.
So the day ends.
Yes Yes Yes
You have to go in the morning or during the day.
We have to go in the day to finish.
Not very wearing.
There was a lot of stuff this week.
Yes is it.
From the evening.
It is very different in.
honestly
You don’t seem to be a child, right?
In a good sense.
Because it is clean.
thanks to
I think you are married, right?
Seeing first.
When you talk, I know.
Or an adult.
Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes
thanks to
It feels like.
Yes to.
Oh, you have a hobby?
Do you like travel?
Where to travel? – Where to travel?
Yesterday in family.
I went to Fukuoka.
Oh is?
Staying at?
Eating in a chair.
This time it is delicious.
Fukuoka
Do you want to go to Fukuoka?
Did you go next?
Not on the side.
Even if the basement.
and Nagano.
The gym.
The Circle Hostel.
Looks like fun.
Fukuoka is good.
It is aircraft.
If you get on the plane.
Soon to be.
If you want to go, tell me a little bit about the Oscars.
Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes
Tell me when you go.
Full of delicious food.
well 😂
I envy it.
You are in a circle.
Yes is
What is Circle?
Do you understand?
What is?
I call it a foot circle.
I understand
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I want to wear a small coat.
The monkey does.
Okay, it is cool.
I played football from now on.
There was no football at school.
I want to do.
I went outside and tried to play football.
Did you make it yourself?
Gather some friends.
Just the boys?
It is unexpected.
About 7 or 3.
Looks like a man.
The first class is full of girls.
If you hit a girl, you will.
Probably do it.
Drinking more
Like a manager.
I like it, I think you like it.
Actually not do.
He comes, but he talks.
I want girls to start.
I want to try football here.
It looks like you are watching.
Looks like fun.
But is she not there?
What a good boy?
Not there is.
You are not there, you are a college student.
still study.
Job
It is circus.
Maybe there is a circle.
The only possibility.
What is there? yes.
The city I.
Why Defender?
cannot offer.
It becomes a type of rifle.
Yes is.
by Batch
He is walking.
Arrived
Go home to.
I read the email.
Yes
by Ramene
by Mr.
Soup and sauce.
I really like Ramsey.
So, the soup was cut.
But when you decide on your age, it’s hard.
Yes is.
Has Ive been asleep?
Yes, I have slept.
He did a good exercise in the hot water club.
The student was praised.
Is it so?
I was pleased.
How about the part?
I want to increase the shift.
It seems like you’ve been busy lately.
Maybe you are in a little bit more.
He was a young man, a young man.
Yes to yes.
What did you say?
I want to, sir.
How many years?
I was 20 years old, I said, a student.
20 years old.
It is young.
You are young, right?
You will probably eat oil.
Again about Ramsey?
So I think I should take a bath.
Yes, you can go to the bath.
You were busy today.
It was quite crowded.
This is sold for lunch.
Oh yeah yeah.
I was so busy.
I could not buy.
Oh, it is hard.
Use that phone?
Yes, something
Knowing in the meantime?
Okay, so to be.
I don’t know, I have a setup.
The set?
Yes is
I don’t know anything about this.
Is it camera?
Yes is
something is.
But here is.
Because it is off.
So I can’t stop.
It becomes a night mall.
Your face is bad.
He healed.
Healed it?
How about?
Maybe healed.
Let us move.
With me?
Clean up together.
He healed.
beautiful here
Stop it, stop it.
thanks to
You don’t know me at all about this.
Please go
Thanks, it is good.
It is fucking.
No, but sometimes
And sometimes?
Something last time.
I told her like she was there.
Yes yes
You could?
No, I have not done it.
Not able to do it.
I have someone I like.
Oh yeah yeah?
The child of work?
The school child?
Work and close.
The Mytan people?
Who? is someone I know?
Is someone you know?
Someone you know?
Oh Oh Oh
Who is it?
You are a young boy of Miyamoto, right?
The University student.
The Daisy child.
No is
Is it different?
the same year.
is older.
The old?
Yes is.
Was he an older child?
Maybe I don’t know.
that
I am talking about Mr. Tammy.
and me?
A joke?
I don’t like Mr. Sham.
Do you really say?
Yes is
Isn’t that something?
Are you not being blamed for?
I really like it, I really like Mr. Sham.
Oh, and me too
I mean, you like it, you like it.
Oh yeah
It’s a hassle, you’re married too.
Yes, I am, and my kids too.
There is
Well, I think there is such a thing.
I really like it.
Too much work.
Look at it or something.
I like it.
I am glad though.
I have my husband’s children too.
A little
I want to sir.
You want a younger boy, right?
There are many cute kids in front of you.
The young boy.
Is it difficult?
Oh yeah
I understand then.
Please answer again.
Go home today.
A little too.
I have to go or pick you up.
I understand.
Please please.
Can I get my last photo?
Yes
Send it.
Just made it.
I came, thank you.
Then go home.
Thanks, be careful
again is
by Tia
Welcome to
Tired of
Oh well you.
today is
Part of ahead.
You are an arabian.
to that boy.
I was confessed.
How can I refuse to do something if I do not hurt?
by
My mom’s mother doesn’t do much.
What is it, you laugh?
No, it is young.
Meaning straight.
I think you should be kind to refuse to hurt him.
You are still young, so you will have a wonderful meeting.
Yes, yes is it.
Yes
I will try.
Okay, I’ll come in from here.
What happened to you?
I said something before, sorry.
Don’t worry, I didn’t say it either.
You are young and you can be a beautiful girl now.
So is it.
I will strive.
Mr. Takeda
something
If you can connect your hands.
Can not do?
The hand?
Yes is
Oh well
If it were hands.
OK to OK?
Yes
Can you ask me another?
Only once.
Or a kiss.
Can not?
Oh is?
The kiss?
It is a little.
I am married.
It is mother.
Maybe a little trouble.
No, I am not sorry.
I said something strange again.
Do not be so depressed.
No, I am not depressed.
It feels like this, just a little.
Do you want to kiss so much?
I want to. I want.
If only for a little,
Really five seconds.
Can I take 2 seconds?
2 seconds
lightly
Okay is it?
Just a little.
Yes Yes Yes
Just a little more.
You should have put it down a little.
A little more.
I have to do something for my child.
I understand.
I like the valley.
I really like it, really.
I like it.
Just now.
Welcome to
Full of
Have you eaten Ramona again?
Jill in front of the station.
by Nirvana  by Nirvana  by Nirvana  by Nirvana  by Nirvana  by Nirvana  by Nirvana  by Nirvana  by Nirvana
I really like you.
Oh yeah, so to say.
What happened to your case, Biden?
Oh you Takahashi?
If you say something properly.
Looks like you understood.
by
who was
Let me open it.
Wait, wait for my grandmother.
When was the last time we kissed?
A kiss, and suddenly.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry
Do you want to kiss?
Yes to?
Do you do it sometimes?
Wait a little.
What what?
It smells like nuts.
It is not okay.
It was a nickel machine.
Come and take a bath.
Yes is
What did someone.
That a little.
Maybe something comes out.
It is OK.
Slowly there.
I will do.
It will end, it will be okay.
So let’s open it.
Oh is?
I want to get a little closer now.
No is not.
What is not?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Why is it?
No, I am married.
Do you know?
No, I am in trouble.
Kissed him before.
Yes, but I mean that.
I want to touch.
No, no no
This happened, there was no other way.
A little, no
No to no.
Great, very beautiful
A shoulder, and great.
What are you doing?
See also
A little
No No No No No No No No
See also from.
See also Baby.
greatly
It is big.
Do you do your husband?
Do not ask that.
When the child comes, you will be angry.
Did you sit a little?
Yes, I was sitting.
Feels good?
Yes, not there.
What is?
It becomes weak.
Do not weaken?
No to no.
Sleep by
It gets hot.
I like it.
No, wait a little.
Please be wet.
I will point.
I have decided too.
Wait, I say no.
really
No no longer.
I will enter.
No, we will enter.
No, no no
No no longer.
I will enter.
No to
really
Yes is
Just now
Welcome to
well is
Oh is
Moving some staff.
I am
It looks like a promotion.
It is awesome.
More and more work.
appears to be more.
Maybe more traveling.
Yes is.
Do not force too much.
well though
Maybe it will go private.
My father has to do it.
Yes is.
How about your partner recently?
Okay, I am busy.
What said I.
He is a job, he wants to.
How are you recently?
Oh, you are not well?
Yes, is it so.
It was much.
Okay, I think I’ll go in for a bath.
Oh Mr Shiva.
Next week the circle will be gone.
It is hot though.
What week? what week?
The Tuesday.
I understand. then
Red Crete
Please please.
Yes
Do something to do.
No is
Yes
It is OK.
No to
No to no.
No, as it was last time.
touching or so.
Can’t just a little?
Didn’t you do it before?
Because not.
Do you feel good?
No...
Wait to...
No to...
Because...
Oh yeah...
No to...
I will catch.
It gets better.
What are you doing.
What kind of prediction.
Wait a little.
Isn’t it anymore?
What do you do.
I am ashamed.
I saw it before.
It is moving a little.
well is
No to no.
It is not moving, no.
Just a little, just a little.
It feels good.
I want to do it.
Ladies and gentlemen, it feels good.
Please wait a little.
I cannot endure.
Let me sleep a little.
Just a little.
Not just that.
Please please.
Go ahead of.
Just a little.
A little bit.
All of
still entered.
A little
really
become to be.
The M...
Clay is.
OK is
Claire
This is a
No to
really
A little bit.
Yes is
A little
You want to ignore it, you want to understand it.
No to no.
What if I find out?
Oh yeah
Oh well π
Spee
Oh my mom.
Oh oh oh oh
Oh no
not come out.
It feels like a card.
I got an email from the provincial office.
Why why?
Iβll do a coverage next week.
Is it so?
In class.
And then, it is a tough job.
You will be busy.
Yes, yes is it.
I will strive.
Next, please do not get close.
Oh yeah yes.
be strong.
It hurts...
This feeling.
and...
No to...
Oh yeah...
The stunning...
Oh no no no.
Oh yeah...
A hard woman.
hurtly
I love it.
Good morning.
With Mr. Tadeo
I did not think I could.
pleased
Do not tell me to be forever.
I will not say.
I have to say.
A lot of talk.
If you really hate the people, you will know.
I wash too.
Yes thanks
Are you ever ever a Walt Disney?
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah.
Since when?
As long as students.
This side type?
Yes
Hair is touched all the time.
Mr. Tupac is so soft.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
After you realize.
Just just got out.
It touches you soon.
How about here?
No to no.
Because I have to pick you up.
Just a little, there is still time.
No to
I have to go quickly.
The mothers are getting late and they are getting late.
But only a little.
Just a little more.
touched more.
If you are hungry, you will not be able to get it in time.
I will stream.
to flow.
I go after the water and wash my furniture.
I want to lick your tongue.
I cannot endure.
I need to pause a little.
I was a little hungry.
How to
Shake there.
Let me smoke.
How to
Can you, guys, get me in front of you?
Feel good.
It looks like your face.
You feel good.
I want to do more.
Such a soft.
Too much pressure.
I thought I would go soon.
Feel good
A little more.
Please please.
How long do you keep your mouth in your mouth?
R is...
The mask...
Masks, masks, masks, masks, masks and other things.
Letβs go out.
I have already taken it out, okay?
Feel good
I got out.
I put a lot in.
How about the recent part?
Yes, I am busy.
Yes
My country brother, this time.
I told him to send me vegetables.
Yes is.
Yes
Maybe thereβs some food floating.
Yes is.
Good was
Speaking of vegetables.
Health tests and blood sugar levels.
I went out and made meat a little bit.
It is best to eat vegetables in the center.
I donβt eat too much of Ramadan.
I think we should also share here.
How about his work recently?
Okay, do you want to?
Yes, I am working normally.
Yes, it is good.
Yes
It is time to take a bath.
Sorry, but I will finish.
Why is it?
I am married and I am sorry for my husband.
I think you are qualified as a mother.
It is not so.
The team of Mr. Shamash is also working hard.
I like it.
But I know.
Because this is not good.
Let us finish.
I understand.
The last
Can I hug you?
Yes, well well
Sorry to
I stood up.
Oh is?
Can you sleep for the last time?
Please please.
This really is the last.
I like it, Mr. Tuchel.
I like it.
Please please.
Mr. Tucson, look at me here.
Oh yeah
from below
The child who is.
It is cute.
I have been watching it all the time.
Oh yeah
They are eating in.
there there
Feel good
Can you pizza?
I want to do it again.
It feels good.
Feel good
It feels good to drive a distance.
It feels good to go there.
Please go quickly.
Feel good
Oh yeah
You have to bother a little.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Oh yeah
Thanks so far.
Thanks to.
You slept well.
Yes, I was tired and slept.
Iβm on a trip tomorrow, but stay up.
I think tomorrow my grandmother will take care of her.
I will take you with grandma.
Yes, I understand, that is how it feels.
Yes
Be careful, go out.
thanks to
I am going to take a bath.
well
No to
Are you filming?
I photograph a little.
I am ashamed.
Okay, very cute
No, a little
Where are you filming?
Where is?
A little no.
there there
It gets heavy.
I am ashamed.
I will see it later.
No is
here here?
What is here?
Oh, a little
No, do not photograph it.
It is wet.
See also
Look at it, not.
Yes
Shamefully
See also
Oh, oh
Oh yeah yeah
No is no.
Oh well!by
Where is Lun?
Have you been?
well was
I photographed it.
No no more.
You are filming video.
No to
Do not photograph.
Oh well.
I can really do it today.
Yes
OK is.
We are not watching each other today.
Anytime anytime
I have left it to grandma.
Is it true?
pleased
I like it bad.
I prefer my own.
What is it.
Yes
You can slow.
Yes, it is important.
I want to see.
Okay to?
It is great to see whenever.
Did you do it recently in Danish?
No, I did not do it at all.
Just an altar?
Yes
I don’t know, my husband.
Oh, I don’t know but.
Because he is sensitive.
It is insensitive.
The man may hide it, but he is good.
How about it.
Oh yeah
Oh, this is awesome.
No, where was he?
Was it a Sendai?
The Sendai?
Yes, probably
When will you buy it?
As a decoration.
As a decoration?
It is 200 yen.
Who is that?
in the stone.
More to Tia.
More to
Go, I’ll drink today.
Oh what?
Is it sweating?
Oh yeah
Oh well, very much
Put it in your ass.
No to?
I found it.
Put it in your ass.
Oh well, so well
Very very beautiful.
I went in, usually.
Not much image.
Maybe not open.
Why are you in today?
I went in for special.
Liked very much.
still scared
Something very good.
Feels good?
Yes, it feels good.
Are you picky?
Yes, it feels good there.
You know it up, right?
Add the internal organs.
Throw it in your ass.
and pinsome
hurtly
The internal organs are open.
It is difficult.
No to
Have you seen your eyes?
Did your son see your eyes?
Feel good
No to no.
No to
if
Stay a little quiet.
Yes
If if
Oh, if if
The Lakers
What happened?
I was calm, so I thought I would call you.
I am sorry, goodbye.
How would you be well without me?
Yes, you are okay.
Oh well well.
No, I’m going around a lot of things today.
It was so.
Yes, I have already broken.
by
During the time you walk around.
I went to the Sandy store before.
There was a lot of ram.
Oh well well.
Yes
But something, something
Maybe it was just special where I went through.
I think there were a lot of bird-boat boats.
Oh yeah, that is.
There was a lot of taste, or something like that.
Oh, and so
Raman would probably prefer it.
Oh yeah, maybe so.
I mean, it doesn’t fit down.
Do you feel like that?
Sorry, I got a call, so I will cut it off.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
again is
Yes
Then is.
I will find out.
Do not know, it is okay.
What do I do, I find out?
Is Rick still silent?
Yes, you understand
Have you gone?
Feel good
More of
Let me go.
It feels good.
It hurts.
hurtly
I breathed a little.
Oh is
No to
What are you wearing? is it okay?
Yes, well well
Check your face.
Before the operation, you must slide with the torus before you break.
When exposed to electricity, there is no pain.
Shame is a good form.
When he is trying to get tough on his legs, to try to break out what was on his two ends.
Yes
Oh yeah
No to
Yes
I mean
Drink my mango.
Can I drink this?
Yes
Oh...
Oh is
Oh well...
by
It hurts.
It feels good, there.
Do you sleep slowly?
Is it quick?
You will go immediately.
Departure in 1920
Oh my dear, wait.
I call that way.
Again to?
A little...
Later the hand.
If if
What happened? what happened?? to
Is the country okay?
Yes OK
With Ira.
I just talked about Ramsey, right?
Okay to OK!
Well, because it doesn’t fit with me.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
When I got home, I couldn’t eat here.
You think you should eat every day for a week.
Yes yes yes
Salt, peanut, and barricada, what about?
Oh yeah, yeah, is it okay?
No, I will do that.
So, I think it’s better to be yours.
Or do you want something to give a gift?
A gift to you?
What is it? what is it famous?
If you say a player, you can even say a jute?
Yes, I think yes.
Do you like cattle?
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah.
Sorry, but I’m going to play the game soon, so I’ll be able to stop.
Oh yeah, it is.
I will contact you again.
Oh yeah I understand.
Yes then then.
Yes to.
Mom, it is enough.
No to Maya.
Is it good?
Tamiya is okay?
What kind of ram you like?
I want to see, I like Jarocky.
Very, very strong
by
coldly
Maybe cold?
I don’t eat so much.
Do not eat?
What are you afraid?
What do you like?
I am
Delivery of sauce.
Hardly hard?
Do something
any of them.
Any of them?
It is here.
I fear
The sperm?
Why Why?
by
Really comfortable.
with eyes and voice.
My eyes and voice hurt.
I will hunger.
Glad to sleep.
Oh I hate.
Probably really once again.
Hatefully
Oh yeah
Mr. Karma, you are in a mess.
by
badly
Do not look like that.
by
excitingly
Yippidy yi yippity yay.
Oh well bel.
by Ube
Relaxed
Yippidy yi yippity yay.
by Hoo Bel
Oh well UX.
Oh, and Nicky
Hoh and
The outbreak
Oh well, oh well
Oh you
Oh yeah yeah.
The series’ shop, Mesamics, is back.
Watts is so beautiful.
Pitched
by Tj
very well w
much to
I do not know.
I don’t know, son
You are crying here.
Let me tell you to go.
slowly to
Let us dance.
A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A
Oh Gandhi.
Again, he fell down.
Very happy
If you get too much, we will do it again.
Okay, let’s have a full.
It hurts.