I'm sorry.
Good morning.
How was the first draft?
The final price is 132 yen.
132 yen?
Yes.
I told you it was 135 yen.
That's right.
I made a mistake.
No, Ichida.
I always say this.
It's the company's profit.
In the end, it all comes back in numbers.
I'm sorry.
It's okay this time.
132 yen.
Please give me an order.
Yes, I understand.
I'll call you.
Yes.
Good morning.
I'm Hiyama.
Yes.
Are you playing golf?
That's good.
By all means.
Next week.
In Chiba.
I understand.
No.
I owe the president a lot.
Yes.
I look forward to working with you in the future.
Excuse me.
The president likes to play golf.
That's right.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm irritated today.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Please give me an order.
Yes.
Can I go to the office?
Let's go.
Yes.
I'm going.
The next day.
Hello.
I'm Hiyama.
Yes.
That's great.
I see.
I understand.
Yes.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
I'm irritated today.
Ichida.
Come here, Ichida.
Yes, ma'am.
I can't do it today.
I don't feel well.
Ichida, let's go out.
Yes, ma'am.
Excuse me.
I don't feel well.
I really don't feel well.
I'm sorry, Ichida.
I don't feel well.
The detectives don't know anything about the scene.
Is that so?
I don't know.
I really don't feel well.
We're negotiating seriously for one yen each.
But the president says golf is the second.
I like golf.
If you like golf so much, you should become a professional golfer.
I'll do my best.
I don't feel well.
Sit down, Ichida.
This is the entry fee for JET.
How did the investigation go?
I looked it up in a book.
I found something.
What did you find?
There was a movement like a ball.
I'm investigating it.
I see.
Excuse me.
I don't feel well.
The president called me again.
Hello.
I'm Hiyama.
You're Ken, right?
Yes.
I'm Yunaho.
How are you?
Are you Ken?
I see.
Yes.
I'll write your name here.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Can I have some tea?
Director.
I had a stomachache yesterday.
I see.
I'm sorry that I gave you 3 yen.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad you gave me 3 yen.
It can't be helped.
But, when I'm stressed and anxious, it's good to relieve stress like this.
You're right.
I'm glad you gave me a job.
I know.
You did your best.
I used to be a director.
I'll do my best from now on.
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
What is this?
This?
This is the material for the project I'm working on now.
Is this the new project you talked about last time?
Yes.
I see.
The new project seems to be complicated.
Yes.
It's hard to do it alone.
Can you help me, too?
Me?
Yes.
But, it's my second year.
I only ask for a simple content.
Don't worry.
I see.
I want you to put the materials together today.
Yes.
For the time being, please put these materials together.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Here is the Excel.
What?
Is it wrong?
The cursor is wrong.
Oh, thank you.
Oh.
Did I put something in the grave?
This is...
Please fix it.
Yes.
Oh.
It's done.
I'll fix it.
I see.
It's amazing.
Can you check the schedule later?
Yes.
Please do it as soon as possible.
I see.
I have a lot of plans today.
Yes.
Did something happen to Akane?
Speaking of which, I have something to tell you.
Well...
The manager was angry that you didn't come today.
I see.
So, he quarreled with me about the price.
I think the manager left it to me.
Yes.
I'm worried about the manager.
I have no choice.
I'll call you later.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Speaking of which,
I sent you a letter the other day.
Can you check it now?
Now?
I sent it to the manager yesterday.
This is it.
Which one is it?
I opened it.
This is it.
I'll check it now.
This is not it.
I made a mistake.
Did you make a mistake?
It's out of alignment.
I'm sorry.
I did it carefully.
Please check it.
I put it in.
Excuse me.
Please check it.
I put it in.
What are you talking about?
Don't put it in.
Put it in properly.
I put it in.
Did you make a mistake?
I have to look at the screen.
Please check it.
I'll check it.
I made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
Can you tell me in detail?
Okay.
I made too many mistakes.
Can I get my phone?
I'll make a phone call.
Please be quiet.
Please.
Hello.
Yes, I'm listening.
This is Ichida.
Yes.
Is Mr. Sato in the sales department?
That's right.
Please.
Yes.
I'm listening.
That's right.
Will you come to the swimming school next week?
I'll be there at 2 p.m.
Okay.
I'll send you an e-mail.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I found Mr. Sato's ID card.
I'm glad.
I'll send you an e-mail.
Okay.
Thank you.
I feel refreshed.
I'm going back to work.
Me, too.
I have a meeting after this.
I'll go there.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Before that...
What is it?
You asked me to make juice, didn't you?
Yes.
I want you to make a copy of this.
Okay.
I'll make it in three minutes.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
It's nothing.
When do you want to do it?
Yes.
It's okay.
I got it.
Yes.
It's nothing.
It's always like that.
How about French?
Yes.
Okay.
Like this.
Yes.
I got it.
I'll be waiting for you.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Oh, it's Tuesday again.
I have to go to work.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm so frustrated.
It's your schedule, isn't it?
Yes.
Okay.
It's Tuesday, isn't it?
Tuesday night.
Okay.
I got it.
I'm so frustrated.
Hey, Ichida.
Yes.
I'm so frustrated that I can't do anything today.
Is it because of the sale?
Oh, is that so?
I want you to talk to me.
Here?
Yes.
It's okay, isn't it?
I'm in charge of today, right?
I can't miss it.
Well, that's true, but...
It's okay, isn't it?
It's a little early.
It's an important matter, so I want to be careful.
Yes.
Hey, by the way.
Yes?
I just got a call.
It's from J.E.D.
I see.
Did you finish the meeting the other day?
Yes.
I sent Mitsumori to the front.
What about her?
I called her again about the sale the other day.
But she didn't pick up the phone.
I see.
The president of J.E.D. often invites you to the club, doesn't he?
Yes, he does.
Because he's a man.
I see.
Excuse me.
The president of J.E.D. often invites you to the club, doesn't he?
What do you think?
Yes.
There's another clinic after this.
I want you to be a hero there.
Yes.
Thank you.
The president of J.E.D. often invites you to the club, doesn't he?
I've been thinking about the president of J.E.D. as a woman recently.
I think I've got that kind of feeling.
What?
I want to kiss you.
No, you can't do that.
But...
I said no, didn't I?
We have a business-like relationship.
So I don't want you to be in a relationship.
No, you can't.
No?
You promised you wouldn't kiss me.
Why can't I kiss you?
That's what you promised.
You promised you wouldn't kiss me.
Let me do it again.
Okay.
I like you, president.
No, you can't.
I can't be in a relationship with anyone else.
I like you, president.
No, you can't.
You know that.
I like you, president.
No, you can't.
You know that.
I like you, president.
No, you can't.
What do you think?
Can I kiss you?
No, you can't.
It's time for the consultation.
I think you can be discharged soon.
Yes, I can be discharged soon.
Then, put it in your mouth.
Please.
No, you can't.
I like you, president.
Put it in your mouth.
Please.
I like you, president.
I'll put it in your mouth.
It's done.
It's time for the consultation.
Let's go.
President.
Yes?
It's time for the consultation.
It's Saito Shouji, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I'm not good at talking to people who are in a bad mood.
Don't worry.
I'll do something.
Please.
What?
That was special.
If you throw it away, I'll fall in love with you.
But, no.
You and I have a physical relationship.
It's a business-like relationship.
Yes.
Let's do our best.
Let's go.
Yes.
I'm glad the Wi-Fi is connected.
Yes, it is.
I'm relieved.
I'm glad I could use the Wi-Fi in a city hotel.
Yes.
Thanks to you, I was able to order it.
I'm glad I was able to order it.
Yes.
I feel like I'm getting better.
I've been walking since this morning.
I see.
Oh.
If you don't mind, I'd like to rub your feet.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it.
Yes.
Please lie down here.
Here?
Yes.
Please lie down there.
Okay.
Is it around here?
Yes.
I feel like I'm getting better.
You're right.
Oh.
I've been outside all day this morning.
I had a remote meeting.
I've been at the hotel all day.
I see.
By the way, how was it?
The result of the meeting.
Did you get an e-mail?
I haven't received it yet.
I was told that I needed some time.
Have you been waiting for it?
No, I haven't.
I was told that I'd get an answer tonight.
I see.
But you didn't say what time you'd come at night, did you?
I didn't get an answer about the time.
I see.
If you just wait for an e-mail, you won't be able to do anything.
So, call me and check it again.
Okay.
Manager.
Yes?
The cause of my leg pain is in my waist.
Oh, is that so?
I need to check my waist.
Please check my waist.
Excuse me.
My legs hurt, too.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
How do you feel?
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Is that so?
Thank you.
I have a stiff shoulder.
Could you massage my shoulder, too?
Okay.
Can you stand up?
Please sit down comfortably.
Please raise your arms.
Do you want me to take this off?
Yes.
I'm worried about the fabric.
This is a good suit, isn't it?
I don't think so.
Please raise your arms again.
I'm sorry.
This part is stiff.
You usually have a stiff shoulder, don't you?
That's right.
Is that why you have a stiff shoulder?
I think I've been looking at the screen too much.
I want to go out.
I still have a lot of work to do.
Do you want me to massage your shoulders a little?
Is that okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Can I kiss you?
Just a little.
I love you.
I told you before.
Don't say that.
I love you.
Please go to bed.
Wait a minute.
We're business-like.
I don't want to be in a relationship.
I know.
I'll do my best.
I'm glad to hear that.
Wait a minute.
Make me feel better.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Can I take it off?
Yes.
Boss.
We're business-like.
That's right.
Are you okay?
Let's talk about this later.
Let's do our best.
Please tell me.
How to do it.
Okay.
I love you.
I have to go out.
I'll take it off.
Thank you.
I have to go out.
Are you okay?
Yes.
That's right.
About that...
Yes.
It's okay.
Oh, it's okay.
Yes.
In that way.
Understood.
Yes.
Thank you.
Well then.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Well then, I'll go.
Let's go.
Damn it.
Damn you.
Yes.
Can you give me the details of tomorrow's meeting in PowerPoint?
I got it.
I'll download it from Excel into PowerPoint.
I'm counting on you.
The phone call just now,
Did you mean the day before yesterday?
Yes.
Did he say anything?
I don't know.
I'm hungry.
Wait a minute.
I'm in the car.
Please be quiet.
Thank you.
Yes.
I got it.
This way.
It's okay.
It's nothing.
This way.
Yes.
I see.
Even so,
Compliance-wise,
I'd like to think positively.
Yes.
In that case,
Excuse me.
Yes.
Manager.
It's rude of you to say that.
It's okay.
Today's
14 o'clock
I'll cancel it.
Ouch.
It's because of the poison.
Put it in.
Yes.
This is over.
Put it in.
It's delicious.
Yes.
You want to be refreshed, don't you?
I want you to lick me, too.
It's okay.
Do you want me to lick you?
Please.
It's okay.
Manager,
I want to ask you one thing.
Yes.
You're good at sex, aren't you?
Is that so?
Have you ever run a pillow business?
No, I haven't.
I'm not good at it.
Because you're very popular with the people you work with.
I don't know how to do it.
I got it.
I'll tell you how to do it.
The trick is to respond sincerely.
Yes.
Manager.
The other day...
Yes.
You gave me this.
It's a payment form.
It's 100 yen.
I made it myself.
Yes.
But it's a little expensive.
I'd like you to check it with the manager.
Okay.
I'll check it.
I'm sorry, but...
I have data on my computer.
Can you take it?
This?
Yes.
I'll open it.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
This is it.
It's 100 yen.
Yes.
How is it?
It's good, isn't it?
I think it's good.
How about this?
But...
The last part...
I'd like you to fix it.
Yes.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Hey.
I'd like you to deliver it to my store.
Yes.
I got it.
Hurry up and deliver it.
Yes.
Is this okay?
Ichida-kun.
What is it?
Yes.
I'm sorry to ask you this.
But...
Yes.
Ichida-kun.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
Yes.
Do you have a partner?
I didn't say anything.
Actually...
I'm Matsui-chan.
Is that so?
Yes.
I was married when I was young.
I was always working.
I got a divorce.
But...
I...
I like you.
Yes.
I can't stand...
a business-like relationship...
that the manager says.
I respect the manager.
But I'm in love with you.
Matsui.
I'm Ichida-kun's...
I'm in love with you.
You're amazing.
What?
It's leaking.
No.
It's raining.
It's pouring.
I'm sorry.
It's raining.
I can see from the outside.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
My legs are so big.
Watch out!
Wow.
I want to do more.
I feel like I'm floating.
I can't go any further.
Can you let me go from behind?
Hang in there.
If you move too much, you'll fall.
No.
Not yet.
I can't go any further.
I feel like I'm floating.
It hurts.
I can't go any further.
Ouch!
I want you to let me go from behind.
I can't go any further.
Ouch!
Hang in there.
I can't go any further.
Ouch!
It feels good.
I like it.
I can't go any further.
Wow.
Hang in there.
It feels good.
Wow.
It's bigger than the last one.
I can't go any further.
Ouch!
It feels good.
Touch me.
What?
I want you to touch me.
I like it.
Ouch!
It feels good.
I can't go any further.
Ouch!
It feels good.
I can't go any further.
It's amazing.
It's so good.
I can't go any further.
It's not fair to say it's so good.
It hurts.
Can I go further?
No.
Hang in there.
Can I hang in there?
All right.
It feels good.
I can't go any further.
I love you.
Cancel all my plans.
All right.
Let's continue.
I can't go any further.
Let's do it again when I take a bath.
Himori.
Yes?
Is Miss Mori coming?
Well...
Four more cars are coming.
When do you set the deadline and the date?
I leave the date to the negotiator.
No, Himori.
Himori.
Listen.
I always tell you.
You shouldn't be impatient about your work.
It's all about the company's profit.
All right.
I'm sorry.
This time, it's all right.
Send me an e-mail as soon as you get here.
All right.
Kawamura
Hello, this is Kawamura.
Yes.
Dinner?
By all means.
This week?
All right.
It's all right.
No, no, no.
I'll leave it to you.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Yes, thank you.
You always say dinner.
You're so lazy.
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm irritated today.
Yes.
All right.
I'll go to the negotiator.
See you.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Oh, yes.
Oh, thank you.
No, no, no.
Yes.
Yes, it's all right.
Yes, then.
Yes, thank you.
Yes.
Okay, thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Okay, excuse me.
I'm a little irritated.
Himori-kun.
Director.
Come here.
Yes.
I'm a little irritated.
I'm not feeling well.
It's hard for you, Director.
Himori-kun.
Yes.
Let's have a light meal.
Yes, Director.
What do you think?
Please lick me as usual.
Yes, Director.
Excuse me.
I have to do it every day.
Yes.
It's really hard for you, Director.
The management doesn't know anything about the site.
Excuse me.
I'm negotiating the price for one yen.
That's right.
I think the director is doing his best.
Yes.
I have to do it every day.
Thank you for your hard work.
Yes.
Recently, there have been a lot of drinking parties and dinner parties.
The president and the staff are talking about drinking parties.
Yes.
It's hard for you, Director.
It's because it's not the Showa era.
It's the communication of the Showa era.
It's fashionable.
It's hot.
By the way, Himori.
Yes.
What happened to the JET project?
What do you think?
Have you done any research?
I haven't done it yet.
I don't know the details yet.
But I've got the information.
That's good.
Yes.
How is it?
Is the investigation going well?
Yes.
I'm going to be fired soon.
That's good.
Yes.
Director.
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
Leave it to me.
Thank you.
Really.
There's no one there.
It's hot.
Okay.
Sorry.
I understand.
Excuse me, director.
I'm sorry.
Director, I'm on the phone.
Yes, I'm on the plate.
Yes, what did you do?
Yes, yes.
Yes, over there.
Please wait a moment.
Thank you for waiting.
Yes, yes.
Thank you for contacting me.
Yes.
No, no. Thank you very much.
No, no.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Chief.
I think it's been a while since we've been in this relationship.
Yeah.
You can think of it as a relationship where you love me, right?
What are you talking about?
You've been saying it for a long time.
I don't need that kind of love.
I'm not good at work, but it feels good.
So it's not love.
I just want to feel good.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I made you come so early.
No, I don't want to.
I'm not ready yet.
I'm sorry.
We're business partners.
That's right.
We've been business partners for a long time.
I'm sorry.
You're out.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
You have a strong taste.
Did you have a lot of it?
I had a lot of it.
I'm sorry.
It's very strong.
It's thick.
I'm sorry.
I feel better.
Please send me the e-mail I just sent you.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry.
Yes, by all means.
Thank you.
Then, president.
How about French this time?
Yes, by all means.
Yes, that's right.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I have a company dinner again.
I'm sorry.
I have a company dinner next Friday.
Can you schedule me?
Yes, ma'am.
I have a company dinner.
I feel sick.
I'm very irritated.
I think it's because I have a company dinner.
What?
Please let me go.
Go?
Come here.
Yes.
What?
Here?
Yes.
I have a company dinner in the afternoon.
I feel better.
I can't work if I don't feel better.
I just went to the bathroom.
You just went to the bathroom.
By the way, Himori-kun.
What happened to Mitsumori-no-ken you told me before?
It's the same.
I see.
Mitsumori-no-ken
Director.
What?
I want to be the director of Kikkisu.
No.
Why?
Why are you saying that now?
I want to be the director of Kikkisu as a woman.
No, Himori-kun.
You and I, as I said before,
You and I have a business-like physical relationship.
I'm sorry.
I have to do my best at work.
I can't sleep.
I can't sleep now.
I'm getting older every day.
I'm sorry.
You and I are business partners.
We don't like each other.
I'm sorry.
It's time for the consultation in the afternoon.
Can you deliver it?
Yes.
I can deliver it well.
I see.
Nice to meet you.
Yes.
Please deliver it in my mouth.
I like you.
Why don't you say that?
I see.
Why?
I'm sorry.
I like you.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm late for the consultation in the afternoon.
I'm going.
Yes.
Get ready.
I see.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's just a business relationship, you know.
Let's go to the first floor.
Okay.
Good morning, Hiromi.
Good morning.
Would you like to take a break?
Yes.
Come here.
Excuse me.
You must be tired.
Yes.
Let's take a break.
Okay.
I want to go out today, too.
Let's take a break here.
Who are you?
There's no one here but us.
I thought it would be nice.
What if someone comes?
It's okay.
It's already this time.
That's right.
If you work until this time, you need a break.
I'm tired, too.
Let's go.
What?
You said kissing was special.
If you do this, I'll fall in love with you.
That's different from this.
I'm tired.
Director.
What?
I made a plan for the Mitsumori show in Ose.
Well...
Director Yamashita saw it, too.
He told me to lower my eyes from other companies.
So...
I made a plan, but I can't decide on my own.
I'd like to get your advice.
Okay.
I'll keep an eye on it.
Ah...
By the way, I have a plan for tomorrow.
Yes.
I'm going to work again.
Ah...
Tomorrow at 2 p.m.
I'd like to change it tomorrow at 2 p.m.
Please.
Yes.
I'll keep an eye on it.
Thank you.
Ah...
Excuse me.
Yes.
The meeting report for the day after tomorrow...
Can you make it in PowerPoint?
PowerPoint, right?
Yes.
Excel is fine, but...
PowerPoint is easier to handle.
Ah, yes.
I'll make it in PowerPoint.
Ah...
Excuse me.
I love you, Chief.
Why?
I love you.
I can't.
I can't do that.
I don't want to be in a business relationship.
As a woman, not as a boss, I changed from respect to love.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I want to be in a relationship other than work.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to be in a business relationship.
But, I feel better than usual.
I'm surprised.
I'm sorry.
Chief, don't say that.
There is a security guard.
Don't say that.
I'm surprised.
Chief, are you free today?
I don't need it today.
You don't have to work at my company.
You can work as a staff.
You feel good, right?
You too, Himari.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I don't need it.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I love you very much.
Are you sure?
I'm surprised.
Do you really love me?
I love you.
Excuse me.
I'm happy.
I love you.
I'm tired.
I'm sorry to ask you about my private life.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
I'm glad to hear that.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I'm single.
Are you sure?
I'm a divorcee.
I'm a housewife.
I'll do it.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Let's go over there.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad to hear that.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
We're serious.
We're not in a business relationship anymore.
I can't be a dreamy girl anymore.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Look at me.
Go ahead and laugh at yourself.
Iori-kun...
From now on...
I'm counting on you.