Thank you for watching...
May I come in?
Would you like some tea?
Would you like something cold?
Yes, please.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I'm tired.
You must be tired.
Would you like to have some sweets?
Yes, please.
You are very busy this week, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
I feel like there are more students than before.
I think so, too.
How is your shift going this week?
This week?
I'm going to Suimoku.
The university is going to start soon.
So, I can't go to Suimoku this week.
I see.
The manager said that he would do a special sale next week.
Really?
Yes.
If you do a special sale, you must be very busy.
Yes, I am.
So, I may change my shift schedule.
How often do you go to Suimoku?
I go to Suimoku four times a week.
You go to Suimoku four times a week and go to a sports club, too.
Yes, I do.
There is a sports club on the 6th floor of the station building.
How is it?
Are there more students than before?
I think so.
I want to attract more students to Suimoku because it's getting warmer.
Do you have a lot of macho people?
What?
Macho?
There are a lot of them.
Do you have a lot of macho people?
Sometimes.
I see them sometimes.
Do you?
Yes.
I go to the gym on Mondays and Thursdays.
And, I go to the gym with my instructor.
Do you have a favorite body type?
A favorite body type?
Well, I think...
Do you like muscular people?
Muscular people?
No, I like skinny people.
I see.
I like skinny people.
I have to go to Suimoku, too.
But, you don't play sports, do you?
No, I don't.
I see.
I was wondering if I should ask you about it.
Really?
How do you feel about it?
How do I feel about it?
For example, I do yoga.
Yoga?
Yes.
How do you feel about it?
Well...
I train my butt.
Do you train your butt in yoga?
Yes, I do.
But, I don't know how to do it.
Can you show me?
I've done it before.
I stretch my butt like this.
Like this.
Do you stretch your butt more?
Yes, I do.
Like this.
How is it?
Try it, Takumi.
Like this?
Yes.
Yes, like that.
Doesn't your butt stretch?
Yes.
Around your butt?
I don't usually move my butt.
So, I feel my butt is stretched.
Really?
It's the same at first, isn't it?
But, I can stretch my butt when I do it.
Does your butt become soft when you do yoga?
I think so.
Let's check it out.
Yes.
When you stretch your butt.
How do you feel about stretching your butt?
It costs about 9,000 yen per month.
It's not so cheap.
But, I recommend it.
Does your instructor teach you first?
Yes, he does.
He has a lot of equipment.
Yes, he has a lot of equipment.
I do aerobic exercise by myself.
I see.
Do you have a yoga class?
Yes, I do.
You have a time limit.
You can practice yoga at this time.
Or, do you play other sports?
Yes.
I have various classes.
I teach yoga.
How do you feel about the age group?
Do you have a young person or an old person?
I think it's a wide range. From about the 20s ... I don't know the above. About the 80s?
80s?
Maybe! But I'm also doing something with my peers.
Recommended! Oh, but I see, Takami-kun is a college student.
Oh, I see. Then it's quite busy.
I wonder if I can go home by the end of the summer.
Hmm.
But after all, since I'm in a sports club, I'm a miss. Miss.
Something like a miss.
Eh! No, no, no.
How do you feel about abs?
Abs?
Do you crack?
Eh! No, no, no. It's not like that yet, but I'm doing my best!
Can you show me a little?
Ah!
Hmm.
It's a good feeling.
Is it like this?
Can you see it?
No, it feels like it's broken.
Oh really?
Yes.
Thank you. But I'm still thinking about doing my best.
Do you usually invite your children?
Children? I don't have any yet.
Because children are given.
Hmm.
So can I help you?
Ah!
Because I'm not born yet.
Ah! Maybe.
Ah.
Maybe so.
Yes, yes, yes.
Hmm.
Then I'll go home and break my abs.
Eh!
Isn't your abs broken?
Hmm.
Hey.
Eh?
That's right, Takami-san.
Don't you have a girlfriend?
No, I haven't.
Ah. I see.
Eh. Something unexpected.
Because you seem to be very popular.
Really?
Yeah.
It's cool.
Do you think I'll be popular if I train in sports?
I'm sure you'll be popular. I think you'll be popular now.
But I like older people.
So you don't have someone you like yet?
I have someone I'm interested in.
Oh, I see.
Because I'm older.
Oh, I see. I hope it goes well.
Oh, I see.
Oh, eat it.
What do you think of younger people?
Younger people? I think they're cute.
Is your husband older?
Yes, he's the second oldest.
He's delicious.
The next day.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
The bath is ready.
Oh, thank you.
I worked hard today.
You always work hard.
I'm going home tomorrow morning.
Thank you for your hard work today.
Thank you.
You look busy.
Yeah, I'm busy.
How's your sports team doing?
Oh, sports team?
I'm working hard.
Oh, I see.
I'm working out my abs.
Abs?
Yeah.
Let me see.
I can see the results.
Results?
Yeah.
Like this.
Don't you think it's a little tight?
What do you think?
I don't know.
I'm working hard.
Oh, really?
I think I need to work harder.
Yeah, I think so, too.
I'll do my best.
Oh, by the way, you said you were working out your abs.
Yeah, I did.
I heard the store is busy these days.
Oh, I see.
So, I was told to shift again.
By the way, what was the name of the young girl who works part-time?
Takumi?
Oh, yeah.
She said she was coming to my house.
Yeah, that's right.
She comes to my house and talks to me sometimes.
How old is he?
I think he said he was 20 years old.
Oh, 20 years old?
Yeah.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, he's a college student.
Oh, a college student?
Yeah.
Does he talk to you?
What?
We talk to each other.
Really?
Yeah.
What do you talk about?
Well, it's about work.
He asked me what I was doing at the gym.
So, I told him I'd recommend him to me.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
I think we have something to talk about.
You're worried about him, right?
No, I'm not.
You're not?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, because he's 20 years old.
Yeah, I'm used to it.
I can't look at him like that.
Oh, I see.
So, he's not your type?
No, not at all.
Oh, I see.
Oh, by the way, can I take a bath?
Oh, sure.
Thank you.
Yeah.
I'm going to take a bath.
Okay.
It's hard, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
I lie down like this.
Oh, I see.
I lean forward a little and lean back again.
Does it work?
Yes, it does.
I feel like I'm stretching.
Oh, I see.
It's okay if you're stretching.
How long do you usually do it?
I do it for about 1 to 2 minutes.
1 to 2 minutes?
Yeah.
I think I can stretch a lot.
How many kinds of poses are there?
Oh, I see.
I'm going to learn various poses.
You said your body was hard.
Wow, I can stretch a lot.
Really?
Yes.
Your body is more stretched.
Really?
Can I see it?
Sure.
How about you?
Yes.
I know you have a job.
Oh, I see.
I've heard a lot about you.
By the way, what kind of job does your husband do?
My husband is an IT programmer.
Does he come home late?
Yes, he always comes home late.
Do you have a night shift?
I don't have a night shift, but I have a lot of overtime.
I feel like I can do it at home, but I don't.
Oh, I see.
My husband often goes to work.
Does he usually stay at home?
I don't think so.
How about a hip pose?
I recently learned a hip pose.
Can I see it?
Yes.
Okay.
Bend your knees and stretch your legs like this.
Your joints are very stretched.
They are very soft.
Really?
If you stretch your legs like this, you can stretch your heart.
I see.
Like this.
Try it, Takumi.
I can't do it.
Really?
Yes.
You can do it.
Just a little more.
Okay.
Can I try it?
Yes.
Like this.
It feels good, doesn't it?
How is it?
Do you feel better?
Better?
I don't think so.
I feel like my legs are relaxed.
I feel like my joints are rotating.
Can I try it?
Yes.
Try it.
It's really good.
Do you want to do it here?
Yes.
Like this.
Yes, like that.
Wow.
My legs are very stretched.
I see.
If your legs are stretched, they will be stretched more.
Does it hurt?
Yes.
I see.
I'm not used to it yet.
It's important to relax your legs.
Really?
Yes.
If you do it for a long time, your legs will be stretched like your daughter's legs.
I think so.
Try it.
Okay.
Let's take a break.
Do you want some tea?
Yes.
Here you are.
Your legs are stretched.
Yes.
Do you sweat a lot?
Yes, I sweat a lot.
It's a good exercise.
I'm tired.
By the way, you said you didn't have a girlfriend.
How have you been since then?
Actually, I have a girlfriend.
Really?
I see.
It's embarrassing to say this to you, but I have a girlfriend.
I'm surprised.
I see.
By the way, when was the first time you had a girlfriend?
What?
How many times?
The first time?
Takumi, I've heard something amazing.
I can't tell you.
It's a secret.
I see.
You said you had a crush on someone.
Yes, I did.
How have you been since then?
I have a crush on the same person.
I see.
Can I ask you something?
Actually, I've liked you since 2003.
What? Me?
Me?
I see.
Thank you.
I'm surprised.
I'm serious.
I see.
It's not a prank?
No.
I see.
I like you.
Let's practice yoga.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I was surprised, too.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Let's do stretching.
Okay.
Do you remember the pose?
Yes.
Do you remember?
Like this?
Yes.
Like that.
You're stretching a lot.
Really?
Yes.
It's good.
Stretch.
Yes, like that.
I see.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
It's good, isn't it?
I like it sweet, so I can't help it.
You like it sweet, don't you?
Yes.
It's good.
By the way, do you remember Takumi I talked about before?
Takumi?
Yes.
The one who did the part?
I was confessed.
What?
I was surprised.
I was surprised, too.
Yes.
I'm still young, and I heard that there is a good girl in college.
So, I was wondering how to tell her not to get hurt.
I see.
The girl at that age is quite normal.
She is straight.
Yes.
I think so, too.
I see.
For example, I think you should tell her not to get hurt because she is pure.
I got it.
Thank you.
I'll tell her that.
Yes.
You are really popular, aren't you?
What?
I'm not popular at all.
Really.
I see.
I was really surprised.
I'm not popular at all, but you are cute.
Thank you.
By the way, you are tired, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Actually, I went to a cafe because I was tired.
I see.
Then, I'll give you a massage.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Is this okay?
What?
Yes, it is.
It's good.
Is it good?
Yes.
Do you go to a sports club?
I go to a sports club to stretch.
I see.
I do yoga.
Oh, you do yoga.
Yes.
I think it's good to have a body like this.
I think so, too.
I can relieve my fatigue.
It's good.
Really?
Yes.
I feel good.
My muscles are relaxed.
Really?
Yes.
That's good.
It's good.
This is a script.
It's okay to sit on the sofa.
I want to talk to you.
Really?
I see.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What should I do?
When I stay at home alone, I can't stop washing dishes in the sink.
It's annoying.
Really?
I can't help it.
I see.
It's better to wash them right away.
That's right.
I can't help it.
It's annoying to wash dishes.
I see.
I'm tired.
It's a special day.
Yes.
I washed a lot of dishes.
I was a little tired.
Yes.
You were a little tired.
It was hard.
Yes.
I was busy, too.
So, I was tired.
Don't you feel pain in your legs?
My legs?
Yes.
Anyway...
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's over.
I see.
You told me the other day.
Yes.
I was very happy.
You are still young.
I think you can have a good child soon.
Do you think so?
Yes.
But...
I can't do what you recommend.
Thank you.
But, there are many cute girls around my age.
But, I can't find a good one.
I'm not used to girls.
I see.
Can I practice holding your hands?
My hands?
Yes.
Okay.
Can I?
Yes.
Your hands are warm.
Are they?
I don't know how to hold your hands.
I think you can hold my hands as you do now.
Like this?
Yes.
I think you will be happy if you have a child.
Really?
Yes.
I see.
Can I ask you a favor?
A favor?
What is it?
I've never kissed before.
I see.
Can I practice kissing?
No, you can't.
I have a husband.
No, I can't.
I'm sorry.
There are only three women who can ask you this favor.
But, I think you should do what you like.
Okay?
Just a little bit.
What?
No, I can't.
Just a little bit.
But, I have a husband.
Okay, I'll do it.
What?
Okay.
I'll do it.
No, I can't.
Just a little bit.
I'm sorry.
You look so happy.
What?
You have a premonition of this situation?
Yes, and?
Are you going to bother me?
No, I'm fine.
Just a second.
Okay.
I'm going to clean here.
Neko-Kichi comes to the Clinic very
Are you planning to finish your sister's bath?
It was a free time when I found out I couldn't take it any longer.
Is there not anything more like here?
Otokaramaru
A few days later
I'm back
Welcome back
Good job today
I'm sorry for doing all the housework
Not at all
You helped me a lot
Really? I'm busy with work
You've been working hard
Thank you for everything
By the way
How did it go with Ken?
Ken?
The one who did the artwork
You told him that you confessed
I did
But
He said no and understood
So it's fine
How did he say no?
Did he get hurt?
He said it's fine
Really?
It's fine
I was worried
I consulted with him
I see
It's fine
I gave him advice
That's good
If I gave him the wrong advice
He might fall asleep
I think it's fine
Really?
Did he listen to you?
Yes, it's fine
I see
If it was him
He might fall asleep
Really?
He might say he got rejected
I see
But he was nice so it's fine
Thank you
I can feel his kindness
I see
You were busy today
Yes, I was
How was it?
You can sit down
I wanted to talk to you
I see
It was hard
But
I'm used to it
Because I do it every day
Can you do it at home?
No, I can't
I can't sit down easily
I see
It's nice
I can't sit down easily
I see
Why?
There are many reasons
I see
When I kissed you the other day
Yes
I was serious
I see
Did you think about me?
Yes
What did you think about me?
You were serious
So I thought about you
But I'm older than you
And you're younger than me
But I'm serious
I see
I'm sorry
I'm married
So it's hard for me
You can't do it?
I see
There are many girls in college
I have to be a girl
I see
I can't
Wait
I can't stand it
Since I kissed you
I can't
I'm sorry
I love you
I know you love me
But I can't
I can't
Can we stop now?
Yes
Can you lift your head?
Help me
I don't want to graduate.
I see.
I understand that, but...
Really.
The only person I can ask for help is my daughter.
I understand.
Give me your hand.
Can I practice kissing a little more?
Practice kissing?
Yes.
Just kissing?
Yes, just kissing.
Is that okay?
Yes.
Is it okay?
Is it painful?
No, it's okay.
Where? Here?
Yes.
Is it okay to just kiss?
Yes, just kissing.
Is it painful?
A little.
It's big here.
Is it painful?
Don't.
Don't touch my body.
No, don't.
I told you I couldn't do it.
I can't do it either.
I can't do it.
Show me your neck.
It's embarrassing.
Can you do it?
I can't do it either.
Your neck is big.
It's embarrassing.
I can't do it.
I can't do it either.
Don't hide it.
I told you I couldn't do it.
Show me your neck.
I can't do it.
It's embarrassing.
Do you feel good?
I can't do it.
It's embarrassing.
Are you all right?
Do you feel good?
I didn't feel good.
I feel good.
I can't do it.
Wait a minute.
Thank you for your hard work.
I heard that you're going to be on the show.
Really?
That's great.
Congratulations.
I'm glad.
You're always doing your best.
I'm doing my best.
I'm going to have more overtime when I'm on the show.
I'm going to have a lot of work.
I see.
Don't overdo it.
I'll do my best.
That's great.
I'm going to have more work.
I'm going to have more overtime when I'm on the show.
I'll do my best.
That's great.
What's your name?
I'm Shiriotaki.
I'm 19 years old.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm in UV now.
Takumi, do you have something to say?
I'm busy with work.
I see.
Yes.
I'm not bored.
I see.
I'm going to take a bath.
Okay.
Take your time.
Thank you.
I'm going to take a bath.
Is this your bedroom?
Yes.
That's right.
I'm in trouble.
The other day...
Yes.
I got a delivery.
I'm in the middle of it.
But you can't do what you did the other day.
But...
I felt like you said yes.
But you really have a husband.
But you're married.
Right?
But I'm serious.
But you really can't do what you did.
I've been at a loss since that day.
Really?
I see.
I want you to practice with me a little.
Practice?
Yes.
And if you can feel it, don't say anything.
What is practice?
It's like this.
Yes.
Don't reply to me.
I see.
You can just scratch my back.
Yes.
I see.
Okay.
Yes.
I'll scratch your back.
Are you sick?
I can't stand it.
You can't.
You can't stop it.
I'm sorry.
I don't know if I can do it, but I'm going to do my best.
I'm going to do my best.
Wait a minute, please.
I can't do it.
I don't know what to do.
He looks fine to me.
You don't have to worry...
Has your body finished?
Yes, I have.
Are you fine?
My mouth hurts.
This is a practice, isn't it?
Yes, this is a practice.
Are you ready?
Not yet.
I can't do it anymore.
Please practice a little more.
I can't do it.
I can't do it anymore.
Just a little more.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm sorry.
I love you, Misumi.
I love you.
I'm so embarrassed.
Please stop.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm so embarrassed.
I told you that it's not good.
You're sweating a lot.
That's because...
I can't do it anymore.
I'm so embarrassed.
Don't look at me like that.
You're so beautiful.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm so embarrassed.
Really?
You don't have a rubber band, do you?
No.
I lost because of this.
Do you have a rubber band?
Yes.
When do you usually wear a rubber band?
I wear it when I have to.
I see.
Do you know how to wear a rubber band?
It's my first time to wear a rubber band.
I see.
You should put your hands like this.
It's my first time to wear a rubber band.
Just a little bit.
Be confident.
I see.
Just a little bit.
Do you feel it?
It's cold.
It's hot.
I am freezing.
It was so hot.
Do you think you can breathe with this?
Yes.
That's good.
Wait, wait.
It's all the way in.
I'm serious about you.
I can't stand it.
I just did this a while ago.
That's not funny.
Just a minute.
Don't do that.
I can't breathe.
Are you okay?
It was so good.
I'm so full.
You're so energetic.
Do you want to practice more?
I don't want to practice.
I'm serious about you.
I like you.
I don't want to practice.
Do you want to practice more?
Okay.
Let's do it one more time.
Do you have that much?
Yes.
Do you know how to put it on?
Try it.
That's right.
It's difficult.
You're good at it.
Do you know how to put it on?
I want to try it.
I don't know if I can do it.
It's okay if you put it in slowly.
A little more.
A little more?
Around here.
Over there.
A little more.
It's different from normal.
I can feel it.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
I'm glad.
I'm afraid I'm going to go again.
You can't go again.
That's great.
You're doing great.
You can't go again.
That's great.
You're doing great.
I can't do it.
It feels good to be put on.
I'm glad.
I can't do it.
You're doing great.
I can't tighten it.
Do you want me to help you?
Are you tired?
No, I'm fine.
I can't do it.
I'm going to put it in.
It feels good.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
By the way, what's the schedule for next week?
Next week?
I see.
Friday and Saturday.
And the weekend in Germany.
It's three days.
I see.
How about you?
I'll be there on Friday.
We'll be together.
I see.
Don't you feel uncomfortable doing this at work?
But it's a secret.
I can't tell anyone.
Okay.
I'll do as usual.
It's a secret between us.
Okay.
It's a secret.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It hurts so much.
It's amazing.
It's like a hairpin.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's dangerous.
It hurts so much.
It's amazing.
It's like a hairpin.
It hurts.
Can you see the hairpin?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It tickles.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
I'm going to die.
I feel good.
I'm sweating a lot.
Thank you.
I'm glad it was you for the first time.
I'm glad it was me.
No, I'm glad it was you.
I'm glad.
Can I kiss you for the last time?
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm going to take a shower.
Let's go together.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Thank you.
Was it different from when you graduated by yourself?
Yes.
I'm glad I graduated with you.
I'm glad.
I'm glad it was me again.
Didn't it hurt?
No, it didn't hurt.
You've grown up a lot.
I'm surprised.
It's my first time.
I didn't know.
You slept a lot.
I slept a lot.
You slept twice.
I'm surprised.
Do you take care of yourself?
How about you?
I'm good.
I'm glad I can go home on my birthday.
That's why I always go home alone.
That's lonely.
I'm going to take a shower.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
My chest feels good.
It's good.
Can I do it, too?
Yes, thank you.
It's good.
It's dangerous.
Thank you.
It's good.
Your buttocks are very big.
Really?
I had a complex about my big buttocks.
Isn't it strange?
No, it's very attractive.
It's amazing.
What?
Help me.
Your neck is very stiff.
It's very comfortable.
It's going to be stiff again.
It's good.
It's amazing.
It's getting harder.
It's good.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Can you raise your head?
How about your face?
It's good.
It's hot.
I'm going to take a shower.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
It's good.
It's very hard.
It's hot.
Thank you.
It's good.
It's getting harder.
Can you raise your head?
Yes.
It's good.
It's hard.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Did you want to get a surgery?
I wanted to get a surgery on my big breasts.
I see.
Your dream came true.
My dream came true twice last year.
I'm exhausted.
It's hard.
It's hard, right?
I'm starting to feel better.
Really?
Ah...
It's delicious
What's the matter with you?
Please stop so intensely.
It works again.
Damn.
I always cry when I am with you and you can make me feel good to pinch myself,
You understand, don't you?
Yeah, you do!
You went to bed again.
It was very pleasant.
Sei, you slept a lot.
Thank you.
It was fun.
I'm nervous.
It's the start, so I'm nervous.
Shall we start?
I'm nervous.
I'm back.
What did you do?
I was stretching.
I'm back.
I'm tired.
Thank you for your hard work.
How's your part-time job?
I'm busy.
I see.
How are you busy?
Do you have a part-time job?
I see.
I'm busy with a part-time job.
I have a lot of customers.
You have a lot of customers.
How many customers do you have?
I have a lot of customers.
I'm always busy.
I see.
It's hard.
Yes.
I have a lot of people.
I have a lot of work.
I can't do it alone.
I see.
It's hard.
I'm really tired.
You said you wanted to go on a trip to Hong Kong.
Yes, I did.
Which do you want to go to?
I don't know.
I'll go wherever I want.
Where do you want to go?
I don't know.
I see.
You went to the sea in Atami.
You said you wanted to go to the sea.
Yes.
How about going abroad?
How about going to Hawaii?
I don't know.
How many years ago did you go to the sea?
Two years ago?
Yes.
I want to go again.
Me, too.
Oh, I almost forgot.
The baseball game is about to start.
I'll watch the game.
Thank you for the tea and sweets.
You're welcome.
Well...
I think we should break up.
Why?
Because I'm married.
I feel sorry for my husband.
I think we should break up.
Can't I do that?
No.
You're younger.
I think it's better to find someone better at the university.
If you're a guy, you'll find someone soon.
I love you so much.
Yes.
Well...
Can I kiss you for the last time?
I'm going to do it one last time.
Okay.
One last time.
It's getting a little bigger.
You're right.
I'm going to do it one last time.
Can you do it one last time with your mouth?
This is the last time.
Okay.
This is really the last time.
This feels good.
It's hot.
Is this really the last time?
Yes.
This is really the last time.
Is this really the last time?
Yes.
I'm going to do it one last time.
It's hot.
This feels good.
I love it.
It's hot.
It's important to breathe.
I'm going to play sports games after this.
Are you okay?
It's hot.
Just a little more.
I don't want this to be the last time.
It's hot.
I'm married.
You've been touching my tongue.
Don't say that.
You know that, right?
It's hard for me, too.
It's hot.
Can I touch you for the last time?
It feels good.
It's hot.
I love it.
I fell asleep.
Thank you for listening to me.
I'm sorry.
Can I kiss you?
It's hot.
I'm going home.
Take care.
Thank you very much.
See you.
It's hot.
One world of not existing
Transmittal
Ah. Listen,
The curriculum instructor in Jin had quit.
Really?
I'll ask about that.
Oh, is that so?
Yeah.
Have you ever changed?
What?
Well...
The instructor who taught me for a long time quit.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
I wish I had a new, better instructor.
Oh, I see.
We have a lot in common.
Yeah.
I see.
How about your part?
What?
My part?
Yeah.
I'm doing my best.
Have you ever changed?
Yeah.
I've never changed.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
I was curious about that.
I'm doing my best as usual.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
I'm going on a business trip tomorrow.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
I'm counting on you.
Okay.
Yeah.
Be careful.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best at work.
Yeah.
Well, I'm going to take a shower.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I'll be back soon.
Okay.
Bye.
Oh, hello.
Hello.
Oh, how are you.
I'm fine.
Really?
How was your business trip?
I had a lot of overtime work today, so I was pretty tired.
Oh, I see.
Thank you for your hard work.
You're always busy, even on business trips.
Yeah, I'm busy.
I'm in Sendai right now, but it's cool here.
Oh, I see.
Is it cold?
No, it's not cold at all.
Oh, it's not cold.
Yeah, it's not cold.
Oh, I see.
How are you today?
I'm fine.
Oh, really?
Oh, by the way, did you get the mail I asked for the other day?
Oh, I haven't received it yet.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Oh, I see.
When will it arrive?
I think it'll be here soon.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Oh, I see.
How are you?
Oh, I'm fine.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I still have some laundry to do.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, I just wanted to do that.
Yeah.
See you later.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
See you later.
Yeah, see you later.
Yeah.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was on the phone with my husband.
Well, let's get changed.
Yeah.
Are you free tonight?
Oh, really?
Then let's drink a lot.
Yeah.
I can't forget you.
I can't.
How do you feel?
What?
Do you like me?
Yeah.
I like you.
Really?
Yeah.
Okay.
Do you like my big face?
Yeah.
I see.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
Give me your big butt.
It feels good.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't smell me.
Does your buttocks feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Your legs are moving a lot.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
I can't do it.
Is it here?
My chest hurts.
Touch me.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
I'm getting better.
You're getting better.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I'm embarrassed.
I want to go home.
How do you feel?
I feel warm.
Can I touch your chest?
I can't do it.
Does it feel good?
I'm glad.
I can't do it.
I want to go home.
It feels good.
I'll make you feel better.
I can't do it.
Does it feel good?
It feels good to be licked.
I can't do it.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Please speak more.
I'll make you feel better.
I can't do it.
It's embarrassing.
You're wet.
I can't do it.
Can you feel it?
You have a lot of blood in your mouth.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
I'm your wife.
Please be quiet.
Hello?
How are you?
I'm fine.
Really?
I'm sorry.
I washed the dishes.
I see.
I bought some souvenirs for you.
Really? Thank you.
This is beef tongue.
Beef tongue.
There is a sweet rice cake called tsunda mochi.
It looks delicious.
Which one do you want to eat?
I want to eat both.
Do you want to eat both?
Which one do you want to eat?
I heard a strange voice.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Really?
I want to eat both.
Do you want to eat both?
I see.
You look different from usual.
Do you think so?
I'm fine.
Do you have any problems?
I don't have any.
I haven't changed at all.
You haven't changed?
Are you okay?
Do you have a fever?
I don't think I have a fever.
I'm fine.
I'm in a good condition.
I didn't hear you.
I'm fine.
I'm in a good condition.
I'm out of breath.
Is that so?
I'm sorry.
I'll call you later.
Okay.
I told you to be quiet.
I couldn't help it.
I was desperate to cry.
I'll call you later.
I feel sick.
I feel sick in my stomach.
I want to go to the bathroom.
I feel sick.
I'm sorry.
I'll go to the bathroom.
Woof.
Cotton can!
I've improved completely.
You surprised me, Womami.
Coco, I want you to be comfortable.
I can't stand it anymore.
Yes.
Can I put it in?
But I ran out of rubber.
Rubber?
Yes.
Oh, I see.
Well, it's okay.
It's okay.
Really?
Yes.
Today is a good day, so put it in.
Okay.
It's good, isn't it?
Is it different from when you sleep?
It's totally different.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I feel good.
I hope you don't go to bed right away.
Yes.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
I feel really good.
I feel good.
I can't do it.
Wait a minute.
If you put too much pressure on it, it will go away.
I can't do it.
Put more pressure on it.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I feel good.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
Don't do it again.
Hello?
I wanted to hear your voice.
Really?
Thank you.
I'm tired.
I was watching a drama.
Really?
Yes.
You like dramas, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I often watch them, so I was watching them today.
How about you?
I'm on a business trip.
What?
I'm on a business trip, so I'm far away.
I know.
What's wrong?
I'm thinking about where to go.
That's good.
Where are you going?
I heard something.
What?
Where are you going?
I don't care where I'm going.
Is there a place you want to go?
I'm thinking about the sea.
I like the sea.
It's a little warmer.
I want to go there, too.
When did you go to the sea?
When was it?
I don't remember.
It's been two years.
How many years ago?
I haven't been there for two years.
You haven't been there, have you?
You know, I like fish.
You're right.
I like fish, too.
I want to go to the sea abroad.
I want to go to the sea in Japan.
That's good.
I'm sorry.
Can I go out later?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
See you later.
Wait a minute.
I'm going.
I told you not to play pranks on me.
You've been patient enough.
That's not true.
I've been patient enough.
You've been patient enough.
I feel good.
One more time.
That's great.
You've been very patient.
You're going to the sea abroad.
That's good.
There!
I'm sorry...
It's so great, I can finally breath...
I'm totally satisfied...
And, now that you are back...
Ha...
Ahh...
Ah...
Oh, it feels good.
Ahh...
Ah, I'm dying.
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
It's hard.
One more time.
I'll turn around.
It's hard.
Can you stand on your knees?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Touch my head.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I'm happy.
Please be more gentle.
It feels good.
It's hard.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
If you take a break, can I do it again?
Again?
You're not on a business trip.
I'll do it again.
I'm sorry.