I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to die if I don't do something about it.
Hello?
You?
Yes, I'm fine.
How are you in Singapore?
Oh, I'm fine.
How are you in Japan?
Oh, I see.
By the way, when do you plan to return to Japan?
Oh, Mika?
How are you doing?
You seem to be doing your best in the university circle.
Oh, I see.
Well, then.
I'm home.
Oh, welcome home.
Oh, Mika, welcome home.
I'm home, Mom.
I'd like to have a meeting at home for the circle today.
So I brought my friends, Takuya and Kouta.
Oh, nice to meet you. I'm Takuya.
I'm Kouta. Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Welcome.
Oh, Mika, what did you say?
A circle meeting?
A costume meeting?
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to do a costume for the boys.
I'm going to do a lot of things like remodeling their costumes.
Oh, I see.
It's hard.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Take your time.
Oh, the thickness of the fabric is good, isn't it?
The color is good, too.
I'll measure it a little.
Yeah.
Well, it's about 70 centimeters.
But what should I do?
Hey, please be a little embarrassed.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Isn't it a little vertical?
What?
What are you doing?
I'm measuring it.
Show me.
What are you doing?
Don't do that.
Don't you think it's cute?
I'll show it to Mika.
I don't need it now.
Let's measure the back.
The back?
What is it?
I think the longer the back, the better the design.
That's good.
I think it's better to have a longer back than the front.
Write it down here.
Yeah.
This is for the number of people, and this is for the budget, right?
Yeah, the budget.
By the way, doesn't Mika's mother draw water?
Isn't she beautiful?
She's so beautiful.
Mika's father used to be a secretary.
He remarried, so she's his new mother.
So she's his stepmother.
I see.
That's good.
They get along well.
They're kind, too.
They have a close relationship.
She's beautiful.
Let's measure it again.
Okay.
Mika.
Please have some tea.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
Please have some tea.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Please have some tea, Mika.
This is a bag.
What are you doing now?
I'm measuring the clothes and checking the fabric.
I see.
You're measuring it like this.
Yes.
It's detailed.
I'm going to use it at the school festival.
Oh, at the school festival.
I have to think about the budget.
That's a lot of work.
Yeah.
It was a good continuation.
Where should I measure it?
I think it's around here.
You should measure the chest, too.
How should I make the chest?
The fabric is cheaper to use nylon.
But I think polyester is better.
I think so, too.
That's right.
There's a budget, too.
That's a lot of work.
It's like this.
It's pretty neat.
It's around here.
How wide should I make it?
It's about 35 cm wide.
By the way,
Takuya, are you Mika's...
Oh, you noticed?
I see.
He's my important boyfriend.
Your boyfriend.
I'm sorry.
I'm Takuya.
I'm dating Mika.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
It's okay.
I don't mind.
I'm sorry, Mom.
It's hard to take off the actual costume.
It's like this.
I see.
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
You can keep going.
I'm sorry.
Let's measure it.
The shoulder is...
It's about 60 cm.
That's a lot.
I can't spend much money on it.
I can't measure this one, either.
Right.
Well...
It's smaller than this.
I think so, too.
And I'm a little worried about swelling.
That's true.
Sweating, too.
That's right.
It's hard for girls to sweat.
Then, raise your arms a little.
Is it easy to get up?
Like this?
Yes.
It's easy to move your arms.
When you dance,
can you move your arms?
Yes.
Like this?
Doesn't your wrist hurt?
No, it doesn't.
Then, how about this one?
Like this?
Well...
It's a little tight here.
If the sleeves are wide,
it'll be easier to move.
That's right.
Let's make it loose.
Loose?
Loose.
How about this button?
I don't think it's necessary.
That's right.
It's annoying.
Let's take it off.
I might get in the way.
You can take your time.
Thank you, mom.
It's hot.
Mom?
Are you there?
Yes.
Mom?
Are you there?
Yes.
Kouta has a part-time job.
He's going home.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Please come again, Kouta.
Yes.
I'm Takuya.
I want to go to school with you tomorrow morning.
Can you stay over?
Of course.
As long as you're okay,
I'm more than happy.
That's great.
I'm sorry to bother you, mom.
You're welcome.
I'm going home.
Thank you.
See you tomorrow.
See you.
Don't be late.
Okay.
See you.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm going home.
I'm sorry.
Do you have a towel?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Where did I put it?
Here you are.
I'm sorry.
Where is Rika?
She's doing a report in her room.
I see.
By the way,
how long have you been together?
About a year with Rika.
I see.
What's your relationship like?
Are you in love?
Yes.
I heard from Rika.
Your mom is a psychic.
Is that so?
I used to work at my husband's company.
That's how I got here.
I see.
Do you have a part-time job?
I work at a gas station.
I see.
I'm sorry.
From now, we'll start a report.
Felicia is not a good kid.
I'm going to make a hole in the middle of the dough and put a piece of butter in it to make a hole in the middle of the dough.
I'm going to put the catnip powder on the catnip.
arents
I locked the door.
I can't help it when I see my mother.
Mom
I can't help it.
I can't help it anymore.
Mika-chan
I can't help it.
Mika-chan will wake up.
I'll wake up.
Please be quiet.
I can't help it anymore.
I can't help it.
What are you doing?
Please be quiet.
Mika-chan will wake up.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I can't help it.
Don't do that.
Wait a minute.
I can't help it.
I can't stop thinking about my mother.
Wake up.
I can't help it.
What are you doing?
Please be quiet.
Mika-chan will wake up.
I can't help it.
Wait a minute.
Don't do that.
Be quiet.
Mika-chan will wake up.
Wait a minute.
I can't help it.
What are you doing?
Don't do that.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
Where are you?
I can't find you.
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
Did you sleep well last night?
Yes.
Good morning, mom.
Good morning, Mika-chan.
Good morning, Takaya.
Good morning, mom.
Good morning.
You're not late.
No, I'm not.
Really?
I have to go now.
I see.
See you later.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you today?
You look upset.
Mom.
I'm sorry for what I did last night.
It's okay.
Please raise your head.
I'm sorry.
I was excited when I saw you.
I'm sorry for what I did last night.
It's okay.
Please raise your head.
I'm sorry.
Are you calm now?
Yes.
Anyway, have some tea.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I have to wipe it off.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Can you go home with this?
Really?
It's okay.
I'll wipe it off.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You're so used to it.
Hang in there.
I'm sorry.
I can't stop loving you.
I know it's my fault.
You smell good.
I'm sorry.
I can't stop loving you.
It's soft.
What are you doing?
It's hot here.
It's hot.
You smell good.
No.
It's hot.
It's soft.
You have a nice butt.
It's hot.
Stop it.
You have a nice butt.
It's hot.
It's wet.
It's warm in the umbrella.
It's hot.
Stop it.
You dropped your foot.
It's hot.
It's like a face.
Stop it.
It's hot.
You have a nice butt.
Stop it.
It's hard.
It's soft.
It's hot.
You don't have to lick it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Stop it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's hard.
You have to stop it.
Stop it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Stop it.
It feels good.
It's my turn.
Stop it.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Stop it.
It's amazing.
It's hard.
Stop it.
It feels good.
It's hard.
Stop it.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Ah! Ah! That's no good!
That's no good!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! No!
Meg-kun!
No!
It's hard to say only mom.