I'm going to make a cake using the leftover dough from the previous video.
I'll bake it at 1950 degrees for 20 minutes and I'll roast it at 120 degrees for once.
I'll bake it at 1950 degrees for 20 minutes and I'll work the outer parts.
I'll bake it at 1950 degrees for 20 minutes and I'll risk it.
I'll bake it at 1950 degrees for 20 minutes and I'll roast it for 12 minutes.
I'll bake it at 1950 degrees for 12 minutes and I'll roast it for 12 minutes.
I'm going to bake it at 1950 degrees for 15 minutes.
2 days later
Good morning.
Is it okay to be so slow?
It's okay.
Here's your miso soup.
Thank you.
Hey, mom.
Yes?
I told you not to put onions in the miso soup.
It's okay. It's delicious.
What?
I can't eat this.
You have to eat it properly.
I don't need it anymore.
What?
I made it for you.
Make sure you get enough water.
Yes, yes.
You'll get dehydrated in the winter.
I know.
Did you forget that your dad passed away because of that?
My dad was a carpenter.
On a hot day, he had a heat stroke and fell off the roof and died.
It happened three years ago.
Waji, who said he couldn't study, taught me a lot of sports.
I respected Waji.
What is it?
Nothing.
Hurry up and close the door.
Hasemi, you have it, right?
Yes.
After my dad passed away, my mom and I lived alone.
I became a carpenter in my dad's place.
Good morning.
Today's game is a little noisy.
Is that so?
Be careful.
I understand.
The live broadcast the other day was a little noisy.
That's right.
You have to be careful.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay today?
I don't know.
You saw me making lunch, didn't you?
Yes.
Why did you leave it?
I'm sorry.
Good morning, Sayu-chan.
Good morning, Hasemi-san.
You're lucky to have such a beautiful mom make you lunch.
Thank you.
Be careful.
I'm going.
Yes.
Mr. Atsumi, who worked with my dad,
I worked under Mr. Atsumi.
How is it? Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
Are you used to working?
Yes, a little.
It's good.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to drop out of college.
Don't talk about that anymore.
But...
It's okay. I don't regret it.
You were smart enough not to care about your parents.
I really don't regret it. It's okay.
There's rice on it.
What are you doing?
It's okay.
I'm a parent.
I see.
You like hamburgers, don't you?
Yes, I do.
You're going to finish them all.
Do you want to eat mine?
Can I?
Yes.
Go ahead.
Here you are.
I'll have the rest.
Okay.
Eat a lot.
Good morning.
Let's eat.
Okay.
I wonder where Rohan's work is going.
I hope it's close.
You think so?
Yes.
Can you sleep well?
Yes, I can.
Really?
Yes.
That's good.
It's good.
You should hurry up.
Mr. Otsumi is waiting for you.
I know.
Okay.
Don't be so slow.
Good morning.
Are you going to Chiba today?
Yes, I am.
By the way, I'm going to take a day off today.
I see.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Good morning.
I feel cold.
Thanks.
I made you lunch.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Is Mr. Sato doing well?
Yes. He's so good that I can count on him.
Thank you very much.
I owe Mr. Sato a lot.
He died without leaving anything behind.
I'm a bad parent, too.
Please do it before it cools down.
Please leave this to me.
Mr. Katsumi.
Sae-chan.
I don't have time.
Mr. Katsumi.
My mother was secretly held by Mr. Katsumi.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Please wash your hands.
Let's eat.
Thank you for the meal.
It's good.
Is it good?
Yes.
Did someone come?
Why?
This is a cigarette.
An old friend of mine came.
Is that so?
Let's eat.
Thank you for the meal.
It ended earlier than I expected.
Would you like a drink?
But...
I'll make it easier for you.
Let's buy a Hachimori and drink.
Is that okay?
I'll give you all the money.
Thank you.
Let's go home.
Let's eat.
Thank you for the meal.
It's good.
Eat a lot of meat.
Thank you for the meal.
You have to work hard.
You should eat, too.
Thank you for the meal.
How about sashimi?
I'm glad I didn't have to cook.
Thank you for the meal.
It's all thanks to you.
There's a squid ring.
Squid ring?
Drink it.
I'm fine.
Drink more and more.
You'll remember how to drink.
Can I drink this much?
It's okay.
I'll make it easier for you.
Thank you for the meal.
Let's go home.
How about simmered fish?
Thank you for the meal.
I don't usually cook because it's a hassle.
That's right.
Do you eat a lot of rice?
I cook a lot.
That's why you have a good style.
I'll drink it.
Do you want more?
You're young.
You should know your limits.
That's right.
Drink it.
There's Japanese sake, too.
Is that for you?
It's okay.
I don't like Japanese sake.
It's good, so try it.
You should know your limits.
Try it.
How is it?
You're thirsty, right?
It's good.
It's the taste of an adult.
Really?
Can I drink this?
It's the first step to becoming an adult.
That's right.
Are you okay?
Get a hold of yourself.
I'm sorry.
Satoshi, do you understand?
You shouldn't drink Japanese beer.
That's your limit.
Don't drink it until the next time you drink it.
Okay.
Why did he say something like a father?
I didn't understand at that time.
How is Satoshi?
He's sleeping soundly.
You made him drink too much.
He knows his limits.
I'll stop drinking until the next time.
It's okay.
What is it, Sumi?
Don't tell Satoshi.
You were raised by a woman.
Don't say that.
It was hard, wasn't it?
You're not my mother. You're a woman.
It's wonderful.
Don't do that.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
Sumi.
Come here.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
Stop it for today.
Satoshi is here.
Stop it, Natsumi-san.
Stop it.
Look at me.
Natsushi is here.
Stop it.
You like it, don't you?
It's hot.
Are you trying to do that?
You're attracted to Satoshi.
Stop it.
Natsumi-san.
Your back hurts, doesn't it?
Stop it.
Like always.
I see.
I'll take care of Satoshi.
Stop it.
Let's go.
Sae-chan.
You're the best.
Let's make a happy family together.
I'm sorry.
I broke up with her because of my mother's sex.
Good morning.
You drank too much yesterday.
Natsumi-san said she's free today.
What about her?
Natsumi-san?
What do you mean?
I went home at night after you went to bed.
From that day on, I started to see my mother as a woman.
What's wrong?
Do you like him?
Like what?
Natsumi.
I don't like him.
You don't like him, but you feel that way.
You feel that way about him.
Did you see it?
You said you'd support him.
Did you get money from him?
Did you sell your body for money?
It's not like that.
Satoshi.
I'm going to open the door.
I think you're mistaken.
Good night.
Good morning.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I don't think so.
Are you sick?
I'm fine.
Did you eat?
Yes.
Let's go.
Good morning.
What's wrong?
Don't dry your hair like that.
I'm fine.
It's hot today.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Satoshi.
Mom.
Forget about Atsumi.
I'm sorry.
I had a chance.
I...
I quit my job.
What are you talking about?
Atsumi is not a bad person.
I let him do it.
So don't tell me you're quitting.
Satoshi.
Stop.
What are you doing?
Mom.
Satoshi.
Stop that.
Don't talk about Atsumi.
Atsumi is not a bad person.
Stop it.
I can't stand this.
Let go of me.
You made me show my true self.
Stop it.
I can't stand this.
Let go of me.
Stop it.
Let me go!
Stop it! Let me go!
Listen to me!
I can't take it anymore.
What are you doing?
I told you I can't take it anymore!
I can't take it anymore.
Stop it!
Satoshi!
Do you know what you're doing?
You can't do this!
I can't take it anymore.
I told you I can't take it anymore!
Satoshi!
Let me go!
I can't take it anymore.
Stop it!
Satoshi!
It's over.
Stop it!
It's your fault.
What are you talking about?
Stop it!
I can't.
Satoshi!
Stop it!
What are you doing?
No!
Stop it!
Satoshi!
No!
Stop it!
I can't take it anymore.
Satoshi!
Stop it!
Mom.
Satoshi.
Mom, you're doing a great job.
You're doing a great job.
You're not sick.
Mom.
Don't suck so hard.
Be gentle.
Don't treat me like a child.
I'm not a child.
Don't suck so hard.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm begging you.
Please forgive me.
Mom.
Satoshi.
It feels good.
Mom.
Satoshi.
It feels good.
Stop it.
Mom.
Satoshi.
Stop it.
Where did you get this?
Mom.
What are you doing?
I want more.
It feels good.
Mom.
Stop it.
There's a lot in there.
Mom.
Satoshi.
It feels good.
Mom.
I want more.
Satoshi.
Mom.
Stop it.
It feels good.
I can't get up.
Why?
When you do what you like,
put on the rubber band.
Get out.
Mom.
Good work.
You've been acting strange lately.
I see.
Is Sayo-chan doing well?
Why?
She hasn't been answering her phone lately.
She's doing well.
I'm going to the convenience store.
What?
Are you still dating him?
Him?
Atsumi.
I'm not in a relationship with Atsumi.
Don't look at me like that.
Good work.
Good morning.
Hurry up and eat.
You're going to be late.
I can't go to work like this.
What?
Mom.
Please.
Satoshi.
I can't go to work like this.
Please.
Mom.
Don't tell anyone.
What?
What you're going to do now.
Can I?
Mom.
Satoshi.
Hurry up and eat.
Mom.
No.
I can't.
I have to go.
Mom.
I can't.
Satoshi.
Stop.
Mom.
I can't.
It's going to be all right.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
I want to put you in the tent.
No.
I'm just trying not to put you in the tent.
I want to put you in the tent.
Don't do that.
This is Matsuri.
I want to put you in the tent.
It's fantastic.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
Satoshi.
Hey.
Good morning, Sae-chan.
Good morning.
How's Satoshi?
He's not feeling well.
I think he'll get better soon.
I'll take him to the site.
Okay.
Sae-chan.
I got a call recently.
What happened?
Satoshi is upstairs.
I'm sorry.
Tell him I'll be waiting for him at the site.
Okay.
Mom.
Don't do that.
I know.
Satoshi.
Don't do that.
Go to him.
I can feel the warmth in your mouth.
Don't do that.
I know.
Mom.
Satoshi.
Get ready for work.
Mom.
Satoshi.
I'm going to look for you like a dog.
And you will look for me too.
Mom.
Satoshi.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Sit down.
Why?
Mom, did you say something to me?
No.
I see.
I'm going to the convenience store.
Good luck.
Mom and I started to have a relationship.
Mom made me promise.
I won't tell Atsumi about this.
I will treat Atsumi normally.
I didn't like it.
I was asked to keep this promise.
I see.
Mom.
It's okay to sleep.
It's your day off.
Yes.
You have a strong body.
My father worked hard to build this house.
For me and Satoshi.
It's a renovation.
But it's hard to maintain this house.
That's why Atsumi helped me.
I'm a bad mother.
No.
You are a good mother.
I'm a bad mother.
No.
Mom.
Satoshi.
Why are you standing up?
It's morning.
I can't help it.
Mom.
You have grown up.
I'm sad.
It's good.
Satoshi, it's good.
Satoshi.
You have grown up.
It's good.
I want to stop making this.
Let me stop.
I want to stop.
It's good.
Satoshi, it's good.
I can't stand it anymore.
I want to stop.
I can't stand it.
It's good.
Satoshi, it's good.
Satoshi, you are so fat.
It's good.
I want to stop.
Mom, move by yourself.
By myself?
It's good.
Satoshi, it's good.
Satoshi.
It's good.
Satoshi, it's good.
Do you feel good?
It's good.
I'm old.
Do you feel good?
It's good.
Satoshi.
Do you feel good?
It's good.
It's amazing.
Do you feel good?
It's good.
Satoshi.
It's hot.
Why?
I'm sorry.
Mom.
Did you wait for me?
No, I just got here.
I'm glad.
Are you hungry?
Yes, I'm very hungry.
I'm glad.
The break time is short, isn't it?
It's short.
I brought you a lunch box.
Thank you.
Eat it.
It looks delicious.
I'll eat it.
Please eat it.
It's good.
Is it good?
I'm glad.
Chew it well.
The break time may be short, but it's hard if it gets stuck in your throat, isn't it?
I know.
Because it's delicious.
No one takes it.
You don't have to be in a hurry.
It's good.
There are rice grains on it.
Look at me.
Thank you.
Don't eat rice grains.
I know.
It's really good.
Really?
I'm glad.
It's good.
My mother and I left that house.
We quit the thick place and now we are working in a different place.
Now we live in a small apartment together, but one day we will build a nice house for my mother.
My mother said,
I'm sorry for being a bad mother,
but now...