I'm going to take a walk in the park.
I can't Madam ...
I'm going to take a walk in Dotonbori.
shopping
I finally arrived in Dotonbori.
It's been six months since my wife's house suddenly disappeared.
My wife suddenly disappeared without saying anything.
The shop I started with my wife is also closed.
I'm going to wait here for my wife to come back,
so that she can come back whenever she wants.
I'm going to wait here for my wife.
I'm going to wait here for my wife to come back, so that she can come back whenever she wants.
I'm glad you came back.
I thought I'd never see you again.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming back.
Honey.
Before my wife disappeared, my wife and I were running a restaurant.
Thank you for waiting.
You have to drink this.
I'm glad to hear that.
This is delicious.
Thank you.
Please enjoy it.
What are you going to make next?
I'm going to make a cafe au lait.
You're good at cooking.
Thank you.
I started an Italian restaurant with my wife.
I launched this restaurant with my wife.
I introduced in a restaurant with my wife.
Our dream came true.
My wife and I used to dream of having delicious food there.
Thank you.
It's really delicious, isn't it?
Yu, I love you.
I love you.
Yu...
Excuse me.
This is a hot latte.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I brought a new one.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I brought a new one.
I'm sorry.
I was surprised.
I brought a new one.
Please be careful.
You should take it out from the plate.
You know that, right?
I'm sorry.
Be careful.
Ouch!
Hey!
I'm sorry.
I told you to be careful.
I knew it.
I'm sorry.
Don't increase my workload.
I have to get a part-time job.
This is Kanda.
He is a college student.
He is a little clumsy.
So, I hired him.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Can I order?
Sure.
I'm sorry.
Welcome back.
I'll clean the toilet.
Okay.
Welcome back.
I'm back.
What did you talk with him?
We talked about work.
I see.
How was the market?
It was expensive.
It's expensive.
If I had noticed something strange at this time...
It feels good.
I know.
Hey.
What?
We talked a lot today.
Are you jealous of me?
I'm not jealous of you.
I see.
Why are you sighing?
Nothing.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for waiting.
You're a little late.
Take your time.
May I help you?
Yes.
Where is your wife?
I couldn't get through to her on the phone.
I see.
I couldn't get through to her on the phone on my part-time job.
It must be hard for you.
Did you quarrel with her again?
No, I didn't.
I've never quarreled with her.
I hope it's not an accident or sickness.
Excuse me.
Yes, I'm back.
Did you order something?
What did you order?
I ordered a napolitan noodle and orange juice.
Thank you for waiting.
I'll bring it right away.
I should have gone to find Yu at this time.
But I couldn't because I had a reservation.
I regretted it.
Yu.
Why didn't you come?
She's not here.
Yu.
Hey.
Are you there?
She's not here.
Let's take a bath.
Are you taking a bath?
Yu.
She's not here.
Where is she?
Why isn't she here?
Yu.
What do you mean?
Then my wife disappeared from my sight.
Yu.
I'm glad you're back.
I thought I'd never see you again.
I'm sorry.
Yu.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming back.
My wife came back after six months.
My dear.
She was beautiful.
I see.
Here you are.
Thank you.
She was beautiful.
She suddenly disappeared.
Are you OK?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'll get you some ice.
OK.
Yu.
Yu didn't talk to me for half a year.
I didn't ask her either.
Welcome.
Hello.
I'm glad you came back.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Why don't you work here?
I have a lot of things to do.
What do you mean?
Well.
I'd like a cappuccino.
Yes, please.
What's the matter?
Coffee?
Yes.
The usual?
I see.
I'll be waiting for you.
Please wait a moment.
OK.
It's been a while.
Thank you for coming back.
You're welcome.
I'll come back every day.
Thank you.
Yu.
Yu.?
What should I do?
Sorry, I'm late.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Okay.
What's this?
Yu.
A picture of Yu.
A picture that I don't know when it was taken.
And Yu is so much bigger than me.
A half-year-old man in the blank.
His wife is...
I didn't know it was like this.
I can't help but smile when I see you.
Ah.
I wish I could be like you.
Hmm
Mmm!
It's so good.
I can't stop eating.
I'm going to go to a sakura shop.
So, I'm going to go shopping.
It's so hot today.
What do you recommend?
I'll get this and this.
And coffee.
Hey.
What's up with your part-time job?
I can't reach you anymore.
I know.
I was wondering if I should tell you.
What is it?
I saw you and your wife together.
You two were holding a big backpack.
When did that happen?
I think it was six months ago.
6 months ago?
I was about to call her, but I just said it.
It was weird.
I'm going to take a look at the inside of the station.
The station building is a little different from other stations.
Can I help you, sir?
I'd like coffee, please.
I'm glad I met you.
Good morning.
Yu.
What?
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Sit down.
Where have you been for six months?
I don't know.
You were with Kanda, weren't you?
I see.
I'm sorry.
Why?
I was deceived.
I was deceived by Kanda.
I wanted to tell you many times.
Yu.
You are gone.
You are Kanda.
I'm sorry.
What?
You were with Kanda that day.
I'm sorry.
I understand.
I'll tell you everything.
That day.
You are late.
I'm sorry.
What's up?
Where is your wife?
She doesn't answer the phone.
I can't get a job.
I'm busy.
Did you quarrel with her again?
No.
I've never quarreled with her.
I hope it's not an accident.
I'm sorry.
I'm back.
Did you order something?
What did you order?
Napolitan and orange juice.
I'll bring it right away.
I'm sorry.
You are busy.
Kanda.
Are you sure?
Let's go.
Yuu and Kanda stayed in a love hotel until they ran out of money.
To be honest, they made fun of their part-time jobs.
I can't believe my wife and Kanda did that.
Kanda.
I'm sorry.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Hmmm
Well,
yeah,
yeah, yeah, yes,
yeah.
Oh,
oh,
yeah,
yeah
Oh oh
me
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Mammmmmmmmm
Mammmm...
Mammam....
Mammm
Mamm
morning
Maahh
Mahhh
Stop it green
I don't want to.
Show me your belly.
Show me more.
You have a lot of pimples.
I'll make it hot.
I'll make you feel more and more.
I feel good.
I can't believe it.
You are very strong.
I feel good.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh
Oh yeah yeah yeah
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah CB
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
.
Ah, it's
so
easy to
get
It's been a long time since I've had a baby, so I'm a little worried.
I'm worried about my baby's health.
I don't want my baby to get sick.
I want my baby to be healthy.
And then I came back.
I won't do it anymore.
Forgive me.
Please forgive me.
I'm sorry.
I won't do it anymore.
Forgive me.
I'm sorry.
I won't do it anymore.
Forgive me.
I'm sorry.
I had no choice but to believe my wife's words.
There's one thing my wife doesn't know.
It's about the picture she sent me.
I couldn't ask her about that picture.
I didn't even tell her.
I couldn't ask her if she put that big thing in it.
That big thing.
I'll have coffee and basil.
Could you tell me how to make salsa verde?
I'm listening.
He wants you to teach him how to make salsa verde.
Salsa verde.
I'll do it.
Basil, olive oil, garlic, and nutmeg.
It's the same as making genovese.
If you want to make it greener, you can add parsley.
I see.
Thank you.
I'll do it.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Are you tired?
Be careful.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Are you okay?
Don't leave me.
I believe in my future wife.
I don't look back.
I believe in the present.
Can I ask you a favor?
Sure.
Thank you.
Hello?
Are you at work?
Yes, I am.
I'm glad to hear that.
I can't beat you.
Excuse me.
Your uncle has been hospitalized.
Is he okay?
He's not feeling well.
Can you take him to the hospital?
Is it urgent?
I'll be back by dinner.
Can I go?
Lunch time is over.
You can go.
Thank you.
You're kind.
Excuse me.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Kanda-kun.
Don't do this.
Then, I should have refused.
Kanda-kun.
Let's not go home.
Don't go.
It's okay.
Kanda-kun.
Don't go.
Let's go to the bedroom.
Bedroom?
Hurry up.
Master is sleeping here.
So, let's stop.
I can't betray him anymore.
Don't go.
He is pretending to have sex with Master.
He is sleeping soundly.
He smells disgusting.
He is excited.
He is surprised.
Don't go.
Oh man.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Oh
Hmm
Yes
Ah
You're breathing with your mouth open.
That's how good it feels.
I want to go home.
Don't go home.
I don't want to go home.
It's amazing.
I love you.
I wanted to hug you.
Please put it in my mouth.
I want you to put it in my mouth.
I don't feel the taste of mustard.
I love you.
I want you to put it in my mouth.
I can feel it.
I don't want to.
I want you to put it in my mouth.
I can feel it.
I don't want you to put it in my mouth.
It's totally different.
It's different.
It's big.
It's in my mouth.
I'm scared.
I can't put it in my mouth.
I feel good.
I don't feel the taste of mustard.
I can't put it in my mouth.
I feel good.
It's in my mouth.
I can't put it in my mouth.
Raise your legs.
It's in my mouth.
I feel good.
Hey, why are you stopping me?
I want you to follow me more.
Follow me more.
It feels good.
Here?
Yes, there.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Hey, why are you stopping me?
Show me that you're in there.
Look.
It feels good.
Show me that you're in there.
Don't do that.
I'm afraid of you.
It's embarrassing.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
You have to do it yourself.
It's getting bigger.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I want you to follow me more.
I'm afraid of you.
It hurts.
I'm in there.
Don't do that.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
What is this?
Does it feel good?
It's hard.
It feels good.
I told you it was hard.
It's hard.
Do it more.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
Let me see.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Don't do that.
It hurts.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It's 3,000 yen.
Thank you.
Three months later.
My wife went out again.
Thank you for your viewing.