I'm not sure if it's a good thing or a bad thing, but I think it's a good thing.
It's time to get up.
Put the dough in a plastic bag and cover it with plastic wrap and let it rest in the refrigerator for 30 minutes.
After 30 minutes, take the dough out of the refrigerator and let it rest in the refrigerator for 30 minutes.
Hey.
You like it, don't you?
You'll go crazy if I touch you.
Oh, no.
You don't have time. Hurry up.
3 years after marriage.
I'm not dissatisfied with my married life, but I wasn't satisfied at night.
I don't have the confidence to deny it, but I want stimulation.
I have a strong desire for sex.
3 years after marriage.
A young man who lives next door.
I often see him on the veranda.
Maybe it's just my imagination, but I feel like he's looking at me.
I don't know why, but I can't help but look at him.
Tomomi, is the newspaper ready yet?
I'll bring it out now.
3 years after marriage.
Here you are.
Thank you.
By the way, I had a fight with a man next door the other day.
Really? Why?
When I was a kid, my parents got divorced and I lived with my grandmother.
But she passed away last year.
Since then, I've been living alone.
I live in a rubbish house and pay the rent.
My parents were angry.
I see.
I heard a complaint from the neighborhood.
They've been watching me for a long time.
So you should be careful, too.
Don't make any trouble.
Oh, no.
I have to go.
See you.
3 years after marriage.
She has been living with her grandmother.
But she passed away last year.
Since then, I've been living alone.
I live in a rubbish house and pay the rent.
They've been watching me for a long time.
That dangerous look.
If he drives me crazy...
I'm not sure if this is a good idea or a bad idea, but I think it's a good idea.
For your wife and children.
Thank you for calling.
I'm worried about something and I called.
What is it?
I'm in charge of fulfilling your wishes and requests for your wife and children,
Feel free to let me know if there's anything I can do for you.
Oh, I see.
But I'm fine, as I thought.
I understand.
If you feel like it, I'll be waiting for your call.
I'll be on my way.
Okay.
Oh, okay.
Hello, Mom?
What? What's the matter?
Please don't worry.
It's us, Mom.
I see.
Make sure you don't catch a cold.
It looks like someone's here.
I'll call you later.
Okay.
What is it?
This...
I put it in my mailbox by mistake.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
This happens sometimes, doesn't it?
That's right.
I've been to my boss's office before.
Is that so?
Um...
By the way, I have a favor to ask you.
The other day,
my laundry...
It's a handkerchief, but...
I caught a cold.
If you don't mind, could you take a look at it?
Is that so?
I'll go take a look.
I'm sorry.
Please wait.
I can't find it.
If you don't mind, could you check it yourself?
Is that okay?
Excuse me.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
I couldn't find it.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Um...
This...
Can you read it now?
What is it?
This.
Please read it.
Thank you very much.
There's a woman I can't talk to.
She lives next to me.
When our eyes meet sometimes,
You're the one who looks at me.
My heart is pounding.
I can't do it.
I just can't help it.
But...
She has a husband.
What should I do?
I have no choice but to ask her.
Please tell me.
This hot feeling.
What should I do?
Wife.
I'm in trouble.
Even if you ask me this question.
You're always hot.
You're looking at me, aren't you?
That's not true.
The thread on your shoulder.
You didn't even look back.
You were showing me your chest.
I can't hold it down.
My feelings for my wife.
With a seductive gaze.
I was slowly hiding my chest.
If it looked like that, I'm sorry.
My wife is lying to me.
That seductive gaze.
What is that seductive gaze?
I'm in that mood.
I'm in trouble.
Such a one-sided...
I'm sorry.
Can you leave?
I have something to do after this.
I don't have time.
Are you scared?
I...
I want my wife.
I want you.
I'm in trouble.
Can you leave?
He's finally here.
Will he come?
Will he leave?
My heart is about to stop.
No.
I can't do that.
Please leave.
I'll call the police.
He's finally here.
He's serious.
I'm going crazy.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
Let me go.
Stop it.
Don't touch me.
No more.
Stop it.
Mom...
It's hot.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Get away from me.
I'm sorry.
Open your mouth.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I can't stop it.
It feels good.
I'm getting used to it.
It's hard.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
I'll do it myself.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I don't know.
I've never had such a strong sex.
I'm going to be a bird.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
No, I'm just a little tired.
It's a change of season.
Be careful.
What about dinner?
I'm sorry.
I don't have anything ready.
I see.
I'll order some food.
I'll take a bath first.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'll do it.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Wake me up tomorrow.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Have you been waiting for me?
No, I haven't.
I see.
It's written on the river.
You want to do it with me.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Put your tongue out.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Tsukusao-san..
Tsukasao-san?
Tsukasao-san-
Say, Satori.
Tsukasao-san.
I can't.
Put me on my back.
wwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwww
fir-
haha
ha
aa
haa
wwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwww
gusu
gh
pw
aaa
aaaaa
a...
aa
a... AAA
a...
a a
Ow!
I can't see.
It's so difficult.
How far has his blood gone?
Oh no it's here...
How nice.
Rooftop
G motivates to keep going
I will not give up
I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'll do my best.
I am the leader of the dropout.
That's a tough one
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh, I lost cooking oil...
Oh!
I ran out of cooking oil so much.
Whoa!
No...
No!
Doctor said it's a masterclass the more you stop using it.
Take it easy Ryo.
The only thing we can do is to the injections.
We still haven't finished our surgery.
Not an easy work to be done.
It hurts
This person's neck is very solid
Don't say that.
I won't.
Don't do that.
No.
I won't.
Hey, Tommy.
Give me a cup of tea.
Hey.
I miss you.
I miss you, too.
Come back soon.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
Look at me.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Show me more.
Show me your waist.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
Can you see?
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Tomomi, where have you been?
I went to the garbage dump.
I talked to the person next to me.
Was he weird?
He wasn't that weird.
Really?
I'm hungry.
Wait a minute.
You can't forget the pleasure you once had.
That's what a woman's body is like.
It's hot.