I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to die if I don't do something about it.
It's great to take a four-day break and camp.
That's right. I'm so happy to be able to drink alcohol in nature like this.
Would you like some hot wine?
Oh, yes.
I made a free wine.
That's nice.
Try it.
Thank you.
Is it cinnamon?
That's right.
Oh, it has a faint scent of cinnamon.
I'm glad. I was worried about my mouth.
No, it's delicious.
I'm glad.
Don't they think camping is just about setting up a tent?
That's right.
They've been drinking all day.
I'm always busy at work, so I think it's a good day off.
You're too kind.
Really?
Yeah.
It's like being at home.
That's right.
I don't want you to think that way because you're good at making sweets and cooking.
I don't have a small sewing set.
I have it.
Really?
Look.
You're kidding, aren't you?
You're kidding.
I don't usually have it.
You usually have it.
There are kind people like you. That's why men go out with you.
Is that so?
You're late.
What?
Did you say something?
I didn't say anything.
Oh, I see.
Hey, bring me a camembert and a tomato.
Why don't you come and get it yourself?
Is this it?
Yes, it is.
Can I eat this?
Yes, you can.
I'll have chopsticks.
Okay.
You're so kind.
Really?
Isn't that normal?
No, it's not.
Hey, you're talking bad about me again, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
I'm a devil's ear.
This is delicious.
We're getting along well, aren't we?
No, we're not.
We always fight.
Let's drink this while eating.
Cheers.
It's easy to drink.
Right?
It's my first time drinking it.
Oh, right, Arata.
Yes?
I made a reservation for a open-air bath.
Oh, I see.
Shall we go in?
Let's go in together.
Okay.
Let's sit around there.
I'm going to go to the open-air bath.
Take your time.
I'm going.
The Kanda couple, who live in the same apartment, and us, the Kimizuka couple,
have a barbecue once a month on the roof of the apartment.
Also, the wife, Hinata, and the Kanda wife, Aina,
decided to scold us husbands.
Today, Kenta and I decided to take a break from camping,
and the two of us decided to go on a three-night, four-day camping trip.
It feels good.
It's a luxury to have an onsen at a camp.
Yes, it is.
Actually, I'm thinking of buying a Petromax this time.
What?
Aren't you going to be mad at me for buying such an expensive one?
It's okay.
I also bought a Banna camping car this time.
No way.
I'm going to buy it soon.
This is also a secret between Aina and me.
Hey, Mr. Kimizuka, let's buy it.
No, no.
I don't want to buy it quietly.
It's okay.
Hinata will be mad at me.
Because a camping car is a man's romance.
That's true.
Let's buy it.
No, but...
I'm looking forward to it.
I wonder if it will come soon.
Don't worry.
Let's buy it together.
I'm looking forward to it.
I wonder if it will come soon.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's good, isn't it?
It's good.
I wonder if the car will come soon.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Did you burp?
I don't know.
Me, too.
You're blushing.
What are you going to do next week?
What?
I have an appointment.
I see.
Where are you going?
I bought a big tent the other day.
That's why your tent is so big.
That's right.
I think I can sleep five or six people.
This is the third one.
Three?
I don't need this.
Three is a lot.
That's right.
What?
Are you talking bad about me again?
That's right.
Don't say that in front of me.
I have a lot of complaints.
About what?
About the tent.
The tent?
Yes.
It's the best.
It's not the best.
The design and the size are cool.
I don't think it makes sense if the inside of the tent is ugly.
Are you still angry that I bought a new tent?
That's right.
You apologized to me the other day.
Let's stop fighting.
We're having fun.
You're still angry.
I can't believe it.
I don't want to be next to him.
Let's drink next to KIMITSUKA.
I have a lot of complaints.
Let's go.
I can't believe it.
Let's stop.
Let's go to AINA.
Don't come here.
I won't go.
Let's go to AINA.
Let's calm down.
Let's sleep.
That's the worst.
I can't believe it.
Calm down.
You're the worst.
That's the worst.
I don't know what you mean.
Let's stop fighting.
Calm down.
I want to divorce him and remarry ARATA.
Let's do that.
I want to remarry HIKINOTA.
I want to remarry KENTA.
You can't do that.
You can't be with ARATA.
That's the worst.
I want to get rid of him.
He's annoying.
He's just saying what he wants to say.
I don't know what to do with them.
I can't help it.
KENTA, it's your fault.
It's your fault.
Calm down, AINA.
I don't like it.
Let's calm down.
No.
Do you think so?
I know what you mean.
Do you know what I mean?
Do you think so?
He's annoying.
It's his fault.
It was a terrible fight.
Are you okay?
KENTA still has a bomb.
What?
He bought a camping car with ARATA.
Are you kidding me?
I'm serious.
It would be terrible if he found out.
I don't know what to do.
You bought something, too.
No, I didn't.
Let's go to bed.
You're lying.
No, I'm serious.
Good night.
What's going on?
Are they KENTA and AINA?
They are middle school students.
What's going on?
You're a liar.
No, I'm not.
You're always lying.
You bought a camping car.
It's very convenient.
You can't use it.
I can.
What's wrong with you?
He bought a camping car without telling me.
It's okay.
It's not good.
You can use it.
No, I can't.
You can.
Don't say that. Let's have breakfast.
I can't have breakfast with him.
I can't eat breakfast with him.
What are you doing?
I'm going home.
But you bought a car.
I'll walk home.
Don't be ridiculous.
Go home.
I'll go home.
It takes 2 hours by car.
It's okay. I'll go home.
It takes a day to walk home.
I can walk. It's okay.
Go home.
Don't say that.
It's okay.
I can't go home.
I'll go home.
Bye.
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
It takes a day to walk home.
Go home.
It's a mountain.
Let's calm down.
It's hard to say.
I understand.
But I can't camp with him.
Me too.
I can't sleep in the tent with him.
Let's sleep together.
Is it okay?
What about me and Arata?
Kenta, let's camp with me.
It's a man's camp.
Let's camp with me and Arata.
Is it a solo camp?
Let's do it.
We can relax and enjoy ourselves.
Just you and me.
Let's do it.
It's okay.
Let's go.
I can do anything.
Do it alone.
Good luck.
Let's go.
Are you sure?
I don't mind.
I don't mind either.
This is the beginning of everything.
It looks delicious.
Great.
It's soft.
It must be delicious.
Can you cut it?
I'll cut it.
You are kind.
It's soft.
You are good.
Thank you.
Is the carrot okay?
It looks delicious.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
Can I eat first?
Thank you.
It's big.
It's delicious.
It's soft.
I haven't eaten such a soft meat for a long time.
You are good at seasoning.
It's delicious.
What are you baking?
I'm baking bacon.
Bacon?
Why are you laughing?
If you apologize, I can help you.
I don't apologize.
Let's stop fighting.
You are stubborn.
You two.
KENTA.
Let's drink as a man.
It's okay.
Don't say that.
Let's leave him alone.
Let's enjoy ourselves.
It's cold.
That's right.
It's delicious.
Who came up with this?
I found this recipe before I came here.
That's great.
This is a simple seasoning.
Salt and pepper.
It's hot.
I'm going to use chicken this time.
What's wrong?
I can't cook dinner with my husband alone.
Then I will...
We will fight again.
Hirata.
Can you take care of Aina?
Yes.
Please.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
He is doing it on his own.
No.
Let's eat before it gets cold.
Hirata.
Please sit down and wait.
I don't know what Aina will say.
You haven't eaten anything since noon.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I want to be kind like you.
What are you talking about?
Aina is kind enough.
You did it on your own.
Let's drink.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Please drink beer and wait.
Thank you.
You just grilled it.
I can't do anything.
I'll cook something better.
Please wait.
I'm sorry.
What are you going to do alone?
I'm going to camp alone.
Alone?
You can't cook?
I'll find a way.
Find a way?
You can do it on your own.
You can cook.
I can't do it on my own.
You can eat.
I'll season it.
I'm sorry.
No.
How do you feel?
Do you want to make up?
I can't.
I see.
Hinata.
What's up?
What are you doing?
I'm going to see Kenta.
What?
You can't do anything alone.
I'll go.
You can't fight again.
But I'll listen to Kenta.
You listen to Aina.
But...
It's a good opportunity to see each other again.
What's up?
I'm with Aina.
What?
Isn't it good?
It's a good opportunity to see each other again.
It's like a marriage exchange.
Yes.
We're going to see each other again.
I see.
You're both stubborn.
I'm sorry.
I'll cook.
Thank you.
What's up?
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
If you're worried, can we go back?
I can't apologize to you.
I see.
I won't force you.
I'll sleep in the tent.
Okay.
Good night.
Your food is delicious.
It's not true.
You're good at cooking.
Really?
I just reheated your food.
What?
I'll scold you today.
I'm sorry.
Can I drink this hot wine with you?
It warms me up.
I'm done.
Let's drink.
How do you feel?
It warms me up.
I'm glad.
This cinnamon tastes good.
The taste of the wine changes depending on the cinnamon.
I'm not good at cooking, but I'm glad you like it.
I'm glad you like this hot wine.
It's delicious.
Actually, I want to apologize for buying a camper van.
You don't have to apologize.
But I want you to understand.
If I had a child, it would be my dream to travel in a camper van with Aina.
You didn't tell Aina about it, did you?
No.
That's not good.
You're clumsy.
Did I drink too much?
You drank too much.
Do you still want to drink?
I'm fine.
I have to get up tomorrow.
I agree.
Do you want to take a bath tomorrow morning?
You drink a lot.
Yes.
I'm going to sleep here.
Please sleep in the tent.
If you catch a cold, Aina will be angry.
I see.
I don't care.
That's where Aina gets angry.
I see.
I'm going to sleep here.
Please sleep in the tent.
I can't do that.
What should I do?
Do you want to sleep together?
What?
Well...
The tent is big.
Yes.
I'll do the laundry tomorrow.
Let's do that.
You can do it when you get up early in the morning.
Yes.
Let's go to bed.
Be careful.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's cold.
Please use this.
But...
Please.
I can't.
Kenta, please use it.
I'm going to sleep.
I can't.
Please use it.
I'm going to sleep.
Hirata.
Please use this.
But...
I'm going to sleep.
Please use it.
But...
I'm fine.
Don't hesitate.
You'll catch a cold.
I'm fine.
Please use it.
Hirata.
Please.
Please use it.
I'm fine.
I'm not cold.
Hirata.
I'm fine.
Aino.
What's wrong?
I wish I could be an adult like you.
You're an adult.
Thank you, Arata.
What is it?
Can I hug you?
Can I hug your back?
No.
I want to cling to something when I'm lonely.
But it's not me.
It's your back.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I was about to make a mistake.
I shouldn't have slept with my neighbor's wife in this small tent.
But I could tell you that.
I can't open the latch.
What do you do when you sleep with Aina?
In that case,
I bring two pillows.
Then we can sleep together.
It's warm, isn't it?
I think so.
Let's sleep like this.
It's hard to catch a cold alone.
You're right.
It's hard to catch a cold.
Let's sleep.
Good night.
Good morning.
I'm sorry I overslept.
No problem.
It's cold, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It's cold in the middle of the mountain.
Did you make breakfast?
Yes, I did.
I'm sorry I made everything.
No problem.
It looks delicious.
Let's eat.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you for yesterday.
Thank you for everything.
For what?
When you hugged me,
I was about to betray you.
What are you talking about?
Everyone is like that when they're anxious.
You're kind, aren't you?
She seems to be sleeping.
I think so.
I think I drank too much.
I drank too much with her.
I think so, too.
I'm going to talk to her.
That's good.
Let's eat.
Thank you for everything.
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
Yes, it is.
I thought it might be a little seasoned.
No, it's just right.
Is it good?
Yes.
I'm glad.
It's very delicious.
Thank you.
Hey.
Kenta.
I'm not Aina.
Hey.
Kenta.
Are you awake?
I'm sorry.
You touched me a lot.
Good morning.
You look like this all of a sudden.
I'm sorry.
Your bathrobe is still warm.
Your bathrobe is warm, so it's stuck.
I'm sorry.
That's not a bathrobe.
What?
Actually, this is...
Hey.
Why are you taking it off?
I don't know.
It was hot, so I took it off.
Hurry up and take it off.
I'm sorry.
Did you take it off?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Maybe it's because it was hot.
Let's keep this a secret.
I'll keep it a secret, too.
Kenta.
Are you listening?
I'll keep it a secret, too.
Kenta, please be quiet.
It's late.
I'm sorry.
I'll keep it a secret.
Did you keep it a secret?
I did.
I'm sorry.
I'll keep it a secret.
It's your fault.
I'm sorry.
Please take it off.
I can't bear it.
I'll keep it a secret.
Stop it.
You have beautiful teeth.
I can't bear it.
Stop it.
Don't you think it's bad for you?
You have beautiful teeth.
No, I don't.
It's not good for you.
You have beautiful teeth.
I can't bear it.
Stop it.
Why are you trying so hard?
You're so excited.
No, I'm not.
I don't know.
Stop it.
You feel good, don't you?
No, I don't.
I don't feel good.
Why are you so excited?
You're so excited.
No, I'm not.
I can't bear it.
Where are you going?
I'll give you more.
Let me go.
Stop it.
I can't bear it.
You're so stiff.
You can't bear it.
No, I can't.
Stop it.
You can't bear it.
Let me go.
I can't bear it.
You can't bear it.
Stop it.
I can't bear it.
You're so stiff.
You're so excited.
No, I'm not.
It's not my fault.
You're so weak.
Stop it.
I can't bear it.
You're so beautiful.
Why did you do that?
Why did I do that?
You were talking about your dream.
I had no choice.
I can't bear it.
Stop it.
You're so excited.
It's your fault.
Let me go.
Let's stop it.
I'll keep it a secret.
I can't bear it.
You're so excited.
Stop it.
I can't bear it.
Let's stop it.
I'll keep it a secret.
I can't bear it.
Stop it.
You're so stiff.
Please sit down.
I can't bear it.
You don't have to say that.
Stop it.
I can't bear it.
Don't take it off.
Stop it.
I can't bear it.
Do you know what you're doing?
I know.
I can't bear it.
You're doing something wrong.
Let's stop it.
You're so excited.
I can't bear it.
Kiku!
I can't take it anymore.
No!
No, you can't.
I can't take it anymore.
Let me go.
No!
It feels so good.
How do you feel?
Ai-chan.
I told you not to do it.
I know how you feel.
Ai-chan.
Is it here?
Let me go.
It feels so good.
I can't take it anymore.
I told you not to do it.
You're so beautiful.
I can't take it anymore.
Ai-chan.
You can't do it.
It feels so good.
Ai-chan.
Ai-kun.
You won't find out if I give you such a big one.
It feels so good.
Ai-kun.
You're so good at it.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
It's okay.
Ai-kun.
Ai-chan.
Please move slowly.
I can't stop yet.
Ai-chan.
Ai-kun.
It feels good.
Stop it.
Ai-kun.
I'm holding you.
I can't stop.
Nii-chan.
Matsuri-chan.
Ai-kun.
I can't stop.
Ai-chan.
Ai-kun.
It hurts.
What have I done?
Let's get up.
I can't get up.
I'm sorry.
Please stop.
I told you I can't get up.
I can't get up.
It's almost lunch time.
You're late for breakfast.
Did you eat too much?
I drank a lot.
I'm fine now.
How can you be so normal?
Don't you feel bad for Aina-san?
I do.
You talked about her so much yesterday.
Yes.
Please take care of Aina-san more.
Hinata-san, you're betraying her, aren't you?
I'm not betraying her.
If you feel that way, it means you're betraying her.
You're the worst.
We're both the worst.
I don't want to be found out.
You don't want to be found out?
That's not good.
Do you want to be found out?
I'm fine now.
I'm going home.
Don't follow me.
Hinata-san.
Hinata-san, listen to me.
Don't follow me.
I understand how Aina-san feels.
Hinata-san.
Don't go home.
Don't bother me.
I can't do this anymore.
I don't want to go home.
Aina-san, what are you going to do?
Let me go.
I can't do this anymore.
Wait.
Hinata-san.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
I can't do this anymore.
Why?
Hinata-san.
I can't do this anymore.
Please close the door.
What should I do?
Do as I say.
I can't do this anymore.
Please lick me.
Lick me.
I can't do this anymore.
Hurry up.
Hinata-san.
Do you want to be found out?
Lick me.
I can't do this anymore.
Hinata-san.
More.
Do more.
I can't do this anymore.
It feels so good.
You're cute.
It was a mischief.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it's hot.
I like this coffee.
Me, too.
Let me try.
Good idea.
Let's do it.
You two look like you just had dinner.
Yeah.
Oh, let's go to the open-air bath together.
Sounds good. We have a swimsuit.
Yes.
I'll go get it.
Thank you.
I can't believe I'm doing this again.
Hinata.
What should I do?
I need to talk to you.
You can come in.
Why?
Good morning, Mr. Kento.
Good morning.
I was just cleaning up.
Aina said we should go to the open-air bath together.
Sounds good.
Let's go.
What's wrong, Hinata?
I have a sore throat.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. I'll be right there.
Okay.
I'll be there when I'm ready.
Go ahead.
Okay.
Why didn't you say no?
I can't say no.
I don't have a face to see Aina.
You can't see her with that face.
You have to wipe it off.
Okay.
I'm glad you didn't find out.
I thought I smelled something weird in the tent.
I didn't know I was doing this.
I'm glad you came to the camp and went to the hot spring.
I know.
It's a nice house.
Mr. Arata helps me out a lot.
He's like a brother to me.
But he doesn't say anything to me.
I feel relieved.
What do you mean?
That's why I didn't go to the camp yesterday.
You buy a lot of things, don't you?
No, I don't.
We buy a lot of things to have fun.
Do you really want to change the water?
No, I don't.
It's not like that.
It's a joke.
Don't make fun of me.
Did you bother Hinata?
No, I didn't.
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
I'm not like you.
What's wrong?
You're angry again.
It's nothing.
You should fix it.
You, too.
You're angry again.
It's not your fault.
What's wrong?
Yesterday...
Let's stop it.
You buy a lot of things.
I buy things to have fun.
Let's stop it.
Let's have fun.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What do you want to do tonight?
Do you want to eat together?
Sounds good.
How about you, Hinata?
I...
Why?
Let's eat separately until tomorrow.
What?
What's wrong?
Don't you want to eat together?
I think we should eat separately.
I think Hinata thinks so.
I see.
I think so.
You don't understand, do you?
I understand.
Matsu will get angry soon.
That's why they fight.
I'm going to bed.
I'll help you.
Wait.
You can take your time.
Please sit down.
Take your time.
Okay.
Why don't you eat together?
I can't eat because I did that yesterday.
Why don't you sleep with me tonight?
I can't.
We're husband and wife.
Isn't it good?
I can't.
I felt it yesterday.
Please remember yesterday.
You seemed to be in a good mood.
Don't do that.
I can't.
Stop it, Hinata.
I'm sorry for yesterday.
It's just for today.
I'm your neighbor.
I'm weak.
It's just for today.
Don't do that.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't.
You can't.
Stop it.
You'll get sick.
I can't.
Please drink a lot.
Stop it.
It's very hot inside.
It's as tight as it was yesterday.
Like this.
I can't.
You can't.
You'll get sick.
I can't.
Why can't you?
You'll get sick.
I can't.
You'll get sick tomorrow.
It's just for today.
We'll be neighbors tomorrow.
I know.
I can't.
Someone will be here.
Just relax.
You're so selfish.
It's very suffocating.
Feels very good.
What should I do?
It's so hot
I'm scared
If you do this, you'll be exposed
I don't want to
Don't do it
What should I do?
Does it feel good?
It feels good
Please feel good
Does it feel good?
It's so hot
It hurts
It feels good
Don't say that
It hurts
I want a hot spring
It's so hot
Is it okay to do this?
It's okay
Hirata
What's wrong?
I'm here to borrow a skeleton
Okay
Here
Where's Aina?
She went shopping by car
I see
What's wrong?
Where did you sleep with Aina?
We slept together in the tent
You're right
There's nothing going on
You're the same
Of course
You're right
It's strange
There's not a single couple
You're right
Well
Hirata
What's wrong?
Come here
Wait
Now?
Hurry
What's wrong?
I was having an affair
I got carried away
Aina, are you okay?
I'm okay
Hirata
Don't do it today
Don't do it here
Don't do it
You'll break it
Please don't do it today
Why?
Hirata
Don't do it
Not today
Why?
What are you doing?
Don't do it
Wait
Hirata
You
Don't do it
Why?
What's wrong?
Don't do it
Hirata, are you okay?
Hirata
You said you didn't want to do it
You were so sleepy
Hirata
You
I'll be waiting for you tomorrow
Okay
I should have noticed my wife earlier
I'm home
I'm sorry I'm late
I borrowed your bed
I thought you wouldn't come back
Did you see your husband?
No
Did you tell him about this morning?
Then
We're even now
Hirata
That's all for today
Yes
Can I talk to him tomorrow?
You can
Thank you
I thought I could make a mistake with you
But I can't win with you
Wait
I'm kidding
Good night
Hirata
Can we kiss like this?
We're just neighbors
We're so close
We can meet anytime
I'm nervous
I don't want to kiss you
I don't want to
Do you always put gold in your clothes?
You're wearing it
Hirata
I'm so nervous
Please give me a hug
I'm going
Good morning
Did you sleep well?
Yes, I did
I'm glad
You look refreshed
Yes
I made a mistake
I'm sorry for being selfish
Don't worry
Please make up
Yes
She's sleeping
Yes, I was the first one
Do you want to wake her up?
No, let her sleep
Yes
Thank you
Can you cut this tomato?
Yes
This tomato is fresh
Is it?
It looks good
You know it
Yes
Do you like tomatoes?
Yes, I do
Lycopene is good for you
Lycopene?
Yes
It's rich in potassium
Do you know what potassium is?
Potassium?
Yes, it's good for salinity
We had sex in the morning
But we haven't had enough
I want to do more
Kenta
I'm not the kind of person to do this
I want to do more
I can't stop doing this
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Ah ah ah ah ha
Crisken...
I love you.
I feel sick.
It's so slippery.
Look at her licking her tongue.
I'm embarrassed.
Look at her more.
Meat!
It's so hard.
It's so hard?
Why are you wearing this?
I don't want to wear this.
I'm getting more and more excited.
It's so hard.
It's so scary.
It feels so good.
I'm going to fall asleep.
It's my first time playing this game.
It's over.
No!
I'm embarrassed.
Don't look at me.
I'm sorry.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's so hard.
It feels so good.
What should I do?
I can't dance anymore.
You don't have to dance.
You'll get stuck in my mouth a lot.
I don't want to.
My mouth is hurting.
It's not okay!
Ow!
Hour..
I love you.
I love you, too.
SUBS BY JEMA inferno
SUB BY JEMA inferno
SUB by JEMA inferno
SUB BY JEMA forever
Ah...
Mm...
I'm dying...
I can't breathe...
Ah...
Does it feel better now?
Yes, it feels so much better.
Ah...
Ahh...
Ah, I'm going to be caught again!
Ah!
I'm going!
This is beautiful!
Ah!
Ah, it feels so good!
It feels good?
It feels so good!
Stop it!
How much do you want me to do?
Let me go!
Say it properly!
It hurts!
It's running away!
It's moving!
Keep going!
That movement is amazing
It's amazing!
Keep going!
Please!
I want you to keep going
I won't let you go
It's amazing!
Keep going!
It hurts!
I'm tired
I know you can't do it
It feels good
It's amazing!
I love it!
It's running away
It hurts!
It feels good
It's amazing!
I'm full of energy
It's coming to me
It's coming to you
It's dangerous
It's coming to me
It hurts!
I'm full of energy
It's amazing!
Keep going!
It hurts!
I'm full of energy
It feels good
It's coming to me
It hurts!
We did it
It looks delicious
Thank you for helping me
I'm going to the bathroom
Okay
Hello
You shouldn't do that
What do you mean?
There was a problem
You were being rude
We were?
Yes, you were so rude
You have to change everything
What are you going to do?
I was in the hot spring until the end
Hinata and Kenta
What are you talking about?
Are you listening?
I heard you were being noisy
There's a customer
I'm in trouble
Are you listening?
I'm going to pay for this
I'm going to make sure
You pay me back
Are you listening?
I'm going to make sure
Customer
Wait!
Customer!
You're here again
Are you going to pay me back?
Yes
Hida
The customer was so rude
I'm sorry.
I'll never forget this.
Do you clean your husband's head like this?
No, I don't.
You don't?
It's a different size, isn't it?
To the point where your husband can't reach it.
I can reach it.
I'm sorry.
With such a big thing,
Hinata...
Even now, I want to hold Aina-san and take revenge.
But,
seeing that difference,
I couldn't move.
I'm sorry.
Let's meet again.
Of course.
Thank you for watching.