It is delicious.
How are you, Mr. Tomo, and how are you doing lately?
It is fine.
Or golf too?
I love golf, but I haven’t been there lately.
Is it yes?
Be busy.
I heard recently that the car was broken.
Okay the car.
A very fun car.
A fun car.
It’s a normal suit, but if you can have a child, you can’t use that car.
I hope to do something fun for now.
Training is good, so you can do a lot of things right now.
Travel or travel abroad with a car.
Travel abroad, even at home.
The couple of Kōta and I, who live in the same apartment, have been the annual occasion to have a drinking party in each other’s apartment once in a while.
I love drinking, and my wife, Shaka, always drink this way.
Today, we and my husband invited us home to serve the hand cooking and wine of our wife’s number.
Don’t be too hard, Mr. Cage.
Yes, because it is a holiday.
No, but I’ll stay tomorrow.
So, I’ll get you.
I drink from the wife of Kiki.
Yes to.
How about this wine?
Okay, can you please?
and continuously.
Thank you, I am more alcoholic than you.
Is it true?
I will eat.
So sorry to.
You drink too much, right?
A doctor is.
The moon, you too.
When is the vacation?
Be careful, really
What is.
I cannot stop.
Just one word.
But it really tastes so good.
Where to buy?
Yes, in this apartment.
He is a good guy.
It is very cheap, this.
No so is.
Because of Arrow.
I am very happy.
Because it is not so.
Thanks always.
Totally
Tastefully
Oh very delicious.
Eat and eat.
I will eat.
Mr. Taro has not drank.
Sorry to
It was here.
Wait a little.
Please please.
What is it.
Oh yeah
This is delicious too.
Drinking too much, really.
Oh well well.
Why Why?
Okay is.
There is only a delicious time.
What is wrong with taste?
It tastes good.
So very tasty.
Sorry to.
Oh happy
It tastes good, this is.
Tastefully
Eat it.
Really happy
Okay okay okay.
Okay please wait a little.
The cheese is broken.
Yes to Yes.
It was done.
Now, Tarot is not too much.
No no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
Do it well now.
Is it so good? no.
Yes to Yes.
Another toast.
well is.
Sorry, I forgot to replace the tower.
Thanks to
Sorry, but my husband always got so bad.
Okay, because I can’t deal with him.
Is it yes?
Both of you are drinking for fun.
Yes is it.
I did it on Wednesday at the Spectrum.
I did that.
I do not remember.
It is only one week.
A week is great.
Go home
Go home to.
Have you not drank too much?
Not that so.
It was just good.
What did you say, he was so excited.
What do you care about talking about?
I care but.
Is it time to leave it?
Yes, it is not good yet.
Yes, there is still wine.
But
Both of you drink too much.
No, the story of the man is funny.
Oh and oh, oh and oh.
You just told me a funny story here.
What were you talking about?
of old television.
and then is
That is
No, it is pretty funny, right?
I was surprised.
It can be done for old.
I can’t definitely do it now.
Please tell me.
I used to do water in the castle.
A couple exchanges for a week.
A couple exchanges their spouses.
exchanging a partner.
Not so great?
There are many combinations.
Because they are different couples.
It was like being a stubborn and a spouse of Zebola.
At first it was a beetle.
It is a beetle.
A week, as time passes.
It is constantly causing chemical reactions.
It is awesome.
Marion drinks, and that is.
When the wine is finished.
Let me open it.
Let me do.
I had a fun conversation now.
really
There is a further one, so right.
The next?
Have you ever seen a good show?
No, I am not there.
There are such shows now, too.
Surely not able.
But I think that something like that seems fun too.
It is an iPhone, I think.
What did you think?
I’m just talking about it, but I’m just going to exchange a couple for a week.
Well, I’m not a case, but there’s a time when a stubborn father and Zoppa’s wife live together.
The first two are so uncomfortable, so it doesn’t seem like we’re together.
But for a week, we will get together and get a little bit better.
No, I think it’s a TV show.
You may be sure that it is important.
But I think we will be friends with each other.
The other couple are getting close together.
It will be so, right?
Will the couple get together?
Yes, I think it is a good thing.
It seems so.
Because we live with different people.
I mean, people know their partner.
Not great?
I think it won’t work so well.
I think I will go.
I think so too.
is right?
What do you think, Mr. Kaz?
Unknown people live together, but it doesn’t work.
Instead, it means that we know each other’s goodness by doing it.
Not so, I must.
I think it’s good to know that we can exchange each other.
No, it’t be so.
Because it is a week time period.
Keep away and you know.
This is a year or two, but in a week.
You know in a week?
If it is important, you know.
I thought you knew.
You say it is a thousand years old.
You always have, you never change.
There is, on the moon.
I haven’t heard of thankfulness ever.
I say, no, but I don’t do that.
Okay, so do you try it with us?
Oh yeah?
How to do?
You can exchange them with each other, right?
You are not in the shadow? said he.
I look funny!
It is.
It is not funny, so is it.
No, I hope you try it, it would be fun.
No, no, I think it’s better to stop.
Okay, I have decided
Try three weeks next week.
Okay is not?
No, no, no yes
Okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
Okay is not?
What are you saying?
But yes, it is fun.
Enjoyed
I think it will change a lot of values.
You are a nice one.
Certainly
Okay is.
Really okay.
This was the beginning of all.
I have to say this.
Are you three days a week?
Three days.
No, it is not good.
No to
No to?
Do you really do?
It was decided today.
It was decided.
You and your partner decided to support?
What is it? are you dissatisfied?
You are determined to be dissatisfied.
If so, I should have said so at the time.
It is 203 days.
I hope you can recognize the couple again.
That is why I don’t want to verify.
If you are worried, stop immediately.
It’s different from camp, because we’re together.
No matter what happens, I don’t know.
It is OK.
Good night.
No matter what happens, I don’t know.
Okay okay okay.
Then came the time for the couple to exchange.
Sorry, let me wait.
They are all together.
Yes is.
So, we exchanged for Sunday afternoon.
Yes is
My eyes are not hidden.
That is my speech.
If you hate it, come back immediately.
Soon it will change.
Yes is
Why the adults?
If you hate, I will go back.
Don’t show me a shame.
You are
Then, change until Sunday afternoon again.
No then.
Good luck to.
You really do.
Sorry, but I forced you.
No, I am forced too, sorry.
I don’t want to tell you this one.
No, our too.
Slow down like your own home.
Can you do.
Yes is it.
Let me put tea in.
Thanks to.
That was okay.
entered the bedroom.
It is OK.
Because they decided.
Yes is it.
Sorry to sorry.
Tastefully
Is it true?
Really delicious.
He says he has a strong taste.
Just good for me.
well was
Oh, and drink, what do you do?
Will you go with meal?
Okay is it?
Do you do it first?
Please Please Please Please
Thanks to.
So sorry to.
Yes is
Then next is.
Okay okay?
Thanks to.
Let’s try toast.
Toast to
Tastefully
It is delicious.
The highest
Because our one is so small.
You always have to use sauce.
Is it yes?
But that’s because Taro is a drunk.
Is Shiki with you?
And yes, it is.
How is it?
It is very delicious.
I often say that our taste is poor.
Not so, it works very well.
Is it true?
It comes from the summer tofu, so it tastes so strong.
Yes is it.
So this food is so delicious.
Good was
This snack is also very delicious.
Please eat more.
Yes is
The chopsticks don’t stop.
I am pleased.
Please listen to me.
He is not a man, he is not a man.
Is it continuous?
OK, women are like women.
Is it yes?
The house is very sluggish and speaks a lot.
I want to say hold fast.
Cody, you are talking about Momo.
is
More than that.
I hope I can work like Mr. Kashi.
I really don’t think I want to eat dinner with you.
Oh, I don’t want to eat dinner all the time.
Can you give them a little bit?
to install?
No to no.
What are you doing?
Yes, is it okay?
I am drunk, but I’ll send you a picture.
No, is it a bad guy?
Yes, see
It’s too big, so I’ll take a normal photo.
But you can’t take a lot more pictures.
Yes but
Look right here.
Yes, well okay
No to
Oh yeah
No, I will not film it.
Are you okay?
by
This will go well.
Really?
Yes
Yes, but a little longer.
No, it is difficult.
No, no, is it better to be close to someone?
To make you jealous.
No No No No No No
Please take your shoulder, look.
No, no, it is not good.
No, please do that.
Can not do?
Not that I cannot.
So please, please see.
No, you definitely care about this, right?
We exchanged the couple.
Yes but
Yes
Yes, so is
No longer enough.
No No No No No No
Not a bit too hard.
It is okay.
Oh yeah yeah.
You have to show me where you drink.
Yes is.
Thanks to.
Stand up and drink.
Yeee
Please stick more.
See also OK.
Very good, very happy.
I have no eyes, a little.
So, will you send me a mail?
Do you really send it?
Which photos are you prefer?
This is?
No, I just shut my eyes.
Oh, then then
Yes
Dinner is
Was it delicious?
Good to be.
I will do a little wash.
Okay okay.
No, I made the food.
Oh but?
No, it is in hand.
Does Kenji always do dishes?
Yes, only in the morning and evening.
I used the kitchen myself and it was okay.
Oh yeah yeah
But I’m angry at this in the summer, again.
It is email.
From whom is it?
Since the summer.
Look at this.
The couple are having fun drinking.
What, this is really.
I am okay, healed this way.
Mr Cate is.
No, I am okay though.
Sorry, but the shark is going well.
No is
Oh, I have eaten it.
Is Kate angry?
I am not angry, this is.
I am hungry.
Wouldn’t you rather be angry?
Okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
So it is okay.
You have no alcohol, right?
Sorry to
See also
We clean up and drink afterwards.
Do you want to drink?
So I will prepare.
Thanks to.
I will just finish this minute.
Please please.
You’t wear that inside.
and no.
Oh, you are worried about something?
No, that is so.
Will you change your relationship with him from now on?
is okay.
I forced it.
You are not doing it, right?
I did not force you.
I pulled the cloth on the seat.
Good night to you.
What is that picture really?
It is true.
What is it.
Is it that you are jealous?
I am not jealous.
Do not do it?
I do not do.
Is it true?
I was a little bit jealous, I thought.
So that.
Yes is it.
It is totally provocative.
Are you jealous of the local?
Not at all, at all.
Really?
It is the evil of Shiva.
Sorry, but really something.
Shikoku is cute.
No no, that is it.
It is another 1 1⁄2 hour.
It was so fun, I drank too much.
What do you do? drink again?
It is OK.
I also agree.
Will I go to the bath tomorrow morning?
I drank a lot.
Oh yeah yeah
Yes is.
I sleep here.
Please use the bedroom.
No, I cannot
What if you say this in the summer?
But
No, do it so.
I cannot sleep in the couple’s bedroom.
Yes, what about this?
What is?
Put the clothes here and let us sleep together.
Oh is?
I want to send you pictures of this, so I want to be jealous.
Did you have that picture, you know?
Is it not certain?
You can also find a place to sleep, right?
Take two pairs of clothes and sleep here.
Is it really okay?
Okay is.
If I could show you that picture.
Do you do?
Yes is
Just drink this, and go out.
Yes is.
Send me a photo?
Oh yeah
Let us stop that.
Should I stop?
Yes is it.
Japanese wine is really good.
Looks to sleep well.
Sorry to.
Do you sleep?
Yes to.
You have drank too much.
Yes is it.
I have not drunk so much for a long time.
It was fun.
I was fun too.
Do you really not regret it? sleep here with us
Cate, you are not doing anything, right?
of course
Good night to you.
Casey
Good morning.
Something has become like this once.
Yes is.
Sorry to
Can I get away now?
I am hitting something.
Sorry to
Can I get you away sooner?
Yes is
Let us keep this secret.
Yes, that is
Can I borrow a bathroom?
Yes is
I will go in the bath.
Sorry I don’t have a towel.
Sorry to sorry.
by S.
Sorry to
I don’t want to look at it, I just want to give you a towel.
I know.
What is that dress?
No replacement pants.
Please enter yesterday.
Kenny, I have no new pants.
Wait in the dressing room.
Yes
No to
Voodoo
Oh yeah yeah yeah
N is n
by BoB
I can no longer endure.
Mr is not.
I let this.
Do not tell me about doing something.
Do not stop.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
You are watching my suffering.
not is
No to
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Crying by Pieter.
I have loved ones.
will take care of.
You and you.
It was warm,
He had a warm skin.
You and you.
You are so dumb in.
Full of stomach.
Oh oh oh oh
Do not stop.
Not together.
I am going to go.
He is crying.
I do not want to cry.
I say to finger.
He was out of face.
Those things.
No, not, I can’t get that big.
What are you saying? you are in.
I am in the manon.
by
immediately
from where?
More more
What to do.
Go on, such a beautiful boy.
Come on, be careful.
No to
Oh yeah
Oh yeah yeah
No to
Do not do that.
Doctor, please touch us.
Please touch me.
by Rush
and AR
No to
Oh is
Drink more.
No to
Oh is
I know that people who do not do this do.
If the signature is broken, it will be broken.
Because of the signature, here.
Very very hard.
Oh is
Very nice is.
It is cute.
I want more.
No to
Oh yeah
Hahahahahah
No to
Yes
by
No to
About Gunn.
I say.
Oh, you can hear it next door.
Oh, oh sorry for that.
No, no and no.
No to no.
A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A
It feels too much.
I feel good.
What did you do.
Sorry, let’s go
No, he was out of the seat.
I always have that in Shikoku.
Oh is?
Yes, nothing is anything.
I took such pictures yesterday and did too much.
Well, I think maybe it’s okay.
Is it so?
is okay.
Oh yeah yeah.
I forgot to shave at home.
I will take it later.
It must be your own shaving.
But the skin is weak.
Very hard is.
I have a lot of drinks, but I always drink.
I always said it was delicious.
really
It is so much like that.
It is delicious, right?
Really
Sorry, please tell me something.
somehow got it.
It happened to that.
Do you not think that it is wrong for Mr. Shay?
But
And also Aida.
I think Mr. Taro is betraying you.
Oh yeah
What is
If I feel so.
I am with you betraying.
Do not say such unreasonable things.
Who should have come.
I brought out.
Shut up and forget.
Wait a little.
Why Why?
Because they are now storing it.
Oh, and so
You have a setup.
I will take.
Are you angry about yesterday’s photos?
You are not angry.
Wait a little.
Yes
Yes, this
thanks to
What happened?
Cage, I wonder what you are doing.
It seems he is still sleeping.
If you don’t like it, you can stop.
Why is?
Because I am in the relationship with your brother.
OK is OK.
I know, thank you
Where did you go? – Where did you go?
It was Mr. Tarot.
Why have you not come yet?
No timing is.
Please come quickly.
Yes is
Can I shave?
Oh yes yes
Thanks to
She was shaved.
well was
What are you looking at?
Sorry to
Tarot is also concerned.
When I took home.
My wife’s expectations were strange.
Do you think something happened?
No is
I mean, I care about your wife.
Do not think it is good.
He also about me.
Maybe you care.
Yes is.
Not so is.
No No No No No No
What do you say.
I mean I absolutely care.
Yes to.
Which channel
Sorry to
I have no time.
I can only make this.
No to
I am also responsible.
Going out at noon.
Yes is
I hope he will come back before evening.
What happened?
No, no no no no no no no no.
I want to contact you again with Aida.
No to
Rushed
Elsa is
Mr Kick
What to do, Moon?
Just now only.
Just now please.
Not in fact.
cannot
You are
Their own
You will not regret being dropped.
I hope it is better now.
I am hungry.
I am not someone who does this.
I am.
No to
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
by
There was only one man, a little boy, who was in.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Can I go with my mouth?
I want to go with my mouth.
well well well well.
Oh go go
What to do.
Only today
Only today.
What happened to you?
Are you worried?
If you are so worried.
What if I go?
But
I am now in my husband’s office.
There is no.
It really violates the rules.
If you face that.
This will worry.
What if you go?
So I’ll go shopping, too.
thanks
Is it going well there?
Oh yes yes
I am worried about the shit.
No so for that.
He went to the pharmacy, right?
Yes is
So, slowly, I’ll go shopping.
to go up?
How are you doing it? do you do it well?
Yes to.
Until tomorrow afternoon.
Yes is.
What happened?
Yes, yes, nothing is anything.
Yes to.
Where did you sleep?
The mountain garden is in the room.
larger than ours.
Yes is
You too, right?
You slept apart, right?
Not of course.
Yes is it.
Yes
It is a sign.
I did not do a couple.
To be alive.
Yes is
Mr Kash
What happened?
Why Why?
Stop today.
Kate is coming back too.
It is OK.
No today.
Sorry to
involved in the exchange.
I should have noticed my wife’s disorder as soon as possible.
I met with Tarot.
Yes is it.
Did you have sex with Taro?
It is delicious.
Good to be.
Would you sleep in your bedroom all day?
cannot be
They are a couple until today.
Tomorrow, you are just a neighbor.
Just today, so please.
When it’s over, I won’t see you like this anymore.
Do you not think that you can do that too?
The little
I understand.
Is Mr. Sharon still worried?
No, I am not worried.
Really?
Have you slept?
Yes is
Really only today.
If it is tomorrow.
Just not to be.
Oh yeah yeah yeah!
It feels good.
Put it in.
Oh yeah
by
by Toni
by Tony
Oh is
No to
Yes
can
Such a kiss.
Donna can’t do it.
No to
Because only now.
Feels good?
Very good feeling.
Oh, so good feeling.
But still farewell.
Have you ever licked like this?
Take the day walk with your head.
Yes
Try it in.
I put in.
Put it in.
I saw it standing.
Oh yeah
Please come here.
Great is
Oh yeah
The voice of the family grew.
The voice of the family is small.
Do not listen to the family’s voice.
The voice of the family grew.
The family’s voice is a little deep.
Oh is
and
by REN
No is
It is not crazy.
Is it??? to
Oh is
and
by REN
No is
Is it??? to
Oh yeah yeah yeah
With Mr Taro.
Check it
Which
Which one feels good.
It feels good for the syllable.
Totally different
Nothing is.
Feel badly
It is completely different.
It feels good at cold.
Really feel good.
It really felt good.
I too
You said great.
Yes
Mr. Taro is not so good.
I like you, you don’t feel so good.
really is?
Can you?
of course
I want more.
I too
Good morning.
You have coffee.
Please go
Have you slept well?
Oh, I slept well.
well was
I hope you’ll be as good as you are on TV.
can be.
Like the TV.
Happiness did not wake up.
and flogged.
I was so tired behind.
The first time
Yes is
meet again
of course
What are you doing.
Why is it.
Have had breakfast.
What happened?
The Gymnastics.
Was there something?
Nothing is anything.
say nothing.
So that
Is it okay?
My wife from then.
Hide from me.
With my neighbor’s husband.