My name is Tuno Kenge, a rural town.
It is passing.
My mother left my house when I was in kindergarten.
Before my dad comes home from work, this time is my time to rest.
Where is it.
My dad loves drinking and loves women.
And my mother loves it too.
Kitty is back, Dad.
She is a new mother.
Think of it.
What do you think?
What, you love that.
Maybe you can’t love it well?
It is so beautiful and glowing.
You have awesome eyes.
Because it is beautiful.
by
He looks so clever, right?
No is?
What is this room? – What is this room?
It smells bad?
The engine!
This fucking shit!
You have gone down, this fucking shit!
Today is it, really!
Do not throw!
Who will do?
What is it.
My father is called Meiko.
I married a young woman of a distant age.
from this day.
We are
It was a relationship between mother and son.
My father is working in a snack shop in front of the station.
Meet Mey in the store.
Drunken together.
I got to meet.
Why do you want to meet a woman so far away?
It is meaningless to me.
Okay okay.
You eat a little bit big.
Why Why?
Why is it you, you.
What is?
Fighting
Do not know?
You are still a boy.
It is true, this fucking man.
No, this fucking guy.
Not much, you shit.
Ken is
You are hindering.
Sorry to
With Mr. Meyer
My dad was laughing.
Why I was angry.
No longer
It is a thousand.
It was uncomfortable to handle the cliff.
You are hungry, you.
Yes to?
Do you want to use a lionza, so you can make your skin fit?
I am pleased many times.
No, it is over.
Yes to see.
Tired of.
Grandma, you have to stop, stop there.
You are afraid to sleep, I mean.
Grandma, I am afraid to sleep.
Jules, you’re going to play there.
You must not pretend.
In the corner of a narrow boulevard, I thought it was a fairy tale to two people who were hiding and cuddling.
But I may have been confused that the sweat-smelling room of the man alone is gradually sweetening and filled with the smell of the girlfriend.
wwwww
Drink a drink.
while eating food.
Go to bath.
Two people were shown in Texas.
I want to do too.
by
Would have died.
I was confused, I thought so.
Sorry Dad.
Oh well Kenji.
His father had an accident on the scene.
My mother is waiting for you at home, so go home.
I should have died, I should have said that.
I should have said I should die.
I will not die if I am killed.
When you die, you ride a car.
My father said that he was replaced.
In the building building, we are working on the construction site.
He fell from a high spot and died.
I am a mother without blood.
I lived with my mother-in-law Miyuki.
Six months have passed since then.
Myriam was always drinking before her father’s buddy.
He did not work day and night, he continued to drink.
I liked my dad so much.
You haven’t been to school lately.
I graduated last month.
Yes is.
Come buy a drink.
No more money.
So do not work.
My father died and the money he had paid for was a bit of a waste.
I love my father and I have to protect my mother.
I started in a factory selling the strawberries.
You are not tired.
Will the company come?
I quit in six months.
I was desperate about my own.
Drinking for money without crying.
I felt so much about Miyamoto.
I felt like I was getting something in my heart.
In the polo shop left by my father, my father and I, together, shouldered each other, and drank together every day, without doing anything, just like my father.
Drinking alcohol with no money.
I felt that joke.
I felt like I was getting something in my heart.
Comfort each other.
What have I already given?
It feels like going back.
10 steps up.
Go again, go again.
information of you.
Yes is
Oh yeah yeah
Soon enough?
Entering in the back.
Oh yeah
to behind.
hit in the back.
Oh is
Oh, that, that, that...
I have a lot of...
Oh... oh...
Oh well...
Do not stay like this.
What do I do.
Stop it anymore.
Stay still.
When do you drink it?
It does not matter.
It is disturbing.
You are not working, just like me.
I lived with you.
What a bad thing? you quit your job, sorry.
What is?
You are more shit than your dad.
I don’t want to tell you.
My dad worked well.
You did a good job.
This is the cyclone.
The worst, you
What are you laughing.
Thousands of fucking fish.
What is?
I say a thousand fish.
be silent.
Thousands of fucking fish.
next to Mom.
I was shock.
Do not laugh, make noise.
It’s good, you have it, right?
Stop it.
not stop
Stop me to.
not stop it.
It is getting harder.
Please please
I am
I missed it.
May it be you.
Let me this.
Please please
Sleep to
Cry to me.
Same form as him.
Stop it well.
His shoulders and his feet are all the same.
You don’t know him, he.
I was hungry.
I missed
No to
Oh yeah
What to
Like my dad.
Do it work.
It is sad.
This kind of...
Such a shit...
Because I protect you.
No to
You cannot endure this too.
If you can’t stand, please please please me.
No to
See more
Oh yeah
No to
Oh yeah yeah yeah
by
No to
Go down it.
by
Do this so.
No to
What
Oh yeah
The Symphony of Tomorrow.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
No to
Oh yeah
Keep it clean below.
Lick it properly.
See also more.
I have such a good.
Touch me too.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh oh oh...
I did more!
It is not over once...
See also,
More...
Touch me too...
Oh well...
Enter it...
Oh yeah
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah yeah
No to
More to behind.
Enter it closer.
No to
by Willie
There is, that
That way, I am
The same chamber.
This is delicious.
Oh well ðŸ˜ðŸ˜
I am probably.
If we live together.
Yes to?
We are on a cocktail.
Oh yeah
No to
by Rene
Yes
Oh yeah yeah
Oh yeah yeah yeah
No to
I can enter now.
Oh well
Same as him.
What is happening.
Oh well, aska
You are
and aska.
What is?
The appearance and reception are completely different.
We are just together here.
I cannot say, so.
The house does not fight.
Very good feeling.
Oh, and this taste.
A little English.
A little
The discernible
See also, be patient.
Such a mess.
You cannot be satisfied.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
No to
What if you have never seen such a face.
Oh yeah
It seems to be going.
Are you calm?
Do not talk anything.
If I look at your face, I will be troubled.
Oh...
here here...
What, just since
slowly
It feels good here.
Feel good
What is?
What is floating?
His hands were closed.
Do you close?
Then see
from behind.
Follow me
See also Fast.
Oh yeah
What about that back.
really
The most tired of me.
Oh yeah
No to know.
More more
Follow more.
Suffering is
and pinned
I know
It felt good.
Tell me about Dad.
Okay is.
She is named Jane by her real name.
This is going.
What to stop.
Not to take a break.
Sit still more tight.
A little bit of this.
This guy is just like him.
I’m going to fit my shit.
Not to go immediately.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh yeah yeah yeah
No to
It feels good to hit this chimpanzee high.
He is like you.
It is Dry.
How dirty are you?
How can I not endure?
Like him.
What is rest.
Come here quickly.
Move to.
No to
Oh yeah yeah
Oh more of it.
to more.
Oh yeah yeah
Start to start.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh
Oh yeah
Oh no more.
What did you not say at all?
Oh is
by
I touched it.
Feel good
A little, a little
Oh well!? to
Oh yeah yeah yeah
and opportun
NN is
AAA to point.
Oh yeah, nasal
by Snoop
and chanting
Why that
That feeling.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
by
Oh yeah
Oh, it can be.
Okay, it is enough.
Leave it out, leave it out.
Oh yeah
Oh yeah yeah.
Oh, and
Oh, oh
Oh...
It is the first time.
with Daddy.
I have the same.
Why is it.
After I hugged Miyoshi, I felt loneliness and feeling lonely.
Stop this way.
I liked your here.
Myth, myth was my own.
In my heart is still a Japanese.
What are you saying.
I am in place of my father.
Give him a spoon.
What is?
Did you not want me to do this?
You are happy, right?
No, that is...
Since my mother was alive.
Think all the time.
It was hard.
Let me do this.
Thanks to you.
Thanks to Mom.
I feel very fast.
What do you feel?
Can’t you stand up so stupidly?
Say it clearly.
What is?
Feel good
Your chest.
Really resembles that guy.
This is hard, thick, and it looks like a long.
What happened? what happened?
Are you going to sleep?
No, you can’t be a kid.
I have to arrange it.
What happened, look at that.
Oh, what happened to you?
Call me, my mother.
My mom is mom,
The breasts are delicious.
Full of it.
Say more of it.
At first, I did more tuition, so the markets were actually open to work, but
Similar to him.
No to
Very good feeling.
well entered it.
It feels good.
MOMMY
No to
No longer
Feel good
No to
Oh is
by
No to
No longer
Mom, I am going out.
by Mama
Go out, go out, go out.
Mom is fine.
Mom, I will go out.
Mommy is out.
Oh to!
I am...
Drink it, is it Mom?
Drink it, Mom
Instead of my father, I can.
Then I went out every day with my screen.
But you don’t like me because you do it.
When I look at it, I don’t call my name.
My chicken is meant.
Treat me like a toy.
I am in the place of my father.
Yes
OK yet.
I tried to imagine.
Zinpo
One of the heavens.
Do not stay like this.
I started working again.
The secondary car.
My father and I are different.
I can make my dad happier than my dad.
You don’t notice that in my mind.
Miyu started working at the snack in front of the station again.
Tired of
Go here go.
I was tired.
Bring me water.
thanks to
Oh that tasty.
No to No.
Mom please please.
Please love my mouth.
I came with my boyfriend and I got this.
What do you think? you like it.
I want to protect my mommy.
Meiko began to meet with Snake’s guests.
And they stopped me from having sex.
Marry me with me.
Mrs
What happened to you?
Did you have that hobby?
I wanted so much.
MOMMY
Please
Please Mom.
MOMMY
Please be quick.
Please fast.
What do you want?
here here?
Do you want here?
My dear, I want to be here.
by Kelly
Kenny, I thought it was the last time you made me happy.
What do you say? I don’t like it.
Get it down.
Keep on joking.
No to
Yes
Tastefully
No to
Oh yeah
have done
No to
Touch it properly.
by Pin
Will you stop crying?
Let it flow.
Spread the voice.
What do you do? drink it quickly.
Oh well...
No...
Oh oh oh oh oh.
Oh well...
by
No...
Oh well...
Put it in your mouth.
No to
No...
by
And then, move your tongue up and down.
Oh...
Oh... oh... oh...
Sanna is licking...
Oh...
Oh well...
Yes, the cockroach is touching too.
No, no no
Oh Oh Oh
Oh yeah yeah
Oh yeah, that feels like.
Oh Oh Oh
No to
Eat more and be satisfied with me.
By the end,
Oh well!
Get out the tongue.
Oh yeah
Oh well!
The Motion!
Oh yeah!
Yes yes
Oh yeah
by
Oh oh
Oh yeah
I think it’s the last time you look at me.
by
Oh oh
Oh yeah
by
Oh...
Look at it properly.
by
Oh...
Oh... I opened my mouth.
by
Oh...
No to
Yes
Oh yeah
No to
You want to fuck.
Oh yeah
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Drink it properly.
by Companion
No to
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Sorry to
I shall say.
Very good including.
2nd
Oh oh oh
Yes
Oh yeah
Oh is
Very good feeling.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah yeah
Feeled
I can’t wait Jimny.
I am not satisfied yet, right?
Oh yeah yeah yeah
No to
increasingly become liver.
Oh well... well...
What is?
Do not
I will not be able to endure.
Will I not be able to endure?
Where do you want to get around?
Where do you want to put all this in?
I want to get in.
of whom?
of mother.
I am not my mom, what do you say?
I do not know Japanese.
I want to say the same complaint.
well is
of my you.
Drink this thoroughly.
No to
Oh yeah
Oh oh oh oh
No to
Oh yeah
Oh well Kenton.
No to
to ah
Oh yeah
No to
Oh to!
Great is
Feel good
by
Simply said.
Oh yeah!
No to
As you know, this.
Feel good
Oh to!
It feels bad to get back.
You feel your destiny, right?
Feel badly
face so.
Feel well.
Can you endure?
be more patient.
The Kenny’s Chicken.
It feels good to rub eggs.
Sorry to
I shall go.
Wait a little.
Because they are one.
What is?
No complaints, no mouth.
I will not allow you to rest.
Wait a little.
again
1st
2nd
3 is
4 is
Kenshots
Feel good
No to
well well
Oh yeah
Kansas is
Yes
Oh yeah
No to
Yes
Oh yeah
No to continue.
The crying of Mr.
Come more here.
Oh oh!