Next, I'm going to show you how to make a simple and easy-to-make cake.
First, I'm going to make a cake sheet.
I'm going to make a cake sheet.
Next, I'm going to make a cake sheet.
Last, I'm going to make a cake sheet.
It's so nice to have a 4-day vacation and go camping.
It's great to be able to drink alcohol in nature like this.
It's the best.
Would you like some wine?
Sounds good.
Here you go.
Is this grape wine?
Yes, I'm sure you know what it is.
Please try it.
Thank you.
It's so good.
Thank goodness.
Does it suit your taste?
Yes, it does.
That's great.
It's delicious.
It's the best to drink grape wine in front of a bonfire like this.
I think they think camping is just about setting up a tent.
That's right.
They drink and sleep from daybreak.
Well, they're busy with work.
I think that's enough for today.
It would be nice if it was a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
They secretly buy camping equipment from me.
Two or three.
Summer, autumn and winter.
Winter.
I have about five.
That's a problem.
Right?
I have camping equipment in my children's room.
I can't help it.
I sent it to his parents' house.
By the way, where is Shohei today?
He's at my parents' house.
He's too young to come camping.
I can't take care of him.
Is that so?
I went to the park with him the other day.
He left Shohei behind.
Is that possible?
I can't believe you leave your own child behind.
I went to the park with him and brought him back.
Did you say anything?
I didn't say anything.
Bring me a Camembert and a tomato.
I'll do it.
Is that okay?
Hold it for him.
Be careful.
I can do it.
Mr. Kazumichi.
You are a kind husband.
Is that so?
Isn't that normal?
Hey!
Did you say anything bad about me?
I didn't say anything.
I'm going to hell.
Aren't you two getting along?
No, we're not.
We always fight.
Let's have a drink of wine.
People say we get along well enough to fight.
That's a lie.
Cheers.
What are you going to do?
Let's go into the open-air bath.
Let's go in.
I'll go in.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to try it?
I think it's good.
It's hot.
Be careful.
The Kanda couple, who live in the same apartment,
and the Natsukawa couple,
have already burnt dishes for diner on the rooftop of the same apartment.
They have already burnt dishes for diner on the rooftop of the same apartment.
Mike, wife of Ayumi,
and Kanda also decided to blame Kanda for the burning dishes.
They decided to camp
because in a sense their hobby is camping.
Because in a sense their hobby is camping.
Three camps, the other and the wife,
three camps, the other and the wife,
will take the classic style camp from now on.
It's great to have CP and hot spring.
I'm glad I found a place like this.
There's no garden camper.
Actually, I'm a friend of the camper Kazumi.
Is that so?
Yes.
Thanks to Kazumi, I can have a quiet and fun camp.
By the way, where's your child?
It's my wife's family.
Oh, I should have brought him.
No, no, no.
He's still small.
And I want to take care of my grandchild.
Oh, I see.
Don't you make a place for Kazumi?
Oh, I leave it to everyone.
Oh, I see.
Oh, by the way, the watch you were wearing earlier.
I think it's called MADMASTER.
It costs about 300,000 yen, right?
Oh, did you notice?
Yes.
Actually, it's MRG.
Wow, that's amazing.
I'll never forgive you for that.
I have a secret gift for you.
Oh, it would be terrible if you found out.
Don't worry.
And actually, I bought a van camping car.
Are you kidding me?
I'm going to buy it next time.
Wow.
That's also a secret for Miki.
Let's buy a camping car for Natsukawa.
No, no, no.
If you say that, Mayumi will be angry.
But it's a man's dream to have a camping car.
Well, that's true.
Let's buy it.
No, no, no.
No, but I'm really looking forward to it.
It's a dream to camp in a camping car with a child.
I see.
Wow.
It's so beautiful.
What's the matter?
Oh, no, it's nothing.
The scenery over there is really beautiful.
Oh, yeah.
It's a really nice place.
I felt like I could understand the feeling of a frog being stared at by a snake.
The other day, there was a tent over there.
That's why it was a big tent for Miki.
It's for five or six people.
I was wondering who was sleeping.
There are three people in the tent alone.
I don't need three people.
That's true.
What?
Is it my fault again?
That's right.
Stop it.
In front of Natsukawa's wife.
The housewife has a lot of complaints.
What is it?
Even if you make it look cool with camping equipment, if it's ugly inside, it's meaningless.
It's not a respectable father.
What? Are you still angry about buying a new tent?
That's right.
Why? Stop it.
Let's stop fighting.
The bonfire is already lit, so why don't we all sit around it?
Bring a chair or something.
Yes.
But I don't like this guy.
I don't like being next to this guy.
I don't like being next to this guy either.
I like being next to Kazumi-san.
Is it me?
Sit down.
Is Ayumi-san okay?
Yes.
I'm here.
Please sit down.
It's really noisy.
Why are you still angry about the tent?
Of course I'm angry.
Didn't you talk about it last time?
We didn't talk about it.
We talked about it.
We just bought it and talked about it.
Then what's the problem with the new camp?
You don't need two or three of the same things.
We can camp because we have the latest ones.
It's comfortable.
If you're going to use it that much, you should use it for academic insurance.
So it's important to camp and release stress.
You only think about your future.
That's you.
You should think about your future.
Let's have a drink.
Kazumi-san, say something.
Thank you.
Let's have a drink.
The wine is getting worse.
It's my line.
Let's stop here.
It's good.
You made this, didn't you?
It was really good.
Really?
Thank you.
How did you make it?
Really?
I'm glad.
He doesn't praise the food at all.
Is that so?
I'm going to divorce him and remarry Kazumi-san.
You should remarry Kazumi-san.
I'm going to remarry Ayumi-san, who is kind and wonderful.
Let's stop here.
You can't do that.
You can't do that, either.
Kazumi-san will definitely dump you.
Let's stop here.
You can't do that.
If you break up with me and Kazumi-san dumps you, it's over.
Shut up.
You can't do that.
That's not true.
Let's stop here.
What did you do?
Good evening.
I'm a manager.
He is my father's son.
I'm Akagi.
Nice to meet you.
This is a nice camp.
It's quiet and the air is good.
Have fun.
Thank you.
It's okay.
I thought you were fighting.
It's a quiet camp.
Shut up.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Have fun.
Thank you.
It was fun.
That's not true.
Shut up.
It's okay.
It goes well with wine.
By the way, there are not many people in this camp.
That's right.
It's like a hide-and-seek.
Don't come too close.
I thought there was something.
I was looking forward to it.
It's like this.
That's right.
It's getting interesting.
I think it's nice.
That's not true.
You are a ghost.
Don't say that.
I can't see you.
It's hard to say.
Kanda and his wife were in a terrible state.
Are they okay?
Kanda still has a bomb.
What?
Actually, I bought a camping car.
Are you kidding me?
It's true.
It's hard to be caught.
That's right.
I think I should use it for my child.
I think so, too.
What if I bought a camping car?
I think we'll fight.
I think so, too.
I hope we don't fight anymore.
Let's sleep.
Good night.
What is this?
I think they are fighting.
Are they fighting?
It doesn't matter.
Good morning.
Are you okay?
It's my freedom.
Good morning.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Listen to me.
He bought a camping car.
I'm jealous of you.
You can't drive a car like that.
You can't take your child to the supermarket.
I can drive a car like that.
I bought a camping car.
You can't drive a car like that.
I can drive a car like that.
Stop fighting.
Let's have breakfast.
I can't eat with him.
Don't say that.
Calm down.
Let's have breakfast.
We can calm down if we have breakfast.
What are you doing?
I'm going home.
I can't stay with you for three days.
Return the car key.
It takes two hours to return to Tokyo.
I only have one car.
Let's walk home.
Don't say that.
I'm going home.
I'll do as you say.
I'll walk home.
Don't say that.
It takes one day to walk down the mountain.
It's dangerous.
Calm down.
I understand.
I don't want to sleep with him in the tent.
Let's camp with me.
Are you sure?
How about you and Kazumitsu?
Let's camp with me.
Let's camp with Kazumitsu and Ayumi.
I want to camp alone.
I can do it.
You can't do anything.
You two...
I'll do it.
Let's go.
Calm down.
Sit here.
I'll make tea for you.
Thank you.
Camping is not good.
I hope we can make up soon.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
Drink this.
Calm down.
Is it good?
I'm glad.
This was the beginning of everything.
Have you calmed down?
Yes.
Do you want to talk to Kenta?
No.
If I talk to him now, we'll fight again.
But we have to calm down.
That's right, Miki.
When I go back to Tokyo, I'll calm down and talk to him.
Well...
I'll talk to Kenta.
What will you do?
I'll talk to him and make up.
You want me to make up with you?
Honey.
I'm sorry to involve you in our fight.
I'll ask my parents to pick me up tomorrow.
No.
You can't go back to the way you were.
That's right.
Let's have fun today.
Let's drink a lot.
Let's have fun.
Well...
That's right.
You were there yesterday, right?
He's my father-in-law's friend's son.
I played with him when I was a kid.
We were in the same place.
We were playing in the garden.
Then he bit me.
You're burned.
I'm burned.
Let's get you up.
Are you okay?
It's hot.
I didn't cut it.
It's delicious.
I haven't seen Kenta since lunch.
You can leave him alone.
I can't do that.
I haven't seen Kenta since lunch.
I'm going to see him.
You'll get sick if you see him again, right?
That's right.
Drink alcohol and calm down.
I'll go see him.
Kenta.
Are you okay?
I'm going to see him.
What's wrong?
It's so hot.
I'm going to call Miki.
Please don't call her.
What are you talking about?
But...
Please don't call her.
You're sweating a lot.
It's okay.
Please don't call her.
But...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Thank you.
I'm glad you're nice.
How was it, Kenta?
What's wrong?
Kenta told me not to tell you this.
He has a fever.
Is he still sick?
Everyone is drinking alcohol.
I think he'll be fine if he stays in bed all night.
I'm going back.
No.
Why?
If you go back, you'll get into a fight.
You're all alone.
I think you should calm down.
I'll take care of him.
You can't do anything.
It's okay.
Let's take him to the hospital tomorrow.
Who's going to take care of him?
I don't know.
I can't apologize to her.
Ayumi.
Don't worry.
Why?
I didn't tell you.
But why?
It's okay.
You really didn't tell me?
I didn't.
You really didn't?
I really didn't.
Don't worry.
I have water.
I'm sorry.
Can you drink it?
Later.
Let me know if you want it.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm fine.
Your phone is ringing.
Who is it from?
Can you look at it?
Is it Yasuda?
It's okay.
I'm fine.
Miki and Shohei are taking good care of him.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
This happened because of me.
If you're worried, let's go to Kenta's place.
I can't apologize to him.
Really?
Yes.
It's small, but let's go to bed.
Okay.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm going to sleep.
Okay.
Good night.
I'm going to sleep.
Miki, what's wrong?
I wish I could be an adult like you.
You're an adult.
Thank you.
Kazumitsu.
Yes?
Can I hug you?
No.
When you're lonely, you want to rely on something.
But that's not me.
I think it's on your back.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Oh, right.
Kenta said he bought a camper van because he wanted to travel with you and your son.
What?
Whether you buy a camper van or not, you should talk to Kenta.
That's right.
Let's go to bed.
Okay.
I was about to make a mistake.
I slept with my neighbor's wife in this small tent.
It was something I could say to Ayumi.
Oh, I bit my finger.
I don't usually do this.
I'm sorry for us.
No, it's okay.
As Ayumi said, I think now is our turning point.
Maybe so.
This is delicious.
It's a personal work.
I'm sorry.
Kenta.
Please wake up.
I'm sorry.
When did you become like this?
Please stay away from me.
I'm sorry.
I'm happy.
It looks like you have a tent over there.
I'm sorry.
Please sit down.
Please stay away from me.
I'm sorry.
Did the fever go down?
Yes.
Let's keep this a secret.
I think it's better.
Are you listening?
Kenta?
Please put on your clothes.
It's hot.
Kenta.
Don't leave me.
I'm sorry.
It's bad to be so beautiful.
Don't you think it's bad for you?
I can't help it.
Please stop.
Kenta.
Miki.
I can't help it.
I'm not a great man.
It's hot.
I can't help it.
Kenta, let's stop now.
It's hot.
I can't help it.
It's getting hot here.
Kenta.
I can't help it.
You're so beautiful.
Don't lick me.
Why?
I can't help it.
Kenta, stop it.
I'm not in the bath anymore.
You smell so bad.
Don't bite me.
Kenta.
Do you feel so good?
I can't help it.
You're so beautiful.
Kenta, stop it.
I can't help it.
What are you doing?
You're so beautiful.
I'm not beautiful.
You said you wanted to go camping with me.
I can't help it.
Let's stop it.
I can't stop it.
No, I can't help it.
I can't help it.
I want to be with you.
Kenta, stop it.
I can't help it.
How do you feel?
Kenta, I can't help it.
I can't help it.
Why?
How do you feel?
I can't help it.
Do you know that Miki is here?
She is so beautiful.
I can't help it.
Do you know what you're saying?
It's not good to be beautiful.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
How are you?
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Kenta.
No, no.
You shouldn't be so violent.
I know how you feel.
I'm sorry, Kenta.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Kenta.
Do you like me?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
What have I done?
Hey.
Yes?
Are you always like this with Miki?
What?
Nothing.
Aimi.
Aimi, how is Kenta?
Are you still sleeping?
Wait a minute.
Why?
Kenta is embarrassed.
Wait a minute.
Hey, I'll open the door.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What's wrong?
You just show your face.
Kenta doesn't want to show his face.
Is that so?
Yes.
He'll be angry if he sees Miki's face.
Kenta, how is your fever?
It's gone down.
Is that so?
Are you feeling better?
I think so.
That's good.
Yes.
Let's have breakfast together.
Because I'm hungry.
Yes.
I'll go to the bathroom later.
Let's go together.
Yes.
I'll clean up and go.
I'm hungry.
It's been a while.
Yes.
What are you going to do?
I'm hungry.
Yes.
Let's go to the bathroom.
What are you doing?
How is your fever?
I'll go to the bathroom later.
Really?
Yes.
Get ready quickly.
I understand.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Let's go to the bathroom.
Yes.
I'll clean up and go.
I'm hungry.
I want to talk to him.
Yes.
I think it's good.
Can you hear me?
I think it's better not to stimulate your ego yet.
Yes.
Do you want to have a couple meeting until tomorrow?
What?
Kenta is still single.
I want to apologize to him, but I can't.
I'll persuade him until tomorrow.
I understand.
What?
I think this is the turning point for you and Kenta.
Please cooperate with me.
Yes.
I understand.
Let's go to the bathroom.
Yes.
What are you doing?
I can't help it.
We should have breakfast.
Yes.
It's warm.
Ayumi, you're a good person.
Really?
What do you mean?
Well...
You think about Miki and Kenta.
I'm sorry.
No.
You're a kind person.
Why are you playing a prank on me?
Why do you say that?
I don't want to see him.
Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
What are you going to do if he finds out?
I don't care.
This is what happens to me.
Wait.
No.
Thank you.
I'm going.
What are you going to do for breakfast?
It's not time for breakfast.
Really?
Yes.
If Ayumi doesn't calm down, she'll find out.
Are you betraying me?
I'll tell her.
Promise me.
You'll make up with Miki.
I promise.
If I don't, Ayumi will be a bad person.
You're sweating.
If you come in here, you'll smell like a pervert.
Don't you have a handkerchief?
It's over there.
Why are you taking it off?
I'm going to take it off because I'm sweating.
Are you going to take it off all the way down?
It's not the first time I've seen it, so it's okay.
Please take it off.
Wait a minute.
It's hard for Miki to smell like this.
But...
You have to wipe it off.
Can I have you wipe my back?
I can't.
Please.
Please wipe my back.
I can't.
Mr. Kenta.
Please stop.
I can't.
Mr. Kenta.
Please stop.
You're so relaxed.
Mr. Kenta.
Please stop.
You're so relaxed.
I can't.
Please stop.
You smell like a pervert.
I can't.
Please stop.
Mr. Kenta.
I can't.
It's hot.
Please stop.
I can't.
It's hot.
It's so hard.
Please stop.
It's hot.
Mr. Kenta.
Please stop.
It's so hot.
Mr. Kenta.
Please stop.
I can't.
Why are you so hard?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Both of you are so hard.
It's hot.
Come here.
Hurry up.
I can't.
It's okay.
It's hot.
Are you all right?
I'm going to be exposed.
I'm going to kill you.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to be exposed because there are two of us.
It's okay.
But if you make a loud noise, you might be exposed.
It's hot.
I'm going to be exposed because there are two of us.
I know.
It's hot.
I'm going to be exposed because there are two of us.
So don't make a loud noise.
But...
Your body is very honest.
Are you going to be exposed?
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
I'm going to be exposed because there are two of us.
So don't make a loud noise.
It's hot.
I'm going to be exposed because there are two of us.
Your husband is playing like this.
Let's take a break.
Mother's crying
She cried so hard
I'm sorry.
I knew this would happen.
They'll tell you.
I'm enjoying myself.
Let me kiss you.
I can't.
It's getting lazier now
Hang in there
It'll change
I got a good idea.
You know?
Let's do it.
Oh.
Mmm...
OK, OK.
OK.
That's good.
Good.
OK.
Oh, my.
Yes, yes.
OK.
Yes.
Who do you compare yourself to?
No, I don't think so.
Do you compare yourself to your husband over there?
Eat some more.
Ayumi.
You smell like a pervert.
Don't do that.
Damn it.
Hey.
In the end, I made you smell like a pervert.
It's delicious.
I'm going to take a bath.
I'll go with you.
I want to take a bath alone.
You're right.
You're taking care of my husband.
I didn't mean that.
I'm sorry.
Where is he?
He's sleeping.
He wants to take a bath alone.
I'm going in.
Why are you taking a bath alone?
I'm a stranger.
It's natural.
Is that so?
You should get rid of that perverted smell.
Have you been found out?
When you left the tent.
I left the tent from the entrance of the bath, so I'm fine.
I left the tent from the entrance of the forest.
It was hard for me to sit here.
I rented this place.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you standing?
Is this it?
Don't do that.
What's wrong with you?
It's nice to be alone.
I'll do my best.
What are you doing?
I've been watching you.
Are you interested in me?
Do you always take a bath in such a big bath?
What?
You don't usually take a bath in such a big bath.
You took a bath easily.
It's not easy.
Don't you want to sleep with me tonight?
I can't.
You're just a stranger tomorrow.
I can't meet you easily.
But...
I want to sleep with you tonight.
I'm interested in you.
Okay.
I want to sleep with you.
It's hot.
Who is it?
It's okay.
You're a bad person.
I'm serious.
It's hot.
It's very hot.
I want to take a bath.
You can take a bath here.
Ayumi.
What's wrong?
When I came to see you, you weren't here.
I see.
Did you go somewhere?
Is it like this?
Don't do that.
You can't do that.
What?
You look beautiful.
Do I?
It's because I went to the hot spring.
Really?
Yes.
You look different from yesterday.
I think it's because I went to the hot spring.
Did you go to the hot spring?
Did it have such an effect?
Yes.
Really?
What's wrong?
Can I talk to you for a moment?
What?
Wait.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
What about you?
What?
Wait.
What's wrong?
Don't do that today.
Miki is here.
I'm excited because I'm exchanging couples.
Miki?
Miki will come back, right?
Don't worry.
I'm going to the foot of the stairs.
I can't stand it.
Wait.
It's okay.
I can't stand it.
I'll wait for you tomorrow.
At this time, I should have noticed the change of my wife as soon as possible.
Were you protecting me?
Yes.
How was it?
What?
I had sex with my husband.
Did you peep at me?
Yes.
You have sex with me and your husband.
You're worse than me.
That's...
This is the second half.
That's all for today.
That's right.
Can I talk to him tomorrow?
You'll be fine.
Can I go camping?
If it's his dream to travel with a child...
It's amazing to make your dream come true.
Thank you.
I thought I could make a mistake with you.
What?
But I can't win against Ayumi, who married such a wonderful husband.
Hey, Miki.
I'm kidding.
I'll sleep in the car tonight.
Good night.
Is it okay to kiss like this?
Tomorrow, we'll be just neighbors.
But it's close.
We can meet anytime.
Good night.
I'm so happy.
What do you say?
I want to hold your hand.
No ...
...
Good morning.
Did you sleep well?
Yes, I slept well.
That's good.
Miki also slept well.
That's great.
Let's eat.
I'm sorry that you had to go out with our selfishness.
No, it's nothing.
You're grilling meat, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
It's completely different from when I came here.
They seem to be sleeping over there.
That's right.
Do you want me to wake them up?
Let's let them sleep.
That's right.
It's done well.
Let's eat.
The soft-boiled egg is more delicious.
I didn't think I'd have sex until this morning.
I can do it, too.
Hey.
Let's do it tomorrow.
Let's do it the day after tomorrow.
Okay?
Okay.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Mr. Kenta, don't do it.
I don't know.
Hands off me.
I was hit by something that hurts like this.
...
I want more...
I'm sorry.
You love this, don't you?
You look terrible.
I'm sorry.
Let's sleep together.
You look terrible.
Kenta, tell me.
I'm sorry.
You look terrible.
Tell me.
Do you want me to tell you?
I feel good.
Kenta, tell me.
You look terrible.
I feel good.
Mom.
Mom,sorry.
I'm sorry mom.
I see,I know.
Long ... form.
Look,eriot.
I'm sorry.
Mom,what too sorry.
Oh, no.
Don't worry.
You've made aavoid all troubles.
Hey, Kenta-san, hang in there.
Hang in there.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Ouch!
Hang in there. Hang in there.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Kenta-san, hang in there.
It's all over now.
You're not supposed to do this!
Hang in there. Hang in there.
It's the first time I'm so tired.
It feels good.
If I'm tired, I'll go again.
I'll go again.
It's the first time I'm so tired.
Can you ride on my back this time?
I've never ridden on your back.
You can do it.
It's the first time I'm so tired.
It feels good.
Oh, God...
Somebody please help me!
It's a madhouse.
I don't want to come here.
Oh, God!
1! 1! 1!
Please stop!
Can you do it for me, mom?
I won't, mom!
I... I can't!
Okay.
I'm here now.
That's bad.
I want to do it so badly.
Oh, Mittero.
Someone save Mittero.
Hey, gotta find a way to get to Rokuchen-cho.
Cody,
What?
Oh my God!
What...
Where am I?
Where am I!
Where am I?!
Ah!
No, no, no, no...
Hey, Ami-san.
You have to move yourself.
Why?
Like this.
Slowly.
Ah, amazing...
Amazing...
That's...
That's your...
Hey, Kento-san, please move.
I want you to move.
But...
Please stop.
Ami-san...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Ah ah ah ah ah ah
woo woo
AMAN
Hmm
Ave
Ah ah
Hmm
No...
Here?
It hurts...
You're being tough with your teeth.
I can't stop...
I'm fine.
I'm awful scared.
It's fine.
Stop it...
Let me out...
No, Shinji, no!
Let me go...
Let me-
Let me go!
It's no good!
I can't do this anymore!
Stop this!
Heavens!
Calm down.
I've never done this before.
What should I do?
It's good.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Natsukawa-san.
Good morning.
You're hustling.
Hustle?
In the hot spring.
Hot spring?
You're Natsukawa-san.
You're loud.
What are you talking about?
I was cleaning the back of the hot spring.
You're loud.
I don't have many customers.
Please let me go home this time.
Wait a minute.
What are you talking about?
Last night.
In that tent.
Right?
That tent, right?
It was amazing when I passed by.
Natsukawa-san, you're so loud.
Please forgive me.
What's wrong?
Please let me go home this time.
Wait a minute.
Which do you like better, him or me?
I like him.
He doesn't look at me like that.
I didn't know there was such a big thing in there.
I was surprised.
Which do you like better, him or me?
This one.
Let's take a walk in such a big thing.
I want to hold Miki-san and take revenge.
But I couldn't move my eyes when I saw that rope.
I didn't expect this to happen.
I was glared at by a snake.
I really couldn't move.
My wife fell into that big thing that wasn't love or love.
What happened?
I lost as a male.