I'm home.
Welcome home.
What's wrong?
Oh, Yoshio. I'm sorry I'm late.
Oh, Tetsuya.
Didn't you say you were going to be late today?
Oh, yeah.
I made a mistake on the day we were supposed to study together.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Well, I'll see you later.
I'm sorry I'm late, Yoshio.
See you later.
Tetsuya, why don't you have dinner with us?
No, I'm fine.
Dad's coming home early today.
Is that so?
Well, then.
Take care.
See you later.
Well, then.
Let's make dinner.
Tetsuya
What are you going to do today?
I'm going to make curry.
Curry?
Isn't there a lot of curry these days?
What are you talking about?
Even if you make something else, you say you want to make curry.
That's right.
Mom.
By the way.
What?
Tetsuya.
Are you coming when I'm not here?
Yeah.
He comes to help me from time to time.
Why?
No reason.
You're late for club activities.
Tetsuya's house is a sushi house.
Dad's coming home late.
Don't you miss him alone?
Maybe.
I want to live with him.
Tetsuya's father.
Your father is fine.
That's right.
By the way.
When is your father's business trip?
I think it was next week.
Why?
I want you to buy me a new smartphone.
Didn't you just buy it the other day?
I didn't ask my mother.
Tetsuya.
Mom.
I'm a housewife.
And I'm a mother.
I was having sex with my son's best friend at the place where my son was resting.
I'm sorry.
Mom.
I want to join you.
No.
I don't have time today.
Don't worry.
I'll be back soon.
I can't.
He'll be back.
Don't worry.
My butt.
I'm scared.
I want to sit down.
Wait.
It's hot.
Sit down.
You're wet.
I can't.
You're sweating a lot.
I didn't want you to be like this.
No.
I can't.
It feels good.
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
I can't.
If you're sweating, let me out.
Which one do you want?
I can't.
You're always sweating a lot.
Please.
I understand.
You want me to stay inside?
I can't.
It's hot.
Hey.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
To be honest, I didn't expect him to be so feminine.
I can't.
The reason was that my husband had to go on business trips more often.
And my son is going to college.
I'm going to open my own house.
I'm going to spend more time alone.
I was feeling very lonely.
I can't.
Mother?
You didn't have to do anything today.
Thank you.
Do you have anything else you can do?
Tetsuya can help you.
I do all the housework at home.
I see.
That's great.
But you don't have to worry about me.
Dad is always late to go home.
I see.
I'm sorry to hear that.
You always go to Yoshio's club.
That's not true.
I'm fine as long as you're here.
Is that so?
Yes.
Oh, right.
Do you want to have dinner?
Yes.
Can I?
I'll make dinner after this.
Are you studying in Yoshio's room?
Yes, I am.
Do as you like.
Yes.
I'm sorry to hear that.
What's wrong?
Ma'am.
I...
I like you.
Wait a minute.
What are you talking about?
Tetsuya.
I like you.
Stop it.
I'm serious.
I like you.
Don't say that.
Tetsuya.
Stop it.
Don't do that.
It's dirty.
Look at me.
Don't do that.
Tetsuya, calm down.
Ma'am.
Don't do that.
Stop it.
Wait a minute.
Don't do that.
Please.
Tetsuya.
Don't do that.
Wait a minute.
Ma'am.
What are you doing?
Don't think about her.
I'm serious.
I like you.
Please.
Don't do that.
Tetsuya.
I like you.
Don't do that.
Tetsuya.
I like you.
I want to go home.
Don't do that.
Tetsuya.
Listen to me.
I'm sorry.
Tetsuya.
I know you're old.
But you shouldn't treat a woman's body like that.
I know.
You shouldn't treat her like that.
Do you understand?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I want to go home.
Don't do that.
Don't be angry.
I know.
You're old.
I'm sorry.
Don't be angry.
Sit here.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Come here.
I was surprised.
I'm sorry.
You couldn't bear it?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You've grown up.
It feels good.
You should be gentle.
I can't help it.
Just a little.
I'm sorry.
Here.
I was surprised.
I want to kiss you again.
Be gentle.
Have you ever treated a woman?
A little.
I'm sorry.
You understand, don't you?
Be gentle.
I want to touch you directly.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm sorry.
That's right.
Are you okay?
Can I touch you?
No.
I want to touch you.
Doesn't it hurt?
It doesn't hurt.
It tickles here.
I want to touch you.
Don't do that.
It tickles here.
Show me.
It's embarrassing to look at you like that.
You're beautiful.
No.
It's embarrassing.
It tickles here.
Don't do that.
Don't be so hard on me.
It tickles here.
Don't do that.
You don't like it, do you?
I want to touch you more.
It tickles here.
Don't be so hard on me.
Take your time.
It tickles here.
Don't do that.
I'm going to sleep.
That's all for today.
It tickles here.
I'm going to put it in again.
It tickles!
Ah, it's coming out.
It feels good.
I knew it.
This is a bit...
This feels really good.
My stomach feels really warm.
This is...
not good.
Ah, it's coming out.
Does it feel good?
No, it doesn't.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
What did you put in there?
It's no good.
It's amazing.
What is it?
It feels good.
I'm happy.
It's too big.
It feels good.
It's strange.
Who is it?
I don't know.
What?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's okay.
It's small.
It's no good.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's no good.
It's okay.
Do you want me to do more?
Don't do that.
It's amazing.
I...
I didn't mean to do that.
I'm going to kill you.
But...
You promised me, didn't you?
You said you'd kill me.
I want to kill you.
But...
I can't do it anymore.
I want you to go home.
Please.
It feels so good.
I'm going to kill you.
I'm not done yet.
I'm going crazy over there.
I will hug you.
I can't move.
I'm not doing anything.
It's really disgusting.
I don't want to.
No, no, no, no.
I'll tickle you.
Don't tickle me.
If you don't move, I'll tickle you.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't do that.
I'll tickle you.
I don't want to touch you.
I'm embarrassed to see you like that.
Show me.
Do you want to see it?
This is the last time.
Is this okay?
It's in there, isn't it?
I don't want to see you like that.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm embarrassed.
I don't want to see you like that.
I'm getting old.
I'm embarrassed.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I don't want to see you like that.
Look at my butt.
Let me touch your butt.
I can't move anymore.
I don't want to see you like that.
I'm getting old.
I know.
Don't touch me so hard.
I'm getting old.
I don't want to see you like that.
My legs are moving.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm getting old.
I don't know, but I'm still crying, so I can't help it.
I can't help it.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to leave soon.
Please don't do this to me.
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
Slug..
Are you sleeping?
That's it
Ouch!
I can't take it anymore!
I was about to forget that I was a mother, a wife, and a woman.
But this young man made me remember that.
It was very refreshing, and I was happy and excited.
Of course, I didn't mean to betray my husband and son.
But I just couldn't stop this relationship.
I can't take it anymore.
Kousa, are you okay?
I have some thoughts.
Are you hungry?
I'm sorry, I'll cook.
Place in a preheated oven and bake in 170℃ for 40 minutes right away.
trench goes into an oven
after cooling it a little, let it sit out in the fridge for about 10 minutes before making coconut cream.
Yes.
You're free today, aren't you?
I don't know what to do.
Don't worry.
It's hot.
I can't.
Ma'am.
If you make a noise here,
people will hear you.
I can't.
Please.
You can feel it.
It's hot.
Ma'am.
It's from an old man.
I'll go out later.
Please go out now.
I don't want to.
Let's go out.
Please go out.
Hello?
Honey.
I'm fine now.
What's wrong?
I see.
I'm fine.
Of course.
I'm fine, too.
I see.
I'll call you when I come back.
I'm fine.
I see.
I don't want to.
I'll call you.
I see.
I'll call you when I come back.
What's wrong?
Is it the sound of the TV?
I'm sorry.
I don't want to.
Is it the sound of the radio?
You're busy, too.
I'm sorry.
I have to go shopping.
See you later.
I see.
Why did you make fun of me on the phone?
I didn't mean it.
I was jealous of you.
What are you talking about?
I can't stand it anymore.
You were excited, too.
I'm not excited.
Did you feel good when you called me on the phone?
I didn't feel good.
I can't stand it anymore.
You felt good.
I'm sorry.
To be honest, I felt sorry for my husband and my son.
But I couldn't get out of it.
At some point, I woke up from the perverted part of me.
I don't care what happens to me after this.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm nervous.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Hi, Yoshio.
Are you going to the club?
Yes, I'm going now.
Where is Tetsuya?
Tetsuya hasn't been around lately.
That's right.
I heard that Tetsuya has a girlfriend.
Tetsuya has a girlfriend?
I don't know.
I heard that, too.
I have to go now.
What?
Let's go.
See you.
Tetsuya has a girlfriend?
He is older than me.
Hi, Yoshio.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Tetsuya?
He is older than me?
He has a girlfriend?
Tetsuya and his mother?
Let's go.
Tetsuya has a girlfriend?
He has a girlfriend?
You're extremely erotic today...
I just can't hold myself...
For what?
You're definitely a Tetsuya fanficle.
You're really a pervert.
I was so happy.
I was so lonely.
You didn't come to see me.
You didn't call me either.
But I'm busy with Yoshio.
You don't have to suffer today.
I won't.
OK, stop.
Stop.
I know.
I didn't know you were this big.
I'm so happy.
It's been a while.
I want to touch you more.
I want to take off your clothes.
Let me see.
I'm sorry.
Can I touch you?
I feel good.
Can I touch your neck?
I want to touch your neck.
I'm sorry.
I love you so much.
I love you so much more.
You smell so good.
You're so messy.
I love you so much.
You smell so good.
I love you so much more.
I love you so much.
It feels so good.
I love you so much more.
I love you so much.
I know.
If you grow up so much, you can't stand it, can you?
You're so big.
It feels so good.
Sorry.
One, two, three.
Let me lick you more.
You're so mean.
You look so happy.
You're so happy.
Let me lick you more.
It feels good.
You're so mean.
Let me lick you more.
It's been a long time.
You're so mean.
Breathe in and out slowly.
How is it?
I can't breathe just by inhaling.
Slowly.
Amazing.
I'm not a baby anymore.
Breathe in and out slowly.
I can't breathe just by inhaling.
Amazing.
It's so good.
Breathe in and out slowly.
It feels good.
It's so good.
Amazing.
I can't breathe just by inhaling.
It's so good.
It feels good.
More.
Breathe in and out slowly.
It's so good.
It feels good.
Breathe in and out slowly.
I can't breathe just by inhaling.
It's so good.
It feels good.
I can't breathe.
Give me the tampon.
It's so good.
Hurry up.
It's good.
It's so good.
It feels good.
What should I do?
I'm so embarrassed.
I can't do this.
I really can't do this.
I'm so embarrassed.
I can't do this.
I'm crying.
It's been a long time.
I can't do this.
What happened to her?
She went in from so far away.
I'm sorry.
What's that?
Sorry.
Thank you.
Thank you, Sory.
What?
More.
Look.
I can see it.
It's coming out.
I can see it well.
I can see all the love.
It's coming out.
I can't do anything.
I can see it.
It's gone.
It feels good.
Help me.
It's gone.
It feels good.
It's getting harder.
It's gone.
It hurts.
Help me.
I can't do anything.
I'm going.
I feel sick.
I'm scared.
It's so hot.
I'm standing now.
It feels so good.
It's so cold.
It's so hot.
I can't do this.
I love this.
It's so hot.
It feels so good.
I can't do this.
Aw!
It's cold!
Oh, my back hurts!
Oh, you're slow.
Aw!
You're sweating.
Aw, how can you sleep?
Honey? Honey?
That's right.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Give me everything.
I love this.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
More.
More?
My eyes are going to break.
Give me everything.
This.
It feels so good.
Give me everything.
More.
This is amazing.
Give me everything.
Everything.
I'm sorry.
I may have said it a long time ago.
Oh, my God!
I feel sick.
I feel sick, too.
Are you sick?
Yes, I am.
Let's go to the hospital.
To the hospital?
Let me out.
Oh, my God!
It's not enough yet.
Do it again.
Oh, my God!
I want to see your back.
No, I don't want to.
Do it again.
Let me out.
Oh, my God!
I just went to the hospital.
He was completely insane.
He was in his son's room.
And he was living with his husband.
In this house where they live as a family.
He couldn't have been exposed to such an act.
Poor thing.
His son ran away from the scene.
After that, I didn't notice.
I couldn't help it.
His spirit was coming out of me.
Oh, my God!
I wonder what happened to her.
What's wrong?
You're late.
Did something happen at home today?
Nothing.
Why?
What's wrong?
Did something happen at school?
Did something happen at school today?
Yoshio?
What's wrong?
Wait.
You're mine.
Wait, Yoshio.
What?
What are you doing?
Stop it.
No.
Yoshio.
What?
What's wrong?
No.
What?
Yoshio.
Stop it.
This day...
...I was...
...given to my son...
...my real son.
I was...
...given to him.
Stop it.
Yoshio.
Agamochi.
I'm sorry.
Why are you crying?
Whether you are older or younger, we've been through this together.
I'm so happy.
I'm sure you are the most groovy man.
I guess I could be their young master.
I did it!
Mori, I'm so happy to hear you being happy like this.
Thanks, nice to meet you.
Thanks to you, we've improved a lot.
You can take it out now.
Take it out.
Did you sleep a lot?
You're still standing.
One more time.
I'm sorry.
The relationship with her son's best friend is gone.
Fortunately, her husband didn't find out.
Fortunately, the family disaster was avoided.
More than before,
In the family,
No,
It's a trip with her son.
But,
Really,
I,
Our family,
Is it okay as it is?