It's not good.
Hey.
Don't touch me.
I'm coming.
It's late. Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
What do you mean?
Nothing.
We played together, didn't we?
But we're friends.
We went on a date, didn't we?
It wasn't a date.
I wanted you to be my friend.
What?
Really?
You were very fashionable.
We haven't been friends for a long time.
Not a man?
A woman.
I don't know.
I only have you.
Did you bake me a cake?
No.
Really?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it.
Don't catch a cold.
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
You're cute.
I'm sorry.
This is a gift for you.
So don't worry.
I'm sorry to make you worry.
You can do as you like.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
You can breathe.
It's just a breast.
It feels good.
What?
Look at me.
You are a sweet boy.
Yes, I am.
It's just a breast.
It feels good.
Hey, sis.
What?
I'll wash you.
Are you going to wash me?
Sit here.
I'm embarrassed to wash you.
I'll wash you.
Can I wash you more?
I often wash you.
I didn't expect you to wash me.
What's wrong?
I want to do that today.
Don't you think it's a bad idea to wash me?
I don't think so.
You don't think so, do you?
No.
Yuzuru always attacks my nipples.
That's why I'm standing here.
I have to wash your nipples.
Where?
I don't know.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
But I don't want to wash your nipples.
That's not true.
I don't want to wash your nipples.
Where did you learn that?
I'm just trying to be nice to you.
Do you like my brush?
I always wash your nipples.
It's getting really close now.
Here?
It's ticklish isn't it?
It feels good.
Wow!
It's clean.
It's clean because I rubbed it a lot.
I'll wash it.
You look like an older brother.
Do you want me to wash your hair?
Yes.
Really?
I'll wash your hair.
Do you want me to wash your hair?
Yes.
Wow!
It feels good.
You look like you're in pain.
Wow! It feels good.
Hey, Yuzuru.
Yes?
Yuzuru cleaned your boobs.
Yes.
I'll massage your boobs with this.
How?
Like this.
Wow!
I'll massage your boobs with this.
You'll be happy if I massage your boobs, right?
Yes.
Wow!
I'll massage your boobs.
Your boobs are rubbing against each other.
Yes.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'll massage your hands.
Wow!
It feels good.
I'll massage your neck, too.
Is it okay?
Wow! It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Wow!
It feels good.
My boobs are rubbing against each other.
Yes.
Wow!
I'll massage your mouth, too.
I want you to do that.
Wow!
It feels good.
Oh, it's so good.
Do you want me to give you a massage?
What?
I'll give you a lot of massage.
Oh, it's so good.
I'm not back yet.
Come on.
Thank you so much.
It hurts.
Definitely.
It's still the same, right?
That feeling of it though?
I'll do it.
Wow, that's amazing!
You can see inside it well, right?
That feels good.
Un, un
Ah!
Yes services
Here?
Yes
Does it feel good here?
Yes, I like it here
It feels good
Oh no, I can't do it
I'll put some flour
Oh no
It feels good
I'm going to go again
No, I'm going
Oh no, I can't do it
Oh no
Here?
Yes
I'm going
Oh no
Oh no, I can't do it
It feels good
Oh no
I can't do it
I'm going
Oh no
I can't do it
!!
Hey,
What are you doing?
I'm coming for you
What?
I'm so happy
Do you feel better now?
Yeah, I do
You're such a sweet potato.
But I'm really happy.
That's good.
I heard you're late today.
What's wrong?
Can't I say I want to do it?
No.
You always make me feel good, so it's my turn today.
You couldn't sleep today, could you?
No way.
I'm going to sleep.
Talk to me as usual.
You were going to sleep, weren't you?
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to let you breathe.
So can I feel better?
I'm going to kiss you.
I'm going to kiss you, too.
Don't you like to be licked?
Do you like to be licked?
Do you like it?
I like it.
Do you like to be licked and to be licked?
You like boobs, don't you?
Yes.
I'm going to kiss you.
You're getting bigger.
It feels good to be close to you.
I'm going to kiss you.
It's amazing.
You couldn't sleep because you were so sleepy?
I couldn't sleep because I was sleepy, either.
Let me see.
I'm going to kiss you.
It feels good.
No.
I'm going to kiss you.
It feels good.
You want to be pinched, don't you?
I want to be pinched.
You love boobs, don't you?
I love boobs.
I'm going to kiss you.
You love boobs, don't you?
I love boobs.
It's hot.
Yuzuru's boobs are big, too.
It feels good.
I'm going to kiss you.
You want to be pinched, don't you?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Your boobs are getting bigger and bigger.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
Yuzuru.
I want to go to your house.
You don't want to?
You want to, don't you?
I want to.
I'm going to kiss you.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
Your waist is moving.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
I can't do it.
It's amazing.
Yuzuru licked me.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Why?
You can't do it?
I can't do it.
It's okay.
It's a safe day today.
You can take it out.
I can't do it.
You don't want to do it?
Don't you want to put milk in your sister?
You want to do it, don't you?
You can do it.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
It's a safe day today.
You can take it out.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Give me milk.
You're amazing.
Hey.
You gave me milk.
You're amazing.
Regular milk is good.
You can still do it, can't you?
It's still hard.
One more time?
One more time.
Don't you want to do it?
You want to do it, don't you?
I want to do it.
Kiss me.
It feels good.
You can do it.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
You can do it.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I can do it.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
You can do it.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
You can do it.
Thank you.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
It's like I'm touching the earth.
I can't do it.
You're amazing.
It feels good.
You can do it, right?
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Hey.
What?
It feels good.
I want to do it again.
It's okay.
Give me more.
Do you want me to do it again?
Yes.
I love you.
Give me more.
I can't do it.
You're amazing.
I made your bed dirty.
I can't do it.
I love you.
It felt so good.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy, too.
I wish I could stay like this forever.
You can stay like this forever.
When you like me, you can kiss my boobs.
You can enjoy my boobs.
I'm a strong woman.
You keep giving me boobs.
I can't live without your boobs.
I'm sorry.
Forgive me.