I want to work with patterns made by various panels.
It gets a new role because it's been a while since seeing it,
so I feel very proud and I know that
it's going to make a bigger impression on matchmaking to that of children who don't know much about sewing.
Above all, I just want to make myין production happy.
I wonder if I can pass the audition with this.
Oh, are you Hinako Nitori?
What are you doing in the entertainment room in a swimsuit?
Mr. Kuroi, I have a gravure audition in the afternoon.
So I was practicing my pose.
Well, even if it's an audition, you can't wear a swimsuit in a place like this.
Can I ask you a question?
If you think my pose is good, please take a picture of me.
A picture?
If you really think it's good, say yes.
I think it's good.
Do your best with that smile.
Yes.
Mr. Kuroi.
Thank you for the other day.
I decided to star in a movie.
That's great.
After the teacher took the picture, I passed the audition and decided to star in a movie.
I think it's thanks to the teacher's support.
That's not true.
You're attractive.
Am I that attractive?
Really?
You were looking at my boobs, weren't you?
I wanted to practice kissing with you.
What are you talking about?
The teacher didn't look at my boobs.
There's no way a teacher and a student can practice kissing.
How's my boobs?
What are you doing?
If someone sees this, it'll be a big problem.
Your face is turning red.
You're cute.
What are you talking about?
Stop it.
Mr. Kuroi.
What's up?
I'm here to solve a big problem.
What?
If you two go to the love hotel over there, no one will find you.
What are you talking about?
I can't do that.
You can touch my boobs as much as you want.
Stop it.
Someone's watching.
No one's watching.
We're finally alone.
I don't like teachers and students.
Will you practice kissing with me?
I want to kiss you, so I'll kiss you.
I'll kiss you.
You can touch my boobs.
I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
How's my boobs?
It's big and soft.
Touch me more.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
You can touch me as much as you want.
I'm sorry.
Touch me as much as you want.
Can I touch you directly?
It's amazing.
Your boobs are beautiful.
Touch me as much as you want.
I'm sorry.
I really like your boobs.
Do you want to see my boobs?
I want to see them.
Really?
It's amazing.
Your boobs are beautiful.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
Is it soft?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Why are your boobs so soft?
It's your favorite boobs.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
Your boobs are beautiful.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
Doctor.
Touch me.
It's amazing.
Can I touch you directly?
Look at me.
It's amazing.
I was so excited.
What's wrong?
Do something.
Please don't.
Don't bite me.
Oh...
I can't do it.
Look at me.
It's a bit...
It's difficult.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
I want to drink water, too.
I can't do it.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
You're the best.
I can't do it.
It feels so good.
Look at me.
It's cute.
I can't do it.
I'm just licking you.
Please have sex.
I can't do it.
Go to bed.
Really?
I can't do it.
It feels good.
It feels so good.
I can't do it.
I love you so much.
I love having you on my neck.
I'm sorry.
I'll leave if you do that.
Why?
I'm sorry.
Go to bed.
I can't do it.
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
It feels so good.
You're the best.
I feel so good as your fear.
I feel good as your fear, too.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it.
I almost give up.
I'm sorry.
No, you can't.
I'm a zombie.
You can't.
You can't go.
I'm so happy.
Oh, no.
She's in my stomach.
You felt better when you were in my stomach, didn't you?
Yeah, I felt really good.
That's good.
Thank you for watching until the end.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating.
I'll wash your hands, too.
What?
Are you going to wash my hands?
Yeah.
Okay, wash your hands.
Okay.
I feel like I'm alone.
You have to wash your teeth properly.
Are you embarrassed?
What?
Why are you laughing?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You're fluffy.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
When I get older, I want to lick you again.
What?
Will you lick me?
I want to lick you.
Do you want to lick me?
I'll wash your teeth.
Okay.
Thank you.
Turn around.
Okay.
I'll wash your teeth.
I washed your teeth very cleanly.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
Really?
Are you okay?
I want to lick you.
Do you want to lick me?
What?
Let me lick you.
Do you want to lick me?
Yes.
It was over.
This is the first time I've seen a baby cry so much.
I'm so happy to see her cry.
I'm so happy to see her crying.
It's a relief.
This is great.
It's Perfect.
Your nipples are getting bigger.
Yes.
Delicious.
It's very hard.
It's so good to be able to sleep.
I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
It's hard.
I'm exhausted.
It's hard, isn't it?
I love your boobs.
I love your boobs, too.
I can do it.
Can I have your boobs?
Yes, you can.
Do it more.
More?
Let me see.
It hurts.
You've grown a lot.
You're a gentleman.
I love you.
It felt good.
Are you happy?
Hey.
I can't wait until after school, so let's do it here.
No.
I can't do it.
It's okay.
What are you doing?
Someone might come here.
It's okay.
No.
What are you doing?
Hey.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I can't do this at school.
I can't do it.
Let's stop it.
Do you like chicken, not uniform?
What's this?
It hurts.
Hey.
When we first met, you were excited to see my boobs.
I can't do it.
I love your boobs.
You love my boobs, don't you?
I love them.
I can't believe I'm so excited at school.
I'm not qualified to be a teacher.
I love you.
I love your boobs.
I have a bump on my neck.
You have a good sense of smell.
Oh, my daughter.
I'm so excited.
You're getting bigger.
Can I touch you?
I want to touch you.
I touched your boobs.
I want to go to school.
Can I touch you?
Your boobs are too soft.
I want to go to bed early.
You can't sleep at school.
What are you doing?
I want to go to bed early.
Show me your boobs.
Stop it.
Come here.
It feels good.
Show me your boobs.
I'm embarrassed.
I want to peee on you.
I want to pee on you.
I want to go to bed.
Okay.
I'll go to bed.
Look at me.
I'm looking at you.
I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'm going to sleep.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Look at me.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I love you.
I'll show you a strange look.
What is it?
What is a strange look?
Can you see me?
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
Put your hands in your pockets.
My legs are moving by themselves.
I want to put my hands in my pockets.
I love you.
It feels good.
My legs are moving by themselves.
Are you okay?
Come here.
Sit down.
It feels good.
I'm not good enough to be a teacher.
Give me a hug.
It feels good.
Please.
Give me a hug.
It feels good.
No.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I made you cry again
You're a bad teacher for making me cry at school
I'm glad I found you
I have a favor to ask you
Can I put this lotion on my boobs and make them wet?
Well, the other day, I was asked if I could put lotion on top of my swimsuit
There was a time when I didn't want to do that
I see, that's right
I don't want to do this
But if you want to do it so much, it's okay
That's why I'm naked
Is it really okay?
It's okay
Can I put it on?
I'm really naked
I took it off
Can I put it on?
Wow
It's wet
Can I sleep for a while?
Wow
It's wet
I can see your nipples
I'm embarrassed
What's wrong?
It's wet
Can you put this on your nipples again?
Like this?
Put a lot on
It's wet
Can I sleep for a while?
It's okay
I'm getting stiff
It's wet
You should have gone home earlier
Before that,
I'm going to put a bandage on your nipples
It's wet
It feels good
Look at me
It's warm
It's wet
I want to go to bed
A little more
I want to see your nipples
I want to go to bed
It's amazing
What's wrong?
Let's go to bed
A little more
I want to see your nipples
Let's go to bed
It feels good
Nacchi, your neck is shaking
It's hot
Let me put a bandage on your nipples
Let me rub your nipples
It feels good
It feels good, right?
Your nipples are so soft
It's hot
It feels good
Your nipples are so soft
Let me put a bandage on your nipples
It feels good
Your nipples are so soft
Let me put a bandage on your nipples
Does it feel good?
I love your nipples
Your nipples are so soft
Let me put a bandage on your nipples
It feels good
Your nipples are so soft
Let me put a bandage on your nipples
It feels good
You really love your nipples, don't you?
I'm sorry that I didn't take a video
It's okay
Let me put a lot of lotion on your nipples
It's all because of you
It's hot
Let me put a bandage on your nipples
It feels good
It's hard to stand up
Let me put a bandage on your nipples
It feels good
Look at this
It's amazing
It's all because of you
Let me put a bandage on your nipples
It feels good
Let me see
It's embarrassing
Why are you suddenly embarrassed?
Let me put a bandage on your nipples
It feels good
It's very erotic
Let me put a bandage on your nipples
It feels good
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, Sugabe-chan
You became Soma-chan
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, Sugabe-chan
Succeeds!
I should do it instead of her.
Oh no!
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
.
Do you want to wake up again when sir?
It's hot.
Look at this.
Hey, I'm going to put this on you.
Oh, I see.
Does this feel good?
Yes.
Do you like my wrist?
I want to go to the bathroom as soon as possible.
I want to go to the bathroom.
Oh, I feel good.
I feel good.
Do you want to go to the bathroom?
Yes, I do.
Okay.
Put your hand there.
Do you want to go to the bathroom?
Yes.
Hurry up.
Oh, I feel good.
I like you.
I like you, too.
Oh, I feel good.
I feel like I'm going to sleep.
Look at me.
I'm the worst teacher, but I feel the best inside.
Oh, I feel good.
I'm full of your blood.
I'll clean your boobs.
I'm really sleepy.
Oh, it's hot.
Let's go over there.
I'm still sleepy.
I'm sure you're the best teacher.
I want to go to the bathroom.
I love your boobs.
Look at me.
I feel good.
I love your boobs.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh
It's
Good
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh oh
oh omg
oh
oh oh
ahh
Please lie down.
It's continuously crying.
Do you like it here a lot, doctor?
It's crying.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
I have a lot of pimples.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Please do it again.
I have a lot of pimples.
Your pimples are the best.
Please do it again.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I love you.
Please do it again.
I can't do it.
Look at me.
Please do it again.
I can't do it.
I love you.
You have a cute face.
I love your boobs.
Can I touch your big boobs?
You can touch my favorite boobs.
I can't do it.
Please clean up.
I felt good.
I felt good, too.
I want to do more with you.
I can't do it.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.