Falling over and over again isn't a bad feeling.
Because you may only do so much for the others.
You need to understand if you're sleeping which direction you are looking at,
Do you and you don't know absolutely nothing.
HopeThis video was helpful for you.
I need toboth read these and modify my nightmares fix code.
This email is not changed to 100 ingredients,
This notebook is 100 zl Apps.
This email is from a subscriber.
It only has a link of something to BING ¥20 per month.
This email doesn't contain supplements and other necessities.
Hey, sweetheart, can I do this today?
I'm sorry.
Today I'm tired so help me für like this
Hey sweetheart...
I'm sorry
No, I really can't
Now, it's your turn
I'll help
Let's go.
Hey, do you want to go jogging with me on the weekend?
You've been getting fat lately.
I don't exercise enough.
Let's go together.
Jogging?
Why not?
I don't like it.
So I'm going to quit.
If you're getting fat, I want to treat you to a meal.
Why? Why would you say that?
I'm going.
Hey!
Personal gym.
I didn't know there was a personal gym here.
I didn't know it was in my neighborhood.
Let's ask for an experience.
Excuse me.
I came to see the sign.
Are you looking for an appointment?
No, I'm not.
I just wanted to explain.
Then I'll just talk to you.
Okay.
This gym is a personal gym that makes it easy to make a reservation.
I'm showing you around for free for a month.
Is it free for a month?
Yes.
I haven't been exercising lately, so I'm not feeling well.
I'm going to try it out for stress relief.
Thank you.
How about tomorrow?
I just got a cancel.
It's open.
Tomorrow?
I'm free tomorrow.
Thank you.
I'll be waiting for you tomorrow.
Hey, honey.
There's a personal training gym in my neighborhood.
I went to see it today.
Then they said it was free for a month, so I came to see it.
Is it okay?
I think it's okay if it's free.
Why don't you go see it, too?
I'm not interested.
Why?
It's early tomorrow.
Good night.
Hey.
It's done.
Thank you for your hard work.
You did your best.
Next, let's do stretching.
Stretching?
Yes.
Inhale and exhale from this side.
Let's do it a little more.
Are you okay?
I'm a little numb.
3, 2, 1.
It's done.
It hurts.
It hurts a lot.
It hurts, right?
Next, let's do training on the back of the thighs and abs.
Look this way.
Put your feet on your head.
Put my feet on my head?
Yes.
Put your feet on my head.
Don't let go of this.
Raise your hips as it is.
Raise my hips?
Yes.
That's right.
It's hard.
Put strength on your abs.
Abs.
It's hard.
Do your best.
I'm shaking.
It's done.
Turn around slowly.
Next, let's do muscle training.
8, 9.
Do your best.
Don't put strength on your abs.
Put strength on your chest muscles.
Be aware of this part.
It's done.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
You did your best.
It's hard.
Is it hard?
It's been a while.
Are you relieved of your stress?
I'm relieved of my stress.
There is a way to relieve your stress.
Do you want to try it?
What is it?
It's a way to relieve your stress.
Is it an exercise?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
It's a way to relieve your stress.
I'm relieved of my stress.
This is the best way to relieve your stress.
If you use your muscles, you can relieve your stress.
I'm relieved of my stress.
You are tired.
You should do this.
You should relax.
I'm relieved of my stress.
You are relieved of your stress.
It hurts.
I'm relieved of my stress.
You should relax your muscles.
You feel hot, don't you?
Because you are using your muscles.
I'm relieved of my stress.
It hurts.
You feel hot, don't you?
I'm relieved of my stress.
Breathe in and breathe out.
Please stop.
You should do this.
I'm relieved of my stress.
You have growth hormone.
You should do this when you have growth hormone.
I'm relieved of my stress.
You will be beautiful.
You are sweating.
I'm relieved of my stress.
It's not difficult.
It's natural.
I'm relieved of my stress.
You should be aware of your body.
I'm tired.
I'm relieved of my stress.
There are only two of us.
There are many people.
I'm relieved of my stress.
You should be aware of your body.
You have a scar on your foot.
I'm relieved of my stress.
It's so embarrassing.
Relax your legs.
I can't use it.
Focus on where I'm touching.
It's getting wet.
I shouldn't have touched there.
Ma'am.
You must have been dissatisfied with the bath.
No.
It's not like that.
What's wrong with you?
It has nothing to do with me.
I know.
If you look at your body, you'll feel better.
I can't do it.
What's wrong with you?
You're shaking.
It's not like that.
I'll make it easy for you.
It's okay.
It's amazing.
It's painful.
Don't do that.
You're dissatisfied with the bath, aren't you?
You want me to do more, don't you?
It's not like that.
It's okay. No one will find out.
Let's go to bed.
I can't do it.
It's painful.
You're sweating a lot.
Don't you wear underwear?
I don't wear underwear.
I'm training.
You were going to do that, weren't you?
I'm going to change my clothes.
I can't do it.
You're sweating a lot.
It's not like that.
It's hard.
You're sweating a lot.
Concentrate on your fingers.
I can't do it.
How do you feel?
You're finally telling the truth.
It's comfortable, isn't it?
I can't do it.
You're especially sensitive when you're sleepy.
Let's stop.
How do you feel?
I feel like I'm being killed.
I can't do it.
I'm going to stretch your back.
Please raise your legs.
I can't do it.
You can sit down.
It's getting bigger.
I can't do it.
Please look at me.
You can sit down.
It's getting bigger.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
It's been a while.
It's amazing.
Are you okay?
I'm going to lick your tongue.
I can't do it.
It's hard.
You look like you're in pain.
I can't do it.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I want you to lick me more.
Do you get excited when I lick you?
I can't do it.
You want to lick me, don't you?
It's the same as before.
If you want to lick me, you can do it.
If you and I keep it a secret, we won't be able to do it.
I can't do it.
If you want to lick me, kiss me.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I can't do it.
Please restrain yourself.
You didn't want to do it, did you?
You didn't let me do it.
Is that so?
I can't do it.
You can move more.
I'll make you feel better.
I can't do it.
Can you do it?
If you don't stop now, you may not be able to do it.
If you stop now, you may not be able to do it.
I can't do it.
You don't have to cry.
I want to do more.
I can't do it.
What's wrong?
I'll be waiting for you tomorrow.
I can't do it.
Now I'm completely out of my mind.
I'm young and muscular.
I've become to want his body.
You have to be strong.
Your blood pressure is dropping.
I can't do it.
Don't lose your pace.
Come here.
I can't do it.
I'm training.
Come here.
1,2
Don't lose your pace.
I can't do it.
You haven't lost your pace at all.
I'm going to do the next training.
Come here.
I can't do it.
You have to be strong.
I'm still in the middle of the training.
I can't do it.
Please spread your legs.
Please lie down.
What's wrong with you?
Please raise your hand.
Please hold it down.
It's just a bruise.
What's wrong with you?
You're not sweating, are you?
I'm not sweating.
Do you want to feel better?
I want to feel better.
What's that?
Do you use this?
It's to make you feel better.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
What's this?
You're standing up.
I'm standing up.
It hurts.
Do you want me to help you?
No.
Can I help you?
It hurts.
How do you feel?
Do you feel uncomfortable?
It hurts.
How do you feel?
Raise your legs.
It hurts.
Don't do that.
Do you want me to stop?
Tell me when you're ready.
No.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
No.
Don't do that.
I don't want to live.
Don't you want to live?
You can't live if you hold it in.
You have to hold it in.
Okay.
Hang in there.
You can't do it yet.
No.
It's okay.
If you want to live so much, you can do it.
You can do it.
Hang in there.
Did you feel good?
I felt good.
Do you want to feel better?
I want to feel better.
No.
I feel good.
You can't do it yet.
You can do it.
No.
You can't do it yet.
Do you want to feel better?
I want to feel better.
What is this?
It's a pimple.
No.
It's not a pimple.
Look.
It's a pimple.
Are you excited?
Don't look at me.
Really?
That's amazing.
I'll give you an injection.
Your feet are wet.
What are you doing?
My leggings.
Your leggings are amazing.
I just bought it.
It's easy to see.
What is this?
It's a pimple.
It's amazing.
Thank you for the meal.
Rui-san.
Yes?
You seem to be working hard at the gym lately.
Yeah, I'm doing my best.
I see.
You've lost weight and become beautiful.
I'm happy as your husband.
Is that so?
Well, do your best.
Good night.
Thank you for the meal.
I feel guilty that I lied to my husband who treated me so kindly.
That's all for today's training.
Thank you for your hard work.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for your hard work.
Rui-san.
Yes?
Are you taking a shower?
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I didn't mean to do that.
I'll let you do that.
No.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about me.
I'm not worried.
I'll be fine.
No.
Geez.
Now, lord.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh
Yeah
Hmm
Oh
She hugs him tight and he can cry for her.
You feel like that, don't you?
What do you want me to do for you?
She has been crying for paper money for a long time.
You can't do this here.
You are getting stronger.
I feel sick.
I will disturb you a little.
I'm sick.
lol
I couldn't be strong enough for a second.
It'd be great if today was like this.
But the expectation wasn't that high.
I want to go.
Not yet.
No, no.
I thought I'd let you go if you let me lick your head.
Hey.
I'm tired.
Okay.
I'm going to go to bed.
I'm going to bed.
All right.
Oh...
Oh, no!
Can I take him out of the cage as it is?
He seems to be able to go out
Mom is not finished.
Mom is not finished yet.
It's all right.
to
Ah, ah, ah, ah,
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17,18,19,20,21,22,23,24,25,26,27,28,29,30,31,32,33,34,34,35,36,37,38,39,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40
40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40
40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40,40
40,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50
50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50
50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50
50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50
50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50
50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50
50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50
50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50,50
Mi, that's it?
Let's do it again
No, I can't do it again
Why would be such a thing
It's impossible to do it twice
Good night
I was not satisfied with my husband's sex.
I remembered my sex with him.
Long time no see.
Not yet.
I thought you quit.
No, I didn't.
What were you doing?
Nothing.
I see.
But you've been out of the hospital for a month.
I don't care.
I'll pay for it.
Please train me again.
Do you want to train?
You came back because you liked my sex more than your husband's sex.
What?
I didn't mean that.
Be honest.
You want me to hug you, don't you?
What's wrong?
Please touch me.
I'm not aggressive.
Please.
I think it's too much.
No.
I'm sorry.
Did you hold it in?
Yes.
I wanted you to hold it in.
I didn't.
What's this?
I haven't seen you in a while.
Be quiet.
Oh, no
Oh
Tree
Good
Oh
Ah
She has pain
She's not turning either because I left her her chicken pot on.
This video was shot on the day I had been吃ing chicken alone for over 4 days.
She's moving again...
Close your eyes.
Oh, it's getting wet again, isn't it?
Do you want me to touch you directly?
Yes, I want you to touch me.
Why?
Please touch me directly.
Please.
Oh, it's getting wet again, isn't it?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh,
oh
ah
Ah ah ah ah ah
Why is my hand so stiff?
I don't want to do it anymore.
What's wrong with my hand?
It's okay.
Can I go to sleep?
Of course
I want to sleep
What if I say no?
No
I want to sleep
No, no, no!
Aaah, I can't take it anymore!
Come!
No, that's enough!
Aah!
No, no, no!
It's hot.
Take a deep breath.
How is it?
It's hot.
Let's do training again.
Okay.
I don't think I can compete in this gym for a while.
Thank you for watching.