Yes, I’m going to be in the exam soon, but my Kyuki doesn’t feel at all in crisis.
A child working as a family teacher.
If you want, I would like to ask.
I can ask you.
Sorry to
thanks to
Yes, yes, so please be kind.
Just now.
Welcome to Kyoto.
You have not studied at all.
The daughter of my mother I know.
The family teacher is coming.
I asked him to come next week.
You study hard.
Oh yes, I understand.
Well, I’m going to get dressed, so, I’ll get dressed quickly.
Hi, I am pleased.
I am glad, Mr.
Yes yes yes.
Really please please.
This is please please.
Please come in.
I will hinder you.
Please please please.
Please go.
Stay in the back seat, please.
Sorry to sorry.
I can read Kyoto now.
Yes to.
by Kyoto!
Home Teacher, come here.
I let you wait.
My son Kyoto.
Now I will prepare tea.
Yes, it does not matter.
I am very pleased, Mr Kiki.
I will be taking care of my family teacher today.
It is Karen.
I am a girl student.
With the generation.
Talk about anything.
Yes is
I let you wait.
Please sit down.
Thanks to.
Please go
I will eat.
Yes is
thanks to
I am going to get the exam soon, but I am not in any danger.
Is it yes?
Can you say the previous average?
He went into a normal company like his father.
Not even to be born, it is like a normal life.
I don’t want this kid to be like that.
One is son.
Well, I’m not saying all about academic experience, but of course, if you go to the college, you’ll be more likely to get a job, or even a career, right?
It is.
For my future wife, my future daughter, and my child, I don’t want to be upset.
I know. there is still time until the exam season, and if you study thoroughly now, I think you will know the level of death school.
If it happens, it will help.
is okay.
So, learn quickly.
Yes is
go go
Want to go?
Please please please please.
Where is your room?
I will strive.
Yes, please please please.
I am watching the test results.
Kim is not happy with English.
Oh yes yes
However, since the aspiring school of Kyoto must be English, for now, we must study English.
Yes to.
But honestly, I started studying from this time and won the exam, so Mr. Kyoko is okay.
Let us work hard together.
Yes to.
So, let’s study quickly.
Terminal in English.
No to
Where to do today.
English
for such a beautiful sister.
to teach them to study.
I have never had so much contact with women.
Honestly I was confused.
difficulty
Less than 80.
Why is it?
At first I was confused,
I was in class with Karen.
It was very efficient and fun.
You understand?
Let us try.
Oh, did you do it well?
Oh, you are wrong here.
I always take a class with Karen.
As my grades went up, my love was growing.
No, it is not great, you worked hard.
No, because of the teacher.
No, not so, Kiki has done so hard, so I got this point.
I am not too assistive.
So, try to study more and try to do this.
A special reward.
So what do you do today, math?
of mathematics.
No to
Where to go.
Because I did this last time.
What happened?
well 😂
Mr is
No to?
What is?
If this is done.
I cannot endure either.
Oh is?
No to?
well 😂
Stop it.
What happened?
I like the teacher.
Once you calm.
really
Do you like me?
Want to talk to me?
Because they are hand.
I will lead you.
and then
When I kiss.
Must be kind.
I do not know.
Do you feel your wrist?
The teacher will attack you.
Is it your first time as a teacher?
It feels good.
Will you be kissing your teacher and growing up?
difficulty
No to?
Not to hate.
I will stop.
not stop
Let me hit.
has grown so much.
No to
Oh yeah
Feel good
I will eat.
Oh yeah
Why do you?
by
No to
Oh yeah
Oh well
No to
Oh yeah
Also touch it.
Yes
Oh yeah
No to
Like a nose.
as though
Can I remove?
Feel good
I want to use Manny too.
greatly
by Tjpa
Take off the pants.
Yes, that
I like it.
Teacher, I am very
Yes, to go
Yes, the feeling
Good to touch.
thanks to
Professor I am going.
No is no.
Put in fingers.
Fingered
One by one.
Oh yeah
or to enter.
In this here.
Mixed by
Yes
It feels good.
I just went out, so I’ll go inside.
Wait to
If it is so hard, I will go.
How much... how much...
Going to go.
Oh well... oh well...
Good to touch.
I let him go up here too.
Go to here.
Amazingly...
Wait to?
very much
by
Four cups a day.
Let me drink you.
by
Feeled
very much
Wait a little.
Hardly
Talk about the first time.
by
Let us touch.
Yes
touched together.
greatly
Oh is
This is
Yes
Stop for a moment.
I wanted to know.
What should I do?
Same illness.
Can I get it for the first time?
Yes I will enter.
Yes
Oh well
Great is
Oh yeah
It opened up live.
Oh yeah yeah
It is OK.
Yes
Get out, really.
Oh well
Very slowly.
Eat too much.
A disaster?
Oh yeah yeah
No to
Feel good
Small is
It is small.
When you get out of the house...
I will die...
Oh well...
Oh fuck...
Is it okay?
Montage is
Was it good?
Make it taste.
You can do it again, right?
Can you?
Want to again?
I want to.
Next is
Come here today.
I want to fascinate.
Feels good.
Feel good
Wait, this is so nice.
will come out again.
Going out again.
Where do you want to go next?
Then
Where to go hungry?
Let him go back.
will come out again.
Oh yeah
Oh go go go.
No I will go.
Oh go go
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Studying can work hard again.
Then continue on.
I love you, what happened?
You can’t do it at all, right?
I remembered it before.
It is unmature to me.
No, I just can’t concentrate on myself.
Because only this time.
Okay is it?
If you are happy, can you do well?
promise to
Yes is
Oh yeah
Oh is
No to
Oh yeah
Oh is
Yes
Too much voice.
Your mother will find out.
Yes is
good is
Get up.
Feeled
Not just this.
Concentrate on studying.
Handed
Can I voice my hair?
No to
But
I will be my neck.
Feel good
W W?
Oh yeah
Wait a little.
Studying well?
Do you get this number?
If you can, I’ll play with your breasts.
Yes, I can promise.
really is?
Oh well, it feels good.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Feel good
Go out.
Oh yeah
by
Eat even.
No more
Oh yeah
Do not eat a teacher.
The teacher eats.
No to
Oh yeah
I will go out.
OK is.
Studying hard.
Yes
Oh yeah, it will go.
Oh, I am going
Oh yeah
I was glad.
Can you study hard with this?
So let’s continue to work hard.
Yes
I will hinder you.
Come to me.
Hi to
That is?
Where will you go?
On a trip to the city sea, today my father is also on a trip and I will open a little house, but today is a good day.
Please enjoy your trip.
Kim helps the waterstone and will also buy a gift for Karen.
Thanks to.
Go and go.
Be careful.
Mr Mr Mr Mr.
Sorry, I was in a shit.
Check it now.
Professor what happened?
Something is strange today.
Do you know?
I don’t know, you told me when you first met me.
Talk about anything.
You want me to talk about anything, too.
You remember well.
You said that.
The teacher actually.
Have a boyfriend.
But we broke up yesterday.
Remember that a little.
But now okay.
Study to.
I’t have made my teacher look like this.
Oh is?
Yes
Stop it.
If it were me.
I don’t want to see the teacher like this.
Mr Kiev
Can you comfort the teacher?
The teacher said first.
The girl is
have to be treated carefully.
Sorry to
Let us again.
I should have done it today.
Feeled
and Bell.
Do it again.
I missed the teacher.
No again
Can I touch?
be more kind.
Thanks for the viewing.
It hurt?
beautifully
His face is known.
Why Why?
Touch it too.
Today to Mr.
Mr is beautiful.
really is?
Feels good?
Feels good here?
Yes, it feels good.
But it doesn’t grow up on the top of the tank.
The teacher is wet.
greatly
Because I am a Sush, I grow up.
that
Yes
No to
I want to put my fingers in.
It feels good there.
I am in the collar above.
If you were so tough.
greatly
It is already done.
Professor I went.
I comforted Kim.
I thank you for comforting you when you grow up.
and matcha.
Oh, it looks very hard.
But okay?
Feel good
Why do I want?
I want to lick.
I have grown up, brother.
The teacher will lick you and comfort you.
Feel good
Feels good?
Mr is
I want your breasts.
Sleep to
Do you like breasts?
I like the teacher’s chest.
well
Feel good
That is
Oh yeah
Yes
Do you like it today?
I want you to comfort me more.
How to comfort me.
Strengthen the house.
About the teacher.
Then
No to
Yes, the feeling
Oh yeah
Chris is blue.
Super 4 is dead.
Oh very much.
Also from behind.
I want you to sleep.
You can go to sleep, baby.
Matcha is
greatly
The teacher decided.
That is determined.
greatly
Feel good
Wait, wait that.
was harsh.
The teacher says again.
I want to go.
Stay this.
that
Not to Amy.
This is amplified.
OK is.
and people
will be born.
Hickey
I don’t feel comfortable.
properly
Feels too good.
Because it is growing.
Can I sleep on my teacher?
It is awesome.
The Mr.
Yes to?
Feels too good.
Feel good
My sperm was filled.
It smells like it was just.
Do you like your ass?
I like my ass.
Feel it well.
Feel good
Incredibly hit
The ass, the ass, the ass.
If you touch the chick, it will get so big.
Do you like chickens?
I like the chick.
I will eat too much.
by Chick
I was surprised.
Which of my likes?
by Chick
Have you seen?
See now.
No longer bad.
Tastefully
Yes
How is?
I’t go a little.
Maybe not become.
to be?
Want to go?
Good luck to come.
No, we will go.
So go with me?
No, I go
Go to
Go to go.
Not so much Dora.
I will clean it.
Oh yeah
It tastes guilty.
by Tejas
What is?
I want to kiss.
Oh yeah
Oh, the feeling
What a shit.
Oh well feel.
No to No.
You feel good.
No to no, little
Drink it, Ivy
Feeled...
Because it is very postural.
Tagged,  Tagged  Tagged
Be calm and get the death penalty.
No, I will go.
I really go.
No, no can
No, no no
Stop this.
You guys
Oh fuck it.
No, no, no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
by Rush
Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes
Oh well, it feels good.
Feel good
This one is more excellent.
Oh is
by
I’ve become aware of what I feel like.
Yes
Tell me what it feels good.
What is temporary?
What do you like temporarily?
Yes
Feels good.
Oh is
Oh, it feels good too.
Oh well, it feels good.
Oh, a little
I want more.
Oh yeah
It feels good.
Let me put your breasts.
I want to be in the cake.
OK is.
Oh well, it feels good.
I have gone out before this.
I have to be patient today.
Yes
by Ruth
Oh yeah
Can you be able to stand so fast?
Yes
See also
I will go.
Instead slowly
Oh yeah
Oh yeah also.
Feels good?
Yes
Oh yeah
Oh well Mr.
This is Damn?
Yes
Feeled...
Feel good
Please please
It is awesome.
by Ruth
Oh yeah
Oh oh oh
No more
I have worked hard.
Oh oh oh
Go to sleep?
I will sleep.
Where do you want to go?
I want to put it in my mouth.
Welcome to all.
Tastefully
I could not endure.
Yes
can
Can you blame the teacher?
Yes
It is going well.
Feel badly
I was too hungry.
Chew was direct.
It feels bad.
Feel badly
Great is
It tastes good.
slowly
Feel good
Damn too much.
Go to go.
Put in fingers.
Do you feel good?
Fuck that.
greatly
Feel good
Fuck that.
It feels good.
My stomach hurt.
Feel good
It is time to go out.
Oh, the feeling
Feeled
Oh yeah
by
No to No.
Oh well
Feel badly
Oh yeah
Do not stop.
Feels good.
No to
It feels.
Oh yeah
by Huan
for a while.
Yes
Oh, it is bad.
very painful
Oh yeah yeah
Earl, America is a bit.
America is good.
You are a fucking fucking.
determined
Groch
I had a game.
Oh...
Wait a little, I go.
Oh go go
followed a little.
Wait, it is bad.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Oh, it is bad, it will be.
I am bad, I am going.
Go to go.
Oh go go
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah yeah
to
Oh is
Oh oh oh
Oh yeah
by
Oh, so cute cute
Long time hard.
☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆
Very good feeling.
Oh yeah
Oh oh
by
Oh yeah
No to 🙂
No to
Oh oh
by
Wow, it feels good.
Oh yeah, yeah
It feels good.
Oh yeah yeah
I put it out my breast.
Oh go go
Oh yeah yeah
Kane is
It makes no sense at all.
Really worried, but so.
Really I am sorry.
Mr is
What is?
If only
If you get the exam.
I want you to meet me.
Then
If you want to test.
You can think.
Mr is