This video is a derivative work of the Touhou Project. It may be disrespectful of character image and may not be suitable for all ages.
Please be careful as this is a derivative work of the Touhou Project.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, Haruka, let's go!
Ah, this is bad.
Ah, it's coming out, it's coming out.
Ah, it feels so good.
It's the best.
It's amazing.
A lot came out.
Hey, Haruka.
You said it a lot.
Ah, it feels so good.
You didn't notice the act of lying at all.
It feels so good.
You're the only one who feels good.
Everyone, be careful on your way home.
Ah, that's right.
The environmentalists, please wait a moment.
Please submit the materials for today's test at home.
I'm really irritated.
Um, Nanase-san.
What?
No, um...
The documents for the committee?
Nozaki will do mine too.
Anyway, you promised to go home with your boyfriend today.
If you go home without permission, you'll get scolded by the manager.
You should be grateful that I'm still here.
Ah, yes.
Nozaki Yoshizuki.
The same committee in the class.
Otaku.
The type I hate the most.
The novels I read are disgusting.
I'm a big guy, but I'm still doing this and that.
Most of all, the most disgusting thing is...
Ah, here it comes.
If I show up a little bit,
this guy will bite my foot.
Do you think I haven't been found out?
Hey.
Nozaki, do you think I haven't been found out?
This is perfect.
I'll relieve my stress with this.
Take it off.
What?
In order to show that you don't know about me,
I'll put your dick on the group line.
How big is your dick?
Size?
It's about normal.
I see.
Come on, get up.
But...
Come on, take it off.
Really?
In a place like this?
Yes, come on, take it off.
He's trying to steal my panties.
Anyway, his dick is small.
What are you doing?
It's disgusting.
I'm not doing anything.
No way.
It's not the same size as my panties.
What? Don't lie to me.
I can't take off my panties at this moment.
What?
No way.
I can't take off my panties.
Hey, Haruka.
I told you.
Shut up.
Don't be shy.
I want to have fun, too.
Hey, Nozaki.
Well...
Can you make a surprise with this?
What the hell am I doing?
Don't make a surprise with this.
Hey.
Nozaki.
Don't tell anyone.
I'll kill you if anyone finds out.
Oh, no.
It's too big.
It's under my belly button.
It's disgusting.
I'm so excited that I can have sex.
Don't make a mistake.
You're just a dildo.
Don't tell anyone.
Don't make a sound.
It's disgusting.
Yeah.
Rubber doesn't fit your size.
If you feel good, say it.
If you say it, I'll kill you.
Oh, no.
I'm being pushed up.
Don't tell anyone.
What was that?
My body was shaking.
I think I can do it.
It's totally different from a big one.
I can do it.
I'm making a serious voice.
Oh, no.
Wait a minute.
Why are you pushing my chest?
I told you I don't care who you are.
Oh, no.
I didn't do it on purpose.
What are you doing?
You're too big.
You're disgusting.
Oh, no.
What are you doing?
Who gave you permission?
Oh, no.
Don't go there.
You're too big.
Oh, no.
Stop pushing my chest.
I didn't do it on purpose.
Who gave you permission?
Stop it.
Oh, no.
Don't go there.
Why are you so big?
Oh, no.
Stop it.
You're moving too much.
Shut up.
Don't call my name.
I'm sorry.
You're moving too much.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Oh, no.
I haven't given you permission yet.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you so big?
You're gross.
Oh, no.
Hurry up.
It hurts.
Oh, no.
Stop it.
It hurts.
Oh, no.
Wait a minute.
It hurts.
Can't you hear me?
Wait a minute.
Stop it.
It hurts.
You're gross.
Hurry up.
Wait a minute.
I can't go any further.
What are you doing?
I don't feel good.
I can't get closer.
Are you stuck inside?
No way.
Wait a minute.
Are you trying to get inside?
If you get inside, I'll kill you.
I'll kill you.
No way.
I'll be kicked out.
I've never forgiven Ryosuke.
Wait a minute.
No.
Don't get inside.
I'll get inside.
It hurts.
What are you doing?
Can you get up?
It hurts.
I'm stuck inside.
I just said it.
I can't stop feeling good.
Haruka, cheer up.
You apologized for being late yesterday.
I'm not angry.
Then why are you so upset?
If you have any complaints,
Don't be upset.
I'm sorry, I'm late.
Why do you know my LINE?
I heard it from your friend, Otaku-kun.
You avoided me for a week, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
You didn't go to the party.
What can I do to make you forgive me?
You're disgusting.
I really hate him.
But...
What are you doing?
I like this.
It's too big, isn't it?
I'll clean it up for you.
I'm getting hot just by drying it.
There's a lot in me.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
That's not good.
That's amazing.
Why?
I...
I can't forget how I felt at that time.
I can't reach Ryosuke.
I feel like I'm being crushed by this big dick.
Why?
You should be grateful to me.
Wait a minute.
I'm the only one who can make you feel bad.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
Come here.
What is that?
I don't know.
Who is that?
I've been feeling like this recently.
I don't feel good when I have sex with you.
But when you have sex with me, I love you so much.
Really?
Yes.
Oh, it's so annoying.
I can't love you because you're so small.
I don't think there's anyone who supports you.
Shut up.
If I get better, I'll be better.
You're not a girl at all.
I'm so scared.
Is he listening to what I'm saying?
Oh, no.
I can't hold my voice because I'm suffocating.
I feel like I'm being spoiled just by sucking.
What should I do?
I want to put it in soon.
I'm scared.
I can't hold my voice.
I'm so scared.
You can't hold your voice.
It's not good for you to be weak.
I can't hold my voice.
OK
Aftermath of call
Where are you guys?
I've just been called up by Haruka
As expected
I have to go
You don't wanna go today?
No...
Let's go back to the dorm.
Let's go back.
I'll go first.
Let's go back to the dorm.
Let's go back.
I'm tired.
I did it.
I chose
the grosser bed
than my boyfriend.
Nagase, are you okay?
I'm not okay.
It's not enough.
Nagase,
let me sleep like that time.
It's hot.
It's comfortable.
It's amazing.
I didn't know this kind of sex.
It's comfortable.
Let me sleep more.
It feels so good.
Feels good?
Give me more.
I want more.
Here.
There.
More.
Give me more.
There.
More.
Give me more.
Let me go.
Sex with him?
I don't think it would..
It's amazing.
It's hot.
It feels so good.
It's coming.
It's hot.
Musaki's genitalia are coming out.
It's amazing.
I'm definitely hooked on this.
It's coming out.
It's okay.
I'm pregnant.
Give me more.
It's hot.
What are you doing?
Don't get close to me.
I can't kiss you.
I'm having sex.
I can't.
I can't kiss you.
It's hot.
I can't.
I understand.
I understand why it feels so good.
I'm being forced.
I'm pregnant.
I can't.
Don't get carried away.
I'll leave some time for you.
Don't tell anyone.
I won't.
I'll call you again.
I can't.
That's disgusting.
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm scared of the baby.
I don't like you.
That's disgusting.
I hate this kind of meeting.
I didn't know it was like this.
Do it again.
You can do it.
Someone might come.
I can't believe it.
We've been together for a long time.
That's no good.
You're getting bigger.
You haven't told anyone about me, have you?
I haven't told anyone.
Really?
Really.
That's good.
Are you okay?
That feels good.
It feels good.
It's good.
What?
Can I touch your chest?
Are you out of your mind?
I'm sorry.
Does it hurt?
What?
You're not yourself.
Are you out of your mind?
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I don't care.
It's heavy.
I'm sorry.
What?
Can I touch you more?
I can hear you.
It feels good.
I can't.
Nozaki found my weakness.
What are you doing?
It feels good.
What?
Are you out of your mind?
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Can I touch your head?
Here?
Yes.
It feels good.
You know how to touch.
I'm sorry.
You're loud.
I can't sleep.
It's amazing.
You...
Shut up.
Let me lick you.
Do you mind?
No, I don't mind.
It feels good.
Shut up.
What?
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I don't like you.
I'm sorry.
Shut up.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I'm too nervous.
I'm going to cry.
It's amazing.
You're a good boy.
Everything is destroyed by this guy.
Do you go out first and then come out?
Yes.
Make sure no one is there.
What am I doing?
Nanase.
What?
It's winter break.
I have something to do with my family.
Can I see you during winter break?
What?
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
This guy.
He asked me to do it because it's a game tomorrow.
Is this the end?
A rough sex.
I'm the only one who's satisfied.
I'm not satisfied at all.
If it was Nozaki at a time like this, it wouldn't end like this.
What am I thinking?
He's not here for a while.
I'm going home.
Are you going home?
Yes.
I see.
I'm going to sleep a little more.
Yes.
Nozaki hasn't replied yet.
Of course.
It hasn't been that long yet.
I'm sorry.
No.
It's a little big.
I can't be that gross.
It feels good.
Haruka, you're so strong.
It felt good, didn't it?
Besides, Nozaki is the same as me.
It's annoying.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
I fell asleep as it was.
Today is the day to go to the dormitory with Ryosuke.
I'm going to change my clothes.
I feel like I'm going to fall in love with him on the way home.
I'm going to put on some makeup.
Is it Ryosuke?
I'm going to change my clothes.
Hey, Nanase.
Is this your house?
Yes.
Is something wrong?
No.
Come in.
I've never been in a girl's room.
Can I really come in?
Yes.
Is this your room?
He entered my room in a hurry.
He is very active.
Oh, yes.
This is a souvenir.
If you don't mind...
I don't care.
But...
I wanted to see you.
Hey.
My father won't come home until tonight.
I don't have any plans today.
But...
Isn't this bigger than usual?
No.
I've been with my family all the time.
I didn't have time to take it out.
I see.
So, you have a lot of them.
Yes.
It feels good.
No.
I can't stand it anymore.
Get up.
I can't.
If I put his bed in front of me, it will be hot.
I have to start preparing for the baby.
The medicine...
Your eyes...
Hurry up.
It feels good.
Yes.
I don't know what I'm doing.
I brought him to my room.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Wait, Nozaki.
It's been a week.
I'm not used to it yet.
No.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I just put it in my mouth.
I couldn't feel it with Ryosuke.
It feels good.
It's hot.
This is the weapon when he is about to die.
Really?
It's hot.
I'm being pushed.
My spirit is like a coffin.
I'm filling the inside of the earth with this.
It's hot.
I have to eat this.
I'm being pushed.
Your mouth is dangerous.
I'm happy just to be praised.
I don't want to resist this temptation.
It's hot.
My smartphone is ringing.
Are you okay?
I don't care.
I'm sorry.
Shut up.
You should focus on me.
It's hot.
I'll put this in your mouth.
Do it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I want more.
Break it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Calm down.
Break it.
More.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm going to pull it.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Ah
Hmm
Oh
Ah
ouch!
oh, my...
it hurts...
ouch!
oh!
what are you pulling out?
sorry...
don't pull it out
oh!
oh, it feels good
it feels good
oh!
Beware of women.
Akira?
I love you!
I feel good here.
Ouch, ouch!
Hey, hey!
Stop, I'll get your blood!
All right.
It's okay.
Come closer.
Ron, what are you doing?
There.
I want to move it more.
It feels good.
But my knees and leg get stiff.
They are strengthless.
Ah, okay, ah, okay, ah, okay, ah,
This is
a
figure
love
ah ah
Oh, no.
Let me move more.
There.
Oh, no.
That.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
I want more.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Masae,
Let's take a break.
What?
Oh, no.
I want more.
I can't do it.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Oh, no.
I feel very tired.
It feels very good.
Oh, no.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
I'm going.
The real root of good and evil.
I like it from behind.
I'm going.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
I'm not satisfied.
It's supposed to be gross, but it feels good.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
It's really deep.
I'm going.
Why am I being swept away?
This is becoming a habit.
I'm becoming Naho Masaki.
I really like this.
I can't, I can't, I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to sleep.
I can't.
I can't sleep.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
I can't.
I've had enough.
Crush me.
I can't. It feels good.
I want more.
Let me out.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
No one can see you when you go home.
I'll take this.
I'm sorry.
I just dropped it.
Hey.
I'll call you again.
Take care of me.
I'm sorry.