I'm glad I got a job in Tokyo, but it wasn't the kind of job I wanted to do.
Half a year later, I became a slacker.
In the end, my boss found out that I wasn't motivated, and fired me.
Now, I'm living in my hometown.
But why did I go to Tokyo when I wasn't motivated?
It's been a while. Nothing has changed since I went to Tokyo.
It's only been half a year, and nothing has changed.
Well, let's go upstairs.
Mom, Manabu is here.
Oh, Manabu, it's been a while.
You've gotten so much skinnier since you went to Tokyo.
Is that so?
Come on, don't talk to him like that. He's already an adult.
He's been coming here a lot since he was little.
He's like a child to me now.
Oh, I see.
Anyway, hurry up and make me a snack. I'm going out for a drink.
Yugo, you don't drink much, do you?
If you do, I'll make you lunch.
The reason why I went to Tokyo when I wasn't motivated
was because I loved Yumi.
I didn't want to fall in love with my best friend's mother.
I thought I'd forget her if I left her.
It's a waste to go back to Tokyo.
Is that so?
If I went to Tokyo, I'd pick up girls every day and hang out with them.
Yugo, stop eating and talking.
Oh, shut up.
Manabu isn't a man yet, so I'm trying to make him a man.
What are you talking about?
You've never been in a relationship with a girl, have you?
I hang out with girls every day.
I was confessed to by the same girl yesterday.
Yes, yes.
Manabu, you don't have to listen to her.
Oh, I see.
But you have someone you like, don't you?
Someone I like?
I do have someone I like.
You do?
But you can't talk to her yourself.
You've been like this for a long time.
I'm talking to Manabu right now.
You shut up.
It's okay.
I'm trying to make Manabu a man.
You've been quiet for a long time.
Right, Manabu?
Damn it.
I win again.
Don't use tricks.
I hang out with girls every day, so I'm good at games.
I see.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Come back soon.
Okay.
I'm going to steal all of Manabu's life.
I'm going to steal Manabu's life.
Good morning, Manabu.
Where is Yugo?
He's still sleeping.
No, it's Sunday.
He'll have breakfast soon.
Yes.
Women should be a little more aggressive.
Is that so?
If you think you have a little bit of it, you can do it.
Yuko, can't you eat a little quieter?
So I'm teaching Manabu how to treat women.
He's been on the back foot for a long time.
You can't talk to your favorite woman, can you?
I was talking about that, and I got an invitation from a woman.
What? You want me to meet you right now and have a date?
I can't help it.
It's Keiko-chan, who works part-time. I'm going.
I'm sorry, Manabu.
Oh, no.
This is the last plate.
Thank you.
You don't have to help me.
No, thank you for the meal.
Manabu, when you talk to people, speak firmly.
I'm sorry.
Manabu, if you're confident, you'll be able to be popular.
You're pretty good-looking.
If you can tell your feelings to the person you like, you'll be fine.
Really?
I like you.
Yes, that's right.
No, that's not it.
I've liked you for a long time.
What are you talking about?
You just told me that if I tell you my feelings, you'll be popular.
What?
What are you talking about?
Are you okay?
Stop it.
Hey, Manabu.
What's wrong?
I really like you.
Manabu, what's wrong?
What are you talking about?
Stop it, Manabu.
Please.
Stop it.
Manabu, what's wrong?
Let go of me.
I like you.
What are you talking about?
Stop it.
Let go of me.
Please.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
Stop it.
You know I like you.
That's not true.
I like you.
I'm your friend.
It's none of your business.
Stop it.
Please.
I like you.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
Stop it.
I like you.
Let go of me.
Manabu, let go of me.
I like you.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Let go of me.
You know I like you.
I'll tell Yugo.
I'll tell him you like me.
Wait a minute.
You can't do that.
I like you.
What are you doing?
You can't do that.
Stop it.
I like you.
You can't do that.
It's wet.
Don't touch me.
You can't do that.
I can feel it.
It's wet.
You can't do that.
Stop it.
It's wet.
You can't do that.
What are you doing to your friend's mother?
Stop it.
You can't do that.
Everything is delicious.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
You can't do that.
It's wet.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
You can't do that.
You're so beautiful.
The water is overflowing.
You can't do that.
You're amazing.
You can't move your fingers.
It's going to overflow.
You're amazing.
Stop it.
Ah! Ah! Wow!
Ah! Yumi-san! Are you okay?
Don't take it!
No! No!
Ah!
Don't!
Ah! Yumi-san!
It's delicious.
Why? Why? What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Ah!
I'm eating all of your offerings.
Oh! No! Don't!
Stop it!
It's delicious.
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm sorry.
Yumi.
Yumi, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Yumi.
Yumi, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Yumi.
Yumi, I love you.
Don't say that.
Yumi, I can't take it anymore.
What are you doing? Stop it.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
Yumi, I want to go inside.
No.
You can't do that.
Stop it.
I can't.
I'll do it with my mouth.
With my mouth?
Please.
I want to go inside.
Wow.
I'll do it with my mouth.
You don't have to put up with it.
Please do it.
Yumi.
I'm sorry.
No.
I feel so bad.
I love you.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
You don't want to go out yet?
Where does it feel good?
It feels so good.
Does it feel good here?
Yumi.
It feels so good.
Does it feel good here?
It feels so good on both sides.
It feels so good.
Yumi.
I want you to lick my nipples.
Do you want me to lick your nipples?
It feels so good.
Does it feel so good on your nipples?
It's okay.
Don't hold it in.
Let it out.
It feels so good.
I'll do it.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
I want you to lick my nipples.
You can't do that.
Please, Yumi.
What are you saying?
You can't do that.
Let it out here.
Yumi.
You can't do that.
I want to be with you, Yumi.
Why are your nipples so hard?
Yumi.
Don't hold it in.
Let it out.
Why?
What's wrong, Yumi?
You can't do that.
Let it out here.
Don't hold it in.
What's wrong?
You can't do that.
Please, Yumi.
You can't.
Yumi...
I'm so sorry, Yumi-san.
No!
Why? Why did you do this?
Because I love you, Yumi-san.
I love you so much, Yumi-san.
No, no.
Manaka, stop it.
Yumi-san.
Stop it.
I love you, Yumi-san.
Manaka, why did you do this?
I love you so much.
I love you, Yumi-san.
It's in there!
Stop it!
It's connected!
It's connected to my finger!
Stop it!
What are you doing?
It's connected to my finger!
It feels good.
Stop it!
I can still do it.
What are you doing?
It feels good.
I can still do it.
Shake your hips.
It feels good.
Don't let it out.
I'll show you more.
It feels good.
Don't do it.
Don't let it out.
It feels good.
Don't do it.
Yumi.
I'm sorry.
Don't force yourself to do things like this.
But I really like you.
I feel like I'm going crazy.
Yumi.
I know.
I can't help it.
But don't tell anyone.
Yumi.
I'm home.
I'm tired.
Welcome home.
Manabu, you're still here?
Yes.
I missed you.
I see.
Let's stay here tonight.
Let's play a game again.
Did you go home?
You're late.
Keiko asked me to stay longer.
You said that again.
You forgot that you had a part-time job.
You're so stubborn.
I'm different from Manabu.
Manabu is a very manly person.
He has a lot of things going on with the person he likes.
What are you talking about?
I heard a lot of things while you were away.
Of course.
Did you take a bath?
Don't lie down.
It's okay.
You should take a bath too.
Okay.
Yumi.
You're not yourself.
Wait.
Yumi.
No.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Yumi, you're gross.
You're gross just by doing this.
Yumi.
Yumi, your butt is so elastic.
You don't have to take it off.
What are you talking about?
Yumi.
Your butt is so elastic.
I'm going to blame you.
What are you doing?
Yumi.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Yumi.
You've grown so much.
Yumi, you're so loud.
I can hear you.
I wonder if he can hear me.
What should I do?
Mom, I don't have any medicine.
I put it in the shelf above the mirror.
I told you before.
Did I?
Why are you two still fighting?
It's okay.
Go wash your face.
Okay.
Yumi.
I'm sorry.
No.
Yumi.
I'm sorry.
You're so dirty.
You need to take off your pants.
You can't do this.
I don't care about my pants.
I can't stand it.
Really?
Let me do it.
Yumi.
It hurts.
You're sucking me so hard.
Yumi.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Yumi.
No.
I can't stand it.
Yumi.
You're so dirty.
You told me to do it.
Yumi.
I want to dye your hair.
What are you talking about?
Yumi.
Look at your butt.
You're so dirty.
Yumi.
Can I do it?
No.
You can't do it.
Yumi.
I'm sorry.
I can't move my hips.
Yumi.
I'm asking you to do it.
But I can't.
You know that, right?
I can't.
My voice is getting louder.
Yumi.
I can't.
You're a bad person.
Your son's friend did this to you.
Yumi.
Don't say that.
I'll teach you more.
Yumi.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't.
I quit my job.
I had nothing to do.
I stayed at Yumi's house.
I stole Yugo's eyes.
I did a lot of dirty things.
It's like...
I've been keeping it deep in my heart.
I want to make Yumi's feelings explode.
Many times.
Yumi.
Manabu.
What?
Don't touch me.
Manabu.
What's wrong?
Yumi.
I can't live without you.
Please.
I beg you.
I can't live without you.
I know.
Manabu.
No.
I'm not home.
My family is worried.
Please go home.
Manabu.
Yumi.
You're amazing.
I'm sorry.
Don't say that.
No, you can't say that.
I'll let you say that.
I'm sorry.
Don't say that.
Yumi.
I feel good.
Manabu.
You feel good here, right?
I feel good.
Do you feel good here?
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
Do you feel something?
I didn't expect you to lick me like this.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Yumi.
I'll keep it a secret from Yugo, Manabu's parents.
Of course.
Yumi.
I feel good.
Something is coming out of here.
I feel like I'm eating rice cake.
I feel good.
Yumi.
I want to dye you my color.
I feel good.
Yumi.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
If you feel good, put it in my mouth.
No.
I want to dye you my color.
Put it in my mouth.
Yumi.
I feel good.
Put it in my mouth.
No.
I want to put it in your mouth.
Okay.
I won't put it in your mouth.
Be my girlfriend.
What are you talking about?
I can't do that.
Be my girlfriend.
I love you.
Yumi.
I'm full.
I'll put it in your nose.
Yumi.
No.
Okay.
I'll put it in your nose.
Be my girlfriend.
I won't put it in your nose.
Yumi.
If you don't be my girlfriend, I'll tell Yugo.
No.
Don't tell Yugo.
Don't tell him that we're having an affair.
No.
Be my girlfriend.
Yumi.
I'll put it in your mouth.
I'll make you feel good.
Otherwise, I'll put it in your mouth.
I have to go.
I'll put it in your mouth.
Let me go.
I'll go.
Oh, Yumi-san.
Yumi-san, I want to be your child.
I want to be your child and be with you everyday, Yumi-san.
What are you talking about?
She's still sleeping.
What are you going to do in Yugo's room?
Yugo always makes fun of me.
So I want to play a prank on her.
What?
I'm going to wake Yumi-san up in front of Yugo.
Yumi-san.
Wait.
What are you going to do if she wakes up?
Yugo will be shocked and leave the house.
What?
Then, I'll live here.
Wait.
Yumi-san.
Take off the clothes I put on you.
Take off the clothes in front of Yugo.
There's a storm.
There's a storm in the house.
Wait.
Yumi-san.
Do you feel good?
No.
I didn't know it was this strong.
Yumi-san.
You're sweating a lot.
You're getting wet.
Yumi-san.
Are you okay?
Look, you're in tears.
Look at you, in front of your son.
You're so sad.
Look at you.
You're in front of your son.
Look at you, in front of your son.
It's amazing.
It's easy to get a cramp.
Look at you, in front of your son.
You're so sad.
It's amazing.
Look at you, in front of your son.
You're so sad.
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this to me?
That's right.
And you're so wet.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for making you so wet.
I'm sorry I'm a bad mother.
Look at you, in front of your son.
Where are you being licked?
You have to tell me where you are.
I'm sorry.
Are you being licked?
I'm going to lick your whole body.
I'm sorry I'm a bad mother.
I'm sorry.
Look at you, in front of your son.
Your fingers feel good.
It feels good.
I love you.
Your fingers feel good.
It feels good.
I'm going to lick your whole body.
Your fingers feel good.
It feels good.
Hold my butt tight.
Harder.
I'm sorry.
My back hurts.
I'm going to rub your back.
I'm sorry.
My back hurts.
It feels good.
My neck hurts.
I'm begging you.
I'm sorry.
You made me like this.
You're so nice.
Look at me more.
Touch me more.
You're so nice.
I'm getting hot.
Smell me.
How do you feel?
I'm going to stimulate your lower jaw.
I'm going to stick my tongue in your mouth.
I want you to lick my tongue.
It hurts.
How do you feel?
You're so mean.
You were licked in front of your son.
I'm sorry, mother.
Your son is licking his mouth.
Are you licking me?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, mom.
It's dirty.
Shake it.
Oh, my God.
It's so dirty.
Shake it.
Oh, my God.
Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
I want you to do this, too.
I was licked a lot.
Do you like being licked?
Oh, my God.
Touch me a lot.
You're my ideal person.
Really?
Oh, my God.
You're so cute.
Touch me a lot.
Your tits are getting harder.
It's getting really hard.
I'm so sick.
If your tits are getting harder, your lower back will move.
Oh, my God.
I can't stand it anymore.
I can still smell your clothes.
I was licked a lot.
Oh, my God.
Yui.
It feels so good.
Tell me what you're talking about.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done it, Mom.
Mom.
I'm so...
I'm such a naughty kid.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it's good.
It feels so good.
Oh, wow.
Oh, Yui.
It feels so good.
My body can't take it anymore.
My stomach is hot.
Can you lick my stomach?
I want to lick it.
Lick my stomach.
Oh, it feels so good.
It feels so good.
Oh, my stomach.
Oh, lick my stomach.
It's good.
My chest.
Lick my chest.
It's good.
It feels so good.
I'll massage your stomach.
It's painful, isn't it?
It's painful, but I'm happy.
Are you happy?
Are you happy that you can't breathe?
Okay, I'll do more.
I'll do more.
It feels so good.
I want you to suck my butt.
I'm embarrassed to see you.
You're so mean.
Oh, it feels so good.
I'm embarrassed to see you.
It feels so good.
It's hot.
It's very hot.
I'm hot, too.
It's hot.
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
Mom.
It feels so good.
What's wrong?
I got him
Uuu...
Boo!
How do you feel?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I can hear you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It feels good.
It feels so good.
It's amazing.
It hurts.
Don't do that.
Don't cry.
It hurts.
It feels good.
You can do it.
Let's do it again.
I want to do it again.
I want to do it.
I want to see your butt.
Look at my butt.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
Touch my butt.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
Touch my butt.
I can't go any further.
It's amazing.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
The relationship between Mr. Yumi and me with which it has robbed deeply and deeply
goes deeper and deeper with the time
but I will tell its story again at another opportunity