A few days later
Mom, hurry up!
Okay
Okay, I'm going to bring the sweets
Here we go
Hard, hard, hard
How is it?
It depends on the spirit
It depends
Hard, hard, hard
I can do this forever
How is it?
Thank you, Kanako-san
Mom, hurry up!
Okay
Who do you think will win?
Japan
I'm going to win
In this big house where my husband is not here,
it's always just me and my son Takashi
But today, my son's best friend Yu-kun came to play
It's been a long time since we've had such a lively night
I'm looking forward to the weekend's Japan Championship
I'm looking forward to it
Let's watch it together
Are you sure?
It's okay, even if it's noisy, it won't be a nuisance
But is it okay?
Isn't it a nuisance?
That's not true
Let's watch it together
All right, it's decided
Let's watch the Japan Championship together
Really?
We're going to watch it all together?
All of it, of course
It's going to be fun
Mom was the manager of the soccer club
Oh, really?
Go, go, go!
You can do it!
It's going in!
It's coming, it's coming!
All right!
I'm sorry
It's a big news
I just hugged my son's friend by chance
It was just a coincidence
But...
Is this excitement a sign of joy?
Or...
I'm sorry to bother you
It's okay
I'm sleepy
The next game is at home
I'm going to go
Yes
Oh, no!
I can do it
There's still time to hurry
Uta will do something
Go, go, Japan!
Please win
I'm sorry
I didn't know my son's friend would be so upset
What did I do?
I'm sorry
But...
Right?
Yeah, you're right.
I got it.
I'm sorry.
Let's watch it again.
Yeah, let's watch it again.
The next match will be the most interesting.
I wonder what will happen.
But we'll definitely win.
We'll win.
We'll win, we'll win.
Right?
We'll win, right?
Yeah, we'll win.
Yeah, right?
3, 2, 1
Yes!
We won!
I'm so happy.
Seriously?
We won, we won.
I'm so happy.
I'm so jealous.
Let's go to bed, everyone.
What?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Let's go to bed.
I might not be able to sleep.
3, 2, 1
Excuse me.
Yuu-kun?
What's wrong?
You have to sleep.
Kanaka-san, you're avoiding me, right?
No, I'm not.
The kiss the other day.
I can't forget the kiss we had that day.
Since the day we hugged, I've been thinking about you.
You too, right?
That's not true.
Ah, sorry.
Thank you.
You can't.
Yuu-kun, you can't.
I'm Takashi's mother.
You can't.
No.
Hurry up and sleep.
You can't do this.
You can't.
I'm fine.
No.
You can't.
Don't look.
You're sleeping.
I'm sleeping.
No.
You can't.
Stop looking.
Takashi.
No...
This...
I'm sorry.
But...
Can I come to see you again the day after the match?
If it's just a flu...
He came to see me every time there was a match.
No...
I'm sorry.
Good job!
Okay, put your hands here.
Put them here, too.
Look up and put your hands here.
You got it.
I don't know what to do.
Sit down?
I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
so I feel like I need to learn more and better.
They all believed me and thought this was my strongest talk.
Unfortunately, I don't think I can team up with someone who can handle my languages because attention is danger.
I do useят scans a lot, but they liked me more than I thought.
I think it's important for us to be aware of the fact that we are not alone.
We are not alone.
It feels good.
I'll put it here.
It's a little cold.
The miracle of the Japanese representative
He and I
The miraculous event
The miracle of the Japanese representative
The miracle of the Japanese representations
Give me milk
Yes
Can you smell it ?
Let me know if you have any questions.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to my channel.
See you next time.
Bye.
I love you.
Are you excited?
Open your legs.
What should I do?
What should I do if you wake up now?
I feel like I'm going to puke.
Can I kiss you, Kanako?
Can I give you a kiss, Kanako-san?
It's okay.
I'm going to go.
I can end my bad relationship with my son's friend.
Hey, Yuu.
I'm going.
What's wrong?
Oh, Yuu, I forgot something.
Takashi, you go ahead.
Oh, really?
Okay.
Let's go.
Hello, everyone.
It's been a long time.
It's been a long time
I don't know what to do with myself.
I don't know what to do.
Help me.
I love you so much.
Is there anybody?
What could I do for you?
Try to speak.
Is there anybody?
Kuu..
Kuu
I'm itching
I'm scared.
I'm hurt.
I'm sorry.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
What's going on with you?
It's getting harder.
Do you want me to pat you?
I want you to lick me.
Look at me when I lick you.
It's okay.
It hurts.
I see. I'll leave my stuff in my room.
Here you are.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Would you like to stay here tonight?