Yes, I know. I will try.
But, Mr. Tsipras, I am so glad you can tell me about this.
So I will continue to work hard from now on.
I am very excited to welcome the new members tomorrow.
Mr. Kitty will come too.
The work will definitely end.
Is it okay, drinking?
You can drink.
I like to drink.
I am very excited about tomorrow.
You cannot destroy.
Absolutely okay.
You look forward to tomorrow.
Thanks for today.
Good night to you.
I’m sorry I talked to Mr. Stevie, I’m looking forward to tomorrow.
What if you feel good with Stevie?
I never drank, but can I control it?
not cleared up.
She is pleased.
I want sex.
by
really
Finally finished.
This is this.
What to do.
Oh is?
What is?
Not even her sister.
No is nothing.
Nothing is
I am not working.
Just stay home.
I don’t work, but I sweat.
You can always enter.
So, get tired, just take a bath.
Why am I getting to work early in the morning?
Because I work, it is great.
I don’t want to tell people who don’t.
I say I will stop working.
No stop to.
I say I will stop in three years.
I will never stop 100%.
100% in three years.
Never cease to.
Based on what you say.
There are many things.
But not stop.
I will not stop 100%.
Yes, there are a lot of things.
I don’t want to tell people that there are no things.
Brother back to.
Go to my room.
Why is it?
The real guy.
Oh well Cotta.
Yes
Are you doing something today?
How are you doing the weekend?
The Weekend
Oh is?
What are you going to do?
work
I will find you, okay.
It is time.
Work, so do it.
also here
Looking for it, okay.
Oh well mother.
See also Man.
You should think a little slowly.
My dad would be so sweeping.
How many months have passed since I quit working?
Yes, it is.
Well, but a little more.
Let me look.
Oh oh oh
Good morning
Brother, you are disturbing.
Some of your costumes came to the board.
really is?
Yes to.
You are already a good social worker.
I am not yet accustomed.
It fits well, really.
Really pleased.
How about the company?
The company?
It is fun.
is fun.
Yes to.
All the elders are kind.
It’s very nice, I’m in a company like that, and both my mom and dad are reassured.
I want your brother to see you too.
It is an upward company.
But, is your brother not working?
You are not that face.
Better do it properly.
Oh mother.
So, I’m late at the company’s new welcome party.
So you said.
Meaning to drink?
Drinking a drink, is it okay?
It is OK.
is okay.
My mother is strong too.
I can drink.
Your brother is kind, right?
Yes, it is kind.
But it just is fine.
and your father and mother.
I’m going to dinner with your friends today.
Yes is.
Wait a minute, what is my food?
You are no longer a child.
It is in the refrigerator, make it yourself.
Because there is only time.
Certainly there is time.
My brother, it really is bad.
Really sad, right?
I want everyone to learn to read.
What is it, sham.
It is time.
Give this.
Oh yeah?
No need anymore.
I will go a little company.
Come up here.
Yes
Not to do?
not is
It is serious.
Do not be late.
That’s all too much, and you should make a good chicken.
If you are good.
When I was a kid, I often made it for me.
Sorry, I am here.
Wait a moment, I can lock it.
Thanks to.
There is definitely someone.
What are you doing?
What is?
What is.
It is heavy.
came to
Did you enter?
What is?
It’s dirty, wait a while.
Sorry to
Oh yeah?
It is hot.
How much did you drink this?
I want to toilet.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No to no.
Toilet is.
Do not have to.
This is a drunk fish.
Do you know your conditions?
This, until then
Touch it well.
Yes
Not a bad thing.
My friend, if you touch it, I will love you.
Oh what are you saying.
You will love the house if you touch it.
I don’t know, I don’t understand meaning at all.
Sleeping in the water.
Heat is
I knew it was hot.
I took off.
It is awkward.
Did you see the teacher?
I have not seen.
You are watching, right?
Look at this.
Give it your water.
I have not seen.
You are not looking at the house?
See also
Close the feet.
Because it is dull.
by
What do you do, this.
Thanks to.
Little boy, I don’t know.
Rise up
Stand up
I’ll take you to the room.
Okay well well.
The land house.
I cannot get my breasts out.
Just be calm, you.
well is.
My ass is not broken.
I’m talking to Pence.
Talk, my teacher, you are very good at teaching.
No, no, no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
Because he is a perversion.
otherwise
Oh, I go quickly.
Mr. Todd, are you coming home?
You can only take it to your house.
I have to sell a shower.
I’m going to shower, really.
I have to take care of it too.
Okay so well.
The land.
House, where did you go?
Yes is
The land.
where
Oh yeah
The baggage
I will leave it here.
The land.
I have come to you.
Really a lot of honor.
You are you.
Stones are dirty.
Sorry to
I mean you hear.
You hear it.
The land.
The house is full of hunger.
What what what
not touched it.
Stop to stop.
Can you touch me?
not touched.
Oh yeah?
well well
No a little.
It feels like that today, right?
What are you doing too?
Do you want to drink?
Please touch it a lot.
Please touch the house.
Please touch more.
It does not look unexpected.
The land.
Not a landlord.
Touched a lot.
I am glad that your father touched me.
It’s getting hot, so I want to take off my clothes.
If I take off my clothes, I will go.
Please go.
Oh is?
Are you watching? right?
No, it is okay.
A little, that
Please touch more.
well well
You are good style, you.
Is it true?
I touch more.
No, okay is okay.
Oh well
The first time.
The book was chosen by the landlord.
I am very pleased.
Is it enough?
What is OK?
Ending here.
No to no.
This too
properly
Touch me with a smile.
Oh oh oh oh
So much
I might really like the house.
I like it.
You like the land.
Do not chew?
No, it is
Chew is good.
Sorry for seriously.
Oh is?
Oh yeah
No to
Okay is?
Okay, the house of the land.
Oh yeah
No to
that
cannot be
The house is very close.
I am very pleased.
Their laughing face is so cute.
The housewife laughed very much.
It is cool.
Why do you dream, really?
Happy is
No to
Heavy
A little
What are you doing.
Mr the land.
I saw home.
No, not to no.
A little
No to no.
A little hindering.
Oh yeah
It is fine.
The house teacher.
It is very hot.
Hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot
This is the first time such a great teacher.
Oh is
greatly
Wait a little, wait a little.
So I will lick you.
Oh yeah!
Feel a little.
A little bit.
A little hurt.
Oh, a little
Okay, look at me.
Going away, that is what it is.
Okay go go go.
Oh yeah?
You can go.
Oh, a little
Oh Oh Oh
Okay, I think you’ll get a lot of stuff out and the house will be out.
You can get the landlord out.
Can I go out?
Okay is.
Please get out a lot.
and sweat.
It hurts.
Yes is
There was a lot of voice out.
by Tanya
Sorry to
I was laid off because of the house.
A lot of out.
Are you not well yet?
You are still a binary.
It is
Do something.
Okay is.
More of
boldly
Okay is.
Feel cheap
Even when children are studying.
son to son.
Oh yeah
Really wait.
Exit out
Stop it.
No to
Wait a little.
I seem to cry.
Can I cry?
No to
Wait a little.
Do not cry.
Seriously
Oh is
Oh well 😂
Oh oh oh oh oh
Oh is
by
is happy.
Clean it up you too.
by
Oh yeah
You invited me, it was your fault.
So don’t tell everyone.
I understand
The shop was delicious yesterday.
Really good.
I drank too much.
Good morning
Oh well, here
Yes
What happened to the dinner yesterday?
Oh yeah
Oh well
What happened?
You made something, right?
Oh no
You do not remember.
I drank it.
Sorry, I seem to forget.
Stay firmly.
There was a lot less in the refrigerator.
You probably made something.
Sorry, I do not remember.
The food was frozen and lost.
You made something.
Oh yeah
What is South today?
Oh is?
Was he here?
No, you have not gone yet.
Oh is?
Usually, you have time to wake up.
It is rare.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Was it okay now?
Good morning
It was too late.
I have a headache when I drink.
Is it okay?
It is not wide yet, right?
Yes is.
Is it okay?
OK is OK.
The company?
arrive on time.
You drank a lot.
I drank.
My husband sent me home.
Did you send me?
Didn’t you bother me?
Maybe you bothered.
You are a good old man.
Oh yes cool.
I will teach you work well.
Is it so?
Eat lunch often together.
This is day?
Yes
Maybe I will present you next time.
A little early?
Urged to.
So, I would like to tell you in advance when I introduce you.
Yes it is.
You have to go first, you can come in quickly.
Yes, you guys are so old.
Yes, it has already been.
I want to drink stronger.
But it is not so strong to feel.
How can I do it?
Yes, I went to the store with my mom yesterday, and I’ll go with my dad next time.
No, your father is not.
It is stupid and good wine.
The wine?
I say, you should be getting stronger gradually.
Is the wine good?
It is delicious, you don’t know the kids.
I never drank, I don’t remember you.
I never drank, but you.
I went to the 1000 yen yesterday.
Yes
The house was normal.
I was so drunk.
Come to me, come to me.
Why is it.
I say we have a talk.
I do not like.
Okay, come to me.
Oh, I do not like it.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
I don’t remember you like yesterday.
Yesterday, my husband sent me home.
Later many older men.
Yes
by
But it wasn’t so bad.
This guy is not really nice.
Oh that ah
No to?
Even if I come out of the man.
Brother, do not interfere with me.
Oh oh oh
Oh yeah
I think there will be more such opportunities.
by
But I didn’t think I was so drunk.
Was something told?
Yes, to the company.
Drink it.
Too drunk
I think it’s better to repair alcoholism.
was bothered.
So, let’s practice drinking.
Drinking training?
Yes Yes Yes
Drink and get immunized.
See also Great.
by
Meaning to drink?
Yes, we will drink both.
Have you bought that?
Oh, and sometimes
I want to drink both.
Okay but
Talk very quickly.
So open it.
Toast to
At least these things.
I drink the can.
Try to go.
Eating is okay.
Have you drunk?
Let me drink again.
still is
You are drinking great.
Can I drink?
No more cannot.
Oh yeah?
Can you not get one?
No more cannot.
Headache is
No to no.
Is it not too fast to say one?
No, no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
to the stone.
Do not drink consistently.
No to no.
No checking is.
Because there is still drink.
Let’s drink.
be
Drink it?
Drinking is
This is delicious.
Oh my goodness.
Oh well Gee.
Yippidy yi yi yippity yay.
Go to go, go to go.
Yes, yes yes yes yes yes yes
Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Is it okay?
Oh, I cannot
His face is red.
I really do go wing.
It is OK, OK.
You need to drink more and get more immunity, so drink this guitze.
Yes, yes, yes, we are going to go.
Oh, you are broken, it is fine.
Is it okay?
is OK.
Really, I don’t talk at all.
Oh is?
No yes yes.
I will get it.
If it is hot, you should wear it off.
Are you no longer wearing clothes?
Take it off.
I am increasingly excited about which one.
I will help you a little.
Oh, you are super cute.
I can no longer drink.
Did you say you could drink?
It can be GIGY.
What is it.
The face too red.
It is not red.
But it is hot.
Heat is
If you have more pattern.
That is?
There is a nice guy.
The landlord?
The land.
Why do you say?
No, not by chance.
I went around here, I was drunk.
Oh yeah really?
Really really
You said well, you know.
No, I sent you yesterday.
Oh, and so
Yes Yes
Is it okay? a little.
Drink a little more?
Let’s toast.
Okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
Sorry, but I’m just toasting.
Is it like drinking a lot?
Drinking again?
Why not go?
You are drunk, what happened?
No, it is not so.
really is?
I am really drunk.
I have not found a very nice guy, but I am very cute.
Why are you watching?
Because we are not so close together, we.
Yes, of course of course.
What do I do? show me more.
What to do.
Please please.
Okay is.
This is super cute.
I was very excited.
Is it true?
I am very excited.
Is your employee drunk?
Drunk and drunk.
It is also becoming like this here.
Really is
well is
Okay so well.
Today is kind.
Why am I always so hard?
I am unhappy.
Because it is work.
Now is the time for private.
What is it?
Yes is.
by Mr.
What is?
I am Berber.
I said he was drunk.
by Shrink
You can do anything when you are drunk.
You are a good girl.
What are you doing?
Is it full?
Can I stop this?
Oh is?
Pause, do it
Okay, my landlord
thanks to
If you don’t, you’ll come to Ultron.
Dad, I can’t drink at last.
Oh well fuck.
Drink well, and drink yourself.
Look at my.
It is a real channeling.
Very good feeling.
It is cold, it is good.
It is a real channeling.
This will hinder.
be hard.
You are joined.
Oh, we will go.
Oh yeah
Show me.
It is because of Chase.
That is
Try to rub the shit.
Yes
Okay, here is a rough.
Okay is.
Oh, I beat him.
No to
Still standing still.
What to do?
Oh is?
Please tell me.
Then by yourself.
Turn the ass.
Spread the hole.
Yes is
Really nothing to do.
I mean not to.
Yes is.
Because it is a sperm.
I am
Yes
I always remembered the house.
Think of me?
Yes is
You are going to be a girl, with her brother.
Why are you talking about your sister?
Why is it?
Oh is?
Move it yourself.
It feels good at all.
It feels good.
Drinking at this time is great.
Is it true?
Really good.
Really to?
Mr Mr said.
See also 😂
Fly with hands.
Just just.
Yes to.
You feel good up.
Do you wake up and see you are in?
He is hungry.
See also
It is bad.
It is in.
is in.
by
Her face is red.
Is it not?
I too, Berber
I will not remember my face tomorrow.
I remember it.
It feels so good.
It is bad.
The highest
I see you come in.
See you?
See also
No to.
The Southern Bambi.
It feels good.
Press it more.
The Earth Bambi.
go out.
Do you do it after I get out?
Okay to?
by
I have endured.
Still not yet, though.
Stay here now.
Stay this
greatly
You are well, baby.
Because in this work.
If you are well, get up.
by
No one felt completely.
Get up and move.
Press it toward me.
Still upstairs.
not to be.
Okay well...
I see already...
You are in.
Just say goodbye.
Oh no... no.
It will come to your head.
It is OK.
It is your little boy.
I like it.
Yes is.
Can I go again?
Let us go together.
Really to?
Okay
Oh go go go.
Out again.
by
Taste is
Really, it was a reward you gave.
The highest
I am also the best.
Super love is good.
So, I made it to my grandmother.
Take your room back.
See also
Well, well, I hope you sleep well there.
Yes is
Oh well, look at me.
I will sit.
A very cute room.
What are you doing?
No to?
You are here, here.
No, no, I am not here.
Oh yes, again
Oh is?
What are you saying?
No, no, but it is not so.
In the company, there is always something.
Are you sick? no, it is not.
Are you okay at this time?
It is OK.
Yes is.
Yes is
Oh is?
Have you already forgotten?
Did you send me a welcome party?
New welcomed?
He was drunk and took a taxi.
You sent me home, didn’t you?
Oh well?
That is, is it?
No, I was drunk too.
It was like we were separated in a taxi.
But I think about the house, I don’t get to work.
Oh is?
No, how do you say.
Because it
What is it? what?
Oh is?
Can not?
What is?
What are you doing, guys?
You want to avoid it immediately.
Well, because it suddenly happened.
Yes
No, a little
I fear
Oh is?
Do you always do it, right?
Always to?
Oh, a little
Oh is?
So that
Okay is
Oh is?
Do you hate?
No, not to hate.
So that
Even in relationship.
Do not always say so.
Oh well
Please touch me.
properly
Do you like to see?
No, a little
A very girl like that.
Not done, not good.
What I always do.
Always to?
The landlord.
You touched me.
Oh is?
The previous drinking room.
And then after that.
and then?
Do you hate?
Not like it.
Did you forget that? he did it.
I did so.
What are you doing?
What I always do.
Do you always do this?
You did it too, right?
It is terrible to forget.
Do it really.
Okay, anyway.
It is OK.
The house as usual.
Has the chicken changed?
I always think it’s the first time.
Oh is?
Is something strange?
No, it is not strange.
Are you concerned?
No, it was my mistake.
I can’t stand it when I see it.
That is damn.
Oh my god, you are sick.
No to no.
No, but I’ll go very soon.
Oh, shit, I really am going.
I really go.
Please be patient.
No, I’m going to go really soon.
I really go.
Was it always early to go to the house?
Yes, always, because it always goes too soon.
Yes, you are very well today.
No, but he might be fine.
Oh, really, I’m going to go soon.
I really want to go, wait a little.
How about? not?
The food is very good.
Do you do?
Do you really do?
Do you not? – Do you not?
Yes is
Or both of you.
You cannot go out.
You are always watching?
Damn, always
Please put it in here.
Very bold you are.
here to
Please come in quickly, Mr. Dutchman.
But I have to do that rubber.
You don’t always wear it.
Are you always doing that?
I am doing it.
It is awesome.
Great recently.
Then really put it in.
Yes is
Oh yeah
by M.
What happened?
A little nothing.
Show me your hand.
Oh yeah
Have you already gone out?
No to
Ferrari felt so good.
Was it just there?
Oh sorry to.
Because I am going out immediately.
It wasn’t always like this.
Oh yeah yeah?
Usually it is.
Sorry a little.
I am a bit quick.
Oh is?
Can I use a little tick?
Yes, it is okay.
Sorry to
What was it not?
If I say something, I’ll be a little excited.
Different from usual.
I’ve been there a long time, but I’ve been a little busy and quiet.
No problem.
Don’t do this, I’ll have to prepare for it.
You may be bored of me.
It was a dream at that time.
But I definitely have a memory.
Oh Sunday is.
Drinking wine
Why drink a drink?
He is drunk on Sunday and drunk.
You really have a good body.
He really looks like a good fish.
Forget about the rope.
Have sex today.
OK to this place.
What to do today.
What are you doing?
Okay as usual.
You do not remember.
As usual, they are in shit.
Oh is?
What do you do? sleep or get a tooth?
You can close it.
What to do?
Oh is?
Maybe it is.
I have been in agreement with you so far.
My brother?
Oh is?
Are you not sleeping now?
I just drank and slept.
The lie?
Is it true?
I thought I was always talking with the landlord.
I’ll show you my underwear.
More than how much.
I also endured it at first.
But you will be tired, and I will show you my underwear.
Even if I am wrong, I will be wrong.
We are here, hiding each other in this chest.
My brother felt better.
Oh is?
My brother felt better than his brother.
The worst
Oh is?
Let me check for a little.
What are you saying?
Wait a little, wait a little.
No, wait a little and wait.
No well
Oh oh oh oh
Oh yeah
Oh is?
This is
The channels I always used.
Oh is?
Oh no, yes it is.
Oh, a little
Why is?
He was really my brother.
Oh no, no, you look too much.
No, show me it.
Oh, oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh is?
No, you are not drunk, you are not drunk, you are not drunk.
Certainly
So, keep each other in your hearts and forget.
Oh myne.
Failed there.
Oh yeah that.
Is it okay?
Wait a little.
Oh Mr Minami?
Was he drunk?
Oh is?
What happened?
OK is.
Oh yeah
by
is delicious?
Oh yeah
I understand
OK is.
It feels good, brother.
This is
Yes
No to
Oh yeah
on
No to
go to
Oh is
No to
My ass hurts.
by ass
Oh is
OK is.
My brother’s chest is big.
Compare to whom.
Is it okay?
Yes
Because he is still singing.
I will sing you again.
Riley loved himself.
Directly to
Turn to end.
Riley loved himself.
Oh, and
It feels too much,
Oh well
by
Yes yes
N is
No to
OK is OK.
Is it okay?
Try moving yourself.
It was a quick and easy thing to do.
Give it out.
Oh yeah
No more cannot.
Let us rest a little.
Seriously
Stop it.
Oh yeah
by
Because I can’t.
Oh, and I said I came home.
Wait a little.
Oh my little, wait.
I know, I know, I know
Will you come? a little.
Stop it, stop it.
Oh well well
Yes is