A few days later
I can't sleep at all.
I did it until last night, but I couldn't get any sleep.
That's right.
Do you want to take some medicine?
Medicine?
I can't do it now.
I'm going to bed.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to do this because I did it last night.
I was thinking about you, too.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It doesn't hurt
Pretty
Love...
I love you...
Today is a busy day, isn't it?
What do you mean?
You seem to be in a hurry.
Maybe I'm in a hurry.
I see.
I have to hurry.
I want to touch you.
I want to touch you, too.
Can I touch you?
I'm already touching you.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It hurts.
It's hot.
Did you have a cold?
Mr. Kameda is in a hurry today.
You, too.
Do you have time?
Yes.
It's hot.
You seem to be in a hurry.
You can do it, right?
But I just took it out.
Mr. Kameda, you don't finish it in one go.
That's right.
I'll do it a little more.
Can I do it?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's amazing here.
That's no good.
Is it really no good?
It's not selfish.
It's too hot.
Mr. Kameda, please.
It's no good.
I'll move more.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Ms. Misaki, do you like this?
I can't do this.
It's not no good.
It's hot.
I can't do this.
I'll do my best.
It hurts.
I took out the IV again.
Can I do it again?
I didn't mean to take out the IV.
I'll do it again.
It's close.
It's Ms. Misaki's hair.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
I'm happy.
I can't stop it.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
I can't stop it.
I'm tired.
It's hot.
Ms. Misaki.
I'm sorry.
It felt good to do it with you.
It's been a while.
Would you like to take a break?
Yes.
It's the same menu as today.
It's hard to be a housewife.
It's the same with food.
It's the same with laundry and cleaning.
But it's easier to be a housewife than to go back to work.
Who's next to you?
That's right.
I'm Misaki.
I'm Kameda.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
We often meet in the morning.
Is it the same time as recently?
Yes.
It's the same timing.
I quit my job a while ago.
I'm doing my hobby now.
I see.
That's why you're taking a break in the morning.
That's right.
It's lame.
That's not true.
That's right.
Housework is hard, isn't it?
It was hard, wasn't it?
Yes.
Well...
Yes?
Would you like to have some tea at my house?
What?
If you have time, I'd like to talk to you.
Well...
Are you busy?
No, I'm not busy at all.
Well, then...
May I?
Yes.
Thank you.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Well, then...
Go ahead.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm sorry.
Here you are.
Is that all right?
Yes.
But it's for you.
My husband doesn't eat sweets.
So I bought it for him.
I see.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It looks delicious.
I bought it for the first time, too.
I see.
Try it.
Thank you.
Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
I'm glad to hear that.
Well...
Misaki's house is a little different from my house.
Is that so?
Yes.
I see.
Can I see your house next time?
What?
My house?
Yes.
But it's not as clean as Misaki's house.
No, it's not.
My house is a mess.
By the way, your husband seems to be busy with work.
He often comes to see you in the morning.
Yes, he seems to be busy.
Your wife seems to be busy, too.
She seems to be busy recently.
That's a good thing.
I think so, too.
But she often comes to see me at home.
It must be hard for her.
I think so, too.
I see.
Well...
Yes?
What do you think of me?
What?
Do you think I'm boring?
No.
I think you're very beautiful.
I don't want to say this to my husband.
After my husband cheated on me, I lost confidence in myself.
I see.
Why does your husband cheat on you?
As I said before, I think you're very beautiful.
Is that true?
Well...
I don't mean it in a strange way.
At least, you're more beautiful than my wife.
You're beautiful.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to drink it all at once.
OK.
I don't know what to say.
What's going on?
Wait a minute.
She's crying.
What is it?
She wants to get out.
Do you think it's okay to let her out?
She's out.
I can't help it.
My head is still hard.
Is it around here?
That's right.
I can't help it.
Please help me.
Ouch!
I can't help it.
It's so dirty.
I can't reach it.
I want you to put this on me.
I can't do it anymore.
You can't do it anymore.
Are you okay?
I can't do it anymore.
Are you really okay?
Mr. Kameda.
Yes?
We can meet anytime, right?
Yes.
It's okay.
We're the only ones here during the day.
What?
Misaki.
I fell asleep.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I fell asleep.
Oh, right.
I had a dream when I first met you.
What?
Is that so?
I'm embarrassed.
I know.
Next,
we'll go to the main building.
Okay.
I'll be back soon.
Are you going to spend the weekend with your wife?
No, I'm not.
Are you going to spend the weekend with your husband?
Can I ask you one last question?
Yes.
Do you need a bed sheet?
Don't worry about it.
Really?
Yes.
I have to go to work.
I'll go home today.
Okay.
Thank you.
It's sunny.
Yes, it is.
It's a nice day.
It's like a laundry day.
Yes.
It's a walk day.
Do you want to go to the park?
I think it's a good idea.
Let's go for a walk.
Okay.
Do you want to eat ice cream?
Do you think so?
I think so.
Let's go to the convenience store.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm washing the laundry.
I'll do it.
No, I'll do it.
Really?
Yes.
Let's take a break.
Let's go to the park.
I see.
We don't have enough exercise.
But I have to wash the laundry today.
What?
You seemed to be in a good mood.
You seem to be in a good mood.
Yes.
Why do I have to work on my day off?
I was asked if I had any plans at work.
I can't do it right away.
I see.
I have a lot of work.
It's hard.
What are you doing?
What?
I'm looking at my cell phone.
I see.
You've been looking at your cell phone lately.
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at what to do for dinner.
It's hard to think about what to do for dinner.
I agree.
What should I do?
What do you want to do today?
Misaki.
Are you looking at your cell phone?
Yes.
Did you look at my cell phone?
I don't look at your cell phone.
Do you stay at home during the day?
Yes.
What?
There is a trace of someone.
I see.
Do you know anything about it?
I think so.
I see.
Do you know anything about it?
If you know anything, please tell me.
Of course.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Did he find out?
I don't remember leaving such a trace.
It's delicious.
By the way.
Did you meet your neighbor's husband?
But...
I'm at home.
I cook.
I clean up.
I'm a housewife.
But your husband is having a hard time.
What?
Of course.
It's hard, but it's different.
We are salarymen.
We work in companies.
But it's different.
I work every day.
But I have to go to work.
So I met my boss.
I can't spend my time elegantly.
Did you get a message from someone?
What's up?
Hey, what have you been up to lately?
Did someone come here by any chance?
Why don't you say anything?
Is there something you can't say?
You just want me to say no, right?
By the way, have you been wearing more skirts and dresses lately?
You used to wear a lot of pants when you got married.
And I've seen you wearing a lot of flashy underwear lately.
Can't you answer me?
Go home early.
I'm going to work.
About what we talked about yesterday, please forget about it.
It was nothing.
I'm going to work.
What's wrong with you?
Can I go to Mr. Kameda's house today?
You were with your husband yesterday, right?
That's why you were so happy earlier.
I'm sorry.
I really just want to be with Mr. Kameda.
You two are husband and wife.
Isn't that a good thing?
Of course.
I like Mr. Kameda more than my husband.
I'm sorry.
Am I bothering you?
No, it's not a bother.
I just feel a little uncomfortable.
I feel like I'm being watched.
I feel like I should spend more time with you today.
Do you think so?
Yes.
Okay.
But I want to be with Mr. Kameda today.
I want to be with Mr. Kameda today.
I'm sorry.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or a bad idea, but I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break
after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's
a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's
work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take
a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think
it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard
day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and Iundred
hands me a break after a day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's
a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break
after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work, and I think it's a good idea to take a break after a hard day's work
I love you...
It's so hot.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's so hot.
What about me?
I'll make you feel better.
Do it.
It's so hot.
I can't do it.
I'll help you.
It's so hot.
I want to do it again.
Okay.
It's so hot.
7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8
8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8
8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8
8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8
8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8,7,8
I can't run away from my current life.
I have to face it properly.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Not at all.
You look good in a suit.
Really?
Yes.
Is my wife at home?
I heard the sound of a video, so I think she's at home.
It's definitely yoga.
I've been addicted to yoga since I started working.
You have a hobby.
It seems so.
That's good.
By the way, is your husband on a business trip today?
Yes, he is.
I was able to face it properly, so I went on a business trip.
That's good.
Yes.
Well, shall we go?
Thank you for watching.