Why do I have trouble in the morning?
Somebody help me.
I know there is no one, but I don't have to get up.
I have to work like this.
I'm sorry I couldn't wake you up.
It's okay. I'm going to be late today.
You told me yesterday.
I want to go home in 8 hours.
I'm busy every day.
It was decided to be 8 hours.
That's right.
I'm a normal salaryman.
I'm worried about my health.
Even if I work 3 jobs, my body will break.
How long will it last?
If I work this much, everyone will quit.
The working environment is important.
I don't have enough sleep.
Don't oversleep.
I have to answer the phone.
Hello.
I understand.
I'm fine.
I'll be there soon.
The next day.
It's Takara.
It's been a long time.
Did you go shopping?
Yes, I did.
Me too.
It's hard, isn't it?
Yes.
Do you have time?
Don't you come to my house?
You have time, don't you?
You've never been to my house, have you?
No.
Come to my house.
Okay.
The next day.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Please come in.
Thank you.
This is a gift from abroad.
Really?
It's from abroad.
I put it in the box because you came.
I bought it as a souvenir when I went on a business trip.
Souvenirs are not good.
Why?
Thank you.
Smell it.
It smells good, doesn't it?
Yes.
It has a unique taste.
Isn't it easy to drink foreign tea?
Yes, I think so.
Right?
You like it.
I've met you before.
At the meeting at the apartment, right?
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Yes, it's been a while.
Are you still a housewife?
Yes, I am.
I see.
Do you spend a lot of time at home?
Yes, I do.
You don't have time, do you?
You don't spend a lot of time at home, do you?
Yes, I do.
You have time.
Sakura, are you interested in a part-time job?
A part-time job?
Actually, I'm renting an apartment.
I see.
So, I started men's esthetics in that room.
Do you know men's esthetics?
Men's esthetics?
Yes, there are only men in the room.
And women do esthetics.
That's how I started.
That's amazing.
So, I thought you'd like to work at a men's esthetics.
But I...
Do you have time?
But I've never done esthetics.
I don't have time.
It's easy.
You can just do it.
I'll teach you.
No, no, no.
Is that so?
Men's esthetics, even if you don't have experience,
it's okay for a housewife to apply oil and do it.
So, it's easy to work.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm also a housewife.
I have a part-time job.
I thought you'd like it, too.
Well...
You like beauty, don't you?
I like beauty.
And esthetics is a little expensive, isn't it?
Well, that's true.
It's not that expensive because it's in the same room as the apartment.
It's easy.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's just for men who want to relax.
And I'm a men's esthetician,
but I'm giving the concept of a housewife doing it to customers.
A housewife doing it?
Yes, yes, yes. Doesn't it sound a little interesting?
Men like it, don't they?
Well...
Yes, yes, yes.
That's why everyone knows that housewives do it in between.
I see.
How is it?
Well, but...
You can do it by yourself. Don't you want a part-time job?
No, but my husband works for me, so...
What? But when you start, you'll be popular,
and you'll be able to make a living.
Make a living...
You're free at this time, aren't you?
Well...
You can do it in an hour or two, so you can work for a short time
and earn money by yourself. It's very fulfilling.
Well...
How is it?
Well, but...
You know, when I look at you,
I wonder if you're satisfied with your life.
What?
When I look at people, I can see that.
Are you doing something fun?
Well...
It's quite fulfilling to buy your favorite bag or shoes with the money you earn.
Well, that's true.
Don't you think so?
Yes.
That's why you need to work, earn money, and live a fulfilling life.
I think that's what you need right now.
I can see that.
It's true.
If it doesn't suit you, you can quit right away.
It's like a trial.
Oh...
But I think you can make a lot of money.
So it's a waste to stay at home.
I see.
Why don't you try it?
I'll teach you.
You and I are friends.
We live in the same apartment.
That's true.
Right? Let's do it.
Let's do our best.
Let's try it just once.
You're interested, right?
We have time.
Let's do it.
I'll teach you everything.
You have a good memory.
You'll do it right away.
Let's set a date for this week.
How about this week?
Isn't it better to be early?
You don't know my number.
Give me your phone. Let's exchange it.
You'll definitely be popular.
I guarantee it.
It'll be great if you have a lot of customers.
It's really great.
You can make a lot of money.
Let's try it.
Just once.
You can make money in your free time.
What should I do?
I said yes.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
You're late for work.
I had a hard time today.
Did you eat?
I ate outside.
I went to the convenience store today.
You must be busy.
It's hard.
I thought I'd be calm.
I'm busy tomorrow, too.
Why does everyone stop working?
Am I strict?
I don't think so.
Is it my fault?
It's a phone call.
I can't answer the phone.
I told you to answer the phone.
Don't answer the phone.
I'm sorry.
Hello?
You have a manual, right?
Tell me.
You can't do it?
I'll do it tomorrow.
I'll tell you again.
Don't worry about it.
Is the bathroom open?
The bathroom is open.
I have to go to work early tomorrow.
Is it okay?
I changed my clothes.
Thank you.
You are very beautiful.
Are you really married?
Yes, I am.
You have a ring.
You are lucky.
You are very beautiful.
It's my first time.
I heard it on the phone.
Really?
It's okay.
I practiced it.
Thank you.
It's helpful.
Don't worry about it.
I'll do my best.
I'll start with the ring.
Okay.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Is it okay to use oil?
Yes, it's okay.
Okay.
I'll apply oil.
Is the temperature of the oil okay?
Yes, it's okay.
It's warm and pleasant.
That's good.
Please let me know if you have any questions.
Okay.
I'll apply oil.
It feels good.
Really?
The pressure is just right.
I'm glad.
I think it's okay.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
You can apply oil to the back of your neck.
Okay.
Isn't it too heavy?
No, it's okay.
Please apply a lot of oil.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
That's good.
Here?
It feels good.
I'm glad.
That's good.
It's good.
I'd like to apply oil to the back of your neck.
Okay.
It's good.
Thank you.
Can you apply oil to my calf?
Your calf?
Okay.
Like this?
Yes.
Okay.
Here?
It feels good.
It's good.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
I'd like you to apply oil to my soles.
Soles?
Yes.
Okay.
It's good.
Can I apply oil to your feet?
Feet?
Yes, feet.
Okay.
Excuse me.
That's good.
It's good.
Excuse me.
It feels good.
Thank you.
Can you roll up your sleeves?
Roll up?
Yes.
Like this?
Yes, like that.
Okay.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Okay.
It's good.
Can I apply oil to your back?
Okay.
Excuse me.
It's good.
You can roll up your sleeves.
Is it okay?
Yes.
Excuse me.
It feels good.
You're really good at it.
Really?
That's good.
I'm sorry for asking you to do everything for me.
No, not at all.
It's okay.
I'm really good at it.
That's good.
I'm sorry for asking you to do everything for me.
Can I apply oil to your back?
Okay.
I'm going to apply oil around your chest.
It's good.
It feels good.
I'm sorry for asking you to do everything for me.
It's okay.
You have a good style.
No, I don't.
What would you do if I didn't have a good style?
No, I wouldn't do that.
Wait a minute.
No, I can't do that.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
I can't do that.
What?
I was told that I could touch you on the phone.
I'm supposed to set a fee for that.
What?
I was told that I could touch you on the phone.
I see.
If you don't allow me to touch you on the phone, I don't think it's a good deal.
But I think I can touch you anywhere.
I think it's okay.
I think it's okay to do it while massaging you.
It's amazing.
It's soft.
It's hard.
It's amazing.
Do you really do this?
Yes, I think it's normal.
I see.
It's amazing.
Wait a minute.
That's...
What?
Don't you have a pain here?
A pain?
Yes, it's a pain.
You can squeeze my hand.
You can lick my hand.
You'll get in trouble.
But I do it in secret.
What?
It's a secret.
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
Please.
That's...
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
You'll get in trouble.
It's okay.
I do it in secret.
No, you can't.
Wait a minute.
Hold my hand.
Are you okay?
Do you pay for it?
No, I don't.
How about 10,000 yen?
How about 2,000 yen?
No, I don't pay for it.
You don't need it?
No.
Please come closer to my face.
Your face?
Yes.
Like this?
That's good.
Wait a minute.
No, you can't.
It's okay.
Wait a minute.
That's good.
It feels good.
Can you do it for me?
Me?
Yes.
It's okay.
Everyone else does it.
Okay.
It's a secret.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Like this?
Please lick it.
I'll lick it.
You're good at it.
That's good.
Can you drool?
Yes.
Like this?
That's good.
It feels good.
Please do it more.
Yes.
That's good.
It feels good.
You can do it.
That's good.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
That's good.
It feels good.
There's a lot of hair on your face.
I'll wipe it off.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It was the best.
It felt good.
Really?
Yes.
I'll come again.
Thank you.
It was the best.
Please keep this a secret.
I understand.
I'll keep it a secret.
Yes.
I'll definitely come back.
That's good.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
I'm tired.
You're late.
What's wrong with you today?
I changed my clothes.
I see.
You're going home today, aren't you?
I sometimes want to eat rice.
It's like a movie.
Is the bath open?
Yes.
You'll fall asleep if you don't take a bath.
I'm going to take a bath.
Welcome back.
I can't believe I'm living like this.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm sorry for asking you to come today.
It's okay.
Did you have a good time?
Yes.
It's okay.
How was your part-time job?
It was fun.
I told you so.
I'm glad.
It was easy, wasn't it?
That's right.
I'm glad.
I thought you'd do it because you were good at it.
It was fun.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm glad.
Sakura is definitely popular.
You should do it.
There are several people who work at my company.
I think she's the cutest.
It's true.
I'm sure she's popular.
When do you want to join?
You're always free, aren't you?
You're a housewife, aren't you?
Let's decide today.
Okay?
Don't you think you can join 2 or 3 times a week?
I don't want to.
Why don't you join other than Saturday and Sunday?
It's about 1 or 2 hours.
It's a week, isn't it?
Think about your salary.
If a man says he likes you, you'll get a bonus.
It's amazing, isn't it?
You'll get a bonus.
That's true.
You're grateful, aren't you?
You can buy your own cosmetics and accessories at home.
You can buy a new one every season.
It's fun, isn't it?
That's the fulfillment of life.
Hello?
Yes, that's right.
Thank you very much.
I have a housewife at home.
Yes, that's right.
Oh, you're Sakura.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I'm free at that time.
Yes, I'm Sakura.
Thank you.
Yes, I'm free.
I'll be waiting for you.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
That's good.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
You have beautiful and big boobs.
That's great.
Can I touch your boobs?
I was told on the phone that I could touch your boobs.
That's fine.
I'll give you a massage.
That's great.
Can you give me a massage from above my head this time?
Yes.
Please come this way.
I see.
The other way.
Yes, this way.
Like this?
Yes, that's right.
I'll apply a lot of oil.
I'm sorry.
I see.
Please give me a lot of massage.
Yes.
Like this?
Yes, that's right.
Please give me a lot of massage.
Please give me a lot of massage from above my head this time.
Yes, that's right.
I'm sorry.
Can you do a face-to-face massage?
You can, right?
This way.
Please do it.
Face-to-face.
Can you do it?
I got it.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Can you bring your face closer?
My face?
A little more.
A little more?
Yes, a little more.
Yes.
Let's sit down.
Okay.
Can I have your hand?
What?
No.
Can I have your hand?
Just a little.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Wow.
You're so cute.
Look at me.
Okay.
It feels so good.
You're so cute.
It's okay.
I can't believe it's been a year since I've had a baby.
I'm so happy.
I was so happy.
Hold on a second.
Please wait a moment.
O...kay, come here.
Sorry about that.
Were you surprised?
I feel bad for you.
Put some towel on my face.
Yeah, up to here.
I love you.
You have a lot of hair.
Let me see.
Wow.
I'm glad.
You have a lot of hair.
I feel great.
Wow.
I think I can do more.
Can you give me a massage?
Okay.
Can I do it?
Let me do it.
I think it's enough.
Wow.
I love you.
I'm glad.
Come here.
Do you feel warm?
Yes.
Okay.
Let me rub your head.
Move your head.
Like this?
Yes.
Move your head.
Okay.
Press your head.
Move your head.
Okay.
Do you feel good?
I love you.
It's hot.
I'm glad.
I give you a little more medicine.
Just a little more…
I think it's about enough.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Let's do it again.
I can't do it.
Why?
You looked like you were in pain.
I'm not in pain.
I can't do it.
You look tired.
H...oi...
Huh?
Ho... oi...
Ketic...
Oh, no.
Let me help you.
What's wrong?
I'll take you to the vet.
Oh, no.
Let me help you.
Do you need a hand?
Oh, no!
Oh, no.
You are doing great.
I feel so good.
I can't.
I'll call you again.
Can you come here again?
See you again.
Hello?
I'm taking a shower now.
I changed my clothes, so I'm going to start the surgery.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
I took a shower.
What happened to your clothes?
I changed my clothes.
Did you change your clothes like this?
Yes.
I'm glad.
Did you like it?
It's the best.
I'm glad.
I'm glad, too.
Are you really married?
Yes.
This is my second marriage.
Your second marriage?
Yes.
Are you pregnant?
This is not a fake, is it?
No.
My husband doesn't take care of me these days.
What does your husband say?
Is he okay?
He's not pregnant yet.
Is that so?
You have such a cute wife.
Your husband doesn't take care of you at all.
If I were you, I would take care of my wife.
Let's start the surgery.
Okay.
I'll start with the uterus.
Please.
Like this?
Yes.
Please let me know if you feel uncomfortable.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Is the temperature okay?
Yes, it's okay.
It's warm and comfortable.
Really?
Yes.
I'm glad.
What's wrong?
I'll apply oil to myself.
To yourself?
Excuse me.
Okay.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
What's this?
It's amazing.
It's very sticky.
Yes.
It feels good.
The oil feels good, doesn't it?
The oil feels good, but I feel good when you apply it to me.
Really?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It doesn't loosen.
Really?
Yes.
I hope you feel better.
Thank you.
I want to see what's going on.
Can I look this way?
Face forward?
Yes.
Okay.
Wow.
It's amazing.
Does it stick out a little?
It sticks out a little.
It sticks out.
Wow.
It's amazing.
Is it amazing?
Yes.
I'm impressed.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Wow.
It's amazing.
It's very sticky.
I don't know if I can ask you this, but what kind of cup is this?
It's a J cup.
J?
Yes.
I've never heard of it.
It's thick.
Can I touch it?
Can I?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Wow.
It's soft.
It's amazing.
Come here.
Yes.
Wow.
It's amazing.
Wait a minute.
Wow.
Your face is close.
Your body is amazing, but your face is cute, too.
I'm glad.
Really?
Yes.
Wow.
It's soft.
It's very cute.
Oh, right.
Yes.
I asked you on the phone, but can I touch it?
Yes, you can.
Really?
Yes.
Then, I'll touch it a lot.
Please touch it.
Wait a minute.
It's very soft.
It came out.
It's amazing.
It's soft.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I feel good, too.
It's amazing.
It's soft.
Can I touch this side, too?
Yes.
Wow.
It's very beautiful.
Can I praise you for this?
No.
I haven't had many customers lately.
I see.
But you have customers other than me.
Yes.
It's rare.
I can't touch it.
Please touch it a lot.
Yes.
I'll touch it a lot.
It's soft.
It's amazing.
It's amazing on the top, too.
Yes.
It's moving on the bottom, too.
I want to move.
It doesn't depend on how you look at it.
It's amazing.
I'll move on the bottom, too.
Yes.
Please.
Excuse me.
Yes.
It's amazing.
It feels strange.
Does it feel good?
Yes, but it's my first time.
Yes.
It's amazing.
I'll move on this side, too.
Yes.
It's good that my body is warming up.
That's right.
It's getting hot.
Yes.
It's amazing.
It's getting hot.
That's right.
Is it the effect of the massage?
I see.
I'm going to massage a lot.
Yes.
Does it feel good?
It feels really good.
You're massaging here, too.
Yes.
I'm glad I came here.
I'm going to massage a lot.
Please.
It's amazing.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Don't you take off your clothes?
Do I take off my clothes?
Yes.
I don't take off my clothes.
But you do it in secret.
No.
I don't take off my clothes.
Everyone does it, including you.
Everyone does it?
Yes.
Everyone?
I think everyone does it except you.
Everyone does it?
Yes.
Does it feel better?
Excuse me.
I see.
Do you take off your clothes?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Please.
It's amazing.
It's getting harder and harder.
Yes.
It's amazing.
Please feel better.
It's very big.
It's amazing.
If you look at it, it'll get bigger.
I'm glad.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good here?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Then, I'll put it in your mouth.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Does it feel good in your mouth?
No.
It's amazing.
Why are you laughing?
Because you looked like you were in a good mood.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Excuse me.
What is it?
I'll use my boobs.
Really?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's because of the massage.
It's getting harder and harder.
It's amazing.
It's soft.
Does it feel good in your boobs?
It feels good.
I'm glad.
It feels soft.
It feels good.
It's really hard.
It's hiding in your boobs.
It's amazing.
I can't see it.
It's small.
It's true.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It feels good in my boobs.
It's soft.
It's amazing.
You got a lot.
Yes.
It's amazing.
It's still hard.
Is the massage effective?
I think so.
It's amazing.
Can I do it, too?
Yes.
You have a long arm.
I want to touch it.
It's scary.
Do you like it?
It feels good.
I see.
It's hard.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's soft.
I'm going crazy.
It feels good.
It's a little damp.
I'm getting used to it.
It feels good.
I can't do it from the top of your pants.
I'll do it directly.
Directly?
Please open your eyes.
It's amazing.
It's very pink.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Don't be.
It's amazing.
You said it felt good from the top of your pants.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
What's wrong?
You can't do it?
Don't lick it.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Show me your butt.
I can't do it.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You're very sensitive.
It feels good.
It would feel better if I add this.
Okay.
Excuse me.
It's amazing.
It's very soft.
It feels good.
It tickles.
I can't do it.
You're very sensitive.
What do you think about putting it in?
Putting it in?
Yes.
It's okay.
It's okay?
Yes.
Yay!
You're standing up again.
I'm going to stand up.
I'm going to put it in.
Okay.
It's amazing.
Your stomach is shaking.
It tickles.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
It tickles.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Please put it in a lot.
It feels good.
It tickles.
It's amazing.
Your stomach is shaking.
It tickles.
It feels good.
Please move.
It tickles.
It feels good.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, it hurts.
It hurts, it hurts.
Ah, ah, it hurts.
Ah.
Wow, it's amazing.
I'll turn your head up.
Okay.
Wow, it's amazing.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it's amazing.
Wow, it's amazing.
Please be comfortable.
Okay.
Wow, it's amazing.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Good job.
Wow, it's amazing.
Wow, it feels good.
Please let me out.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Please let me out.
Oh, no.
You're really out.
One, one.
Wow, it's amazing.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes.
Wow, it feels good.
Please let me out more.
Okay.
Please turn your hips this way.
I can still do it.
Okay.
Wow, it's amazing.
Wow, it feels good.
Turn your hips this way.
Wow, it's amazing.
Wow, it feels good.
Oh, no.
You're out.
Oh, it hurts.
Wow, it's amazing.
You're really out.
Oh, it feels good.
Can I move?
Please follow me.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, no.
You're out.
Please follow me.
Oh, it hurts.
Oh, no.
Oh, it feels good.
Please turn your hips this way.
Oh, it's amazing.
It feels good.
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
Feels good!
Oh! Feels good!
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
I'm getting hot
Oh! No!
I can't take it anymore!
It hurts!
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
It feels so good.
I can't take it anymore!
It feels so good!
Please...
Please follow me.
It feels so good!
It hurts! It hurts!
It hurts!
One more time?
Yes.
It feels so good!
It feels good!
You're amazing.
You're amazing!
Ah, it feels so good!
Wow, it feels so good all over!
Can I touch your neck with my fingers?
Yes!
Ah, it's the best!
Does it feel good?
Yes, it's the best!
Ah, it feels so good!
Ah, it's getting harder and harder!
That's right!
Ah, it feels so good!
Ah, it's so tight!
Can I put it on your chest when you take it off?
Yes, please put it on my chest!
Ah, it feels so good!
Please let me take it off!
Ah, I'm sorry, your chest is dirty!
Ah, it's okay!
Can I use this?
Thank you very much!
Then, I'll wipe it off!
Wow, there's a lot!
Ah, it feels so good!
It feels so good for me too!
Can I do this a few more times?
Yes!
I did it!
Ah, it feels so good!
I'm going to do this every day!
Maybe I should take a break from work too!
Ah, maybe I should take a break from work too!
Yes, thank you very much!
Ah, it feels so good!
Mahiru!
Hey!
It's time to wake up!
It's a good time!
What's wrong?
Hey!
I'm going to work!
Why are you so tired?
You've only been doing housework, haven't you?
I'm sorry!
You haven't been waking up at all lately, have you?
I haven't slept this much, but you've been sleeping a lot!
I just can't wake up!
Did something happen?
No...
Not really...
Hello?
Yes, I'm on my way!
Yes, I understand.
Hello?
Hello, Sakura-san?
Good morning!
Yes.
I'm on my way.
Did you go to work?
Yes.
You have a lot of reservations today too!
Good luck!
Yes.
You're so popular, so you have a lot of reservations!
Can't I take a break today?
What's wrong? You want to take a break?
You can't!
What's wrong?
I told you!
There are a lot of people who like you!
It's just a short break!
Good luck!
Do you want me to pick you up?
Yes, I'm on my way.
Get ready!
Let's meet at the usual place!
Yes.
Sakura-san...
Thank you for watching!