I'm home.
Welcome home.
Do you want to eat?
It's getting late, so I had dinner.
I see.
Naoki, are you still in the office?
Yes.
You're going to school tomorrow, right?
Don't stay up too late.
It's okay.
Naoki became my partner.
Really?
Yes.
I'm going to take a bath and go to bed.
Okay.
Naoki.
What's wrong with you?
Why did you do this to Mei?
Don't say bad things about Yuichi.
But...
Are you going to kiss me?
Yes.
Sorry.
I told you to just kiss me, didn't I?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You promised to kiss me, didn't you?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You're still here?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You look so sad.
I can't see you.
It's okay.
I won't make you feel lonely.
Thank you.
No.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Just a kiss.
If it's just that...
I can't betray you.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
Okay.
Kiss me.
You're really cold.
Just a kiss, right?
Yes, but...
No.
Hey, let's go to sleep.
Let's go to sleep.
Okay.
Thank you for getting along with Naoki.
Yeah.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Actually...
I'm talking about the money.
Yeah.
But it's not decided yet.
It's about the devil.
Yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
The destination is overseas.
What?
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah.
To be honest...
It's a rare opportunity.
Yeah.
It's a so-called success.
That's good.
Yeah.
So...
I can't come back for a while if I go once.
Yeah.
But when I come back,
it seems that the post is promised.
Yeah.
And...
Well, it's closed.
Yeah.
If possible,
I want you to come with me.
What?
Well, I understand.
Well,
it may not be a sudden story.
It's not decided yet.
It's just a trial,
so I have time to think about it.
Yeah.
Well, that's what it is.
I want you to think about it.
Well,
don't rush to answer.
Yeah.
Well,
recently,
I've been very busy with that.
Yeah.
I apologize for being careless.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Well,
I'm very grateful
that you do housework
and care about Aki.
I'm thinking about
your future
and your children.
Yeah.
Well,
I've been working.
Yeah.
So,
it's not that I'm careless.
Yeah.
Well,
I'm sorry
for being careless.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, too.
Yeah.
Me, too.
I'm sorry, too.
Why?
Yeah.
It's not your fault.
Well,
recently,
I think
your mood
is getting brighter
than before.
Really?
Yeah.
Well,
you've become
very feminine.
What's that?
Recently,
I haven't been like that.
Yeah.
Well,
Finally,
you've gotten older.
Yeah.
Well,
I wonder
whether you're
I'm getting nervous.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
I'll try to do it.
Hello?
I see.
Excuse me.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
What's wrong with your finger?
I washed it in the morning.
It's okay.
Thank you.
I heard about the
I'm going to New York.
Overseas?
Yes.
And I'm going to go with you.
So, I want to end my relationship with Naoki.
You know, Yuichi,
I thought you weren't interested in me.
But you've been thinking about me all the time.
So, I can't do this anymore.
I'm sorry.
Then, can I kiss you one last time?
But...
I'm sorry.
It's just a kiss.
It's the last time.
I can't.
It's okay if it's just a kiss, right?
Here and here.
It's dirty, so I can't.
I can't.
I really can't.
You can't?
I can't.
It's okay if it's just a kiss, right?
It's just a scratch.
It's dirty.
It's okay if it's just a kiss, right?
It's okay if it's just a scratch, right?
I'm sorry.
Kiss, kiss, kiss.
It's just a kiss.
Kiss, kiss.
Kiss, kiss, kiss.
I'm sorry.
It's just a kiss.
Kiss, kiss, kiss.
I'm sorry.
Kiss, kiss.
Kiss, kiss, kiss.
I'm sorry.
Kiss, kiss.
It's just a kiss.
I'm sorry.
Kiss, kiss.
It's just a kiss.
No.
You can't kiss me like that.
It's just a kiss.
It's okay.
I don't know what to do with this
It's number 2
I'm just kissing
Gross, isn't it?
I can't eat it because it's too spicy.
I'm going to throw up.
I can't eat it.
I need to have a kiss.
Kiss.
I need to kiss.
No, please don't!
No! No! No!
Oh, no!
I'm sorry.
Don't put it in there.
It's a child.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Mei.
I like you.
I've liked you for a long time.
Thank you.
I like you.
I want to kiss you a lot.
I'm sorry.
I want to kiss you.
I feel really bad!
It hurts!
What the hell...
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry.
Me too.
Will you kiss me again?
If it's just a kiss...
I'm sorry.
It smells good, but what are you cooking?
Kimpira-gobo.
Kimpira?
Yeah.
Sounds good.
Oh, right.
What time do you have dinner?
Around 7.30 or something.
Can I go to your house before that?
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
I'll go home by then.
Have a good day.
Kimpira-gobo
What are you going to make with kimpira?
Oh, grilled fish.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Sashimi would be nice with fish.
What?
I can't.
Tell me already.
I'll go buy some after I get home.
How about that?
Oh, that would be nice.
I'm going to eat grilled fish with sashimi.
You're going to eat grilled fish tomorrow?
Yeah.
Okay, then.
I'm going to eat grilled fish with sashimi.
Okay.
I can't.
Let me do it.
How many pieces of fish do you have?
It's probably three.
Three is fine, though.
If it's a tuna, you can just buy a medium-sized one.
Yeah, I usually try my best.
Yeah.
I heard you eat something thick.
Hmm.
Something oily?
I don't know if it's oily or not, but it's too oily.
I wonder what it is.
It's a tuna.
It's a medium-sized tuna.
Yeah.
It's really good.
I see.
It's a good sound.
Yeah.
It's a double sound.
You don't have anything like this, do you?
Oh.
I enjoy drinking water.
You don't drink water, do you?
Yeah, that's all.
I'm sorry, but what are you making?
Do you make that kind of sound with a
machine-made piano?
What?
I do.
By the way, what's the yakiniku?
Hmm.
Dori?
Dori.
I see.
Yeah.
You don't like it?
I don't hate it at all.
I'd rather not.
Yeah.
I love it, I love it.
That's nice.
It's decided, then.
Yeah.
It's luxurious today.
Should I go buy that?
Yeah.
That's nice.
It's nice, right?
Yeah.
I'll cool the beer.
I got it.
Can I have a beer?
Hmm?
Yeah, then have a can.
Yeah.
Hmm?
Excuse me.
I'm used to being alone with you.
Are you really okay with me?
Hmm...
Do you want to get pregnant?
Ah...
Hmm...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh
I'm sorry.
Give me more.
I want to sleep.
Risa.
Amazing.
I want to sleep.
Risa, I want to sleep.
Give me more.
Over there.
Wait.
I want to sleep.
Risa.
Over there.
I want to sleep.
I love you so much.
Okay...
It was hard for me again after my surgery.
Did I say something?
Let me make two massages.
Yawn
Ahhh!
I was able to do it!
I can't do it.
It's hot!
I can't do it either.
I can't do it.
Nn? More...
Give me more...
I'll try again.
You may be able to see the big dove in the branches.
Don't cry.
Are you okay?
I'm full.
Give me your hand.
Damn it!
I want to pee.
I like this.
Do you like it?
I want to pee.
Give me your hand.
I hope you come back.
Me too.
I'm going to go now.
Wait.
Is it cold?
Thank you.
It's colder over there.
Please keep warm.
Eat your meal.
I know. Don't worry.
I'm sorry I can't go with you.
I have to work hard for my child.
My father will do his best.
I'm going now.
Have a nice day.
Naoki.
Take care of yourself.
I'm going.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
Haru and Sofa invited me to join them
Sofa and?
What do you mean you are?
Haru and conceptwoman Mr. cherish
What's wrong?
So cute.
Uh-huh?
Uhh!
Ah!
Ahh...
Ahh!
Ah-huh!
Ah!
Ahh!
Uhh!
Ah...
Uh...
Ahhh...
Uhh...
Ahh!
Uh...
Hmm...
Furthermore...
Umm...
Ough...
Hmm...
Ah, well...
Hmmm...
Nagase's
How does it feel?
Does it feel good?
I don't feel anything.
Finally.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I want to massage you a lot.
I messed up.
What?
More.
I'm sorry.
Wow.
It's hard.
More.
Take it easy.
I'm sorry.
More.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm sorry.
Wait.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm sorry.
Wow.
More.
Take it easy.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
, I used to say
, yes ah ah
Oh, no!
It hurts...
Wahh…
Wahh….
…...
Go go go….
Ah!
Ah...
Don't talk.
I'm tired.
Ah...
Don't talk.
I'm getting too tired.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
I have his blood!
It feels great!
You're so cute.
Really?
I have to rest now.
I want to do it a lot.
Let's do it one by one.
I'm tired.
I'll die.
Come on!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
It's struggling!
What?
It's цвет!
Ah!
I can't do it anymore.
Slowly.
Inu Inu Inu Inu Inu Inu....
More
feels good
Today, I'm going to perform with the director.
Does it feel good?
Amazing.
I want to do it.
It's over.
What's going on?
It feels good.
I'm sleepy.
My heart is pounding.
What's going on?
I'm pregnant.
You can put it in.
I want to do it more.
40.
One more time.
I want to do it more.
It's over.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Did you feel good?
I love you.