Yes to.
Is Mr. Kato happy?
Oh, oh, oh, how about it.
Iris, come back when you’re done.
No, I don’t want to go.
Why is it.
Come and find tea.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, I don’t want to go, this.
No, say this
No, what to do.
No, I don’t want to go.
No, why is it.
Say to me.
Go to
I go to
Nothing is anything.
Go to?
The River
The previous documents.
Named by
Why not.
and again.
Thanks to.
Not that you.
Please take a little.
Do it.
Close your eyes in 10 minutes.
OK is?
Have you lost?
Can I send you email again?
Please be kind.
Take it right away, you.
You are the troubled.
Take it, close your eyes now.
In five minutes, in five minutes.
Yes yes yes.
Because I just sold it.
Very much lying.
Mr. Sato, I was getting a gift.
Yes, it is over already.
well is.
Thanks to Mr. Sato.
Not like any other actor.
Thanks, so keep going.
Yes, I understand
Mr. Sato can work.
No is so.
The fourth year?
Oh yes is.
Really good sales qualifications.
Oh it is true.
But the water has not lost.
Thanks to.
compared to that,
It is Togo, Togo.
Are you here? – Togo
Email cannot be opened.
You can’t open the email.
A half-month sales report
You know it?
I have not taken it, this is the number.
No, a little by chance.
It is coincidence.
It did not work.
Did I sleep in the car?
Look at them, they are both.
Did you open the email, not the email?
You opened the email.
No, it opened up.
Oh, you opened it up?
No, I am crazy.
It is here.
Oh here from here?
It was open.
Go to bed.
Yes I understand.
really is.
If it were, if it was me.
I told you not to come at this time.
Will come home this week.
Your mother is worried.
I said I am busy.
Are you busy.
Your mother is worried.
Come back home.
Try to go home next month.
The next month?
No to
My dad got a little bad.
Are you going home this week?
Is it so?
Is it okay?
It is hard.
I am fine.
You are okay or you are alone.
What are you doing?
No one to go home.
Good enough.
You are 25.
How many times do you say that?
Not because it is no longer decided.
You have to buy a house, have a family, or anything.
I am married too.
Why Why?
Is it so?
Take her here.
Yes, bring it with you.
So take it here.
Okay, I’ll prepare it here.
I understand.
This week.
Enjoy it.
Yes
I am waiting for you this week.
Because they do work too.
Then is.
Go here and go around the store.
Good to you.
Not a little reassured.
But what kind of person.
Will Sato get married?
No, I have a little parents, get married, get married, because it’s noisy.
You said it with strength.
So it is not that.
Absolutely different.
You are not there.
Because I only do work.
What is the water? what is the water?
No, no, I am sorry
Were you interested?
No, not so is it.
That is.
No, it is a little bit.
not the.
Congratulations to you.
I don’t like to go ahead.
A little fun.
So, wait this week, if you want to come home with me?
It is not to say that no one will take you.
Yes, yes, no, I am sorry, yes, I am okay.
I can do something. thanks.
Then then.
Tired of.
Good morning sir.
I think Mr. Sato is going to get married.
Did you not listen?
Well, I’ll say, I’ll call your dad soon.
Oh yeah yes.
Get married, get married, and make a noise.
I told him I was going to get married a little bit.
Oh, and do you do?
Yes, I will not.
Oh, I do not do.
But something, something
I’ll go to my wedding this weekend and tell my parents.
What do you do?
I called a friend, I tried.
Everyone said they can’t.
I have a matching app or something, and if someone takes it, what if they are in there?
No, I don’t think the people I met on the app might meet their parents.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
So, bring something nice.
If it really does like marriage, I don’t want it.
There are a lot of hippies around us.
The high spec?
There is no good guy that your parents don’t like.
No man, no man, no man, no man, no man, no man, no man, no man, no man.
So, Mr. Todd, what’s going on this week?
I have a little request.
I am with you, Mr. Tohoku.
Thanks, I am pleased.
It is called Tōgoku Suarez.
Welcome to.
Sorry for the late greeting.
This is boring though.
If you like, I am sorry.
thank you.
Oh my dear, thank you.
and afterwards.
Let’s eat later.
It was far away, right?
No, yes yes yes
Are they both in the same department?
Yes yes yes.
The same colleague.
Yes to.
And face to face for a long time.
well is.
Yes, the desk is next to it.
It is now.
Is the desk next door?
Do you know the workplace?
No, I have not talked yet.
Yes, I am not talking.
So to say,
I don’t know what Tucson likes.
I made your favorite cup today.
You like your mother’s food, right?
really is?
Can you still eat?
Is it okay?
Do you not like it?
not is
I will prepare.
In the meantime, relax a little.
You can sit.
Sorry to
to mother.
Spice, what university is it?
How about?
I am anyway.
It is already cold.
I said, I said.
Oh my old man.
Oh really?
Drink and drink and drink.
Sorry, I’m going to go first.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay
What is.
Oh no no no.
Yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
Oh thank you.
Please let me catch you.
My daughter’s wife is okay, so I’m okay.
is there.
Is it your wife? – No.
Enjoy it today.
After hearing me.
And then toast.
Is the mountain still alive?
No, I have never met you.
Oh yeah, so is it.
What happens when students go to the store often?
It was before the station of Machu Picchu.
Is it a coffee shop?
The thousand land?
Maybe it was a coffee shop.
Oh, and so on.
I used this coffee shop very often.
You met often, right?
Is it yes?
Well, I know you, because you know me at college.
It is yes.
Are you in touch?
A good boy has come.
We are talking, right?
So, is it from there?
No, it is from a completely different place.
Where are you from?
I am Nagano.
Oh and Nagano?
Yes Yes Yes
I am also Nagano.
Oh, was it so?
Which city is it?
I am Matsumoto.
Is it Matsumoto?
Are you no longer old?
Oh, that is something.
Born in Matsumoto.
Growing up, and that.
Born by Matsumoto.
by Nagoya
Oh yeah yeah yeah
You do not know, you.
Oh, I didn’t say.
But I was wrong with other people.
Oh, and so on.
Oh well well well.
Well, but there are also such things.
Okay, you are well.
It comes from Matsuda.
Not close to your grandmother’s house.
Oh yeah yeah.
Very close to.
Do not forget.
Not great.
Tastefully
Is it okay? is there nothing to cut?
It really tastes.
This is, here is
Is this delicious?
Sorry to
and salt.
Always very much.
No, but well
We haven’t talked about the con yet.
Why did you not talk?
I said that I’m going to get married, but that’s just what it might be.
No matter what, both are now.
What about it? – I was presented for free.
How about Todd, are you going to get married?
There is
Oh well was.
Yes is it.
Is there a name for your father?
Have you already decided on the venue?
It is not determined.
For example, there is a good place for a church or a good association.
What place do you like?
Both seem to fit well.
Oh yeah yeah
Would you give me a sacred place?
The tombs are fine.
Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes
What are you happy with?
How many kids do you think about?
The child?
About how many?
Or six people?
Six people?
6 is!
Ballet and ballet usually make a team.
Oh well well!
Is it one?
Not all parents have a team, right?
No, it might be that too.
Okay, it is fun.
If you want to change it, you can make it to two families.
Oh well okay.
Decide about something.
If you get married, you also need a home.
Yes, I hope it happens.
It has expanded.
Okay is it?
Absolutely OK.
I still want to do my job and I just got a big job.
If you are a child, you have to be a worker yourself.
Yes is it.
This is a little bit of a shame, so you need to protect your home.
Oh well, yes is it.
See also!
That big job should be done by separating it?
You should start working early and take care of your family.
Only family can feel like that.
But it is already 25.
When you get married, you have to think about your family first.
Yes, here is the third grandson, Suzuka, now the second grandson.
Yes is.
Yes, in this area.
It’s too early, but here.
Well yes yes.
The house is home, shit.
Marrying is home, so leave it.
Well, well, but it’s time to get married.
Timing and timing.
It is a big wave, you have to go when there is history.
No to no.
I met a good guy.
No to yes.
Why not talk to yourself.
Talk about it like that,
It is me who will be hard later.
You should talk now.
Because the river is no longer relevant.
I will be told afterwards.
It tastes good, this.
It tastes good.
Drinks around here.
Yes is what.
The most pressed.
Drink a little.
If you drink it, it will be expensive.
I dream of drinking safely.
No, please let me catch.
Not extending too much.
Okay, okay is okay.
If you can’t go home anyway.
You do not need to go home.
What are you saying?
Sorry to.
I should stay here.
No, it is not good.
Why is it?
It is delicious.
Tomorrow is too early, right?
Oh to?
I’m not saying you’re going to go up the mountain tomorrow, right?
No, I won’t go tomorrow.
It will rain tomorrow.
Is it okay?
No, I am not going tomorrow.
How to climb?
It was the mountain department.
Oh, oh, oh, yes really is it.
Yes, yes is yes.
Exciting to climb together.
Oh well okay.
Let’s go with you on a clear day.
Okay is.
Do not connect the station.
Why not? well okay.
Go out and change clothes, right?
Oh well.
I think so too.
This is really delicious.
Sleeping is easy, this.
But so much, okay?
Sleep to sleep.
Sleeping together and together.
Now, but go home sooner.
Oh well Mr. Kowalski.
You’re going to stay here today, right?
Oh well okay?
Okay, it is absolutely okay!
No, it is anything!
It is OK!
My daddy’s pyjamas are new.
Sorry about something...
Be slowly!
It is OK!
Oh yeah!
Oh, and your dad, right?
But isn’t it too upset for the river?
It was the first day and...
No, I am absolutely...
I have always thought of salt.
Why about the Kashmir...
Did you call at the time?
I haven’t told you about dating a company yet.
Usually in the company.
Oh well well well.
Yes is.
It is different at home.
How is it called?
See also Couture.
Mr Cottage is.
here here?
Which of them?
Both are.
It changes by day.
Yes to Yes.
You read it under the name below.
Yes is yes.
Stop and stop.
Then it is decided.
Good thing, Dad.
So I have to arrange it.
Drink and I will go.
I will eat.
Then
Give her a pyjama.
Going to the bath?
Yes, so I’ll prepare a bath.
Do it, do it.
So go in both of us?
No, they are not good at both.
It’s not a very small bathroom, so we’re both.
No, we are both, a little.
Because the next?
I am dating.
Because you still have your mom and dad in there.
You will go in together, right?
Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes!
So I’ll come to use the bath.
is delicious?
It is delicious, right?
Something or something.
I really love you, hi.
I will be a good girl, this.
So, I’m going to talk a lot about it.
I don’t want to take a bath with you.
No, if it was going to flow, it would have been like that.
When I answered yes, I didn’t think it would happen, so I couldn’t work.
No, no, there is no atmosphere.
No to no.
Yes is
What is
Today, I love the bathroom.
Because he is no longer a child.
Yes thank you.
Have you seen?
Yes I saw.
Oh, it is awesome.
Great, where you are going.
Are you in?
Come in, go in there.
Which of them?
Wait behind you.
Together and together.
You have to look through the mirror.
Oh, I haven’t seen it anymore.
No to, how about?
Not yet in.
It will cool.
Wait a little.
You have seen it.
I have not seen.
Is there anything?
No, do not touch it.
I did not touch.
I have to go in this too.
Yes, there is no other way.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, no
Oh no, no, I thought I would tell you where to put it.
On the washing machine.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Okay, okay, I have taken it off somewhat.
Should I take off my pants?
Okay, yes is it.
Do not look.
No, look at it, don’t look at it.
I didn’t see it, I didn’t see it. – Now it’s not.
What is?
Oh a little.
Oh no no no.
What are you guessing?
I do not guess.
What to do?
Let us enter.
Yes, yes, you can go in.
meet for a long time.
I like these things.
It feels good.
is
by the way.
Why not return it.
I was there when I entered.
Oh, it was so.
It was too much priority for work.
You are definitely working hard.
Is there no such place?
No, there is no.
There is not, but.
something like this.
No, no, no otherwise is okay.
Do not make a boyfriend?
Do you feel like your job is a lover now?
I feel something bad.
really is?
I don’t have any wishes that I would marry in the future.
I think I’ll be single all my life.
Oh, otherwise
Can your boyfriend be working together?
by Mr Sato.
Oh, it is not that kind of equipment.
I did not look like that.
You can’t focus on just one thing.
I cannot even do one thing.
Yes is.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah.
That is the river, right?
What are you watching?
Oh yeah no no.
Mr. Kashmir
I put my pyjamas.
Thanks to.
Wash your body.
I washed, washed, washed, and washed as usual.
As always, yes
Yes, so do it.
It feels good.
No, because I do it every day.
The other is.
Great that thing.
Shia, you think your breasts are bigger?
What is it going well?
Where are you touching?
What are you touching?
Great, it is there.
Do not touch here.
Do not think you have grown up.
It has grown.
What happened? is it okay?
Okay, it is warm.
I am not okay.
Why? he did nothing.
You can know.
What do you smell?
by nearby
Do not shake a little.
to shake?
Because I am just washing.
A little bit.
Sorry sorry sorry
A little
Sorry to sorry.
You did not hit.
When did it disappear?
But, maybe, but maybe
Actually, listen to it right away.
by
A possible type.
It seems possible, right?
Possibly he will come back soon.
and so on.
Wash it as usual.
Please please
Please today.
with today.
Feels good.
must be quick.
Feel good
slowly
Follow it by way.
Thanks to Shia.
Yes, I like that feeling.
I don’t know what my dad likes.
Oh yes yes.
I want the cakes to wash well too.
What here?
It feels good.
A little bit,
Be quick.
Yes Yes Yes
Not well there.
No is
I do not know.
Look at it a little.
No to
Do not think you are.
I think there.
What do you know.
No, you know.
I know your father’s feelings.
Definitely there.
Because there is definitely.
It feels good.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Yes, we will come.
here here
What to do?
Go out, go out.
Sorry to
I didn’t say the bus stop.
No, it doesn’t matter, I have to do that.
must do this.
You feel good, Siso.
very much.
Oh well was.
Send me a mail when I leave.
Shane, can you give me a bubble?
Ok to.
You can stream.
Is this going to sleep with you?
Oh, no, it is not a bit appropriate anymore.
Sorry, it is really a bit appropriate.
It is fine, how are you concerned?
Thanks, I will borrow you.
Sorry, but the bed is a bit small.
Is this not a crap?
What are you saying?
You are always sleeping with me, guys.
You are dating.
Yes, we are sleeping together.
Yes is it.
The clothes cannot be placed separately.
is.
Yes is it?
Yes is it.
Even though the night is still long.
Sleep slowly.
It is long, night.
Dad, can we go?
So let’s go.
and slowly.
Go to sleep slowly.
Because I do not interfere.
Sleep slowly.
Good night.
You should have slept and pulled the cloth.
Bed is bad.
In the hands of your father and mother,
When we go to bed with you,
It is also strange in reverse.
Change and well.
It is strange to sleep together.
If you were dating,
Sleep together.
Go sleep with me, as usual.
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Sleep together.
You are nervous today.
It was the first time I had that kind of greeting, so I was nervous.
I was so excited and wanted to get rid of Coke.
Oh is?
The Dutch?
Yes, it is always. – As usual.
A vacation before going to bed.
The vacation chick.
As usual as usual.
So I will.
Yes to.
A little better.
As always
always is
that
A little
What do you.
Do not have to go here.
well now
No is
Watch from Sion.
Yes is.
I look, I look.
Daddy and mother.
must continue
I will be loved.
Now, at the moment
What happened?
You said.
It’s a show, so you don’t have to go here.
No, but if you don’t, your father and mother may die.
I need to seek reality.
No so is.
My mom and dad went there, so we went to sleep.
No, but I do not know.
Maybe he was still behind the door.
again is
Let us sleep.
Again on the wall.
Because this follows...
Okay, let’s go to sleep.
I will take it out of your mouth.
So is okay.
This is dirty, so I drink it.
Better to drink.
You are already a binary.
At work, do so with attention.
Do not look too much.
But yes is.
Yes, is well
Continue to.
You do not need to have breasts.
No to no.
See also Continued.
No more
Yes
No to
Go home tomorrow morning, when you get home.
Of course I go home.
This happened on Monday in the company.
Do not be happy.
Yes, I think I can normally.
Yes to.
Siro’s that, operation, oxy, chickpeak, feel easy, sickness, or something like that, I will never say, even if I speak.
Not full of courage.
No, I am not saying, that is.
I promise, really
I will not say, I will not say.
It is easy to paint, it is easy to paint, it is not so, I will not say, so be calm.
You don’t have to say that every time.
If you say something.
No, it is okay, I don’t say that.
I do not say anything bad.
Good or definitely good.
But thank you today.
If there is anything else that helps, I will go.
Sorry, but I said I had to drink.
No to?
Oh, wait a little.
Tish and Tish.
Is it okay?
Yes
So go to sleep.
I sleep on my right side as much as possible.
Sleep on your left as much as possible.
Then
Oh good night.
Good night.
Oh well.
He is dead.
is noisy
Mr Sato
Yes
What are you doing, Mr. Sato?
Wait a little.
What this, a little.
Mr Sato
Where to lick.
A little
Mr Sato is
Really not.
A little
No, a little
that
No to
What are you thinking?
What to enter.
No to no.
It is open.
A little
Is it awakening?
Let’s have breakfast.
Good morning
Good morning.
It was clear today.
Good electricity.
Good morning mother.
We will both have breakfast.
something
It seems like East Coast has been working.
Yes, I have to go out in the morning.
Oh, yes, my mom had me ready for breakfast.
Sorry, but hurry a little.
Will Sio go with me?
No, I have something to do.
Yes, I won’t go with you.
So, you can get dressed up and go for breakfast.
Sorry, I can’t do that kind job.
I’m waiting for you below.
I promise you to go out in the morning.
promise that.
Get ready and get out.
by
I guess I could only have a spoon.
No need to look here anymore.
Prepare to quickly.
What this.
Because of me.
I think it’s weird to do something while I’m asleep.
Take it off or put your finger in.
almost somewhere.
Okay, go out there.
Because we are lovers.
What a shameless thing.
It ended yesterday.
Okay, leave it out.
So, salt, you are so beautiful.
Well, I don’t buy much or anything.
Yes, you really live with Mr. Kowalski.
Yes, I live there though.
Not much too much?
I have just moved recently, but I haven’t moved yet.
Is it so?
But let’s get a little around here.
Do you have toothbrushes in front of the TV?
Yes, I’ve just cleaned it up and left it somewhat weird.
Oh yes.
So what, is it Tada?
Oh, what, I’m ready to move now.
I said it before, but I am moving.
Maybe they are going to pick up their bags.
Oh, can I help you?
Yes, because my mother is coming.
Sorry to.
Oh is?
Yes, that is what.
Just ask for convenience.
You have a plan, right?
Oh, there is something?
Climbing the mountain alone.
The mountain climb?
The hobby.
Well, it is probably so.
This weekend, it was a bad weather.
The view is good.
I have not slept lately.
Next week will be okay.
Please really.
Because I do anything.
Anything is?
Yes
Anything really?
Anything is okay.
Yes, if I could do what I could.
Oh, and so on.
There is nothing but Mr. Sato.
I said, whatever.
As it was last time.
Oh, oh, oh, that is a matter of fact.
What do you say in the company?
Oh what
Oh what is.
So about helping.
to lick.
Oh that.
It was flowing before.
The atmosphere of that place.
Oh, but I am fine.
Every day he is being demonized by his father.
It doesn’t matter to me that you were caught.
What to do?
It depends on Sato.
I think I’d be either.
If you listen to that request.
Will you continue to cooperate?
Thinking about what can we help?
What to do?
Just like before, just go to the mouth.
really is?
Yes
So, let me give you.
OK is.
So then, then then then.
Oh, and here?
Oh is?
Talk about now, right?
Only here is.
He seems to have gone home with the boss.
Only now.
Why are you growing up now?
Sorry sorry sorry
Okay okay?
The girl moves.
What are you filming? is it stupid?
Because not can?
You are determined not.
No, I think I am a personal person.
Is it over?
It is no longer over.
So then then
Never show it to anyone.
Yes, I will not.
Oh, Mr. Sasha, you are so good.
No to
No to well.
is good.
Not so though.
No to
Cut off.
that is
that
Just move, just sit down, and move like this.
Okay is?
Oh yeah, thou shalt
Oh, this is good.
something completely different.
What, what what what happened?
What happened?
was too hard.
Sorry to sorry.
Great to
Is it okay?
I want you to sit a little.
Yes Yes Yes
sweetly
What do you touch?
No, I would rather do this.
I can go fast.
Just a little.
Are you looking at your breasts?
I thought I had not seen my breasts.
by Brist
Oh yeah yeah
I want to continue.
by Brist
Feel good
Feels good?
Very good feeling.
Oh is
A little Suzuki.
was perfect.
that is
That gold.
Can not drink.
Oh well
Oh, I’ll be lying here.
No more move.
But it felt good and it moved immediately.
I have to go quickly.
be hasty.
No, but I am not in a hurry.
It is crazy.
Everyone has returned.
Because I say I’m going to do this.
Now I can’t pull it back.
Is it good, good, good, good feeling?
Oh shit, I am going out.
Dad, what do I do?
No, what to do.
What to do.
Put it out like this.
Sorry to sorry.
Wait a little, wait a little.
Tishy
This is a beautiful guy.
It is neither clean nor dirty.
Okay but thank you.
Yes, I clean it up.
Why put so much in it?
No, because it is not.
He has gone out.
Oh my shirt, come in.
Because I promise.
This weekend, you have not forgotten.
Yes, this weekend though.
Please please.
So, dress up quickly.
Because he just came home.
Is the seed okay?
Okay now.
But, you know, your mother married and went home.
When your mother came into the house, your father worked hard, built the house, and you also did the job in school.
But we both have a relationship that supports work.
I think I might be worried if I miss my job.
In business or in private, I want to be with you.
Oh, you have come.
Is it Tajo?
Yes, look at me a little.
Do you really live?
Did you go wrong?
It is noisy.
No, because I don’t know you’re coming for the first time.
Yes is it.
And the address I sent you was different.
I and my brother have gotten a little bit of a goo.
Gulliver? is it
Oh well mother.
I think they live together, but they are suspicious.
Yes, I know, I have nothing to do with me.
It is.
Come in now.
Oh, a little
Just now.
Welcome to.
I am hindering you.
Were you here?
Welcome to.
Just now.
Oh this.
thanks to.
Do not calm down at home.
Yes, you are tired.
You always leave it here.
The suitcase is here.
Oh my mother.
thanks to.
Yes, it is good to have your own home.
Yes is.
I want to get that, that, and everything else here.
Yes, because I only have this.
It is true, right?
Today was the day to change your toothbrush.
Yes is.
Change it every week?
Yes, I am changing every week.
It is important, because it is important.
Thanks, I am full of it, okay.
It was heavy. – He was heavy.
Let’s have a toast, right?
I bought it right now, okay? Oh thank you.
Please choose what you like.
Do you always buy it like this? Yes is.
When I get home, I’m mostly going to dinner.
It is so.
Which is good?
So let me go here.
from now on.
I am this.
Is it okay?
Yes it is okay.
I will open.
thanks to.
Then I open.
Okay well okay.
something is,
I am always like that too.
Then then,
thanks to.
and again.
well is.
Toast to.
I just said I wanted salt and I wanted to go.
Something will feel like that.
Yes, of course it is.
Yes, I will go back.
So when is the move completed?
Yes, what was it?
You are moving now.
Move on, yes
Oh well...
You live together, so think well.
said it was not.
You are a company, right?
Does your company have people who expect to speak?
First of all, there are not many women, so it is not so bad.
Yes to?
Oh yeah yes.
Not a little to fix.
You came out of town when you came out of town, right?
It is good to enter the family.
Did I say that?
What I said, it was true.
Oh yeah then yes.
and no.
Yes, women come into the house.
The men work outside.
To support the family as a pillar.
The secret is, it will work.
My mom drinks too much tea.
Okay, okay now you too.
Can you go home properly?
Do not say work.
Think about having children, right?
I still don’t know.
Oh, baby, you have a tooth in your stomach.
Meaning is
If you were born at 20 years old.
You have to think, right?
After 30 years, you have a birth.
It is hard, Mr. Tohoku.
Yes, you think so, right?
I think, yes
It’s not your mother’s problem, right?
No matter what, you are in the sea, and you will not get married.
Mr. Todd, I don’t think you’re going to go anywhere.
Oh, I’m not the type of shit.
He is more attracted to my ass than me.
You want to work, right?
Yes yes but.
You are getting that feeling.
Okay, that is a place.
Do not let me endure.
You are your mom, it is time to go home.
What, it is still okay.
I should have come with your father.
Well, Mr. Kowalski, now I’ll be going home and leave my family.
I have to take a horse, take a tower, go to Gigi.
Guggy
Yes
Don’t have to ask, Mr. Kowalski.
What about the job? – Not even the chance of a life out.
Well, it feels like a dirt.
It seems you are already working hard.
So, it’s time to get married and try it.
Otherwise, I could not have been born before.
Oh, was it so?
is married.
Not told to?
There was not much around me.
Now it’s time for women to work, isn’t it?
Isn’t that a little room for the men?
Oh, maybe it may be.
You are not married to a boss, right?
The boss is married.
It is important to say marriage.
Certainly.
It is cool.
This is a shot, but Mr. Oakley must hold his attention and pull him to death.
You are ready to live with them, right?
Yes, of course, I mean living together.
You will care about it, right?
I intend to.
Yes is.
I love the salt.
I will care.
Good was.
I want to see my grandson’s face.
My mother slept.
I will bring a little bracket.
If you sleep here, you get a cold.
The cold will fall.
Is it okay?
Go to bed in the morning, it will be light.
Yes
Oh yeah, and so on.
Yes to?
So what, what then?
Just said
What is?
Her mother is.
I told him to get married soon.
I told you.
Oh is?
Did you say something?
You said.
I get it somehow.
Sorry, what did you say?
No longer enough.
Let her mother sleep.
Oh yeah, it looks like.
will fall.
by
well is
well well well
This is OK.
Time to go home.
Go home to
How to do.
No final train?
Oh is
I think you’re enjoying it, or a taxi.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Walk along the way and take a taxi.
I would rather enjoy it if it was real.
Okay, I am sorry for that.
I couldn’t, I came today.
No, but it is absolutely okay.
If she wasn’t there when she woke up in the morning, she would rest.
Let me sleep here, and sleep with you both.
Put it now?
No, I will finish later.
I only have a pyjama at home.
Oh yeah, now it is.
If it were your own home.
Can I borrow this?
I want to sleep here.
Go to bed normally on top.
Oh, no, my mom is already sleeping.
You will not come to see.
Not a day for a boyfriend or anything.
I think it’s better to sleep separately.
Yes, no longer
Okay, I can sleep here.
Do not care.
But I don’t look like you were before.
Instead, you should sleep normally.
I had to come here for that.
I cannot say you sleep in the opposite.
I have always heard your mother’s stories.
No, not in any way.
So keep your words.
Yes
I’ll go to this floor.
Macro is
Okay, I cannot use it.
Macro is okay, yes, yes.
Oh well good night.
Oh good night.
Even if it was a play.
Not so is it.
No to
Don’t say anything strange, I go to bed.
No, maybe that,
Maybe you’ll come to see it.
I am not coming to see.
My mother is drunk and she will not wake up when she sleeps.
No, that is all good.
If you think it’s a play, you might still doubt.
Thinking too much.
What are you touching?
No, I thought it would be better to have a wall and a love.
I didn’t get cold until then.
How is it.
Sorry to say.
No to no.
Maybe if
Now is
You may listen to the wall.
Not listening to.
No, I am lying, I don’t know.
Have you seen?
I have not seen.
A bit of.
Do not smell.
Not a little.
Now I am going to sleep.
Okay, so stay here and sleep here.
The back?
Just calm down here.
Okay then then.
Good night.
Not on the back, but on the hands.
You put it on your seat, right?
I want to sit.
No to
Do not touch the neck.
not do it.
You don’t have lips.
I have thick lips.
It does not matter.
Not really.
It is back.
No to
What are you doing.
Because tell me.
No, no to
No, no, no no
We are not real lovers.
Not a lover.
No, no no
No to
really
If not not.
Do not do it.
Oh, a little
and more and more.
What are you doing.
Try to touch there.
If you are a lover, you will.
If you were a lover.
No to
Something is hidden.
If you are visible.
Do not eat a little.
No to
My mother came.
was evident.
No to
Let her wake up.
Wake up.
Where we are in love.
The mothers are reassured.
I would not like to see such a mother.
Oh yeah
A little
by
If you have such a relationship.
What to look like in the company.
I do not, I
The street now.
Do it to.
You cannot do.
Because it is one day.
by you there.
You came here with your hands.
No more, no more.
Stay away and stay away.
I will not be able to see the river at work.
I will not see.
Oh, a little
So let’s try a little.
The Rivers
Oh well, oh well
Oh, a little
Do it, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
If you really do dish, no.
No dish.
Oh oh oh
Oh yeah
Stop it.
Oh oh oh
Oh is
Yes is
Why is
Tell me.
Talk to
What are you doing? what are you doing?
It is lying.
What are you thinking? what are you doing?
No, what do I do.
Why do you put your finger?
No more no.
Do not put your fingers.
Why is?
not hungry.
He is already vomiting.
How here?
How about...
10 speed, so that is.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah...
Oh, oh, oh, I am going to be fucking!
I am going to be fucking! 😂😂😂
Oh, the puppy...
No longer...
Why is...
What to do, what to do.
I am so upset, why...
Oh...
It is dirty...
Oh, oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Oh yeah...
No, it is not dirty.
Well, a little, what...
What are you doing?
No, it is fine.
A little
Oh yeah
What this
rightly
Oh oh oh
Oh yeah
Yes is
No to
Oh well
What this
Oh yeah
immediately this
A little
Oh yeah
A little more...
No to...
Oh yeah...
Oh...
Oh well...
Such...
Really...
Oh well...
Just to fuck...
Maybe not...
Cheating and cheating...
Oh well...
No to?
Oh, and it hurts...
Stop it! stop it!
Oh yeah
Oh well...
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah yeah...
Sorry to...
Oh well...
No to no.
by
Oh yeah
Oh yeah yeah
No to no.
There is
D is
Oh is
No to
Very good feeling.
that
What do you do.
Oh oh oh
A little... a little...
It does not work...
Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings... Feelings...
Turn to me.
Oh Oh Oh Oh
My mother is
by polite
No to
Oh yeah
Oh Oh Oh Oh
Oh Oh Oh
Eeee
Go to
Waited to
by
Oh Oh Oh
Oh yeah
No to
Go to
hurtly
Sorry to
I have already slept.
I have slept.
Maybe her mother has come now.
Come here and tell me.
and voice.
Or the voice.
My mom came and we were struggling.
Oh yeah, so is it.
So let’s be friends.
It is already hindering.
Feel good
Sleep to
Sleep by
Can I enter?
I entered.
Feel good
It feels good.
Very good feeling.
A little bit.
Let’s go big.
Stop it.
Soon to
The last one came out so terribly.
Beware of your ass.
Feel good
Heat is
Oh, it feels good.
This is awesome.
Full of seats.
Oh, it feels good.
and back.
by
Oh, oh
Feel good
This is O.
It is sand.
Oh, oh
Oh a little.
It feels good.
Yes, it feels good.
Put it in.
It is great. it feels good.
It feels good.
Oh well ðŸ™‚
Oh yeah
by
Yes is
More of
by HY
No more feeling.
by
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Oh yeah
by
greatly
Oh well
Oh yeah
to use?
Yes
I have sperm.
Okay okay.
clothes are
Yes
From that clothes.
Is it okay?
Let me sleep.
Oh yeah yeah.
The pants?
Tomorrow is a company.
What time should I wake up?
If you should have woke up at 7:30, you’ll be on time.
Is it time? at this time?
Oh, and it’s not about what time.
My brother fell.
Sorry to sorry.
Do not get a cold.
Yes
Oh well okay.
OK is.
Let us board together.
Good night coo.
Good night.
Okay, it is over.
Do you drink sometimes?
well is.
Will you go to the place of departure?
Go on, because I am.
Really is?
How about, both of you.
I want to clean up my next job sooner.
You can do it differently, Mr. Sasha.
These are these?
I want to come here with a little time.
You look like you meet in Togo?
I seem not familiar.
What, are you going to Togo?
No, there are still people left to do it today.
Always a prequel.
Oh I was wrong.
Let’s go to the sting.
to bite.
Let us go.
No, I will go.
I will go.
It is fun to bite.
Please do not drink too much.
and no.
You have been hard, now.
You have an autopsy.
Sleep too much.
So please both of you.
Yes, I am tired.
I am tired.
Seeing everyone.
Yes is
Everybody has gone home.
Yes
County County
Stop it, side
What are you lighting?
No, I am not illuminated.
You have done something.
Really is.
and
So is
N is N.
It is true that the work is not done.
This has to be done a little.
No to no.
I will help you later.
and later
What to do.
Let me understand.
What is
What about
The buying?
No, here, there is the office.
But I told him that I had to cut it down there.
Do you remember?
Yes I remember.
True is
You have grown up.
Yes
Let’s remove this.
I went through the mess.
Sorry to
I am glad.
really is?
Yes
Feeled
Oh is
Yes
Down very soft and feel.
No to
Yes
Oh, oh oh
No to
Oh yeah
by
No to
Oh, oh, wait a little while.
I guess you like your voice.
Do you like?
Fuck it cute.
Shame on this dress.
Oh, it is awesome.
It smells.
It does not smell.
It smells good.
Patch is closed.
Maybe I was thinking about Kobe all the time.
Really?
Yes
pleased
greatly
I sleep.
Can I extend it straight?
extend it.
I cannot endure either.
I cannot endure.
Oh oh oh oh oh!
Oh, it is soft and feel good.
Oh well, oh well
Feel good
Oh, it is awesome.
Oh, oh, it feels good there.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh!
by
good is
Sit there.
cannot go
No to no.
Not to speak loud.
Sorry sorry sorry
Wait and more.
Stay on.
Go to
can go
Head taken up.
Go again.
Oh is
No to
Con is
as before.
Yes
Let me remember.
Oh yeah
Okay is?
Feels good?
Feel good
Tupac is in.
It is fucking.
It really is.
Two are open.
Feeled...
How is it? feel good?
It feels good there.
Oh well well.
Maybe something weak.
I will go immediately.
Next to me, what do I do?
There... there...
Help there.
There...
Come to me.
Feeled...
Feel good
More...
Oh well...
Go to go!
Oh, oh oh oh...
Oh well...
Oh, oh...
Oh Shia...
Oh...
Oh well...
Is it okay?
Okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay.
Why is...
A company...
I am clean...
No, no, it is dirty!
A little...
Oh well...
Eat now, well.
Yes
Is it okay?
Take it.
No problem though.
Only today.
Can I take?
got taken
cute and crap.
I will get it up.
I want to lick.
Then a little.
Feels good?
Feel good
It feels great there.
Feels good?
If it is so hard,
Not to get in because you can.
It is not.
That is tired.
Tired of
You are still working.
A little left.
I forgot my phone.
Yes, only what I forget.
You have to be careful, right?
I said I didn’t want to say it before.
I forgot you, you
Because it was good.
What, are you still not done?
Yes to.
How much is left, you?
No, that and that,
and that,
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
It is a complex document.
Oh,
What is?
Be careful of forgotten things.
Come to understand.
What are you doing in that century?
What is what?
This is not your century.
No, that computer
A little bit.
I freeze it.
The freeze?
You probably didn’t destroy it.
No, no is not.
And in the urgent.
Because I have to do.
With Mr. Sato
What happened to Mr. Sato?
Oh, oh, I have gotten home.
Have you already gone home?
I went home.
At least, at least once more.
You seem to be busy.
How many minutes ago did you come home?
I thought I was back ten or fifteen minutes ago.
No, I seem to be busy.
Yes is
Come back when you’re done, change.
Oh yeah, I can’t.
Oh to?
No, I want to go.
I want to go.
Yes is
by
See also Mr. Hato.
Maybe a boyfriend.
No, no no
How about you?
No, I do not know.
Probably not there.
You should ask yourself.
You don’t listen to it, it’s so direct.
How about marriage.
I said something.
No, it is so.
But is
I said it wasn’t before I heard it.
There is no.
Maybe it is now.
No no no no no.
Because it is a job.
Oh so it feels.
Yes, because he is a serious person.
I know there is no.
No to No.
What is?
No to no.
The Me?
Did you say that?
I said it.
You said nothing.
I’m there, I’m there, I’m there with my phone.
No, there is no here.
There is no here.
Or not a toilet.
I’m not going to the toilet, guys.
You should not look for the bottom.
Why? why?
No, I think not in some way.
There was, there was.
It was good, right?
Mr. Sasha, you are very close.
I do not know the house.
Oh, it was near.
Oh yes is it?
No, but if it is too hard,
I can cut it off, no, it’s not good.
Yes, of course of course.
Dad, I am really sorry to be cut.
Yes to.
Go to go.
Come here when you are done.
No, I don’t want to go.
Why is it.
I have a tea, so come.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, I don’t want to go any longer, this.
No, come to me.
No, what to do.
No, I don’t want to go.
Why not, come here.
Yes, I go
I go to
Have gone?
Nothing is anything.
Yes, are you going?
Yes
Yes is
So you will take it?
Yes
I go to the director.
I say coming from now.
Oh well
A little
Yes is
You will come.
Oh a little.
Yes, later later
I go to the director.
When I feel good, I will enter.
Going to Casablanca?
I will not go.
Go to
You cannot go.
Funny at that moment.
Siro is moving fast.
I went out.
You have gone out.
Sorry, but I put my clothes on.
OK is OK.
I know you have a breast.
Is it okay?
I will leave it here properly.
I didn’t know much about anything.
It was Riga.
It is so terrible that Kobe is still falling.
pleased
Sorry to sorry.
Feeled...
Feels good?
Feel good
Feel good  Feel good
Oh no more.
go to
Oh yeah
No problem.
Because I will be scared.
No longer good out.
Probably
Maybe is okay.
Yes
It feels good here.
Oh yeah
hurt is hurt.
hurtly
It will suffer.
It is OK.
Tomorrow it will dry.
Maybe dry.
It will dry.
Sex is
I want to switch.
It becomes pin.
Give it in.
Feel good
Oh yeah
This is
It looks like a self-photography.
Oh yeah
Oh oh oh
Lying
Enter here.
Feel good
Oh oh oh
Lying
Oh is
Feel good
Oh yeah
Stop this.
not stop.
feet and feet.
Oh, it hurts so much.
I see you come in.
Feelings and feelings.
Feeled
It feels good.
Oh awesome.
greatly
Feel good
It feels good.
Oh awesome.
Feel good
Oh, so good feeling.
Oh yeah
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Oh well well
by
Oh yeah
No to
by
Liked
Oh yeah
here here
Very good feeling.
Yes is
Oh oh oh
Oh, oh
The whole body reaction increased.
It feels good!
Oh well
Oh well...
yet another time.
Do it
here
You can do it here.
Okay is?
Oh my asshole.
by
Is it okay?
Sorry sorry sorry
I want more.
Yes, I want more.
Can you still?
can
No more go.
No, if you are so round.
It became very dark.
Great, great
Yes
I like this.
Interestingly
I told you.
Yes
Put it in.
Great
Oh is
Oh yeah
Oh oh oh
Very hardy.
Feel good
Oh well
Tagged as:
I will clean it.
No to
Also next week.
You’re coming home again, right?
Not for a day.
All the time.
The boyfriend
Yes