It was a bad time
It was a company meeting yesterday.
It's already morning.
What is this?
Why am I naked?
Who is this?
What is this?
Good morning.
The weather is good today.
It's sunny and warm.
I'm sweating.
What is this?
I can see you well.
I'm embarrassed.
What's wrong?
Come here.
You were amazing yesterday.
You are aggressive.
Why are you naked?
Are you awake?
Who are you?
Don't you remember me?
I helped you yesterday.
Why do you forget me?
Please remember me.
What is this?
I can't do it anymore.
I drank too much.
You are lying down.
Who are you?
Brother.
Are you okay?
I can't wake you up.
Brother.
Wake up.
Is this your room?
It's heavy.
Wake up.
Let's go.
I can't get up.
I remember you.
Do you remember me?
You are late.
Why are you still here?
I don't remember you.
You did a lot of things yesterday.
Listen to me.
Did I do a lot of things?
Yes.
What did I do?
You did a lot of things.
What are you talking about?
Listen to me.
You did a lot of things yesterday.
Did I?
You forgot everything.
You are sad.
Wake up.
I can't get up.
It's a good room.
Can I stay here?
Thank you.
I don't go home.
I don't go to school.
It's a butt.
It's a beautiful butt.
What are you doing?
It's gross.
You are drunk.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
Do you hate it?
It's gross.
What are you doing?
You are drunk.
Stop it.
It's a butt.
It's gross.
Did I do it?
Did you remember it?
I see.
It's not good.
I thought I helped you.
But you attacked me suddenly.
I was surprised.
Did I attack you?
It's not good.
I felt good.
I'm going to live here from today.
Why?
Don't you remember anything?
We made a promise yesterday.
Did we make a promise?
We didn't make a promise.
You made me cry.
Can I live here?
Can I live here forever?
I did it.
I'm going to live here from today.
Do you have a house or a school?
It's okay.
I'm in trouble.
Why?
It's okay.
I'm sad.
Please forgive me.
I can't tell you because I'm at home.
I have to live here.
I'm in trouble.
It's okay.
What should I do?
I'm worried about you.
It's okay.
It's not okay.
You can't think like that.
It's okay.
It's not okay.
I'm worried about you.
I'll pay for it.
It's not okay.
It's okay.
Come here.
You should go home.
I don't want to go home.
You can't go home.
I don't have a house to go home.
You have a house.
It's not okay.
Why?
You don't have a girlfriend.
I knew it.
It's not okay.
You did the same thing yesterday.
You should lick me, too.
You can't do that.
Your hands...
You should go home.
Calm down.
It's not okay.
I won't forgive you.
Eat this.
It's not okay.
Calm down.
It's still hard.
Do you want to put it in your mouth?
It's okay.
I didn't put it in my mouth.
What are you talking about?
I didn't put it in my mouth yesterday.
It's not okay.
Wait a minute.
Eat this.
It's not okay.
Are you okay?
Do you want to go home?
I don't want to go home.
It's not okay.
I didn't put it in my mouth yesterday.
It's okay.
It's not okay.
Why don't you do it like yesterday?
Do it like yesterday.
It's not okay.
I have to go to work.
I'm going to be late.
You're wearing the same clothes as yesterday.
You're wearing the same underwear as yesterday.
You don't have to lock the door.
Do you understand?
See you later.
It's just a normal fire этiutie, it isn't a dangerous situation.
You forgot your cell phone, are you hungry?
Does it fit the company address?
I thought, you ditched it to kill time?
26 minutes before the accident
A few days later
Thank you for your hard work.
Is this for next week?
No, it's for next week.
This is difficult.
I'm going to have a meeting.
I'm counting on you.
Kobayashi-san, you have to pay the bill.
Good-bye.
Kobayashi-san, didn't you go home yesterday?
Kobayashi-san, you did a great job yesterday.
How did you go home? By taxi?
I don't remember.
You should work the next day.
I'm really sleepy today.
I don't want to do it at all.
I'm going to check my cell phone.
I don't want to take a video and show it to you.
I heard that your cell phone was stolen.
Is that so?
I'm going to the convenience store.
I'm going to buy a coffee.
Is that okay?
Yes, it's okay.
Kobayashi-san, are you okay?
I forgot my cell phone.
Your cell phone?
Don't you go home to get it?
That's right.
It's a hassle.
Kobayashi-san, you have a visitor.
Come here.
Brother.
I heard that you brought my cell phone.
That's right.
I brought this.
Thank you very much.
You don't work at all.
I want to ask you this.
What is this?
Why did you come to my company?
I didn't lock my cell phone.
Is this your address?
That's right.
Thank you very much.
Why?
You came to deliver my cell phone, didn't you?
Can I show you yesterday's video?
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
You should go home.
You're working.
You're a good boss.
Thank you very much.
You look a little brighter.
Please take your time.
Thank you very much.
You don't work in the morning anyway.
Is that so?
You're a good boss.
You're a good sister.
I want you.
I can't make a sister.
What should I do?
I want you.
I want you to have a younger sister.
You can rent a cell phone.
That's a good idea.
Would you like some juice?
I'm just looking at your work.
I want you.
You two are saying,
You two are saying.
That's fine.
No, I'm working.
I'm working.
No, it's fine.
What are you doing?
Come here.
Wait a minute.
No, no, no.
You're not looking.
I'm looking.
I'm going to be caught.
Oh.
Wait a minute.
Stop it.
It's okay.
It's not okay.
Wait a minute.
I'm not looking.
Is it like this?
I'm sorry.
It's a mess down there.
The garbage is falling.
I'll clean it up for you.
It's okay.
I'm not going.
What is it?
Let's not do that.
Wait a minute.
No, no, no.
I'm going to be caught.
It's okay.
No, no, no.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
That's right.
Can't you make a reservation on the weekend?
Is that so?
You can make a reservation early.
I see.
That's right.
I can't make a reservation.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
It's fun.
You can get a lot of it.
Do you want to have a sister or a sister-in-law?
I want to have a sister.
Sister?
If you want to have a sister, you can have a sister.
I don't mind having a sister.
I want to have a sister.
Do you want to have three siblings?
I want to have three siblings.
That's the best.
I don't know.
I can only have a man.
I only have a man.
I'm sad.
I admire you.
I'm getting hungry talking about this.
You were thrilled, weren't you?
I came here for a lunch.
Did you?
Kobayashi.
I'm going to have lunch.
Do you want to go with me?
Let's go.
I'll buy it as it is.
You came here before school.
That's right.
That's great.
Thank you.
I'm sad.
I only have a man.
I'm going home.
Take care.
Thank you.
I'll come to see you anytime.
I don't have time in the morning anyway.
I'll come again.
See you later.
She is cute.
I didn't have lunch with her.
A few days later.
She is like a child.
Kobayashi has a bad taste.
She is so long.
Good morning.
Welcome back.
I don't want to go to work.
Why?
You were happy.
What are you going to do?
I didn't notice.
That's not the problem.
What is this?
You have a bad taste.
You are a child.
You should go home.
My parents are noisy.
It's boring to go to school.
I'm worried about you.
I'm not.
What?
It's fun to be with me, isn't it?
I'm hungry.
What?
I haven't eaten anything.
I see.
Are you hungry?
I'm hungry.
I want to eat ramen.
I don't want to eat ramen.
You are selfish.
Let's go out to eat.
Let's go.
No.
Don't wear this.
Can't I wear this?
Don't show me.
I'll give it back to you.
Really?
I'll put this away.
What?
What is this?
It's a mess.
I don't know.
Kobayashi.
What?
Come to the bathroom.
Come on.
I see.
Kobayashi, come on.
Kobayashi.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Let's take a bath together.
What?
What are you doing?
I just got home.
Kobayashi, do you feel good?
Yes.
Kobayashi is a good name.
Why?
Yes.
Kobayashi is a good name.
Kobayashi is Kobayashi.
Shio, do you want to take a bath?
Yes.
What?
Shio-chan.
Or Shio-pi.
Shio-pi?
Shio-chan is good.
Shio-pi is good.
Shio-pi is cute.
I have never said that.
Shio-chan.
Shio-chan is good.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Really?
Yes, I'm fine. Besides, it's cold outside.
I know, but you don't have to worry.
I'm not worried. I'm fine.
Why? Do you want me to go home?
I have no choice but to go home.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Sorry...
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry..
I'm sorry.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
Be more confident.
I'm embarrassed.
And you can hurt them to a grandeur.
Simple.
You know, I was told by my mother that if you do this, the 75kg bike will beat you yourself before you can get on the bike.
It's hard, isn't it?
I'm sorry. Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hard, isn't it?
You're amazing.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah , ah, ah, ok
, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
yeah,
Are they in a good mood?
She's even stronger than I thought.
Her short legs is such a neither- SARS nor- COVID-19 virus.
He was nice to me.
I can hear him from far away.
It's still early in the morning, but he's cluding up to talk to my dad.
Good job.
You want more?
Yes
You okay?
Yes, yes.
Thank you.
So, the end of the visit toels is to leave the towels down.
I was able to found some towels.
Let go of me!!!
It winds up in a hurry.
It seems that he can't climb a wardrobe.
I'm so tired!
We're home!
Oh you're home
I was unpacking
Who are you packing?
I'm not that hungry right now, so I'm fine.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
You don't look well.
No, I'm fine.
Yeah.
You don't look well.
It's my hair. I'm fine.
Say something to me.
Yeah. Thank you.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Wait.
I'm sorry. Are you tired today?
No, I'm fine.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
I'm tired.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Do whatever you want.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
You're very sleepy.
Show me your face.
What's wrong?
Get up.
Come here.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'll give you a massage.
I'm sorry.
Do you like it?
I'll give you a massage.
Are you sleepy?
I'm sorry.
I'll give you a massage.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh
This part is the most difficult...
so I put it on the top...
and the first line is...
right there...
and you hold the pin here...
and stick it inside the hairakshi.
When you listen to the whispers,
you can't tell what's inside the ears.
I stick them into the ears because...
they hear the cloistering and fill it with dust.
And I scalp them as I speak.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
voodoo
Hmm
Blee
Mm-hmm
Oh
Ah
You can do it!
Look at me.
Keep going.
You can do it!
I love you, I love you.
I love you.
Can I kiss you?
I really love you.
I love you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
.
Hmm
Yeah yeah yeah
Yeah yeah
Jahren
No
...
What's going on?
Are you okay?
Do you want to go to the doctor?
I'm scared.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
It was fun.
I love you.
I'm sorry I'm busy.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What?
Where did you go?
You don't have any luggage.
Why don't you come out?
You did that yesterday.
I'll live here from today.
Thank you.
It's fun to be with me, isn't it?
Let's take a bath together.
I'm sorry I'm busy.
What should I do?
Did he leave?
I'm back.
Were you crying?
I wasn't crying.
Where did you go?
I went home to sleep.
Home?
Did you go home?
Yes.
I was worried about you.
I'm sorry.
Where is your house?
It's up here.
The top floor of the apartment.
This apartment?
Yes.
Tell me.
You don't live here, do you?
I see.
It's too late.
That's right.
I had a fight with my mom again when I got home.
That's why I live in this house.
That's good.
Why were you crying?
You were lonely, weren't you?
I thought you weren't here.
I was worried about you.
Stop it.
Let's stay together forever.
Let's say hello to your mom and dad someday.
Really?
Of course.
I'll think about it.
Don't be scared.
I'm not scared.