I'm not sure if it's a good thing or a bad thing, but I think it's a good thing.
. .
Handmade
What brings you here?
Isn't it good?
Would you like something to eat?
Yes, like Japanese food.
I'm sorry.
Where did the director go?
He said he had to meet with Ocean City because he couldn't explain it in a letter.
Is that so?
The director is really into this presentation.
I guess so.
It's the last job before marriage, so you want to do it, don't you?
Do you know who the director's marriage partner is?
It's like the president of a pretty good place.
Is that so?
The director didn't tell me, so I asked him when he came to our company.
If you get married, you'll quit your job.
Let's go, let's go.
What else? Japanese food?
What do you want?
I'd like a design that can show 100 years ahead based on the concept of maintaining a balanced relationship between humans and nature.
I see. Thank you very much.
You're asking Mr. Mogi to design the GT, aren't you?
Yes. I was told that it would be completed by next Monday.
What about the data in the surrounding area?
I'm sorry. I'll email it to the director right away.
What about the breast surgery we did together the other day?
I'll submit it by Friday tomorrow.
Thank you very much.
The SNS PR data is under review, isn't it?
Hey, are you listening, Sugiura?
Oh, yes.
I'm so confused. What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Oh, I'll submit the summary.
Thank you.
Oh, it's the TAS data for the past five years of Ocean Sea.
Mr. Ikeda and I are filing it now, so we'll submit it as soon as possible.
I see. Thank you very much.
Oh, I got another email from the head office.
Please turn off the lights on the other floors when you're working overtime.
Oh, again?
Yes.
Yes, it's important to cut power, but...
I see.
It might be better to put all the remaining rooms in one room.
I'm sorry.
Hey, it's rare to go home this early on Friday, so let's go for a drink.
Sounds good. Do you want to go to the store in front of the station again?
I like that store.
Hey, Sugiura, you're coming, right?
What?
Oh, yes.
Excuse me.
Is the director late again today?
I don't know.
There are quite a few cases I'm working on right now, including the present.
I see.
Do you want a drink?
Let's have a drink.
What?
I left something in the office.
Are you serious?
Please go ahead. I'll be right back.
Okay. I'll take a seat.
Come on.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Didn't you go home?
Yes. I still have some work to do.
I see.
The store in front of the station again.
Excuse me, director.
Thank you.
It looks like you're drinking in front of the station.
Sugiura, you're coming, right?
What?
I'm sorry.
I still have some work to do.
I see.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Is he your boyfriend?
Yes.
You're going to get married, right?
I'm going to.
Congratulations.
Can I do that job for you today?
You've been working late lately.
You should see your boyfriend today.
Thank you.
But that's enough.
Then,
can you help me with this?
No, it's okay.
It's okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Sugiura.
I'm running out of battery. You can go upstairs.
I'll take care of the rest.
Hello?
Yes.
Yes, I'm still at work.
What?
I know.
I'll make a decision by next week.
Yes.
Don't be so selfish.
It's no use talking about it now.
I'll make time to talk to you.
Bye.
Jasmine tea.
It's a common tea, but it'll calm you down.
Thank you.
Boss.
What?
What are you doing?
Calm down.
Sugiura, calm down.
You know you can't do that.
I don't know.
Let me go.
Calm down, Sugiura.
Hey.
Are you listening?
Calm down.
I like you.
Sugiura.
Wait.
Don't touch my clothes.
Calm down.
Hey.
What?
Stop it.
Don't do that.
I'm at work.
Hey.
Don't do that.
I'm at work.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Calm down, Sugiura.
Calm down.
I can't.
You can't.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Don't touch my clothes.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
Don't do that.
I'm getting married.
I'm sorry.
I'm getting married, Sugiura.
Are you listening?
I'm sorry.
I can't.
I can't, Sugiura.
Wait.
I can't.
Stop it.
Wait.
I can't.
Stop it.
Don't lick me.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to go home?
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
I can't.
Take it off.
Sugimura-kun.
I can't.
Stop it.
It feels good.
What are you saying?
What are you saying, Sugimura-kun?
Stop it.
This is a company.
I love you.
Stop it.
What?
What are you doing?
Stop it.
I can't.
Sugimura-kun.
Stop it.
I'm sorry, Sugimura-kun.
I can't.
Stop it.
Wait a minute.
I can't.
It feels good.
Stop it.
I can't.
Sugimura-kun.
Stop it.
I can't.
Sugimura-kun.
Stop it.
I can't.
Sugimura-kun.
Stop it.
I can't.
Sugimura-kun.
It's too cold.
I can't.
Sugimura-kun.
I really like you.
Thank you very much.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I think it's a good idea.
I'm done.
I'm done, too.
Can I have another one?
What?
Yes.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Did you turn off the light?
Yes, I did.
The head office told me to turn it off.
Well, I'm really sorry.
Have a seat.
Yes.
Are you going to quit the company?
Yes, I am.
I don't know yet.
I see.
I don't want you to quit.
Hey.
Sugiura, you're not fair.
I thought you were like a brother, but you suddenly became a man.
I don't want to be a brother.
To me, you're like a brother.
But I definitely don't want to be like a brother.
Are you going to call me again?
I'm sorry.
If it's just a little, you can kiss me.
Do you think you're a man?
You have to push me more.
I'm sorry.
Come closer.
Closer.
Give me more.
Touch my butt.
Don't you sweat?
Give me more.
Show me your front.
I can feel it just by breathing.
I feel good.
Don't you sweat?
Give me more.
I feel good.
Are you standing?
Show me your butt.
I feel good.
It's hot.
It's hot strongest than Paris Saint-Germain.
We did very weird things at work.
We did very weird things, didn't we?
Ah...
Ah!
Ha!
Meow...
Ah!
Ha!
My...
Feelings...
Ha!
It's so hot...
Ha...
So warm...
Ha!
Ah!
H...
No...
Ha!
I'm tired...
Ha...
Ha, I'm so tired...
I'm exhausted...
Toro!
I can't do this!
It's so hot.
It's so hot. Bring it to my mouth.
Do you want to go to the bathroom?
Put it in through the first door.
It can't be helped.
You can go in with this, right?
I'm going in.
It's okay.
It feels good.
You're not going to take my clothes off?
Look at my eyes and lick my boobs.
Look at my eyes.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Let me in.
Let me in again.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Come here.
You work here, don't you?
I'm so excited.
I'm so excited, too.
Sit here.
Sit where I work.
What is it?
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Do I have to do it this hard?
It's hot.
I love you, boss.
Boss.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Do you think I'm a man?
If you don't look at me like a man, I'll have sex here.
Take it off.
Is this it?
Yes.
Put this on and have sex.
Hurry up.
Let's have sex.
It's hot.
I'm happy to have sex with you in the corner of the office.
I don't care.
Give me a kiss.
Give me more.
Let's have sex.
Hurry up.
Right.
He's squeezing my arm.
It feels good, doesn't it?
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Try rubbing it like this.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're doing something great on the floor.
It feels good.
How do you feel?
It feels good, doesn't it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Amazing!
I can't do anymore!
Right.
F... Father...
So that's where we're headed.
And the month after that...
That's a lot of people.
Oh yeah, today is Saturday.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Um...
Do you think the presentation will go well?
It has to go well.
I'm sorry.
Director, I just went to the head office.
The head office gave me a letter of resignation.
Thank you.
I look forward to working with you on the case.
Leave it to me.
It's the last job I've done.
I'll do my best with the head office.
Don't worry about me.
Please continue to do your best.
Yes.
Ms. Miyata, can I ask you a question?
What is it?
The design...
The design of the JSON sheet...
This is...
Um...
The process of the process...
I see.
I think it's easier to imagine the other side.
Please wait a little longer.
I'll add this part.
This part.
I see.
Are you really going to quit?
You're asking me this now?
I'll do my best.
Do your best.
You've been looking at me like that all the time, haven't you?
Because...
That's what you're like.
Don't make that face all the time.
Do you understand?
See you.
Can you really promise me this is the last time?
There.
Sit down.
Yes.
Do you want a drink, too?
Beer?
Yes.
Don't close your eyes.
It's cold.
Are you preparing to move?
Yes.
No.
Please break up with me.
Don't say that.
Don't say that now.
It's hot.
Hold my hand.
Lick my armpit.
It's hot.
Are you doing this to a married woman?
Don't say that.
I don't like it.
It's hot.
I like you.
You're still a child.
Show me your attitude.
It's hot.
I'm happy.
I'm very happy.
It's hot.
Are you doing this to a married woman?
Don't say that.
I don't like it.
It's hot.
Show me your attitude.
It feels good.
Lick me more.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Wake up.
It hurts.
It's strange.
I'm so tired.
I can't do this.
They've gone mad!
I love you.
It's intense.
I'm better.
Don't go.
I love you so much.
Look at me.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Look at me.
It feels good.
Don't go.
I don't want to see you.
Oh, my God.
It's all right.
You like me, don't you?
If you like me, hold on.
Hold on a lot.
I love you, so I can't.
Hold on.
I'll stop if you let me out.
No.
I don't want to stop even if you let me out.
Here you are.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
I'm more sorry than that man.
I'm fine, aren't I?
Is it no good?
You've been holding out, haven't you?
You've been holding out for me, haven't you?
Look at me.
Oh, my God.
I'm telling you.
Then say it again.
One more time!
Get up.
Oh, my God.
Don't touch me.
Look at me.
Oh, my God.
One more time!
It hurts.
I can't.
You can do it.
You can do it, can't you?
I'm not sure.
I'm sleepy.
I've got a headache.
Don't look at me like that.
Look at me.
I'm sleepy.
It's hard.
It's still a little hard.
It's hard all over.
My hard part is in my stomach.
What are you talking about?
I'm sleepy.
I love you.
You're so cute.
I'm sleepy.
I love you.
My hard part is in my stomach.
I'm sleepy.
What should I do?
I'm angry at that person.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
If I do that, my manko will break.
It's not funny.
My manko will break.
I'm going to go.
I'm going to go if my manko breaks.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah
Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
It hurts so bad!
Ietekesi, Chiba
Shigera-kun, are your social media PR streams going well?
Huh?
Yes, ma'am.
Show it to me before submitting it to the new manager.
You've been looking at me lately, haven't you?
What?
You're cheating.
Cheating.
What?
You're cheating.