Despite having told me everything I needed to know,he just couldn't come clean about what happened.
I finally understood that the person he was talking about is Tal's mother.
I knew he was talking about the thieves who stole his watch
This is exactly why I asked you to go ahead with the next design at this very cost.
Okay.
I'll consider that.
Can I ask you one more thing?
I'm going to a tender hotel today.
Will you go with me?
Don't make such a scary face.
It's a hotel that my father's group bought.
I'm inviting you for a visit.
Please go with me.
I'm sorry, but I have plans today.
You're always busy, aren't you?
If it's a hotel, I can review this budget at any time.
Where's Wada?
He's going to a tender hotel.
Are you going to lower the budget?
I don't want to take this job.
It's not that easy.
He's a descendant of the Sugiura Group.
Is that so?
Why is he in that company?
My father wants me to work in a company other than his group.
The Sugiura Group has nothing to do with me.
I've known him since he started his company.
I can't turn him down.
I see.
But it's going to cost a lot of money.
That's right.
I have to think about it.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I'm going to make dinner.
What are you writing?
It's a greeting for the student council.
You're more beautiful than your mother.
My mother rarely writes.
She only designs.
Don't make fun of my mother.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
My mother has been like that lately.
Is that so?
Yes.
If the president looks like that, everyone will hate him.
If the student council president says so, it may be persuasive.
Yes.
My mother has to be smiling all the time.
It's like when my father was alive.
That again.
You have a good memory.
I've never met such a violent person.
What?
You can't do this?
Yes.
If you lower it any more, the budget will be over budget.
The budget doesn't affect the design.
Think of it as an investment.
If I go back to my father's company, I'll pay for it.
You know that much, right?
I'm sorry.
Is the president not good at it?
Or is he just an idiot?
He may be an idiot.
I'm sorry.
I've already told the company that I'm going to do it.
So please.
This is the best I can do.
The answer doesn't change.
Thank you for your help.
He wants to make it his own.
It's like he's lowering the cost of the deal.
In other words, if you go back to Sugiura Group, you'll be useful.
It's disgusting, isn't it?
You're right.
If you can negotiate with Sugiura Group, it may be delicious.
I'm sorry.
But I can't trust what he says.
It's not the president's fault.
I didn't want him to come to the company.
It's the same as the president.
Rather than that, why don't you go up early today and have dinner with Rin-chan?
That's right.
Today is the deadline.
We'll do the rest.
President.
Thank you.
But there's something I want to do.
Everyone, please go up early today.
Rin and I will go somewhere the day after tomorrow.
Is that so?
Then I'll do as you say.
Do you want to go after this?
I have a stiff shoulder today, so I want to go to a massage shop.
If you know a good shop, please let me know.
Let's go there.
Thank you.
It's a little expensive.
Is it okay? It's the last one.
It's over early.
It's a little expensive.
What can I do for you?
If you want to talk, please sit here.
Let's make this a bigger company than this small office.
I'll make it come true.
The contract is fine with me, right?
I'm sorry.
No?
Yes.
Then I'll make you my woman.
That's fine.
It's a lot of information to decide before you do it.
What are you talking about?
I'm surprised that I can't go as I want.
That's enough.
Do as I say.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
Do as I say.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
Is anyone there?
Don't shout.
Let me go.
Are you running away?
It hurts, doesn't it?
I don't want to hurt you so much.
Listen to me.
Stop it.
I heard that the president of this company is beautiful.
So I asked her to replace me.
Did you know that?
That's why I'm here.
Stop it.
Are you resisting?
I'll destroy this company.
I'll ruin the reputation of the employees.
You know I can do that.
Do you understand?
Stop it.
You don't have to resist.
I have to go as I want.
I don't want to be violent.
Stop it.
Are you tired?
Do you feel pain here?
Stop it.
Don't you understand?
I told you not to resist.
If you keep resisting, I'll hurt you more.
Do you understand?
Stop it.
You have beautiful breasts.
Let me see your breasts.
Stop it.
What?
Why are your breasts wet?
Why?
Your breasts are wet, aren't they?
Maybe you're not pregnant.
Are you pregnant?
Stop it.
You're right.
You're busy.
You always say you're busy.
You're busy, aren't you?
You've been busy at work for a long time.
Stop it.
You're right.
I'll take care of you.
Stop it.
Don't hide it.
You're busy.
Stop it.
Let me go.
What's wrong with you?
I can't feel your fingers.
Stop it.
It's been a long time since I've seen your fingers.
You're funny.
Do you feel better?
Do you?
Stop it.
It's dirty.
Can't you see it?
Can you see it?
Stop it.
Is it good?
It's good, isn't it?
You're my daughter.
Stop it.
Let me go.
No.
Stop it.
You're dirty.
Do you feel better?
Do you?
Let me see.
Do you feel better?
Why are you moving?
Stop it.
You're the best.
I didn't expect you to change so much.
Stop it.
You said it, didn't you?
You feel better because it's been a long time, don't you?
Say something.
Stop it.
What was that?
You said it again, didn't you?
Stop it.
You feel better, don't you?
Tell me the truth.
Why are you holding your breath?
You wanted to scream so much.
Stop it.
Did you say stop it?
Are you happy?
You're reacting well.
Stop it.
What?
You feel good, don't you?
Don't think about weird things.
You know where I'm from, don't you?
You know, don't you?
Stop it.
Tokyo, Tokyo...
What are you doing?
Let's go here.
What?
Tokyo, Tokyo...
Wait a minute.
I feel sick.
Let's go to the hotel.
It's too late.
I don't want to go to the hotel.
Excuse me.
I'm hungry.
Hurry up and eat.
Who are you?
Mama?
I see.
I've heard that you have a single mother.
You don't look like her at all.
Don't come near me.
But...
I'm trying to make a phone call to you.
I'm trying to make a phone call to the police.
Mama and I love each other.
I can't forgive anyone who gets in my way.
Mama wouldn't like someone like you.
Is that so?
We had sex earlier.
Mama, really?
Don't say anything weird in front of my daughter.
Mama.
Be quiet.
Do you want me to do it again?
What are you talking about?
I want to do it again.
Besides, it's erotic to do something erotic in front of my daughter.
Or...
Do you want me to do it again in front of your daughter?
You can't move, can you?
Look closely.
Don't look at me.
What are you looking at?
Stop it.
Look at me.
What you're doing is a crime. Do you know that?
Crime?
Of course I know that.
This is a real crime.
You've learned a lot.
Look closely.
In the world, there are people who can get away with doing this.
Did you know that?
You don't know, do you?
Children don't know the inconveniences of adults.
It's a social learning.
This is not a social learning.
I see.
Stop it.
I won't.
Look at me.
I'm embarrassed.
Please move to the next room.
I don't want to.
I'm excited to do this in front of my daughter.
I don't want to do this.
I don't want to do this. Stop it.
Stop it.
I don't want to do this.
I'm excited to do this in front of my daughter.
Stop it.
Look at me.
I don't want to do this.
Stop it.
I'll do it.
Please.
You're desperate.
Do you want to help her so much?
Please.
Please listen to me.
Come here.
I'll show you in front of you.
I don't want to do this.
You don't have to do this.
Stop it.
This is fun.
I'm fine.
I feel sorry for your daughter.
This is a big shock.
This will definitely affect her in the future.
Stop it.
Let me go.
Don't get in my way.
Look at me.
Stop it.
Don't look at me.
Please don't look at me.
Stop it.
Why are you trying to run away?
Let me go.
She's trying to run away.
She abandoned you and tried to run away.
She's a traitor.
She's trying to run away.
Let me go.
If you run away, what will happen to your mother?
I'm fine.
Listen to me.
Look at me.
Let me go.
You'll learn.
You're the daughter of the president.
Let go of my hand.
I'm fine.
Look at me.
Listen to me.
You'll learn.
Look at me.
Do you see this?
If you run away,
you'll be in more pain than this.
Stop it.
Don't do that to my mother.
I'm fine.
Let me go.
Did you know?
My mother wears such erotic underwear.
Stop it.
Do you want to smell it?
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Don't do that to Rin.
I'll show you more.
Stop it.
I've never seen you so well-dressed.
I'll show you.
Stop it.
I'm so excited.
Do you feel better?
Stop it.
In this situation?
You're a pervert.
Stop it.
I won't do that to you.
I'll show you more.
Stop it.
Because of a man like you...
Because of a man like me?
I see.
Your father was such a terrible man.
That's why you hate men.
Am I wrong?
I see.
I'll make you hate me more.
Stop it.
Look at me.
Do you know what this sound is?
I don't know.
I'll show you more.
Look at me.
Stop it.
Do you know what this sound is?
When a woman is excited, her body gets wet.
Stop it.
Your mother is so excited.
No.
Look at me.
Stop it.
Don't do that to me.
You'll feel better.
Stop it.
Mom.
She must have left.
No.
Stay there.
Please.
Do you want to see more?
Stop it.
Look at her.
She's doing her best.
Don't do that to me.
You want to be happy, don't you?
You have to be happy.
Mom.
She's doing her best.
I'm fine.
Do you want to do it?
Stop it.
I'll do it.
You'll feel better.
I can't do it.
Mom.
You have to do it.
I'll do it.
Stop it.
I'll do something funny.
You're amazing.
You're like a baby.
Show me your face.
Stop it.
You're funny.
I'll do it.
Stop it.
You're like a baby.
Look at her.
She's crying.
She's crying because she's happy.
You're happy to do this in front of your daughter.
Stop it.
You're excited about this.
You hit your daughter's head.
The employees can't imagine this.
Stop it.
You're good.
I'll show you.
Stop it.
Don't hide it.
Look at your daughter.
She's reacting to you.
She's never cried like this before.
Why are you frowning?
Stop it.
Look at her.
I'll put you on my lap.
Look at your mother.
Stop it.
You're crying in front of your daughter.
I'll show you more.
Stop it.
Did you say you were going?
No.
Stop it.
You said it.
Aren't you ashamed to say that in front of your daughter?
Are you a parent?
Is there a parent who says that in front of their daughter?
I'll show you again.
Stop it.
I'll show you a lot.
Look at your mother.
Close your eyes.
Don't look at me.
I'll hit you if you close your eyes.
Stop it.
I'll show you a lot.
I'll hit you if you close your eyes.
Are you okay?
Stop it.
It's fun, isn't it?
You've never done this before, have you?
Stop it.
I'll show you more.
Come here.
Stop it.
Look at me.
Can you see me?
Stop it.
Your daughter is looking at you.
What should I do?
I'll do it.
I'll go to your daughter.
Please.
I'll do it.
Don't say that.
You should feel better in front of your daughter.
Listen to me.
You want to do it, don't you?
You want to feel better, don't you?
You've been doing it for a long time.
Don't you?
I'll do it to your daughter.
No.
Please.
Let me do it.
I'll do it.
Please.
Shut up.
Stop it.
I told you I'd do it.
Look at me.
Don't do that.
Listen to me.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it.
Please.
You should listen to your daughter.
Listen to me.
Please.
I told you.
Listen to me.
I'll say it again.
There are people in the world who are allowed to do this.
Do you understand?
Did you learn it?
I'll learn it.
You should learn it.
You'll know it someday.
Please.
I'm sorry.
You're crying.
I want to love you more.
Give me a kiss.
You're so sweet.
I'll do it.
Please don't.
Mom.
You should have done it from the beginning.
You don't have to do that.
You just did it.
No.
You really want it, don't you?
You don't want it.
No.
You want it, don't you?
Don't look at me.
Give me a kiss.
How many times do you have to do it?
You're crying again.
You're amazing.
You're funny.
Don't look at me.
Look at me.
You want to suck my boobs, don't you?
Don't look at me.
You're strong.
You sucked my boobs when you were little.
You should try it.
Don't look at me.
You said you wanted to suck my boobs when you were little.
It's like you're sucking your daughter's boobs.
Don't look at me.
Mr. President.
How will your daughter grow up if she experiences this?
She'll become a pervert.
Don't look at me.
You're a pervert.
Your daughter is looking at you.
She's interested.
Don't look at me.
Is she a virgin?
Don't you know?
I'll do it.
Have you ever done it?
No.
You haven't done it.
That's interesting.
You should study a lot.
This is how you have sex.
You were very shy.
You didn't say anything.
Say something.
Have you given up?
Don't do that to me.
It doesn't matter if your mother gets sick.
Don't do that.
You make your mother feel good.
You can't help it.
Don't do that.
Don't touch me.
You make your mother feel good.
Don't do that.
She's gone again.
Come here.
You make your mother feel good.
Look at me.
Don't do that.
Do you understand?
You and I love each other.
No, we don't.
I can't love you.
You're right.
We love each other.
I can't love you.
Don't do that.
I'm ashamed of you.
Don't do that in front of your daughter.
Let me go with you.
I told you many times.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
But
She seems to be a little faster than before…
We consider taking her to Jeff because she keeps her steps in a hurry and she may run away.
Wow, now you're done.
You said you were hungry, didn't you?
Let's eat something.
You said you were hungry, so let's make you something.
Try eating like a dog.
You're the worst person I've ever met.
I see.
I have a dog, too.
This is a crime.
I'm sorry.
He was talking to me.
What's that look?
I see.
Go to the police and ask them to lend you a fork, Sugiura-sama.
Say it.
I don't want to.
You're hungry, aren't you, kid?
A person like you should be arrested and sent to prison.
Hey! Stop it!
Don't get carried away, kid.
Don't lay a hand on Ushien!
Cut it out!
Then I'll make him apologize.
Or I'll make him talk to my ex-wife.
What are you talking about?
It's not a big deal. He just made a mistake in sex.
Or...
I'll kill him.
Stop it!
Let me go!
I understand.
Then...
Let's show them how much we love each other.
Yes.
Mom...
I don't want to.
Don't look away. Look at me.
Give me a kiss.
Come on.
Hurry up.
He'll listen to you.
Give me a kiss.
Look at me.
Come on.
Okay.
Give me a kiss.
Look at me.
You're so sweet.
I'll do it.
Do it from the beginning.
What's wrong with you?
Wait!
Stop it, please.
Don't be lazy.
Stop it! Let me go!
Stop it.
Is it good?
Yes.
It's good, isn't it?
Say, it's good.
It's good.
It's good, isn't it?
I'll put my hand on your tongue.
Give me a kiss.
You're slacking off again.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it.
I told you to do it from the beginning.
Do you understand?
Don't be lazy.
Give me a kiss.
You're so good at it.
Look at you.
You've grown up.
Stop it!
What are you going to do?
Give me a kiss.
I want to see your neck.
I want to see it.
Look at me.
Don't be lazy.
Why do you hate it so much?
Stop it!
Please.
It's in your daughter's mouth.
You hate it so much.
You're licking it because it's delicious.
You don't answer.
Stop it!
I'll lick it.
Is that all?
There's a difference, isn't there?
Are you looking at me?
You know a lot about me.
I don't know much about you, but you're good at it.
I don't know.
You don't know.
Do you want to lick here?
Yes.
Do you know where I'm licking?
It's a hole in your butt.
Stop it!
Don't say that to my daughter.
Your mother is licking here.
Stop it!
What do you think?
It's dangerous as a parent.
I won't let you do that.
What do you think?
Have you ever been bitten?
Stop it!
What are you doing?
Keep licking it.
Stop it!
I'll lick it.
Let me go.
It feels good.
You're good at it.
Stop it!
I'll lick you.
Is this the first time you've been bitten?
What do you think?
Did you ask your father to feed you?
It's the same, isn't it?
Let me go.
Stop it!
I'm tired.
I'll lick you.
Stop it.
Let me go.
I'll lick you.
You're licking Rin-chan.
I won't lick you.
I'll lick you.
Is it good?
It's good.
You like Rin-chan, don't you?
You like her, don't you?
You want her to eat pasta, don't you?
Then make her feel good.
It's sweet.
You want her to eat this, don't you?
You're hiding again.
You're so erotic.
You're making a disgusting sound.
You're so good.
If you want her to eat, do it faster.
It's hard.
What?
Stop it.
Don't make her eat that.
You're hungry, aren't you?
Stop it.
I'm sorry for you.
Why are you throwing up?
Is it bad?
It's not bad, is it?
It's good, isn't it?
It's good.
Then why did you throw up?
I'm sorry.
Apologize.
Apologize for your daughter.
I'm sorry.
This is what happens when you go against me.
I'll stay here until you become my woman.
I'm sorry.
Tell her to become your woman.
Is it painful?
Tell me if it's painful.
You should have told me that from the beginning.
You should have told me the amount of the contract.
You should have told me that.
Yes.
That's good.
Talk to me.
You're my woman.
I'm sorry.
You're noisy.
Let me use the bathroom.
I want you to be my flesh and blood.
Hey.
What are you talking about?
Say that you'll be my flesh and blood.
Come on, say it.
I'll be your flesh and blood.
I can't hear you.
Then say it.
This atmosphere is great.
Hey, flesh and blood.
If you let me go, I'll let him go to the bathroom.
Do it properly.
You're my flesh and blood.
You want me to go to the bathroom, don't you?
You're my flesh and blood, so do it properly.
You're so sweet.
Please don't.
Let me do it.
Why?
Because I'll do it.
Then why didn't you do it properly from the beginning?
I'm sorry.
Please let me do it.
You know this is going to happen, right?
Yes.
You want to do it, right?
I want to do it.
Let's do it again.
If you don't do it properly, I'll kick your ass.
Please don't.
I'll do it.
Do you like me?
I like you.
You have to like me a lot.
Please don't.
Please lick my boobs.
Please.
If you want me to lick your boobs, I'll do it.
You have a bad feeling about this.
I'll do it.
I'll do it properly.
You have a good reaction.
Please.
Please lick my boobs.
Please move your hand.
Please.
I'm not motivated yet.
You're so sweet.
You're slacking off.
No, I'm not.
Please.
Please don't.
Get away from me.
Please.
Kiss me.
I want to kiss you.
Please.
You're so mean.
Please don't.
Show me you're motivated.
Please.
Or I'll touch you.
Let me do it.
Please touch me.
I'll do it.
Please.
You're so lazy.
Do you like me?
Yes, I love you.
I love you.
You're still not motivated.
Why are you so warm?
Please touch me.
I'm warm, too.
I'm warmer.
You're a pervert.
Yes, I am.
I'm a pervert.
Please love me more.
I'll throw you away.
Please don't.
Please love me more.
I'm sorry.
Can I touch you?
Please.
Open your mouth.
Touch me.
Don't touch her.
Please.
Touch me.
Open your mouth.
Please.
Touch me.
Let me touch you.
Please.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to touch you.
I'm sorry.
I want you to touch me.
Please touch me.
I'm sorry.
My pussy is messed up.
Please touch me.
Please.
My pussy is messed up.
Your pussy is messed up.
Please touch my pussy.
My pussy is messed up.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Your pussy is messed up.
Please.
Please lick me more.
You are amazing.
You want to feel better, don't you?
I want to feel better.
Let me touch you.
I'm sorry.
Let me explain what I'm doing to you.
I'll tell you.
I'm putting my finger in your pussy.
What's going on?
You feel better, don't you?
I'll tell you.
I'm putting my finger in your pussy.
Where is your pussy?
I don't know where your pussy is.
I put my finger in your pussy.
Your pussy is dirty.
I'm sorry.
Let me clean your pussy.
Please don't. I'll clean it up.
Let's lick this side.
Please don't.
It's dirty, so clean it up.
Rin, how does it taste?
Please don't.
I'll clean it up.
If you lick it, please lick me too.
Please lick me.
I want you to lick me.
I'll put my finger in your throat.
Please put it in me.
It's very hard.
Please don't.
Please put it in me.
Rin, you're definitely a virgin.
What should I do?
Please put it in my throat.
Please.
How hard can you do?
I'll do my best.
Please put it in my throat.
If you make a noise, I'll think about it.
Please listen to me a lot.
Please.
Please put it in me.
I'll put it in your throat.
I'll stop putting it in your throat.
Please put it in me.
I think it's better to put it in your throat.
I hope you have a hole in your butt.
Please don't.
You have a hole in your butt.
Please stop.
I've never put it in my throat.
You have a good experience.
I'll do it.
Please.
I'll put it in your throat again.
Please stop.
Don't do that to me.
Please.
Please look at me.
Please put it in me.
Please.
Please stop.
I'll do it.
Please.
Please stop.
You can put it in me.
Please.
Please put it in me.
Kiss me.
If you don't kiss me hard, I'll break.
Please.
I'll put it in your mouth.
Please stop.
You have a good experience.
You can't raise an adult.
Please put it in me.
Please.
You'll break.
I'm sorry.
Please stop.
Please forgive me.
Say you love me.
I love you.
Who do you love?
You.
I love you.
Please.
Please put it in me.
I love you.
What do you want me to do?
Please put my finger in your pussy.
I don't like fingers.
Anything is fine.
Please put my penis in your pussy.
It's a penis.
Please put it in me.
I'll open it again.
Don't lie down.
Please put it in me.
Do you want it?
Yes, I want it.
Do your best.
Yes.
Please put it in me.
Do your best.
Yes.
Please put it in me.
Do your best.
You finally put it in me.
Yes, I'm happy.
I'm fine.
Thank you very much.
You were teased a lot.
You feel it, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Show me your face.
Please explain to her.
What's in your pussy?
I have a penis in my pussy.
Yes, you do.
Please explain to her.
I don't want you to say that.
I'm sorry.
You can't stand it, can you?
No, I can't.
You have a penis in your pussy.
Yes, I do.
I can't stand it because I have a penis in my pussy.
It feels good.
You don't have to feel good.
I'm sorry.
I have a penis in my pussy.
Do you?
Yes, I do.
If you don't, I'll kill you.
I'll do it.
Please.
You're too naive.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it.
Rin-chan.
You want to see something, don't you?
No.
Let me see.
I'll do it.
You're too naive.
I'm sorry.
Come here.
I'll do it.
If you don't do it, I'll kill you.
Don't do it.
I'll do it.
Let me kiss your lips.
I'll do it later.
I love you.
Let me kiss your lips.
I'll do it.
Don't do it.
I'll comfort you.
I'll do it.
Don't do it.
You're worse than me.
I'm sorry.
Let me go.
I'll sleep a little longer.
I'm sorry.
I'm getting tired of this.
You too.
Look in the mirror.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it.
Let me do it.
I'm begging you, please don't do it.
Are you ready?
I'll ask you to follow me like a dog in front of my daughter.
Okay.
Please follow me like a dog in front of my daughter.
I can't hear you. Say it again.
I can't hear you.
Please follow me like a dog in front of my daughter.
Please stop it.
Not yet.
I don't want to stop.
You know what I mean, right?
You feel good, right?
Yes, I do.
Yes, you do.
It's getting worse.
I can't stop it.
Sit here.
I'm sorry.
I can't stop it.
It's getting worse.
You put it in yourself, didn't you?
I can't stop it.
Don't go.
If you go now, I'll beat you up.
Please let me go to the bathroom.
You go to the bathroom.
Yes.
Rin-chan, take a good look at your mother.
I beg you.
I can't stop it.
Does it feel so good?
Rin-chan, come here.
Rin-chan, you've become obedient.
I can't stop it.
Say what you said earlier.
What I said earlier?
Please beat me hard like a dog.
I'll do it.
Say it again.
Please beat me hard like a dog.
I can't stop it.
It feels so good.
Sit here.
There.
Your face is close now.
I can't stop it.
Who decided to stop it?
I'm sorry.
Don't decide on your own.
You underestimated me, didn't you?
If you act like a father, I'll kill you.
Do you understand?
I'm sorry.
I can't hear you.
You should apologize to your daughter.
I'm sorry.
Say it again.
Nagasaki.
Your daughter is sad.
I'm shocked.
I didn't know your mother was such a person.
But you should have acted like a father from the beginning.
You should have acted like a father from the beginning.
I'm sorry.
You should have listened to me.
You shouldn't have underestimated me and my father.
I'll wipe it all off.
She's about to cry.
Ask her to come out.
I can't say that.
Your daughter is going to pee.
You can't say that.
You want her to come out, don't you?
Ask her to come out.
What did you say?
You don't have to say that.
Ask her to come out.
I can't hear you.
You can say it louder.
Ask her to come out.
Please.
Dad.
I know.
I'll talk to my father later.
Bye.
I'll tell you this.
You know that I'm the head of the prefectural police now, right?
You know that, right?
President.
If you don't do as I say next time,
I'll give you a daughter.
Bye.
Dad.