I was a teacher until a year ago.
Now I'm married to my husband, who was my colleague,
and we live in the same house.
I'm a teacher.
I'm married to my husband, and we live in the same house.
Hello?
It's been a while.
What's wrong?
What?
Where is the hospital?
Are you okay?
Yes.
A group of bad guys barged into our street.
I was looking around.
Then a motorcycle came from behind.
Who was it?
He ran away.
I didn't see his face on the internet, but he was wearing our uniform.
I guess he was after me.
Because I was hated by the student council.
What did the police say?
The higher-ups stopped us.
They said that if we made a big deal out of it,
the school's reputation would go down and the tuition would be reduced.
They said it would be bad for serious students to become free.
Well, I guess that's what they really want.
I can't work for a while.
I'm sorry, but can you take me to school?
The culprit collapsed on the cover he hit me with.
He's probably injured.
Let me wear it.
I can't wear it for the rest of my life.
Please take a seat.
Please be quiet.
Quiet!
Take a seat.
I'm Fuyuka Maezawa, and I'll be in charge of this class from today.
You're Mr. Maezawa's wife, aren't you?
Mr. Maezawa, you were hit by a motorcycle, weren't you?
Did you die?
What do you mean, did I die?
Your life is not in danger.
What are you talking about?
You're boring.
Quiet! I'll take a blood test.
Abe.
Kato.
Sato.
Suzuki.
Yes.
If you know who the culprit is, don't hit him.
Hashimoto.
Maeda.
Yuki.
Yes.
Thank you.
No problem.
I'm a class rep.
You're trusted.
No one wants to do it.
But I think it's good because it's advantageous to the recommendation.
Are you aiming for a recommendation?
I'm not interested.
But it would be interesting if a student like me was chosen.
See you.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
Suzuki in the same class was injured.
Do you know why?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask him?
Let's start the lesson.
Please open the textbook.
I'm sorry.
Everyone has a good heart.
For example, when you see a child who is about to fall into a well,
you should want to help him.
It's not because you want to be praised.
It's because you have a moral heart while you're born.
By learning and making an effort,
we can extend this moral heart.
Then you can be a wonderful person no matter who you are.
This is called a wisdom legend.
You can't blame others.
But you can't lie.
Please be quiet.
Suzuki.
Stop it.
Are you punishing me?
Look at me.
I'm injured.
What are you doing?
If you want to hit me, here.
It hurts.
I'll do it myself today.
I'm injured.
When and where did you get injured?
It doesn't matter.
You attacked Mr. Maezawa, didn't you?
No.
Then where did you get injured?
Let the police investigate it.
Don't do that.
Then be honest.
You attacked Mr. Maezawa, didn't you?
No.
I did it to Yuuki.
Yuuki?
He had a fight with his students after school.
Next is Suzuki.
Let's go.
You're losing.
Let's talk about it.
I want to see Suzuki's secret.
He has a secret that no one wants to know.
He threatens everyone with his weakness.
At first, he gets close with a smile.
Then he becomes friendly.
It's a strategy to look normal.
He makes a fuss during class.
It's Yuuki's order.
He may have wanted to offend Mr. Maezawa.
I don't care about Mr. Maezawa's injury.
I see.
Don't tell Yuuki what I told you.
I can't live in this school.
What are you doing?
You're in class.
Go back to your classroom.
Yes.
You're not looking for the culprit, are you?
I was just being careful with the students.
Really?
Yes.
It's hard to get a new job.
You should follow the school's policy.
Go.
What are you doing?
Wait.
I didn't do it.
I was just watching.
You made him do it.
I heard you threatened him.
Who?
Suzuki?
It doesn't matter.
What if he goes against me?
I can't understand.
This is Suzuki's secret.
You can't live if you share your personal information.
Sato's secret is...
Stop it.
It's terrible to threaten people with this.
It's bad to have a secret that you can't tell anyone.
The teacher is serious.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Thank you
It's okay. Calm down.
I'm sorry.
Calm down.
I'm the one who's not calm.
Sit down.
Why are you so scared?
Why are you doing this to me?
I told you.
I'll make you a secret that you can't tell anyone.
I don't need a secret.
I want to make you a secret.
I didn't know you were doing that.
Stop it.
I didn't know you were doing this.
It's not a good thing to do.
Don't do this.
I know you're doing this.
Stop it.
Be quiet.
Did you have a hard time?
Do you like to be tickled?
You don't like it.
Stop it.
I'll forgive you now.
You're kind.
I'll forgive you.
Stop it.
Aren't you dirty?
I'm not dirty.
Calm down.
Sit down.
Does it hurt?
Are you calm now?
Are you cold?
Do you want me to touch you?
Are you calm now?
Open your mouth.
Speak.
I'm going to kill you.
Don't run away.
Stop it.
Come here.
What's wrong with you?
Don't do that.
Don't you understand what I'm saying?
Stop it.
What?
Why?
I'm sorry.
You look like you're in a bad mood.
Did you say that?
Stop it.
You're drooling.
What's wrong with you?
You look like you're in a bad mood.
Stop it.
Listen to me.
I'm sorry.
You're so beautiful.
What are you doing?
Are you cleaning yourself?
Can't you take a shower?
You're so beautiful.
If you drool, I'll kill you.
Stop it.
Doctor.
How do you feel?
Now you have a secret.
You'll listen to me, won't you?
Don't do that.
You won't listen to me?
Stop it.
Get off me.
Doctor, I'll listen to you.
I'll listen to you.
Let go of me.
Stop it.
Go away.
Calm down.
Doctor, I'll listen to you.
Stop it.
Calm down.
Doctor, how do you feel?
How do you feel?
Stop it.
Here?
It's easy to understand how you feel.
Stop it.
Doctor, he's gone.
He's gone.
Are you kidding me?
He's definitely gone.
I see.
Calm down.
Stop it.
You like this, don't you?
Look.
You look like a doctor.
It's easy to understand.
How do you feel?
Calm down.
Doctor, how do you feel?
You look better.
Calm down.
Doctor.
How do you feel?
What?
What's wrong?
What did you say?
Calm down.
Doctor.
You should calm down.
Don't panic.
You're a doctor.
Calm down.
Look.
Stop it.
Calm down.
You like this, don't you?
You look like a doctor.
Stop it.
Do you want to fight?
Don't run away.
Do you understand?
I don't want to fight.
Don't run away.
Do you understand?
Doctor.
Calm down.
I know what I'm doing.
I know.
Shut up.
Stop it.
Do you want to fight?
I feel good.
Do you understand?
Stop it.
You're a doctor.
Doctor.
If you're against me,
I'll put this on the bed.
Now,
you can keep your secret.
I won't do it again.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
tensor
Human nature is evil
and vice is false
This evil is not bad, it is a weak existence.
Lies are for the sake of people.
Humans are weak creatures, so I'm sorry.
This evil is not bad, it is a weak existence.
Take someone with you.
Please take the teacher.
Stop it.
I don't care if it's a class.
I'll keep quiet about yesterday, so you're aiming for a recommendation, right?
I don't want to go to college.
If someone like me is chosen as a recommendation, I'm sorry for those who have worked hard.
That's all.
That's strange.
If you do your best to teach, the teacher's secret will remain on the Internet for the rest of your life.
If your husband sees it, he will be shocked and die.
If you explain it, he will understand.
The teacher's child.
You married and quit school to make a child, right?
What do you think if you see the teacher's child?
I want you to feel good.
I can't.
I can't do that.
Then I'll spread it on the Internet.
Stop it.
Then take it off.
Think about it again.
Take it off.
Then take it off.
What if someone comes?
That's right.
Maybe the teacher seduced me.
Let's shake hands.
It's like a strip club.
If you quit now, I'll be quiet.
Where are you going?
Stop it.
It's annoying, so let's go.
Do you think it's okay to do this?
I'm sorry.
It's like a teacher's chest.
I can't do that.
Hurry up.
There's no point in that.
Stop it.
Do it again.
It's like this.
It's like a teacher's chest.
I'm sorry.
Don't move.
I'm not stupid.
You know I'm not stupid.
Let go of my hand.
Are you okay?
Are you really okay?
That's right.
You're a good boy.
Does it feel that good?
You're feeling good, aren't you?
Next, take this off.
Take this off.
What's this?
You're wearing something like this.
You can feel this, too.
Look this way.
Then, teacher.
Do you want me to feel good?
Stop it.
What if someone comes?
What if I'm the only one who wears clothes?
I think we should take care of each other.
It's like a teacher seducing a student.
I'm going to die.
I'm okay, so don't do it.
Teacher.
Do you want me to feel good?
Put on your clothes.
Come here.
Come on.
I'm going to die.
Look at me.
Come on.
Do you want me to feel good?
That's right.
It feels good.
It feels good just to touch your nipples lightly like this.
You're cute, teacher.
Stop it.
Do your best.
It feels good.
Look at me.
That's right.
Do you want me to feel good?
Touch me.
Stop it.
I've done it so far, but can I upload the video?
Isn't it a waste?
I can still dance now.
Let me touch you.
It feels good.
Let's do it together.
Look up.
You can do it, right?
It feels good.
One more time.
You're good.
You're doing what you usually do.
Don't be angry.
Look up.
You're drooling.
Why are you doing this?
Because it feels good.
That's not what I mean.
I'm angry.
It's good to be relaxed.
If you do this for a long time, someone will come.
It's better to let it out.
Let's do this for the last time.
Your face is scary.
If you do that, you won't appear in the video.
Stop it.
I want you to talk.
Look at me.
I like the intense one.
What's wrong? Are you tired?
Like this.
I'll give you a hand.
What's wrong with you?
It feels better than before.
What's wrong?
You're finally getting serious.
You can't stop it.
What's wrong?
You shouldn't feel it with your nipples.
What's wrong with you?
You have to eat it.
You're too sensitive.
You're cute.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I can't help it.
I'll help you.
You don't want to get hurt, do you?
Look at me.
Put it in your mouth.
Can I move?
You have to do your best.
You have to move fast.
Did you move?
I'll move it for you.
Does it feel good here?
No, it doesn't.
Why are you doing that?
Does it feel good here?
I didn't do it.
I'll move it for you.
You're too sensitive.
You have to move fast.
I'll move it for you.
Can I move it for you?
Does it feel good here?
You're too sensitive.
You have a lot of hair.
I can't.
It's okay, it's okay.
Do you want to pee?
No.
No?
I don't want to.
You don't want to?
It's okay.
I don't want to.
You don't want to?
I will wipe your face.
I don't want to.
Here we go.
Yeah yeah
Amuse
Please open your mouth.
It's painful.
I told you not to do it.
Please open your mouth.
It's painful.
Someone is coming.
Please stop it.
It's painful.
Hello.
Honey.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry I can't go now.
I'm busy now.
I have a meeting now.
So I can't go now.
It's painful.
I can't go now.
If you do it again,
I'll spread the video of you.
It's painful.
Let go of my hand.
Doctor.
Adults are right.
Some people are greedy and dirty.
Some people are beautiful.
But I can't believe it.
I'm looking for something dirty.
It's painful.
You said you were beautiful.
So I was looking for something dirty.
But I couldn't find it.
I was annoyed.
So I tried to make you disappear.
But I failed.
I failed.
I just gave you an order.
You did it.
I'll spread the video of you.
It's painful.
Human nature is evil.
Good nature is false.
Stop it.
Doctor.
It's your order.
Stop it.
Doctor.
It's over.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
Don't disturb other students.
Be quiet.
I don't want to be separated from that teacher.
Stop it.
Look at them.
Put your hands down.
They can't see you.
Stop it.
Doctor.
Doctor, don't you feel good?
Look at them.
They can't see you.
They are scared.
They are interested in you.
They want to see you.
Look at them.
Stop it.
They are interested in you.
They are happy to see you.
Stop it.
Doctor, don't you feel good?
What's wrong?
Stop it.
They want to see you.
Open your legs.
Stop it.
Doctor, don't you feel good?
What's wrong?
Stop it.
Doctor, don't you feel good?
She is scared.
Stop it.
Everyone wants to see the inside of the cage.
Show me.
Don't hide it.
She reacts better than before.
Stop it.
She feels good.
There she is.
She doesn't disappear.
You are amazing.
Why don't you disappear?
Show me.
I don't know.
Don't look.
Show me.
I don't want to look.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't hide it.
She likes to be embarrassed.
Show me.
Explain to me.
I don't want to look.
Don't hide it.
Show me.
You are getting wet.
Stop it.
She is getting wet.
You are getting wet.
Sorry.
She is getting wet.
You are getting wet.
Sorry.
It's not painful at all.
It's strange.
Do you feel the poison?
I can hear the sound.
She is pleasantly crying.
Hotter than 11月.
She can't cry it always.
She doesn't feel it intermittently at all.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I have a dizzy feeling
Don't do it
Stop it…
Wow…
Hiroki is spitting everywhere.
Excuse me, when did you put the bean paste in this dwarf?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Are you okay, Miss?
Are you all right?
We'll be back.
Was she really feeling okay?
Was Miss feeling okay?
I'm sorry.
Miss.
Don't cry.
I'm going to make a lot of mistakes in this video.
No punishment.
The school name is spreading along with the video.
I know that.
What are you going to do if the number of views is reduced?
I'm sorry.
If it's true, I want you to stop taking responsibility.
He said it's no good.
I'm a human being, too.
I have a secret that I don't want anyone to know.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for your visit.
You're welcome.
What about school?
I have permission to go to school.
I see.
I bought this.
I'm sorry.
We're going back to school.
Be careful.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Everyone.
It's about time.
I'm sorry.
Show me the real teacher.
I haven't seen it yet.
I took it.
If the teacher had listened to me, it would have been better.
We're going back to school.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Does it feel good?
Tell me.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Tell me.
It feels good.
You have a lot of blood.
Yes.
You're bleeding, aren't you?
No.
I'm sorry.
This side, too.
It feels good.
You look like you want it.
It's because you do it.
Then you admit it feels good.
It's difficult.
You can put on your underwear.
What are you going to do?
Are you okay?
It feels good.
Tell me how you feel.
I feel like I'm being touched.
Does it feel good?
I want you to do it.
Look over there and put your fingers in.
Ahh...
My youthful...
Ah, ...
Aah ...
Ah ...
Yes, I am.
Let me show you your mark.
Stand up.
What is this underwear?
You are so kind.
You took it off, didn't you?
You have this kind of underwear.
You like kind things.
You are so kind.
Stand up.
It's embarrassing.
Don't hide it.
What's wrong?
You did it, didn't you?
You are so kind.
What's wrong?
Don't do it.
It's uncomfortable.
What are you trying to do?
Don't do it.
Look at the camera.
No.
Don't do it.
It's uncomfortable.
What's wrong?
Don't do it.
You are so kind.
You said you would do it.
That's enough.
Get a grip.
It feels so good.
Have a cigarette.
Don't let go.
Is it good?
What are you going to do?
Don't do it.
I want to put it in.
You want to put it in.
Don't do it.
What are you going to do?
You don't have to do this.
I want to put it in.
You want to put it in.
Come on.
What shall we do now?
Pee in here, will you?
It is easier for you to pee in the high place.
Rah...
Oh...
Ah...
Oh, ah.
Oh...
Huh?
Ah, ah, ah...
What's wrong with your hand?
I don't know unless you say it in words.
You want to move, don't you?
I don't care.
Do it a little harder.
You want me to do it, don't you?
I have no choice but to do it.
Do it a little harder.
I can't.
What are you waiting for?
Did you feel so good?
I can't.
It feels good.
Did you feel so good?
I told you to put it in.
It feels good.
I told you to put it in
I told you to put it in.
I'm sorry I was so mean to you.
It's okay.