New Year's Day
Yes
I'm going to the gym.
I'm back.
Can I go in?
Yes, you can.
I'm going to the gym.
Here you are.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Are you okay?
Are you hungry?
A little.
Would you like to eat with me?
What?
Are you sure?
Did you eat?
It's hard to deliver, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I thought you might be hungry.
So, I drank a lot.
Is that so?
Are you sure?
Would you like to eat?
You're kind.
I don't know.
You don't know?
Here you are.
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
It's good.
Would you like to eat more?
Are you hungry?
Thank you.
I'm going to eat, too.
It's good.
Is it good?
Yes.
I'm glad to hear that.
Here you are.
It's good.
Thank you.
I'll be waiting for your call.
I was nervous.
I'm coming.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What's the matter?
I'm sorry.
Here you are.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
This is how it looks.
Here you are.
Thank you.
What's this?
I'm sorry.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Would you like to come closer?
No.
Excuse me.
Would you like to go home?
Thank you.
I'm going home.
Yes.
Hello.
I wanted you to come in early.
You took a bath.
Did I?
Here you are.
Thank you.
I wanted you to eat this pilaf.
Do you hate pilaf?
I don't hate it.
Really?
Would you like to eat it?
I'm sorry.
Here you are.
Is it good?
It's good.
Really?
I'm glad.
I'll eat it, too.
It's good.
Is it?
Here you are.
Is it good?
It's good.
You're cute.
Here you are.
I can't say that.
Aren't you interested in me?
What?
I didn't mean that.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to make you angry.
I have something I want you to see.
What?
Oh!
I want you to touch me like this.
I can't.
Look at me.
Look at me closer.
I can't.
Are you excited?
I'm getting wet.
Look at me.
How is it?
It's beautiful.
What are you going to do?
Why are you getting wet?
Look at me.
You're getting bigger.
Are you happy?
Come here.
You're getting bigger.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
What's that?
That's not good.
It tickles.
It feels good.
That's not good.
It tickles.
It feels good.
That's not good.
It tickles.
It feels good.
Please don't stop.
It tickles.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
That's not good.
It tickles.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
Just a little more.
I can't do it anymore.
That's sore.
I'm sorry.
ah uh
ah, ah, ah
Ugh
Please forgive me
Ah, sorry
Okay, I'll try to, huh?
Sorry.
He's mean.
Of course he is.
He's really mean, lol.
Hi.
Thank you very much.
Here you are.
May I wash your face?
May I?
Have you ever experienced it?
No, I haven't.
Then, I'll teach you first.
Come here.
Sit down.
What's your name?
I'm Jin.
Jin.
I'm Yura.
Yura.
May I?
You're very nervous.
Yes, I am.
I'm sorry.
I'll lead you.
Okay.
Show me your tongue.
She's nervous.
Are you married?
No, I'm not.
Does it feel good?
Do you want to lick your lips?
This side too.
It's so soft.
Can I touch you a lot?
It's amazing.
It's so soft.
It's embarrassing.
It's scary.
I'm sorry.
It's getting bigger.
It's embarrassing.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Don't do that.
It feels good.
It's getting bigger.
It's embarrassing.
Do you want to drink?
Yes.
I do.
Do you want to drink?
Yes.
Can I ask you a favor?
Excuse me.
It's beautiful.
Can I lick it?
Yes.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
You are very good.
Am I good?
Thank you.
Can I open it?
Yes.
It's pink.
What?
It's sticky.
Thank you.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I want to feel better.
What should I do?
Put your finger in it.
My finger?
Yes.
Where?
Here.
It's very sticky.
Here?
It's warm.
Thank you.
Move it more.
More?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Here?
What?
Thank you.
Next, put two fingers in it.
Two fingers?
It's warm.
Move it.
It feels good.
Thank you.
You are very good.
Am I good?
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Move it more.
It's hot.
Yes.
It's amazing.
Next, put your finger in it.
Yes.
Thank you.
Move it more.
Where?
Here?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Thank you.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Move it more.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Thank you.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Do you want to lick it?
Yes.
Can I lick it?
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'm tired.
Can I lick it?
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Move it.
It feels good.
Can I lick it?
Yes.
It's hot.
It feels good.
What do you want to do?
Do you want to do something?
I don't know.
Tell me what you want to do.
Do you want to try it?
Yes.
Come here.
Do you feel good?
It's hot.
It's wet.
It feels good.
You can move.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Do it faster.
I'll do it faster.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Let's do it again.
Do you know where it is?
It's over there.
It feels good.
Does it feel good here?
You have a cute face.
It feels good.
Do you want to put it out?
Are you scared?
It feels good.
You can put it out.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
You put it out so much.
You're young.
Jin, do you want to go out with me?
My husband is here.
You don't have to be found out.
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
I'll be there in 30 minutes.
Please put it out.
Leave it to me.
I'll pay you 3 million yen for the damage of the seal.
I'll give you 5 million yen in total.
Let's split it up.
I'll give you a wedding in Hawaii.
Leave it to me.
It feels good.
My eyes hurt.
Aichi?
You were going to use me to make money, weren't you?
That's not true.
You're lying.
You were in a fight with your husband, weren't you?
At that time,
I put a knife in the living room.
I can't believe you fell in love with me.
Why did you deceive me?
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
You're annoying.
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
I'll pay you back later.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
I got it.
I'll do it.
What do you mean?
Do it.
Talk to me.
Touch me.
I'll do it.
Do you hate me?
Calm down.
I'll do it.
You used to lick me more.
That's right.
It feels good.
More.
You used to lick me more.
It's not over yet.
You used to make fun of me.
I want you to feel better.
Don't do that.
You used to look at my face.
Look at me.
Look at me and lick me.
More.
I know.
Don't do that.
You used to lick me more.
You know that, right?
That's right.
You used to feel better.
What's wrong?
Take it off.
That's right.
Do it harder.
What's wrong?
You don't like it?
If you're happy, take it off.
That's right.
That's not enough.
What's wrong?
Look at my face.
That's not enough.
Make yourself feel better.
That's right.
Rub your face.
It's late.
That's right.
You have a lot of hair.
Turn your hair this way.
That's right.
Hurry up.
Do you understand?
What are you going to do?
That's right.
You have a lot of hair.
Your hair is wet.
Are you excited?
Do you want me to lick your hair?
Please lick my hair.
Please say more.
Your hair is wet.
Come here.
Please lick my hair.
Does this feel good?
You licked my hair.
That's right.
Hey, move.
Stand your legs. I can't see you at all.
Hey, look.
That's right. Move.
That's right.
Hey, you can't do that.
Hey, move more.
Hey, more.
Hey, come here.
I'll put you in more.
Hey, look.
Hey, move.
That's right.
Hey, move more.
Hey, look.
Come here.
What? You don't like it?
Hey.
You feel it, don't you?
That's right.
Hey, look.
I'll put you in more.
This feels good.
That's right.
You're sleeping so well.
You have to put it back.
Hey.
Hey, put it back.
That's right.
Take your butt off.
Come here.
That's right.
You feel it, don't you?
Hey, move.
That's right.
That feels good.
You want to do more, don't you?
Come on.
Say you want to do more.
I want to do more.
Okay.
Come on.
I'm going to put this in.
That's right.
You like it, don't you?
Come on.
I'm going to put it in.
That's right.
You feel it, don't you?
Stand up.
That's right.
That feels good.
That feels good, doesn't it?
Look at the place where the dung is in.
Go deeper.
Hurry up.
What do you think?
That's right.
Look this way.
Why?
You don't like it?
That feels good.
That's right.
Hiro-san.
Hey.
Let's be together.
You don't have to be found out.
Hiro-san.