My husband is kind and loves me.
But my husband is a little short of money.
My husband can't save money on loans and debt.
I have to borrow money from my father again.
But my father told me not to borrow money again.
I can't borrow money from the bank.
I have to borrow money from Mr. Yoshida.
Is Mr. Yoshida really okay?
I borrowed money from him before.
You still haven't paid back your previous debt of 2 million yen.
Did you borrow money from him?
I see.
I'm fine.
I still have some savings.
Leave it to me.
Is that so?
That's good.
I'm going to eat something today.
It costs a lot of money.
It's okay.
I can borrow money again.
What do you want to eat?
I want to eat something cheap.
It's okay.
You can borrow money.
Really?
You can eat something.
I don't have money.
How about sushi?
It's a good promotion.
It's cheap.
Thank you, Mr. Yoshida.
Thank you for your help.
You're welcome.
I'm fine.
We can help each other when we're in trouble.
You're right.
Mr. Yoshida, do you want some beer?
I'm fine.
I'll pour it for you.
Thank you for your help.
You're welcome.
Let's eat.
You're a beautiful wife.
Thank you.
You're doing your best.
Thank you very much.
How long have you been married?
It's been three years.
It's been a long time.
Yes.
Do you get along well?
Do you get along well at night?
Yes.
Do you do it once a week?
I do it once a week.
It's not enough to do it once a week, is it?
No.
I see.
You're young.
You should do it more than once a week.
I think so.
You're right.
I can do it as many times as I want.
You're such a cute wife.
Do you do it more than once a week?
I do it once a week.
It's not enough to do it once a week, is it?
I'm still single.
I'm still working.
I'm still young.
You're a director.
You're young.
Thanks to you, I'm still single.
I know.
By the way, do you have a cup?
Yes.
Do you have a cup?
My heart is beating fast.
I don't think so.
You have a cup.
I was surprised.
It's an important job to do with many people.
By the way, I have an important document to use at work.
I'm sweating now.
Really?
Yes.
It's a document that I have to return to the transaction site later.
I can't return it without this document.
What should I do?
I see.
Can I go get it later?
Can I?
It's in the company's desk.
I'm sorry.
Can I go get it later?
Yes.
It's an important document that I have to return to the transaction site later.
I can't return it without this document.
Can I go get it later?
Can I?
It's an important document that I have to return to the transaction site later.
Can I go get it later?
Really?
Yes.
It's okay.
Thank you.
I'll go get it.
Mr. Fujii, it must be hard for you.
You have a lot of debt.
You have a lot of debt, so you want to go out and play, right?
If you don't have money, you can't do what you want to do.
I've already made a lot of money, so I'll put in a lot of money.
I see.
That's why I can easily lend it to you.
If you have money, you can do good things.
I see.
It's a good thing to do what you want to do.
Isn't it better for you to do what you want to do?
What is it?
I can entertain my wife more than Mr. Fujii.
Please stop.
It's okay.
It's up to my wife.
I haven't decided on a cast yet.
I'm having a hard time with my life.
It's hard.
I've heard that you're borrowing money from other places.
I heard you stopped borrowing money from there.
I wonder what will happen.
I don't know.
Then let's stop.
I'm in a bad mood.
I just want to help my wife.
I don't want my wife to have a hard time with money.
Mr. Fujii is at work now.
You'll be fine in a little while.
It's okay.
I'll support you in your life.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
I won't hurt you.
She's beautiful and has a good style.
She's the best wife.
If I had met my wife earlier than Mr. Fujii, I would have been very happy.
I'll take you on a trip next time.
I'll take you to the best hotel.
I'll take you to the best dinner.
I'll give you a lot of money.
Thank you.
It's okay.
I want you to lend me some money.
I'm sorry.
When you walk in the city, you will be looked at by many people.
I wanted to be closer to a woman like you.
That's one thing.
It's okay.
Yes.
It's more beautiful than I imagined.
What happens if you touch here?
Does Mr. Fujii always touch you?
Does Mr. Fujii get up right away?
Don't touch me.
I'm glad.
I'm just touching you a little, but you're getting stronger.
Does it feel good?
I'm glad.
I'm sure I can make my wife happy.
Don't close your legs.
What's wrong?
You don't like it, but it's getting hot.
It's getting hotter and hotter.
Show me more.
It's hot.
Mr. Fujii, I envy you.
Your wife's smell is wonderful.
It's okay.
Let's stop here and go home.
You'll know what happens when you get home.
You're so beautiful.
You've got your hair done.
Don't say that.
Your skin is soft and smooth.
You take care of yourself every day.
You look like a rice cake.
I want to give you a big hug.
I can't see you well if you close your eyes.
Open your eyes wider.
You look like a crab.
I can see your hands.
You're so beautiful.
Why are you so soft?
It's overflowing.
I'll make you feel better.
I'll give you a big hug.
You're the best wife I've ever had.
It's so easy to apply.
You're a great wife.
It's amazing.
It's so easy to apply.
You're so beautiful.
Let me see your butt.
It's smooth.
Your butt is beautiful.
Show me more.
You're getting more and more soft.
Does it feel good to be touched by a man other than your husband?
How about this kind of play?
I don't think you've ever done it.
Have you ever been opened and looked at like this?
It's amazing.
How does it feel to be licked here?
It's embarrassing, but it feels good.
You seem to like being licked on your butt.
You're so soft.
I can't stand it when I look at my wife.
What do you think you're doing?
That's all.
No?
Then it's okay.
I don't think I'll lend you any money.
Please do your best.
Are you okay?
It's amazing.
It's been a long time since I've felt this way.
It's very comfortable.
It's soft and elastic.
It's amazing.
Please sit down.
Please stick your butt out for me.
It's amazing.
Look up.
Come here, please.
It's amazing.
I'm scared.
It's terrible, isn't it?
It's really terrible, isn't it?
Are you OK?
It's terrible, isn't it?
It's really terrible, isn't it?
Then, I'll do my best.
Let's make you feel better.
It feels good.
I'm going to burn.
I'll make you have beautiful boobs.
Let me go.
Ouch!
Can you make my boobs beautiful?
Can you do it?
Ouch!
It's terrible, isn't it?
It's really terrible, isn't it?
I'm going to burn.
I'm sorry.
It's terrible, isn't it?
Hello.
Why?
I thought you might forget me.
What are you talking about?
Please go home.
Is it OK?
Do you know Rishi?
Rishi?
Yes.
I borrowed a lot of money from him.
I have to pay him.
I can't do it.
Look.
I have to pay him.
Don't do that.
I'll tell him.
What?
What are you going to tell him?
Gradually?
Wait.
You can tell him whatever you want.
I don't know what he's going to say.
Don't do that.
Can you pay him?
No.
8 million yen.
Don't do that.
Can you pay him?
You said you didn't want to do that.
You're so stiff.
You didn't feel it when you had sex with him last time, did you?
No.
Don't do that.
Let's kiss.
I don't care if you don't want to do that.
Can you pay him?
Can you?
You can't, can you?
You don't hate him at all, do you?
You're so stiff.
Don't do that.
You don't hate him at all, do you?
Can you honestly say that you felt good when you had sex with him last time?
Don't do that.
Open your mouth.
It's getting wet here, isn't it?
Don't touch me.
Can you honestly say that you felt good when you had sex with him last time?
Open your mouth.
I'll take a look at you.
You're pulling a string, aren't you?
Don't do that.
You're happy, aren't you?
You're happy to be touched by a man other than your husband.
I'll take a look at you.
You're making a lot of noise.
Open your mouth.
Don't do that.
It hurts.
Are you trying to say something?
Why?
Please talk more.
Don't do that.
You're drooling.
Do you want to go that much?
Do you want to go now?
I can't help it.
I'll make you feel better.
You're happy, aren't you?
I thought you'd be happy, so I brought it to you.
It's pretty big.
You're drooling a lot.
It feels good when you do this.
Don't do that.
It hurts.
Let's go.
You're drooling a lot.
It's okay.
Okay, you want me to put it back to you?
Here, I'm going to put it in for you
Aqua, come here
Purin cried
You can't do that
I don't know what to do.
I feel tired.
I don't knowwhat to do.
I don't know what to do.
She went back there.
Maybe he started to miss her.
I want to sleep.
You want to sleep?
That's all for today.
Why?
Instead,
I'll give you this.
Please bear with me until the next time.
I want to sleep.
You're a good girl.
I'll take it back.
I want to sleep.
I got a letter from the director today.
It's all thanks to you.
I'm sorry.
Will you forgive me?
What's wrong?
Do you want to do it?
You want to do it, right?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Will you forgive me?
I'm sorry.
Do you want to do it?
I want to do it.
I'm sorry.
Can you show me your buttocks?
It's embarrassing.
I'll rub your buttocks.
I'm sorry.
Give me more.
You're so energetic.
That's amazing.
I can't help it.
Are you okay?
It tickles.
I like that.
Ouch, you bitch forgive me.
Uuu...
Do you...
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
...I love you.
I love you, too.
...
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
...I love you.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
...I love you.
...
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
Ah, ah...
Ah, ah, ah, ah...
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
Ah, ah, ah...
Ah, ah, ah, ah...
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
I want to kiss you.
Let's do it.
You're getting bigger.
You can eat it.
I want to do it a lot.
Can I take it off?
You're getting bigger.
I love this.
You can do whatever you want.
You're getting bigger.
It feels good.
I'm happy.
I love you.
I can't stand it anymore.
Can I lick it?
I love you.
It's hot.
I'm the only one left.
I'll touch you.
It's hot.
It's wet.
Please get on my lap.
Isn't it hard?
It's okay.
It's warm.
I love you.
I've been touching you all the time.
Can I do it harder?
It's okay.
It's amazing.
You're getting harder.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It's the best.
It's getting hot.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good to be tickled?
I know a lot of your favorite places.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good to be tickled?
Do you hate this place?
It feels good.
It's cold.
My nose is running.
You're not enjoying it, are you?
It's cold.
I'll take this off, too.
Do you like my boobs?
I love them.
I'm glad.
I want you to be happy.
It's hard.
Can you see well?
I can see well.
It's cold.
I want you to be warm.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
I'll take this off.
It's hot.
Your boobs are swollen.
It's amazing.
I'm glad.
I love you.
It's cold.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'm glad.
I'll take this off.
It's cold.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It's cold.
It's hard.
I want you to be warm.
It's cold.
You have a lot of boobs.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'm home.
Mr. Fujii.
Thank you for your hard work.
I have something to tell you.
Look at this.
You should report this.
I'll take care of the rest.
Wait a minute.
I have to write a letter of divorce.