A few days later
President
Yes
The meeting of the accounting office from 12 o'clock
Mr. Kim Corporation will come from 14 o'clock
Thank you
It won't take that long
I should think about the schedule from 14 o'clock
Yes, I think it's fine
Tomorrow
I will bring the document of the monthly inspection
Mr. Mori, please
It's helpful
I'm busy with work and hobbies
If you are not in the schedule of work
I will make a hole
It's no big deal
Oh, Nakamura-kun
Humans are fragile creatures
Take care of your wife like me
Yes
I've been with you for three years
I can take care of Shion without worry
If you have any trouble with work
It will be helpful if you listen to me
It will be helpful if I do so
What should I do?
Are you happy, Nakamura-kun?
Yes
I don't have any plans today
You don't have to be there until midnight
I can't do that
I have a lot of things
You are the president
You can say that you like me
You are serious
Well, you can do it
I will meet the staff tonight
I will go to the sauna
If you have any trouble, tell me
Yes
I will go back to the office
Hey, Nakamura-kun
Yes, what is it?
Come back as soon as possible
What?
Humans are fragile creatures
What I said is what the president said
Please
Yes
Excuse me
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you
Are you tired?
I am not tired
Thank you
I'm sorry I'm late
I'm sorry
What?
I told you to give me a massage
Are you tired?
Yes
Excuse me
Say it louder
Louder?
I'm sorry
My arms are tired
Excuse me
How is it?
Good
Thank you
Are you ready?
Not yet
I'm ready
It's not enough
Massage my calves
Yes
Nakamura-kun
Are you looking at me?
No, I'm not
Lick my toes
What?
I said lick my toes
Don't look at me twice
What?
I'm not
Lick my toes
Are you sure?
Yes
Don't just lick my thumb
Lick my other fingers
Yes
Are you ready?
You're good at licking
Stop it
Are you ready?
No, lick my soles
My soles
I said lick my soles
Yes
Are you sure?
Lick my soles
Are you ready?
Stop it
Lick my soles
What?
Stop it
I can't
You're good
Stop it
Nakamura-kun
He said you're looking at me in a disgusting way
Are you going to hang yourself?
Stop it
I have work to do
I like being licked
Like a dog
Yes
What do you want to lick next?
My soles
You were looking at me in a disgusting way
Yes
I was
Stop it
Lick my soles
Take off my pants
Hurry up
Boss will get mad
It's okay
Okay
By the way, on Sunday I ...
W..well then,
please excuse me
Poco-chan, wake up.
It feels good.
Let's go, let's go.
Poco-chan, wake up.
Poco-chan, look at me.
Poco-chan, look at me. You look pathetic.
It's good.
Let's go, let's go.
Listen to what I say from now on.
Then I'll be your pet.
Poco-chan, wake up.
Well then, I'm going.
Take care.
What time do you think you'll be back?
Let me see...
What time was it, Nakamura-kun?
Yes.
He said he had plans at 5 p.m. today.
Oh, then let's go to Ginza for the first time in a while.
Yes, I'd love to.
Well then, Nakamura-kun.
Come pick me up.
Yes.
I'd love to.
Then come early, I'll be waiting.
Well then, Nakamura-kun.
Let's go.
Yes.
Well then, I'm going.
Take care.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
You're late.
Yes?
What's this?
It's your underwear.
No, it's not.
It's not?
It's not.
Why?
I kept waiting, but the stockings got wet.
Lick the wet stockings.
But the boss is waiting.
Just do it.
Yes.
You're sweating, aren't you?
It's a little...
What?
Do you like my stockings?
They are delicious.
We aren't talking.
Lick it properly.
It's not wet.
You don't have to say it, but you're licking my feet.
What's wrong with Nakamura here?
You're licking my feet and making me stand up.
You're a pervert.
Hey, Nakamura, show me your dick.
No, I don't think so.
You're standing like this, so take it off.
Are you done?
Not yet.
Oh, shit.
Nakamura's dick stinks. Are you washing it?
I'm washing it, but I'm done with my job.
I'm going home.
Do you want me to lick it?
Are you sure?
Wow, it feels good.
Are you excited to be licked by the president's wife?
Oh, it stinks.
What's wrong with Nakamura?
Did you think you were going to die?
No, I didn't.
You look pathetic.
I'm sorry.
Nakamura, lick my boobs.
Boobs?
You were looking at them last time, weren't you?
Yes.
Let me see.
Wow.
Don't push me.
I'm sorry.
Can I see your boobs?
Do you want to see them?
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's soft.
I'm sorry for your nipples.
I'm sorry.
Nakamura, lick my boobs.
I'm sorry for your nipples.
I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
Nakamura.
Yes.
Oh, it stinks.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to lick your boobs?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You are very polite.
Thank you very much.
How do you feel, Nakamura?
I feel good.
Oh, that's the smell.
It's so good.
It's so big that I can't see it.
Don't moving so much.
Next, I'll do it with your favorite boobs.
How do you feel?
Does your nipples feel good?
It feels good.
I feel good.
If you do this to your boss's wife, she'll get mad at you.
Don't say that.
Okay.
Don't do that.
Your wife will get mad at you.
Not yet.
Nakamura.
Put it in.
I can't do that.
I'm not asking you.
It's an order.
Okay.
Put it in.
I feel good.
Wife.
Nakamura.
Give me a kiss.
I feel good.
Nakamura.
There.
Nakamura, you don't rest, do you?
Hit me harder.
There.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, I'm lonely.
Oh, ah, ah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah , yeah.
Hmm.
Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Nakamura.
Let me in.
Eh?
Stop it.
Ah!
Hmm
Nakamura...
You're still alive?
Let me out...
Nakamura...
Did you...
Fall in love with me?
Nakamura...
You're still alive?
Having sex with my wife...
Having an affair with the president's wife...
Nakamura...
Nakamura, how do you feel?
Do you like me more than the president?
I thought I wouldn't be able to sleep tonight.
President...
How are you feeling?
I'm fine. Thank you.
I'm the president of this company.
Thank you.
It's all thanks to you.
By the way, what is Shio doing today?
He left in the morning.
I'm at home.
But you know Shio better than I do.
It's nothing.
I'm glad you're with someone who can work.
I'll work hard.
Nakamura...
Oh.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry I had to do this, madam.
Let me go.
Don't worry, ma'am.
I made a calm drink for you.
What are you talking about? Let me go.
Stop it.
What are you talking about?
I drank it.
What is this?
I drank the salt.
I made this special medicine.
What are you talking about?
It's too late to say that.
It will be effective soon.
How do you feel?
Your body is getting warmer, isn't it?
No, it's not.
Your body is getting stronger, isn't it?
Let me go.
How do you feel?
My body is getting warmer.
It's very effective, isn't it?
Let me go.
How do you feel?
It's very effective, isn't it?
It's okay.
Don't be angry.
Open your eyes and look at me.
Do you want to kiss me?
I'm sorry.
Give me your horn.
You have to kiss me.
I'm sorry.
Did you notice my charm?
You feel good, don't you?
Touch me more.
What did you say?
More? Where?
Where?
My nipples.
Here?
More?
I said more.
I have to ask you.
Touch my nipples more.
I'm sorry.
Like this?
More.
More?
I'm sorry.
Don't be angry.
You feel good, don't you?
Let me touch you.
I'll touch you more.
Spread your legs.
What are you doing?
You can touch me.
Tell me what you're doing.
What am I doing?
What are you doing?
You feel good, don't you?
I feel good.
Don't go.
Don't go right away.
I want to go.
Don't go.
If you go, it's dangerous.
Touch me.
Please touch me.
What's with that face?
Nagamura, kiss me.
What?
Kiss me.
I'm sorry.
I'll kiss you.
Open your eyes.
Nagamura, look at me.
Your wife is a vulgar woman.
It hurts.
Nagamura.
Touch my belly.
It hurts.
I feel like I'm being kissed from the outside.
Touch me.
Touch my belly.
I feel like I'm being kissed from the outside.
Raise your elbow and look at my body.
It hurts.
I can't stand it anymore.
Take this off.
It hurts.
I'm going to take a break.
Does my head feel good?
Touch my head.
It hurts.
ere
uje
It hurts.
I don't know why I'm doing this
You did a good job.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh,
Char
Ah, ah, ah
uh, ah, ah
Oh, ah, ah
You want to be petted more, don't you?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh , oh,
Oh yeah,
oh
Mmm
Oh!
How do you feel?
I want you to feel more comfortable.
What's wrong?
What is it?
I don't know if I don't tell you.
I want you to feel more comfortable.
Is it here?
Yes, it's here.
That's good.
I want you to feel more comfortable.
Do you want me to feel more comfortable?
Yes.
I want you to feel more comfortable.
Please say yes.
I'm getting hot.
I want you to feel more comfortable.
Please say yes.
I'm getting hot.
I want you to feel more comfortable.
Look at the camera.
I'm getting hot.
OK, OK.
I'll lead.
Hold on!
I hate...
I hate.
Go there.
OK.
I'm... I'm... I'm...
I'm... I'm...
Get up.
You're awake.
Do you want to go home? It's too early to go home.
It's too early. I want to go home.
Hurry up.
You're awake.
Please lie down.
I love you.
It feels good.
I'm leaving, too.
Please lie down.
This is amazing.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I'm sorry.
I'm sure it's in there.
It's in there.
I love you.
This is amazing.
It feels good.
My mouth is full.
I love you.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
It's too early.
I'm leaving.
Are you leaving?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I did my best.
It feels good.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
...
DE...
nori...
TEMPURA KIDZ is the most serious one as always.
I can't do it.
Jojo experiences relaxation with the electric fan that Jojo had when he was young.
The fan would wake him up while he was asleep.
Jojo lets out some electronic sounds and starts to think...
which he thinks is the most important rank in behind the scenes of his daily life.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
You are holding her migraine.
Your leg!
Close your legs, close them.
This is my last resort.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Please enjoy this video till the end
He seems to be in a good mood.
He is making a sound.