I've told you so many times already that I can't do that.
Don't you remember? Are you stupid?
It's not your first time, Fuzuki.
Don't make me say it again.
You're persistent.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Are you really sorry?
I'm sorry.
I won't do it anymore.
I can't believe it.
I'll call the store.
No, no.
Please don't.
I'll never do it again.
I really can't believe it.
I'm sorry.
It's dangerous.
I'll never do it again.
I'm sorry.
I'll call you again.
I can't ask you for a favor.
I'm sorry.
I'm in a bad mood.
Please go home today.
Don't say that.
I don't feel good when I go home.
We don't feel good.
I hate it.
I'll be right back.
I'll call you.
I'm sorry.
It's not the exit.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
It's the worst.
He took my clothes.
I don't have my underwear.
I don't have my outerwear.
I only have my underwear.
What is he thinking?
I can't believe it.
I'm really nervous.
What is he doing?
What should I do?
I have no choice but to do it again.
I'll do my best.
I'm sorry.
I'm done.
Yes.
What?
I don't have underwear.
I'll be right there.
What's the room number?
What?
Where are my clothes?
You didn't give them back to me?
Didn't you contact that customer?
I contacted the store.
The store?
So?
What about that customer?
He didn't contact me.
He didn't contact you?
Don't be silly.
He contacted the store.
He took my clothes.
It's not cheap.
I understand.
Do I have to stay in this outfit?
I'll buy you something else.
I can't wait.
I'm sorry.
Look at me.
It's Nono's outfit.
Look at my eyes.
Don't look me in the eyes.
You have to tell me what is going on.
What was the result?
Don't look at me.
You're lying, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
You can't reach her, can you?
You should've registered first.
You should have an ID card or something.
That's what I know.
I don't know much about that.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You should study.
I'm sorry.
I'm in trouble at times like this.
It happens.
What are you going to do?
I can't go home like this.
I know.
I don't want to stay here forever.
If I stay here, I'll get mad at that customer.
That's right.
Why are you closing your eyes?
Where are you looking at?
If you keep staring at me like that, I won't be able to communicate with you.
I'm just kidding.
Really?
Think about what you're going to do.
The first thing I'm going to do is...
I'm going to buy clothes for you.
How long will it take you to buy clothes for me?
I really want to go out right now.
Why didn't you bring clothes for me?
I don't know.
You know what I'm talking about, right?
You said you took my clothes.
You should've brought something for me.
Why don't you think about it?
I don't want to waste my time.
I've been standing here for a long time.
I feel like I'm being looked down on.
That's not what I meant.
Then sit down.
You don't like it?
If I sit in front of you and talk to you, you'll look at me, right?
Hurry up.
You can sit down, right?
Talk to me.
What are you looking at?
There's nothing on the floor, right?
What?
Can't you see people's eyes?
Are you naked?
I'm not naked. I'm wearing pants.
Oh, I see.
What?
Your chest.
My chest?
Do you want me to hide something?
No, I don't like towels.
Are you worried about my chest?
Well...
That's...
Isn't it worse to look at it?
You can't see it if you look at it like this, can you?
Oh, your face.
What?
Isn't it normal to be angry at this kind of work?
No, it's not.
Maybe?
I don't think so.
You're playing around and you're tired of looking at women's bodies.
Me?
You're definitely playing around.
No, no, no.
It's not like that.
What?
No...
Aren't you used to looking at me?
What?
I've never seen you before.
You're kidding, right?
You don't like it, do you?
No, I don't.
I've never seen you before.
It's the first time I've ever seen you like this.
No, I really don't.
Are you angry?
I'm sorry.
What?
Are you embarrassed?
No...
No, it's not that.
Please listen to me.
Hey, sit next to me.
Hey, sit down.
It's okay to sit down.
The floor is hard, isn't it?
I'll let you sit down.
It's okay.
I'll sit next to you.
Hurry up.
The bed feels better than the floor, doesn't it?
Why are you staring at me?
What's wrong?
What?
I thought this was a hotel.
This kind of place is also...
What should I say?
You've been to a lot of hotels, haven't you?
No, I haven't.
What?
I'm just waiting outside.
What are you mumbling?
It's not close.
It can't be helped.
You're going to run away.
You don't have to run away.
You're running away.
Hey.
What are you doing?
I'm serious.
You don't like a man who mumbles, do you?
No, I don't.
You're mumbling, aren't you?
I'm sorry.
Say it more clearly.
No.
You can't do it, can you?
What?
Are you teasing me?
I can't hear you.
What?
Are you teasing me?
I'm not teasing you.
I'm just irritated.
I just want you to go out with me to relieve my stress.
That's your job, isn't it?
Aren't you happy?
What?
What are you going to do?
My job?
Yes.
What are you going to do?
What do you think will get rid of my irritation?
Hey.
What?
What are you trying to do?
I was surprised.
Let's wear the same clothes.
No, no, no.
I don't care.
Why am I the only one in this outfit?
I don't understand.
What are you doing?
We should wear the same clothes.
What do you mean by the same clothes?
We're not in the same class, are we?
Wait a minute.
What?
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
You've been naked in public before, haven't you?
I'm embarrassed.
Aren't you?
You've never been naked in front of a woman, have you?
Are you a virgin?
You look like you're having fun.
I'm a virgin.
Are you a virgin?
I'm embarrassed.
You don't have to be embarrassed.
What?
Give it back to me.
You've even exercised.
That's right.
You have a lot of water in your body.
You feel refreshed, don't you?
You have a thin body.
That's because your body is wrinkled.
Don't you take off your underwear?
No, I don't.
What?
Is there a problem with your underwear?
You don't have to take it off.
Why?
You took off your pants, so you don't have to take off your underwear.
You're a virgin, aren't you?
What's that?
Don't you know?
I don't know.
You don't peel off your underwear.
You're peeling off your underwear.
What are you talking about?
You're talking about your underwear.
It's not a vulgar story.
Vulgar?
How old are you?
You're a good adult.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
Give it back to me.
You can't do anything.
You're wearing underwear, but you're not playing.
What do you mean?
Wait a minute.
I'll do something good.
What if the store finds out?
The store?
The store won't find out if I'm not there.
Do you know?
I'm the best.
That's why it's not good.
Even if the store finds out, I won't be the best.
I'll lose my sales.
I'll protect you.
Wait a minute.
You took off your clothes for me.
If I tell you I'm back in this, you'll be fine.
Okay?
Don't hide it.
Wait a minute.
I didn't mean to touch you.
I was trying to make you touch me.
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
Do you always say sorry with your face?
Are you sensitive?
How far have you never kissed a virgin?
How far?
How many times?
Kiss?
When I was a kid.
When you were a kid?
As a friend.
What's that?
It's what everyone admires.
It doesn't look good on your face.
So it's not a first kiss.
What?
Kiss?
Your face is getting closer.
You like it, don't you?
You're a grown man.
I like it.
Do you have to be someone you don't like?
If I kiss you now, you might like it.
What's with that face?
But you want to, don't you?
Come this close.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
What?
It's not a what.
It's a kiss.
Don't you want to do something more fun?
Since we're here, let's know more about the store.
Do you want to know more?
I'll show you what I'm doing.
What are you hiding?
It's embarrassing to show you.
Don't say that.
What's this?
Oil?
Have you ever used it?
No.
Then I'll use it.
Are you scared?
I'm scared.
Does it feel good?
You have a sensitive body.
Hey.
Yes?
I think you know this.
It's illegal to touch girls in our store.
I see.
So you have to be patient.
Why are you touching me?
What?
What's with that face?
I'm good at it.
I'm the best.
Are you crying?
Is that how you feel?
You're like a puppy.
I'm sorry.
It's my first time.
What's wrong?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'm scared.
Don't be shy.
Does it hurt?
Are you happy?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
When I touch you, everything feels good.
It's like magic.
Hey.
What?
Let's not do that.
What do you mean?
Here?
I don't know what that is.
It's a place with a lot of lymph.
It's better to give you a massage.
Hey.
What?
It's shiny.
Don't you like it?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
It's very hot in here.
Hey.
You tend to apologize, don't you?
If you apologize next time, let's play a punishment game.
I haven't touched you yet. What are you misunderstanding?
Do you want me to touch you?
That's right.
What?
I'm sorry.
You can't help but be concerned about your life.
It's okay.
I'm doing a full body massage.
Don't say that.
Are you embarrassed?
If I say that...
Why?
Is the word massage embarrassing?
I haven't done it yet.
What?
Are you going to say that you haven't done it yet?
You're trembling.
You haven't touched me yet.
Do you want me to touch you, so you're moving your body?
Yes.
I see.
Do you remember it on your own?
Yes.
Don't say that.
You're moving your body on your own.
I don't remember it on my own.
Yes.
You're a little crazy.
You're crazy.
Yes.
What?
I'll tell you this.
Yes.
I don't usually do this.
Do you think so?
Of course.
I see.
You think so, don't you?
Yes.
If I touch you like this...
I think it's dangerous.
My customers will go crazy.
I see.
Today is a special day.
It's funny.
It relieves my stress.
It's like a hammer.
Really?
Yes.
But...
What?
Why are you so excited?
I don't know.
You've done it before, haven't you?
I've only done it a few times.
It's the same feeling as touching you, isn't it?
It's completely different.
Is it completely different?
You're wearing this kind of clothes.
You're used to seeing my clothes.
Look at me.
You'll feel better.
Really?
Yes.
It's a little fast.
It's not fast.
Fast is like this.
It's funny how sensitive you are.
What?
Does it feel good?
No.
No?
Why?
It's coming out.
Is it already coming out?
It's too fast.
Let me have more fun.
Even though I'm a virgin.
That's boring.
I know I'm good at it.
Do you like it when I touch you from the front or from the back?
Which one do you like?
I like the front.
You speak so softly.
You're touching me.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Everything I touch makes you feel good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
What?
No?
Is it not enough?
I'm sorry I didn't notice.
You can sleep.
It's not enough.
Hey.
Do you like this one?
What?
It's okay.
I'm scared.
What?
What's wrong?
Why are you being mean to me?
I'm not.
I'm teaching you slowly.
You don't do this, do you?
No, I don't.
I'll hit you, so I'll throw you away.
Stop it.
You're not used to being mean.
You don't have to move.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll rub you if you move.
Do you feel good?
It's warm.
My body is very warm.
Do you want to touch me with your hands?
I don't want to touch you.
I'll rub you if you move.
What are you doing?
I'll rub you.
It's amazing.
I'm scared.
You can touch me more.
I'll touch you more.
Touch me more.
You have to feel good about me.
I don't know if I'm doing well.
You're doing well for a virgin.
Don't you feel good?
I'm happy.
Are you happy to be praised?
You've been scolding me for a while.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's amazing.
I'll rub you.
Don't you feel good?
It's amazing.
You're a virgin, aren't you?
How do you feel?
Have you ever seen it?
I haven't.
Why do you say that?
Have you ever seen it?
I haven't.
Do you want to see it?
It's white, so it might be transparent.
Don't close your eyes.
Yes.
What is it?
It's a manko.
I can see it.
No.
Look at it.
Do you want to see it?
It's amazing.
I can't see it.
Can you see it?
It's amazing.
Look at it.
I'm embarrassed.
It's your first time to see a manko, isn't it?
Yes.
You have to study a lot.
It's beautiful.
How do you feel?
It's like this.
What should I do?
You just have to rub it.
Are you kidding me?
Really?
Yes.
Look at it.
It's amazing.
It's soft.
Is it soft?
It's sweet.
Let me rub it.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Rub it more.
Do your best.
Do you feel good?
It's hot.
It's getting bigger.
Do you know that?
I don't know.
It's a small version of your penis.
Are you kidding me?
It's a penis.
You still have a long way to go.
It's dirty.
Is it dirty?
You licked my penis.
You don't take a shower as a driver.
I'll clean your mouth.
Be happy.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
You're going too far.
It feels good.
But...
This is not the only part of your mouth.
What?
The lower part of your mouth feels better.
That's...
Do you feel good?
Yes.
What?
You know what I'm going to do next.
But...
But what?
You look happy.
Wait a minute.
I don't feel good.
You don't feel good.
You look happy.
Do you feel good?
But...
I don't put anything on my penis.
What?
Look at me.
You don't feel good.
Do you feel good?
It's hot.
It's very hot.
I can't.
You can't?
It's hot.
I put something special in your penis.
Be happy.
It feels good.
Thank you.
Do you feel good?
What?
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
I feel better when you pat my penis.
I move a lot.
Look at me.
What's this?
It's terrible.
You feel good, don't you?
I feel good.
This penis is amazing.
You have a good penis, but you don't have a penis.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
What?
Your face is amazing.
You're always cute.
I love this.
I'll give you more.
I've never said I love it.
You feel good when I put this on you, don't you?
Look at me.
You feel good, don't you?
Do you feel good?
You have a good penis.
I love this.
It's terrible.
You feel good, don't you?
It's hot.
You feel good when I put this on you, don't you?
You feel good, don't you?
What?
I feel good.
I can't do it.
I can't stop.
I love it.
What's wrong?
I'll give you more.
You feel good, don't you?
Do you still feel bad?
It's terrible.
So you should take it.
You feel good, don't you?
You still feel good, don't you?
Do you still feel bad?
I'll give you more.
You feel good, don't you?
Do you want me to give you more?
You feel good when I tickle you, don't you?
I feel good when I tickle you.
I want more.
Please follow me.
I moved a lot, so please move a little.
Please move a little.
I move from here.
It's natural, isn't it?
What do you think?
Please feel it more.
Think of it as a pleasure.
You feel good, don't you?
Don't you feel good?
I love you
I love you too
More
It feels good
I love you
Do you want to be patted?
Don't die
Look at me
It feels good
I love you
You don't have to put up with it
It feels good
When you want to put up with it, do it
More
There's a lot
Is it supposed to come out like this?
There's more, right?
Give me more
I'll show you how much it comes out
It's amazing
There's a lot
It's here, right?
You're obsessed with this, aren't you?
You have to do this
Does it feel good?
It feels good
You're whining
It's amazing how hard you are
Make it harder
It feels good
Did you notice?
You've been looking at me
I can finally look at you
Thank you
It feels good
What is this?
Give me more
It's amazing
I feel like I'm putting out a lot more
How was it?
How did you feel when I brushed you off?
It was amazing
Really?
Yes
But...
I think it's better to report it to the store
What?
I'm going to tell them
No way
I'm kidding
Please forgive me
Were you nervous?
I'm kind
So you can flirt with me again
Really?
Yes
Please
Are you happy?
Yes
I'm going to get the clothes you asked for
Are they mine?
Of course
How am I going to get them?
Think about it
I'll leave it to you
Good night
Thank you
Wait
What?
I don't have any clothes
Why?
What?
I don't have any clothes
What should I do?
Hello
I just finished
I'm in trouble
Can you come now?
Yes, please
Thank you
I'm sorry I'm late
It's okay
Well
The customer was a nice person
Yes
But his clothes were stolen
What?
Clothes?
Yes
I don't know what to do
I'll go and buy some clothes
No
I don't think it's open yet
I see
Do you have any clothes I can wear?
Clothes you can wear?
Well
I might have some
I'll take a look
Really?
Yes
Well
I just came in
Yes
I'm worried
What should I do?
I just came in
I see
Yes
Well
I can't calm down
Hey
Yes
You can't calm down
Really?
I see
Did you steal it?
No, I didn't
I'm just kidding
I'm surprised
Well
I see
Why don't you two sit down?
Okay
Please sit
Excuse me
What should I do?
Should I call the store?
Yes, please
I see
Yes
I left my phone here
Did you?
Yes
I'm sorry
You're clumsy
You're in a hurry
I'm sorry
Why don't we have a talk?
Okay
I see
What's wrong?
No
Why are you so quiet?
Nothing
Really?
Yes
Okay
You don't look at me
No, I don't
Do you hate me?
Really?
No
I thought you hated me
No, I don't
Your ears are red
Yes
You're cute
Don't tease me
Do you like girls?
No, I don't
You don't?
What are you doing?
You're cute
No
I'm embarrassed
What do you want to ask?
What?
I'm a virgin
I can't hear you
Are you a virgin?
Yes
I see
I thought of something funny
Something funny?
You should be a woman
Good morning
Why are you here?
Well
Do you know where my shop is?
Yes, I know
Really?
Yes
Are you sure?
Okay
I'm new here
I'll try
You know where my shop is, right?
Yes
Please put on the same clothes as me
What?
I mean, take off your clothes
Take off?
Yes
You're lying
I'll go to the bathroom
I'm sorry
I'll take off my clothes
Are you sure?
Yes
But
If my shop finds out, I'll be in trouble
Don't worry
I just came here
I'm doing better than other girls
I'm the best
And you like me
Yes
So, you'll listen to me
If you don't want to be found out, you'll listen to me
Right?
Yes
I knew you'd say that
I'm happy
What's wrong?
I have a pimple
Really?
I'm sorry
I got a pimple
Why do you have a pimple?
Well
Are you shocked?
No
I have to talk to you
I'm sorry
I don't mean that
Then, what is it?
What is it?
No
Don't you like boobs?
No, I don't
These are my boobs
Don't you want to touch them?
Well
I want to touch them
Tell me the truth
You want to touch them?
Yes
You know that, right?
You can touch my shop
I don't want to touch them
You don't want to touch them?
No
I don't want to touch them
I'm sorry
What's wrong?
Don't you want to touch my boobs?
I want to touch them
You want to touch them?
Yes
Well
I'm going to show you
what I learned at this shop
You can touch my boobs
Oh
You touched them
I'm sorry
If you don't want to touch them, I'm going to tell the shop manager
I don't want to touch them
You don't want to touch them?
No
If you don't want to touch them, please take off your bottom
What?
Please
Please take off your bottom
I don't want to
Why not?
Oh
Ok, you don't want to
I understand
Because you are a large man
No, I don't...
Are you shy?
I can't wait to see you
Please
What's wrong?
I know
Please
please
Yes
Take off your towel
Ok
Take off your Lance
You said you want to take off all your clothes, right?
Take off all your clothes and go to bed.
You can leave your pants on.
Lie down.
Go to bed.
What are you hiding?
I'll show you my number one ability.
I'll start from the top.
Excuse me.
You're pretty slippery.
Are you sweating?
You're sweating.
I'm nervous.
Are you nervous?
Please relax.
Great.
I told you to relax.
This side, too.
What's going on here?
It's very warm.
If you have good blood flow, it's easy to get a good effect.
You're so cute.
You don't need this anymore, do you?
No.
Come on.
It's no good.
Even if you go to a hotel, the walls are thin.
If you do something bad, you'll scream.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
I'll put this on you.
What is it?
You don't like it?
I'm sorry.
Please don't.
I hope you understand.
Look at me.
I told you not to hide it.
Let's get out of here.
It's like this.
I don't usually do this.
I'll put it on you.
It's special just for now.
I'll use the oil.
It's warm.
Where should I start?
Well...
Don't move.
I'll put it on you.
First of all...
From around.
You said you didn't like it, but you really wanted me to do it, didn't you?
Your face was amazing.
Hurry up and put it on me.
I'll put it on you.
I put it on you.
Do you want it here?
It's warm.
I'll put it on you.
I put it on you.
You look like a baby.
I'll give you a massage here.
Relax.
Please relax.
Does it feel good?
Does it feel good to be tickled?
Look at this.
It's amazing.
Your reaction is cute.
It's cute.
You look like a baby.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
You look like a baby.
Wait a minute.
I think it's going to come out.
I can't let you go so easily.
I want you to enjoy it more.
Next.
I'll put this on your boobs.
Look at this.
It's my boobs.
I'll put it on you.
You're excited to see my boobs, aren't you?
I like honest people.
You were doing it on purpose, weren't you?
I think I was doing it on purpose.
Please show me your boobs like you always do.
Can't you do it?
I'm embarrassed.
Why are you embarrassed?
I'm sorry.
It's my chance to show you my boobs.
It's a waste.
You don't have to do it if you don't like it.
I'm embarrassed.
Will you do it for me?
Yes.
I'm glad to hear that.
Do you always do it like that?
Look closer.
Please show me your boobs.
This service is only for now.
Look at me.
I got it.
Please show me your boobs.
How is it?
It's amazing.
Look at me.
Please show me your boobs.
How is it?
It's amazing.
It's the first time to see your boobs.
Look at me.
It tickles.
What's wrong?
Wait a minute.
Don't touch me.
I'll give you a massage with my boobs.
Don't move.
How is it?
It tickles.
Don't move.
Are you going to leave?
You can't leave yet.
I'll give you a massage with my boobs.
Don't touch me.
Don't move until I say so.
I'll give you a massage with my boobs.
Look at me.
Please drink this.
Don't you like it?
I don't like it.
Is it the first time to touch your boobs?
It's the first time.
It's cute.
You can rub it as you like.
You're good at it.
You can rub it more.
This is your nipple.
It feels good, so touch it.
It feels good.
Touch it more.
Rub it.
Like this?
Is it right?
More.
Rub it.
I'll help you when you want to touch a girl's body.
I'll make you feel better.
You're good at it.
More.
It's good.
It feels good.
Nipples are for love.
I'll touch you with my nipples.
No, not with my nipples.
I touched you.
I'll rub it.
I'll rub your bottom.
My bottom?
I just touched your nipples.
I just thought about it.
I'll rub your nipples with my nipples.
I'll hug you with my nipples.
I wonder if you'll go if I hurry.
I'm looking forward to it.
Do you want me to do it?
Yes.
Really?
Do you really think so?
Yes.
Please say, please rub my nipples with my nipples.
Please rub my nipples with my nipples.
You're cute.
It's good.
Please raise your hips.
Is this your first time?
You're cute.
I want to do it for you.
You're amazing.
First, I'll touch your hands.
What's wrong?
You're trembling.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'll rub your nipples with my nipples.
I'll rub your head.
Do you like my head?
My head is white.
Is it white?
But you can't take it out.
You can't take it out unless you put up with it.
I'll rub your head with my nipples.
What do you think of this?
Do you like my nipples?
Please don't panic.
You're amazing.
I think the customers would be happy to rub their nipples with my nipples.
Please rub my nipples with my nipples.
It feels good.
You can't take it out.
It was dangerous, wasn't it?
It's good.
You haven't rubbed your head with my nipples yet.
I'll rub your head with my nipples.
What do you think of this?
Do you like it?
Which do you like better, slow or fast?
Do you like fast?
You can't say that.
I'll rub your head with my nipples one more time.
You're slipping.
What's wrong with you?
Is it dangerous?
I won't stop you.
It's boring to slip, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
I haven't rubbed your nipples yet.
It feels good.
How do you like my nipples?
Don't you feel good when I rub your nipples?
I'll rub your head with my nipples.
How do you like it?
Do you feel good?
I'll rub your head with my nipples.
You make a bad sound.
What?
Are you going to leave?
I haven't rubbed your nipples yet.
I don't need your nipples.
Please.
Okay.
I'll rub your head with my nipples.
Your nipples are too hard.
You like my nipples, don't you?
What?
What's wrong?
Are you going to leave?
I'll rub your head with my nipples.
Don't you want to leave?
Do you want to leave?
I'll rub your head with my nipples.
You're so cute.
Look at this.
Your nipples are sticking out.
Did you feel good?
Yes, I felt good.
Then I'll have to clean your nipples.
You have a lot of nipples.
Your nipples are clean.
Your nipples are sticky.
Your nipples stink.
I'm sorry.
Did you eat a lot?
Yes, I did.
Can I wipe your nipples?
This is not the end.
Did you think this was the end?
You're the only one who feels good.
That's not fair.
I'm sorry.
Please lie down.
Yes.
You've never slept with a virgin, have you?
Yes, I have.
Really?
Then I'll show you my nipples.
Do you want to see my nipples?
You want to see it, right?
This is a rare opportunity.
Please straighten your face.
How do you like my nipples?
I don't know.
Don't move your face.
How do you like my nipples?
I'll show you my nipples, too.
You look very healthy.
It's hard.
It feels good.
You're cheeky.
That's right.
I can't stand it anymore.
He likes my nipples.
I'll massage your nipples.
Do you know what I mean?
Can you feel it?
I feel it in here.
Don't you want me to massage your nipples?
Really?
I'm going to do it for you.
I'm going to put it in.
Really?
Are you okay?
I'm going to put it in.
Not yet.
Can I really put it in?
Do you want to do it with a live manko?
Do you want to kill your husband?
I'm going to put it in.
One, two.
I can't do it anymore.
How do you feel?
It's hot.
Don't move.
Look.
It's in.
It's hot.
Was it stimulating?
I'm going to do it slowly.
It's boring if I do it quickly.
I'm going to do it on your neck, too.
Does it feel good?
Do you like being licked on your neck?
I've been licked before.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to lick you.
Don't move.
I'm a little nervous.
Bear with me.
Okay?
Okay.
I'm going to move your waist, too.
I'm sorry.
My neck is delicious.
Both of them.
Look at me.
I'm going to lick you with drool.
Okay?
It's hot.
I'm going to lick you more.
I'm going to do it quickly.
It's hot.
Don't get up.
Does it feel good?
It's really good.
It's hot.
It's the best.
Let's do it more.
Okay.
It's really good.
It's the best.
It's good.
I'm going to do it again.
I'm going to lick you with drool.
Let's do it more.
It's hot.
Come here.
I'm going to do it.
One, two.
Look at my butt.
Touch my butt.
It's hot.
It's soft.
I'm going to do it more.
It's good.
Does it feel good?
I can't stop.
Let's do it more.
More.
I'm going to do it more.
Does it feel good?
I can't stop.
It hurts.
You can do it alone.
Look at my butt.
Make it harder.
It's hard.
It's hot.
It's okay.
I'm going to do it more.
Move this time.
What's going on?
I want you to move this time.
What do you mean?
I'm going to do it.
Move this time.
That's right.
Move more.
It feels good.
More.
It's getting hot.
It feels good.
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
It came out.
It came out a lot.
It's amazing.
It came out a lot, didn't it?
Why did you take it in?
It's amazing.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't stand it.
You couldn't stand it?
Yes.
You're a good boy.
Let's do it more.
You can do it, can't you?
You can do it.
You're a good boy.
Can you do it?
Let's start from the back.
Do it.
Get up.
Hurry up.
Do you know where it is?
Don't put it in the hole in your butt.
Here.
That's right.
One, two.
You're not good at it.
You're cute.
Do it like this.
That's right.
It came in.
It feels good.
Aty, move.
Move.
Don't do it as you did before.
It's amazing.
Hey.
I can't move well.
It can't be helped.
Stay still.
I'll move.
Do it like this.
It feels good.
It was good.
Do it like this.
There.
My back hurts.
I can't stop it.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
That's right.
If you do that, you'll be able to move more easily.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I can feel that it's deep.
It feels good.
No.
More.
That's right.
It's too deep.
No.
It feels good.
One more time.
It's amazing.
No.
That's right.
It hurts.
I can't do it.
Pull it out.
Hurry up.
You can do more, right?
I'm scared.
Can you see it?
You can see it, right?
Look at it slowly.
Can you do it?
There.
Put it in there.
It feels good.
You're doing a good job.
Can you do it?
I can do it.
Like this?
That's right.
Why do you have boobs?
Why?
Boobs.
Move a little more.
I like that.
It's getting intense again, isn't it?
I can't move.
I can't stop it.
Are you doing it right?
I'm doing it.
It's getting intense again.
It's getting deeper.
I'm going.
Ouch!
Koharu, you can go further.
Go further.
I want to push you more.
It feels good.
This is good.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
What's wrong?
Let's go together.
It's hard.
You're sweating a lot.
I want you to support me from now on.
I want you to support me.
I'll support you.
Really?
Please say anything.
I'm glad.
I'll support you.
Did you feel good when I brushed your teeth?
I felt great.
It's a secret.
What should I do?
She's not here.
What?
Hello?
Can you come to room 406?
I'm in trouble.
Please.
Where did she go?
I can't believe it.
She didn't take my money.
But she stole my clothes.
What kind of personality is she?
I don't know.
I've never seen her like this.
Have you ever heard of her?
No.
She stole my clothes.
What should I do?
I can't go home like this.
She's not here.
I'm in trouble.
What should I do?
Her clothes were expensive.
If I go to her store, she'll give me a discount.
I think it's okay.
I'll take a lot of money.
I want to talk to the store manager.
What's wrong with you?
You don't look well.
I'm fine.
Really?
I don't know what to say.
Don't worry about me.
Okay.
You don't look well.
Do you care about me?
No.
Are you not used to me?
Well...
Have you ever seen me naked?
No.
I've never seen you naked.
Really?
Yes.
Are you kidding me?
I'm doing this job.
Have you ever seen me naked?
I've never seen you naked.
Really?
I've only seen you naked in videos.
Is it your first time seeing me naked?
Yes.
I see.
You're cute.
Thank you.
You're doing this job.
You should get used to it.
Do you think so?
Don't you have a title?
No, I don't.
You've never seen me naked?
No.
I see.
But...
You should get used to it.
I'll help you.
What?
Don't hesitate.
It's expensive.
Don't worry.
I'll help you.
But...
Take it off.
Don't worry.
I'll help you.
What are you hiding?
I'm naked, too.
I see.
You're cute.
I thought you were a novice.
But you're a virgin.
Yes.
You're cute.
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
Do you have any complaints?
No.
But you'll get used to it.
I'll teach you slowly.
If you get used to it,
you'll know how a girl feels.
You'll be able to work.
Maybe you'll have a girlfriend.
You want me to do it, don't you?
I haven't done anything yet.
You're shaking a lot.
Are you nervous?
Yes.
You've never kissed, have you?
No.
Have you?
Don't you want to?
No.
What should I do?
Stay still.
Yes.
I'll do it.
You're hungry, aren't you?
Give me your tongue.
I'll do it.
You look comfortable.
Yes.
I'll do what I always do.
I'll do it today.
You have to kiss a lot to have sex.
If you massage it,
your blood circulation will improve,
and you'll be healthy.
Do you understand?
Yes.
I'm using this.
I'll do it.
Use a lot of oil.
It warms your body.
I'll do it.
It's warm, isn't it?
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Your body is warm.
Are you nervous?
Yes.
If I do this,
your body will be more nervous.
Look.
I'll massage your belly a lot.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
It feels good to be touched by a woman, doesn't it?
You're so cute.
It feels good.
Your nipples are curled up.
Your belly is bulging.
It feels good.
You're so cute.
Your nipples are curled up.
Does it feel good?
Are you holding back your voice?
You can speak more.
It's not embarrassing.
You have a good voice.
The oil has dried up.
I'll massage your belly a lot.
Your nipples are curled up.
My nipples are curled up, too.
You have a cute voice.
I'll massage your belly a lot.
It feels good.
You don't touch me at all.
You're so cute.
Don't touch me right away.
You're not supposed to touch me.
I'll massage your belly a lot.
How is it?
It's soft, isn't it?
You can rub it harder.
Is it good?
It's good.
I'll rub it with you.
If you have a girlfriend,
I'll do it, too.
It feels good.
You're good.
I'll do it, too.
It feels good.
I'll pinch you.
You're good.
Do you like my butt?
I like it.
I'll spread the oil.
You're good.
It feels good.
It's good, isn't it?
You can do whatever you want.
I'll do it, too.
You like to be embarrassed.
I'll give you a massage.
It's amazing.
Does it feel so good?
I'll give you a special massage.
This is the limit, isn't it?
I'll massage you slowly.
It's amazing.
I'm just touching the back of your head.
I don't do this to my customers.
It's very hard.
You have a lot of hair.
How long haven't you pulled your hair out?
A week.
A week?
Your hair will explode.
I'll give you a side practice.
I'll put a lot of hair in your forehead.
How is it?
You have a lot of hair.
I'll give you a side practice.
No, no, no.
It's better to put a lot of hair in your forehead.
I'll give you a side practice.
You're trying to get rid of your hair.
You should enjoy it more.
You don't want to pull your hair out, do you?
I'll give you a side practice.
You feel good, don't you?
Hang in there.
Did you think you could do it?
Lie down here.
I'll give you a side practice.
You like boobs, don't you?
You're going to get excited.
I'll give you a side practice.
It's not bad to be loved like this every day, is it?
How is it?
It's not embarrassing at all, is it?
I can't stand it.
It's going to come out soon.
You're going to give up.
Hang in there.
You can't let it out on your own.
You like boobs, don't you?
Does it feel good?
It's messy.
You're all wet.
You're getting bigger and bigger.
I can't stand it.
Hang in there.
You can't.
This is how you have fun.
You've been feeling good on your own for a while.
You can feel good about me, too.
You can, right?
Get up.
You've never seen a baby in close up, have you?
What's wrong?
You're always in close up.
You're beautiful.
Am I beautiful?
Look at me.
What's wrong?
Do you want to lick me?
Okay.
Lick me.
That's right.
You're cute.
You're good.
Do you know?
Here.
Lick me.
When a woman licks me, I feel good.
You're good.
Is it good?
How do you feel?
It's good.
Why?
It smells.
Does it smell?
Doesn't it smell?
It smells bad.
Does it smell bad?
That's right.
I feel good.
I'm getting more and more intense.
That's right.
You're good.
Touch my fingers.
My fingers?
I'm going to apply a lot of this.
First, from the outside.
Do you know where to touch?
I'm going to start from here.
That's right.
I'm very nervous.
You're cute.
I'm excited, too.
I feel good.
You can be more intense.
That's right.
I feel good.
It's getting better.
Do you want to put it in?
That's right.
One at a time.
How do you feel?
It's warm.
Is it warm?
That's right.
I feel good.
Imagine putting it in one by one.
That's right.
One more.
Hurry up.
That's right.
A little more.
I'm going to sleep.
This is a salt blower.
When I hit a pleasant place, the salt comes out like this.
I'm going to sleep.
It's amazing for the first time.
That's right.
It's a big deal.
I think you've grown up a lot.
You made me feel good.
Let's do it until the end.
Is that okay?
Don't you want to do it?
I want to do it.
I'll steal your virginity.
It's a luxury for me to do it for the first time.
Thank you.
Come here.
I'm going to sleep.
Leave it to me.
You've graduated from virginity.
I'm going to move slowly.
I'm going to sleep.
I just put it in, but it's about to come out.
Don't do it.
I'm going to sleep.
You're cute.
Let's hurry up and do it.
It's about to come out.
Hang in there.
I'm going to sleep.
It's very tight.
You're in a good mood.
You've been patient.
I'll do it slowly.
I'm going to sleep.
Do you want me to hold you?
You're so cute.
I'm going to sleep.
Let's sleep together.
Virginity really suits you.
I'm going to sleep.
Let me hear a cute voice.
Let me hear a nice voice.
I'm going to sleep.
You're in a good mood.
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
Does it feel good?
Can you hear me?
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
You're so cute that I'm attracted to you again.
Do you want to move this time?
Yes.
I'm going to sleep.
Do you know where this is?
Here.
That's great.
Come here.
I'm going to sleep.
Can I do it harder?
I'm going to hit you harder.
I can't move that much.
Why?
Hang in there.
You have to move your hips faster.
It feels good.
That's great.
It hurts.
Hang in there.
This time...
Let's do it while looking at each other's faces.
I'm going to sleep.
I can't move.
Don't move.
That's great.
It feels good.
Move your hips more.
That's great.
I can't move.
I'm going to sleep.
You're going to sleep.
It can't be helped.
You want to sleep, don't you?
Why did you stop me?
Hang in there.
You want to sleep more, don't you?
It can't be helped.
Put your hips out.
That's great.
That's a lot.
How was your first sex?
It felt good.
I'll keep it a secret.
It can't be helped.
I'll do it sometimes.