Can you find information about change?
No, not yet.
I'm sorry, sir.
I don't think so.
Excuse me.
Please.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
No, it's nothing.
Hey, look at this.
This girl is so strong.
Ichi-kun, where are the documents from the other day?
Chief, that's...
Um, that's...
No, that's not what I meant.
What are you looking at at work?
You have an important consultation next month, right?
Do you understand?
Yes.
Don't do that and read this.
I'm sorry.
If you think it's really bad, you can't see this until the consultation is over next month.
What?
You can't do that either.
Do you understand?
Yes.
By the way, are you still thinking about what Chief Washiro said at that time?
Of course.
If I break it, I'll be told it's satanic.
Really?
That's funny.
Ichi-kun, can I talk to you for a minute?
Yes.
You know what's going on today, right?
I have a consultation with the president of Tsukimura Shouji from 20 o'clock.
Are you ready?
Yes.
And do you keep the promise you made last month?
What's wrong? Are you sick?
No.
I'm counting on you today.
Chief Washiro, I heard you're beautiful, but you're really beautiful when I actually meet you.
Thank you.
I highly evaluate your company.
Please say it as a sign of your approach.
Here you are.
Thank you.
One more drink.
Well, I was nervous about the consultation.
I'm tired. I don't want to just remember it.
You saw it, didn't you? My body is sticky.
I can't think of it.
Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
Would you like to drink again?
I'm still fine.
But I'm going to show you.
Do you want to come to my house?
Let's have a drink.
Wait a minute.
I'm back.
Excuse me.
Here you are.
I'm tired.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'll pay for the taxi.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
Let's drink again.
Cheers.
It's different from the alcohol I drank earlier.
I think so, too.
Is it good?
You don't have a girlfriend, do you?
No, I don't.
You have a girlfriend, don't you?
You're young.
You should play a lot.
Are you okay?
I can't drink anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's cold.
It's harder than before, isn't it?
What do you mean?
Isn't it strange?
I'm a little annoyed.
I'm sorry.
You look relaxed.
No, I'm not.
I've been patient.
Are you patient?
Aren't you slimy?
No, I'm not.
Are you patient?
I think you're a gentle man.
I feel good.
It's still hard.
It's cold.
Did you do your best?
Yes, I did.
You still look energetic.
No, I'm not.
You can stay here tonight.
Thank you.
How many times can you do it?
I have to go home soon.
It's okay.
By the way...
I have to go home soon.
I haven't done anything yet, but my waist is moving.
It's cold.
You don't want to go home, do you?
I'm glad you didn't go home.
Isn't it harder than before?
It's cold.
It feels good.
It's getting harder and harder.
I'll do something nice for you.
It's stuck in your boobs.
It's cold.
Give me your waist.
Relax.
It's buried.
It's very slippery.
Does it feel good?
It's cold.
It's very slippery.
Does it feel good?
Let's hurry up.
Sorry.
I'm waiting for you.
It's getting hot.
Do you feel better?
Do you like it?
Do you like it faster?
Is this enough?
Do you like it?
Do you want to go?
No?
Did you go?
You didn't say yes.
You're eating a lot.
Did you eat it all?
You're still standing.
You can still go?
You're still fine.
You can still feel good?
Do you want to be healthy?
Are you tired?
It's okay.
I'm fine.
I'll put it in.
You're really fine.
It's okay.
It's okay, right?
Do you feel good?
You're going deep.
You're so energetic.
Does this feel good?
What's wrong with your face?
You're too energetic.
It hurts.
It's hot.
I can see it.
You're so energetic.
I have to go home.
It's okay.
I'll follow you.
It's hot.
What's wrong with you?
I'm in a bad mood.
What is it?
I can't go back to work.
That can't be helped.
Don't cry.
Don't say things like that.
I love you.
Does this feel good too?
I love it. It feels good.
I love you.
This feels too good.
Your hips are moving too much.
I'm afraid of babies.
You can't?
No, I can't.
I love you.
How much do you love me?
You're just touching me?
I'm just touching you.
That's what feels good.
Is that what makes you feel good?
Yes.
This feels even better.
I love you.
You're moving a lot.
I'm sorry.
It's really hard.
You're moving too much.
I love you.
Can you breathe?
That's amazing.
I love you.
I don't know what to say
Thank you.
Put some weight on it.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I know.
It's an erotic sound.
It feels good.
I can't stop laughing.
My boobs are half drunk.
It's amazing.
I can't see it.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I can't see it.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Is it scary?
You didn't say it's okay.
It's amazing.
It's coming out a lot.
I have to go home.
I can't work.
It's okay.
Again?
What should I do?
I want to feel good.
You have to go home.
That's all.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
Do you want me to do it directly?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I don't know what to do
It's painful.
I'm sorry.
Can I touch you while licking this?
Lick?
I don't want to do it with my voice, so I'll do it with my boss's voice.
Oh, wow.
Oh, it's good.
Oh, what is it?
Hey, you're standing like this, but you're not going to put it in yet?
You don't want me to?
Hurry up and move.
Hurry up and put it in.
Oh, it's good.
It's harder than before, isn't it?
I'm in trouble.
What's wrong?
I can't think of anything to do.
You're not thinking of anything, are you?
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's good.
It hurts.
I'm not done yet.
Oh, I see.
Oh, it's good.
Chin-chin is so energetic that he's going to fall asleep.
He's going to fall asleep.
He's going to bump his head.
Where are you looking at?
I can only see his head.
Oh, it's good.
Do you have a day off tomorrow?
Yes.