Sorry if so.
No, again the job.
Which of my work is important to me?
Both are important.
No problem, because you are in the end.
Not to be difficult.
It is our half year.
Mickey’s boyfriend is going to stay with Mickey until he’s off work.
I want you to care more too.
You are caring.
I will be at the end of the radio and see you.
Sorry, I have to go back to work.
This is the document you were requested.
Oh, Sanchez, it will help you.
The phone call, is it your girlfriend?
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
You are always together.
What is hate?
Not the other.
I think it is fine.
No, I would do it later.
I have to do work.
I am
About the elderly.
I liked it.
Then I will pick up the drink.
Tired of
I was tired.
has been
Not the last train.
What to say.
Oh, if if
No, I am sorry
at work at work.
No, I know it.
Sorry to
You can listen to me about my story.
Can you go home today?
No, from here.
Taxi is not stupid.
Thinking about what to do.
The river came.
Can I go home?
I am close to home.
I walk a little.
by
Be careful, I will go home.
that
If well
Go to home?
Oh is?
Of course, it is not strange meaning.
I think you are in trouble.
Okay is?
Yes is
Then we are
Eat at the bar.
of me.
Go to
beautifully
Please sit there.
thanks to
What did you say to your girlfriend?
You can’t say it, right?
He came to my house.
Even this,
Because I feel guilty.
Oh this,
Let us drink.
Yes to.
thanks to.
Would Kaka be a boyfriend?
is not there.
Yes is.
Anyone you like?
is not there.
by
She was there, too, and would have trouble.
Maybe she loves her old man.
I think you should care about it, but I’m going to care about it.
Not very well done.
Body comparison is not good.
The body comparison.
You know that you just kissed me, you don’t bite me.
Yes what is.
I have always been serious about myself.
I was around and took a step back and lived.
I always wanted to break my own shell.
Have you just kissed?
The old man.
Please say nothing.
Please touch it properly.
Full of stomach.
Sapphire is waiting.
I still
I have not washed.
Oh yeah
No to
by
Oh well – well
Come to come.
It is a good painting.
Please keep wearing it.
is right?
Oh is
Oh...
No to?
1 is
2nd
No to
Oh yeah
Okay is.
Oh...
Please let it quietly away.
No to
Oh is?
It is not a dream.
I did it.
by
He comes very.
Oh is
If if
What was I doing a little.
You tell me if I call you, you will go out.
Oh is
Sorry I was sleeping.
I do not believe that.
Really, you are not really choking.
No to.
I really sleep at the cafe.
OK is OK.
I’m sleeping more than a shit like you.
I’m angry, so explain it until I agree.
The worst! the worst!
All is my fault.
I told you what you wanted to do, so I met you.
Daley is my first priority.
Really the worst!
Do you always say that?
The girlfriend?
Do you really like your old man?
It is me.
If it were me.
I would never say that.
with me.
How about kissing dress?
The old man.
Please stand still.
Do not move.
You have grown up again.
I am pleased.
It is great, you can use coffee.
I will put it under my elders.
Oh that, that is shit.
It is dry.
It was very dry at that time.
I am pleased.
Yes
greatly
So much so
Yes
I am
I like the old man.
Yes
Stay well.
Can you still?
This is the first time.
Kissing with you.
Very constantly
Gunners, like Argentina
Cut this.
to noise
2nd
No to
by
by Pina
No to
Oh well
Bite more.
No to
Oh yeah
by
by Nirvana
Full of.
well is
by Adieu
I picked up.
I want a knife.
by
well well.
No to
I want to drink.
See also
Feel good
I too.
Oh to
Oh yeah
by
No to
Oh is
by
No to
Oh is
W is
good is
Feel good
Is it okay?
is okay.
No is
Oh is
Yes
Oh yeah
No to
Feel badly
It sounds gorgeous.
No more pain.
Oh awesome.
Feel badly
Oh, I will go.
Stop it.
Oh yeah
by
Oh awesome.
Oh yeah
Oh well.
Oh is
Oh yeah
Oh, is great
Feel good
Feel like stupid.
Not badly
So that is that.
Moving very much.
Please get out a lot.
Toughly
Feel good
greatly
...
When I am with her, I am bad.
But I could not stop myself.
Sorry, do you know where you are, Mr. Rush?
No, you do not know.
Oh yeah.
My friend, I met you.
Wait to.
Oh, no, it feels good.
Wait to
It is not.
I will do it to you.
Yes
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Take it.
No to
2nd
Take it.
Do it a little now.
Yes
and kiss.
I want to go with hands.
Do you leave it out like this?
Who is someone.
Okay is.
Please bring out a lot.
by
greatly
You slept a lot.
Tomorrow is vacation.
Can you meet?
But her sister.
OK is OK.
Can I go to the river?
So I will go back first.
I want to break up.
That word is
I could not tell myself.
I will hinder you.
The old man?
No matter
Did you do?
Because I decided.
Oh is?
If if
What is?
I am sorry and apologizing.
I want to hear something.
Oh, and normally
It is noisy!
Listen to me!
I am tired.
We will split.
It is a joke, right?
It is a lie.
I am not joking about that.
Sorry but
Because I could have loved someone.
Wait a little.
You will never get me from you again.
Do not contact them there.
Wait, wait and wait.
The old man.
Sorry I haven’t made it clear yet.
I want you to meet me.
Is it really me?
I cannot imagine others.
Please do not call them, but call them the cybersecurity.
cyclist
No to
Oh well
very clean.
hurtly
Feel badly
Please tell me about a little retreat!
I want to go into my cycle.
Oh yeah
No to
Yes
Oh yeah
No to
Full of stomach.
The flop!by
I like it too.
I have always loved my old man.
Oh yeah
The old man’s ass.
Very bad feeling.
I too
by
Wait today.
Oh well, oh well
Come back again.
It feels good.
Oh awesome.
I will be.
Oh, that feels so good.
Interestingly
Hair to hair.
Very good feeling.
by SJ
by
Oh yeah
Oh is
not there.
Oh well...
Oh yeah yeah...
Say to me, Shukri.
I did.
Oh well...
Oh... oh...
No longer bad.
by
Maybe not
Hot and hot.
It hurts.
Oh well
Kick
I like the place of Simphi.
Oh, oh, I will give it out.
I will give out.
It feels bad.
Get out.
Oh...
The highest
The old...
So, that old man.
Both without time.
Call me by name too.
I understand.
Mr Cate
Today is our anniversary.
Yes