I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to die if I don't do something about it.
Good morning.
How about breakfast?
I don't need it.
What about school?
I'll go if I can.
What about Yuzuru?
I don't need her.
She doesn't come out of her room, and she's taking a break from school.
She's not bullying her, is she?
I don't know.
She doesn't talk to me much.
She left it with her mother, so she doesn't talk to me anymore.
That's right.
I see.
She really doesn't talk to me.
But it's okay. We're family.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
It's okay.
This is for you, Yuzuru Okuda.
Thank you.
This is for you, Hanko.
Yuzuru Okuda's Story
Well, she told me that he suddenly came into her heart.
Terrible.
I'm really sorry.
Hey, Yuzuru.
Did you really do that?
What?
Don't you trust me?
No, I don't.
Well, as a student, I'm worried about this kind of problem.
So I want you to be careful at home.
Apologize to her again.
Terrible.
You should have called the police.
She'll do the same thing again.
Because she has a bad eye.
Well, that's all for today.
Please be careful not to do this again.
Yes.
I'm really sorry.
Let's go.
Why did you do that?
My grandmother told me that I was cute.
But the girls in my class said I was terrible.
Are you being bullied?
I can't deal with anyone anyway.
So I thought I'd give them a kiss.
You shouldn't do that.
Does your father beat your mother's breasts?
Well, he's married.
He doesn't do that anymore.
I can't have a girlfriend.
I can't get married.
Because it's disgusting.
I really wanted to touch real breasts.
Real breasts were soft.
I'm sorry.
Do you really want to touch real breasts?
Touch your mother's breasts.
I'm sorry.
Are you sure?
Don't touch other girls' breasts.
I'm sorry.
Here you are.
Don't make trouble at school.
I'm sorry.
Touch my penis.
You don't really play pranks on girls at school, do you?
My mom...
She doesn't help me with my penis.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
I've never done that before.
Can I try?
Mother's breasts.
It's beautiful, soft, and the best.
Come here.
Mother's breasts are the best.
I'll put a toothpick in your mouth.
I'll move it faster.
Mother's breasts are the best.
You seem to be in a good mood.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I see.
Mother's breasts are the best.
I'll put a toothpick in your mouth.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to make a cake sheet with the remaining cream.
It is a place where you can feel the atmosphere of the old town.