Koburino
It's OK
Wasn't it hot?
I'm fine
don't worry
Great.
What is this place?
I'd like to go for a drive.
Is it far?
It's quite far.
I have to go by car.
It's been a while since I had a drive, so I'm looking forward to it.
Oh, by the way.
Is your mom coming tomorrow?
Oh, yeah.
I'm sorry I'm off tomorrow.
Oh, no problem.
I want you to buy me something before my mom comes.
Is that okay?
Of course.
Thank you.
Well, let's go to bed.
Hey, Sanae.
What do you think about today?
What?
Today?
Yes, today.
I'd like my mom to come back.
Right?
But, I can't do it when my mom comes.
I haven't been able to do it recently.
Oh, I see.
Let's do it when your mom comes.
Let's do it.
Let's go to bed.
But...
Okay.
I'm sleepy.
Your mom is here.
Get out of bed.
Let's go to bed.
Okay.
Good morning.
It's been a while.
Let me help you.
No, thank you.
Get up, get up.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
You're wet.
I'm fine.
Let me help you.
Were you okay when your mom came?
I was fine.
By the way, you've changed a lot.
Really?
I don't know much about you because I've been with you for a long time.
You're right.
It's been a long time.
I'm glad you didn't get lost.
Not at all.
I don't walk sometimes.
But, I'm getting better.
You're always walking.
I'm glad.
Itadakimasu.
It's delicious.
You're getting better at cooking.
Really?
I can't keep up with your mom's cooking.
Hey, Masao.
Yes?
You like my seasoning, don't you?
What?
Yes, I do.
I like it.
See?
You don't have to imitate me because it's your mom's seasoning.
But, when you go to my house, you always say,
You always say,
No, I like your cooking.
Did you hear that?
I said,
You always say,
I like your cooking.
I tried my best to cook today.
Hey, don't fight.
We're not fighting.
We're friends.
I got it.
Thank you for the meal.
You're welcome.
Hey, Mom.
Yes?
Do you want to go drinking with me?
Do we?
Yes.
I want to go drinking.
Let's go.
What kind of alcohol do you like?
There are many kinds.
I'll go with you.
Can I go with you?
Yes.
Let's go.
Shall we?
I'm so happy.
What's this?
I bought a lot.
Really?
I'm sorry.
I drank too much.
Thank you.
I'm fine.
I'm home.
You're home.
But I...
You're tired.
I'm home.
Really?
Really.
I'm home.
I will tell you about the next class, go to your home?
What's wrong...
That...
No, I'm not.
I'm fine. Calm down.
I just happened to be here.
I know, I know.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Can you put the body down?
I'm sorry.
I just...
I know.
But...
Why?
What?
Well...
Is there something you can't tell me?
About Sanae?
I knew it.
What?
Well...
Hey.
If there's something you want to tell me, say it.
Well...
We're family, right?
Right?
Yes.
So, ask me anything.
Well...
I don't know what happened to Sanae.
Maybe...
Her father left her.
No.
I'm not attractive.
Maybe.
No, you're not.
You're very attractive.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Oh, you're right.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Hey.
But...
Well...
I'm glad.
What do you mean?
Well...
I'm glad I quit on the way.
What do you mean?
Well...
That's...
I...
I'm glad I quit on the way.
Well...
It's bad for your health to quit on the way.
And...
My daughter is responsible for it.
What?
So...
Today...
I...
I'll take the responsibility.
Responsibility?
What?
Mom?
No, mom.
It's painful if you quit on the way, isn't it?
Well...
I'm fine.
Don't say that.
I'm responsible for it, too.
Mom...
Yes?
Well...
Can I...
Can I quit on the way?
What?
Yes, please.
Well...
That's great.
Ah...
Do you want to see more?
No, I don't want to.
Get out of my way.
It's scary.
Mom.
How is it?
It's amazing.
This is amazing.
I have to go this far.
It's amazing.
Like this?
It feels good.
Do you really like this?
It's amazing.
It's getting bigger.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Mom.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
That's good.
But don't tell Sanae about this.
Yes.
Talk to Sanae about this at night.
I'm going to sleep.
Yes.
Good night.
Mom, I heard you had a lot of fun yesterday.
Yes.
It's been a while since I saw you.
Did you go to bed already?
I think so.
It's been a while since I saw you.
Is that so?
What's wrong with you?
What?
You've been acting strange since last night.
That's not true.
Really?
I'm fine.
Sanae.
What?
Why don't we do it?
What's wrong?
Mom is here, right?
But...
Let's do it after mom comes home.
Okay?
I'm sorry.
I'll be serious this time.
I love you.
Then...
But...
You know how I feel, right?
Yes.
It's like a mood.
So...
Oh, right.
The inn we went to the other day.
It's a nice place.
Let's go there.
Okay?
Let's go on a trip.
Then...
Oh, right.
Let's go there.
Let's go out today.
Okay?
I'm looking forward to it.
Okay.
Sanae.
Mom is here, right?
But...
I don't know.
Because mom is here.
What do you mean?
Because mom is here?
Is that what you mean?
Because mom is here.
I got it.
I'm going to make a hole in the middle of the cake.
I'm going to put a lot of cream on it.
a little of caramel
a little of emulsion
I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough.
Open the hole we left at first.
Put the oil on the cutting board and pat the dough with a rolling pin from the edge to fold it.
Pull the dough.
Shorten the dough with scissors to help shape it.
Put the oil on the cutting board and pat the dough with a rolling pin from the edge to fold it.
I was really busy.
So I skipped having dinner the next day...
... and went to work!
What?
Humph!
Asa!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't forget what happened yesterday.
Yesterday?
I couldn't stand it.
You said it was just yesterday.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't stand it.
Even if you say that...
I'm sorry.
Can't I?
What?
You can't?
Because you didn't talk to me.
Did you talk to me?
Yes.
I talked to you.
But you turned me down.
Why?
You have a mother.
What?
Really?
Yes.
I told you to go to your mother.
And...
I was in a bad mood.
Did you say that?
Yes.
But...
Please.
Just today.
Just once.
Please.
Even if you say that...
I'll talk to you again.
But...
I'm in a bad mood.
I can't talk to you.
So...
Please.
Just once.
Then...
If I'm in a bad mood...
I'll talk to you again.
Can we get along?
Yes.
We can.
Okay.
Then...
Please.
I promise.
Okay.
I'm in a bad mood.
I knew it.
You have a mother.
Masao...
I'm sorry.
Here?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Let's get along.
Mother.
Masao.
I can't stand it.
What did you say?
You said no.
Masao.
Stop it.
I get it.
Masao.
Listen to me.
Yes.
I can't stand it.
Listen to me.
Please do this.
Do you understand?
If I wear a rubber band...
Wait a minute.
You're good at it.
I got it.
Rubber band is good, isn't it?
Masao.
Do what I said.
Promise me.
It's okay.
I get it.
I feel so good.
Masao.
Thank you so much.
That's good.
I can talk to you if I wear this.
Thank you so much for today.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
It's been a long time.
I'm going out.
Wow.
You've been standing for a long time.
Hey.
It's still like this.
You can do it one more time, right?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You want to do it, right?
I want to do it.
It's so good.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Masao.
You can go out, right?
Yes.
That's good.
You wanted to do it, right?
I wanted to do it.
Ah.
I'm so sleepy.
It's been a long time.
Ah.
I'm going crazy.
Masao.
Mom.
How do you feel?
It's hot.
Masao.
Are you still not moving enough?
You're getting tired.
It's hot.
Ah.
Look.
It's hot.
Ah.
Masao.
You're sweating a lot.
Ah.
It's hot.
Okay.
Ah.
It's so hot.
It's cold.
I'm going to go.
I'm going.
It's cold.
You're always energetic even though you move so much.
I'm going to go.
I'm going.
It's cold.
What did you do?
I want to make you feel better.
Can I?
Let me go.
It's cold.
How do you feel?
Let me go.
It's cold.
What's this?
I can do it.
It's cold.
How can you do this?
Try to relax.
It's cold.
You must be tired.
Come here.
Okay.
It's cold.
Can I move?
Lie down.
Okay.
It's cold.
It feels good.
It's cold, isn't it?
It's the best.
It feels good.
It's cold.
Can I move?
Are you okay?
It feels good.
It's cold.
Me, too.
I'm sorry.
It's cold.
My body is getting warm.
It feels good.
It's cold.
I'm going to go many times.
Please go many times.
It's cold.
Please go out.
You went out a lot.
Mom.
What are you doing?
Let's go to bed.
It's cold.
It feels good.
I'm sorry for asking you to help me.
It's okay.
It's better to move.
Mom.
What?
Would you like to live with me?
With you?
What's wrong?
It's been three years since my father died.
And...
And?
I'm thinking of having a baby.
That's good.
I think it's safe if you stay with me.
I see.
I'll think about it.
Let's live together.
I see.
But...
Sanae.
What?
Do you get along well with Masao?
Actually...
Not really.
I see.
But I don't hate him.
I like him.
But...
Family is more important to me.
I see.
So, my mom told me...
If I have a baby, I don't have to live with him.
I see.
I want to be like my family.
I think so.
So...
Let's live together.
I'll think about it.
By the way, mom.
I'm going to cook.
I want to eat your cooking.
Okay.
Anything is fine.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to cook.
Okay.
Masao.
What are you doing?
I can't do this anymore.
Why?
Mom was so mean yesterday.
Don't say that.
Oh.
I've never been in such a situation.
Don't say that.
Please.
What?
Please help me.
I can't.
Masao.
Please.
I can't.
I can't help it.
Can I help you?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Masao.
I'm going to put it on the back of my head.
I'm going to put it on my tummy.
I'm going to put it on my chin.
I'm going to put it on my neck.
I'm going to put it on my shoulder.
I'm going to put it on my tailbone.
I'm going to put it on my pants.
I'm going to put it on my socks.
I'm going to put it on my beard.
I'm going to put it on my deadbeat.
I'm going to put it on my shirt.
I'm dying!
Dr.
What?
You're so obsessed.
Are you happy now?
If it's so bad, can I do something I couldn't do before?
What?
I'll go over there.
Wait a minute.
Masao.
Don't come here.
What's that?
Masao.
It's okay.
I don't know what it is.
Wait a minute, Masao.
Masao.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Masao.
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
Masao.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
Masao.
Oh!
Where is it...?
Ohh, it's here!
Wow, it's beautiful.
Wow, it's not over yet!
Where's the scarf?
Oh, oh, oh yeah, yeah...
Yeah!
I'm sorry.
I'm going.
Mom, what's up?
Sanae, can I kiss you?
Yes, I want to eat.
Okay, wait a minute.
Okay.
Mom.
Wait a minute.
Sanae, don't do that.
I'm sorry.
But mom...
I'm in trouble.
Is it painful?
No, it's not.
It's painful.
I'm sorry.
It looks delicious.
How is it?
It's delicious.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad.
It was newly made.
So I bought it.
You're my daughter.
I'm glad you like it.
There are many kinds of sweets.
Let's go together.
I want to go.
Let's go next time.
Let's go.
Mom, I'm going out with Taiko today.
What?
From now on?
Why do you kiss me?
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
What?
It's rude.
It's okay.
But...
I couldn't get this ticket.
I happened to get it this time.
I don't know.
It's okay.
I've been wanting to go with you.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
One day is enough.
It's okay.
Have fun.
You don't have to worry about me.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
I'll buy you something delicious.
Mom, take your time.
Take care.
Thank you.
See you later.
Take care of your mom.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'm glad Sanae went out.
Me, too.
It's such a coincidence.
Yes.
I stopped in the middle of the way.
Don't say that.
I really want you, too.
Masao.
No.
Not here.
Let's go to bed.
Thank you.
Couldn't you stand it?
I couldn't stand it.
Me, too.
Mom.
You wanted to do this, didn't you?
Soran.
Masao.
You're amazing.
I feel so good.
Masao.
Look at me.
I feel so good.
I can't do this.
Masao.
I feel so good.
Wow, it's amazing here.
I can't do it anymore.
You don't need it anymore, do you?
It's so good.
I want to see more.
I want to eat more.
It's so good.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's so good.
Let me take it off.
Let's do it together.
It's so good.
I can't do it anymore.
Look at me.
It's so good.
Do you know I'm crying?
Look at me.
Look deeper.
It's so good.
Look at me.
It feels good.
It's so good.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels good.
Touch me.
It's so good.
Can you see me?
I'm going to cry.
What is this?
No!
Calm down.
You can do it, right?
It feels good, right?
It's amazing.
Take your time.
It feels good, right?
Are you okay?
I want to do more.
I'm scared.
It feels good, right?
It's getting bigger.
I'm going to break.
It's amazing.
It feels good to move together, right?
It feels good, right?
I'm going to break.
It's amazing.
It feels good, right?
If you do that...
It's going to be weird.
No, no, no.
It's amazing.
Look at me.
I'm going to break.
It's amazing.
No, no, no.
Are you okay?
It's amazing.
I'm going to break.
Ehehehe
Ah, where are you?
Ah, gross
Ah, my eyes, my eyes, my eyes
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
I don't want to do this anymore
Ah, ah, ah
It's so gross, I'm going crazy
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
It's so gross
Ah, it's so gross
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
I can't do this anymore
Ah, it's so gross
I'm at my limit
It's fine, it's fine
Just leave me alone
I'm going to cry
Ah, it's so gross
It was great, mom
Me too
Ah, it's so gross
I really
Want to live here with you
I'd love to
Then
Will you do it every day?
Mom
You're still energetic
Look
Ah, it's so gross
It's so gross
Welcome
Ah, it's so gross
I'm going to take it off
Mom is here, right?
Ah, it's so gross
If you want, let's sleep here together