Is it really possible to move?
Wow, there is still luggage here.
What is this?
Oh, this!
It's nostalgic.
Wow, I took this.
Wow, I'm young.
Wow, what is this?
Nostalgic.
This is good.
How much did you take this?
Oh, it's good.
This is really nostalgic.
It was fun at that time.
You don't have to do that anymore.
Why?
Let's watch this.
No, I have to do my homework for manga.
No, I think soccer is more important.
Soccer?
You don't have to do that anymore.
It's okay.
I'm back.
Excuse me.
Welcome, Tetsuya.
What are you doing?
Are you studying?
Yes, I was teaching.
Really? Where were you studying?
I was studying here.
Where did you write your notes?
I was teaching here.
Isn't that Tetsuya's notebook?
I've been teaching here.
But he said he didn't understand at all, so I've been teaching him.
Did you really teach him?
Yes, I did.
But the score of the test was really bad.
I think the range of study was a little wrong.
You can't make such a mistake.
What are you doing?
It was hard to read the characters on the blackboard.
Is that so?
If you can't do it, move to the front seat.
It's hard to say when it's decided.
But if you make a mistake in the range, you can't do it.
That's right.
But it's okay.
You can do it, so let's do our best.
Okay.
It's hard to say when it's decided.
By the way, Tetsuya.
Yes?
Would you like to have dinner with me today?
Is that okay?
Why are you hesitating now?
Let's have dinner together.
Thank you.
I'm going to make dinner, so study hard.
Okay.
This is really fun.
I'm going to make dinner.
Yes.
Tetsuya, it's cold.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What did you do today?
I promised to do my homework with Shio.
I see.
Yocchan hasn't come back yet.
Is that so?
Yes.
Are you waiting for me?
Is that okay?
Yes.
Can I come in?
Would you like to take a break?
Thank you.
But I have to study now.
What are you studying?
I'm studying English now.
I see.
It seems difficult.
I'm not good at English.
I see.
What are you studying?
I'm studying this.
What is this called?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I see.
You want to go to college.
Yes.
You have a year and a half left.
Do your best.
I'm rooting for you.
Thank you.
I wish Yocchan could go to college.
I think she can go to a soccer team.
Is that so?
It's true.
She will be a regular in two years.
Is that so?
I didn't know that.
Don't you know?
She doesn't talk much about school.
I don't know.
I think so.
By the way, how is she doing at school?
What do you mean?
She doesn't bring any friends except Tetsuya.
She doesn't talk to anyone.
I see.
She has more friends than me.
She is reliable.
Is that true?
It's true.
She is popular among girls.
I don't like it.
Is she popular?
She confessed to the cutest girl.
I see.
Does she have a girlfriend?
I don't think so.
She dumped him.
Why?
Isn't she cute?
She is very cute.
She said she wanted to play soccer.
So, she dumped him.
What a waste.
He used a girl for a lifetime.
I know.
I envy him.
I see.
He is popular, too.
I'm glad I'm her childhood friend.
Don't you have a girlfriend?
Me?
Yes.
I don't have a girlfriend.
Really?
You are popular, aren't you?
I'm not popular at all.
I'll keep it a secret.
Tell me.
I'm not popular at all.
I'm serious.
What about your favorite girl?
You have a favorite girl, don't you?
My favorite girl?
Well...
What kind of girl is she?
Is she cute?
Well...
How can I say...
Is she your senior?
Or your classmate?
Well...
She is my senior.
I see.
She is your senior.
What kind of person is she?
Well...
What kind of person...
She is beautiful.
Well...
Yes.
She is beautiful.
Have you ever talked to her?
I've talked to her many times.
I see.
Does she know you like her?
No, I don't think so.
Why don't you ask her out?
Well...
Do you have a boyfriend?
Boyfriend?
Well...
I have a boyfriend.
I see.
But you might change your mind.
Well...
I don't want to break up with her.
Don't say that.
I see.
You might be his girlfriend.
What?
Girlfriend?
Yes.
You should ask her out.
But I don't want to break up with her.
That's not true.
No one likes you.
I see.
Well...
I'll ask her out.
Don't worry.
You can do it.
Hey.
What?
I like you.
Are you practicing?
No.
I like you.
What?
I lied to you today.
I came to see you.
I love you.
I see.
Are you serious?
Yes.
I'm serious.
But I'm an old lady.
I call you an old lady.
But I really like you.
I shouldn't have said that.
I said no.
I lied to you.
I'm sorry.
Are you serious?
Yes.
I'm serious.
I see.
Do you want to go out with me?
Go out with you?
Well...
I don't know.
But I like you.
But you can't go out with me.
I know.
You're married.
You have Yocchan.
Yes.
Don't be depressed.
I'm fine.
Do you want me to be your girlfriend?
Well...
I don't know.
I know.
I forced you to confess your love.
I'll take the responsibility.
What do you mean?
I'll be your girlfriend today.
Are you serious?
Promise me.
Yes.
But you have to find a girlfriend.
I'll be your girlfriend.
Are you serious?
I'll be your girlfriend today.
Thank you.
Do you like her?
Yes.
I love her.
Thank you.
But don't tell anyone.
I won't.
I won't tell anyone.
I'll be your girlfriend today.
Yes.
Give me a kiss.
Give me your tongue.
Are you serious?
I love you.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Let me see your face.
I can't.
You're my girlfriend.
Let me see your face.
I'm embarrassed.
I can't.
You're so big.
I'm embarrassed.
Let me see your butt.
You're so hard.
You're shivering.
Have you ever done this?
No, I haven't.
How do you feel?
You're so big.
You're getting harder.
Do you feel good?
You've never done this before, have you?
Do you want me to do more?
Do you feel comfortable?
You're feeling much better
It feels so good
Are your hands cold?
I feel dizzy.
You did a hard job on that leg
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You're sweating a lot.
I'll clean it for you.
It's not dirty.
It's delicious.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm home.
Wait a minute.
Is Kitsuya here?
Tetsuya.
Why are you here today?
Yocchan, sit here.
Tetsuya, why are you here today?
You asked me to teach you homework.
Did I?
Don't do that.
Don't you sweat a lot?
Let's take a shower.
I've been playing soccer.
I'm sorry.
Hurry up.
Take a shower and clean up.
I got it.
Tetsuya.
I'll keep it a secret from everyone today.
Mom.
I don't have a towel.
This is small.
Let's wash it.
I'm sorry.
I made dinner.
Why are you silent?
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
Is it really okay?
What are you talking about?
You came to me every day.
You asked me so much.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I love you more and more.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to try it?
Please.
I understand.
Is it really okay?
I love you.
Please put your tongue out more.
I'll lick your tongue.
Is it okay?
Come here.
You're amazing.
Your tongue is very hard.
I love you.
You put your tongue out a lot.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to put your tongue out?
Yes.
You want to put your tongue out?
I'll put my tongue out.
I'm going to put it in your mouth.
It's in.
Let's put it in your mouth.
I'm going to put it in your mouth.
Do you know how to put it in your mouth?
Yes.
I'm going to put it in your mouth.
A little more.
Here?
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
How was it?
How did you feel when you had sex for the first time?
It felt really good.
I'm glad you've grown up.
Yes.
There's a lot coming out.
That's amazing.
Ma'am.
What's wrong?
Can't we do it again?
What?
It's true.
It's still standing.
I'm sorry.
Let's do it again until she comes back.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's heavy.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It feels really good.
Does it hurt?
Yes.
That's amazing.
You can touch me.
I'm going to go.
It feels good.
Good job.
How was it?
Relax a little more.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Why?
I told you not to contact me.
I'm sorry.
But I got accepted to the university.
Really?
I'm glad.
I studied hard to meet you.
What?
I'm really into you.
Suddenly?
I want to be with you.
Can't I?
I don't know what to do.
Don't you want to be with me anymore?
No.
I want to celebrate with you.
Celebrating with you is the most important thing for me.
It's the most important thing for me.
Really?
Can't I?
Let's do it.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It feels really good.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
It feels really good.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I want to sleep.
It's okay.
You're really going to celebrate my birthday, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Then, can you do me a favor?
What is it?
I want to do it in person today.
In person?
I want to do it in person.
What should I do?
I wanted to do it with you until recently.
I got accepted to a university today.
I want you to celebrate my birthday.
Then, today is a special day for me.
Really? Thank you.
It's amazing.
I'll do it.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Can I do it?
I don't want you to do it.
I'll do it.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Sumire-san.
What?
Can I do it again?
Sure.
I'm standing up again.
I can't do it like this.
I have to wash it.
But I can't stand it anymore.
I want to do it right away.
It's okay, right?
You felt really good just now.
It felt good, right?
It felt good.
It's okay, right?
It's okay.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It feels good, right?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's okay, right?
It's okay.
It's amazing.
It's really good.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I can see where you went.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
One more time.
Yes.
It's amazing.
I can't believe it.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
I can't do it.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm so full.
Sumire-san, it was so good.
It was good, wasn't it?
Sumire-san's voice was so good.
Really?
You're totally different.
Yeah, totally different.
You're still standing up.
I'm going to stand up.
Let's do it again.
Again?
I want to do it again.
Get up.
Okay.
I'm so full.
It feels so good.
Sumire-san, do you want to take a break?
Okay.
Ouch.
Let's drink.
I'm tired.
Ouch.
I'm still standing up.
Can I do it again?
Let's do it.
Let's drink.
It feels so good.
I can feel it.
Let me do it.
Sumire-san.
What?
Let's do that.
The one you always do.
I want to do this.
What?
This?
Chinchin.
Chinchin?
Yes.
I see.
But that makes me excited.
So, I want you to use that to make me excited.
I want you to use Chinchin.
What's that?
Isn't it good?
Let me do it.
I want you to use this to make me excited.
You are so good.
You are pulling a lot of strings.
It feels so good.
You are about to cry.
It hurts.
Let me do it.
Okay.
I want you to use this to make me excited.
You are about to cry.
You are pulling a lot of strings.
I want you to use this to make me excited.
You are so good.
You are pulling a lot of strings.
I'm just touching you.
Do you want me to do it quickly?
You are pulling a lot of strings.
You are about to cry.
Let me give you a hand.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
You can still do it.
You are about to cry.
I can't do it.
It hurts a lot.
Let me give you a hand.
You are about to cry.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
What?
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
What?
Your phone is ringing.
I don't care about the phone.
You should have left it on.
What?
You did it.
You were so excited.
I can't do it.
Hurry up.
Your phone is ringing.
You left it on.
I don't care about the phone.
Wait a minute.
What?
Your husband called you.
Is he your husband?
Wait a minute.
Your phone is ringing.
Hello?
Where are you?
I'm shopping.
What?
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
I'll go home now.
What?
Are you okay?
I'm okay, but I'm going home today.
Are you going home?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm going home.
I see.
Don't worry about me.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'm fine.
I'll pay for it.
Thank you.
See you.
What should I do?
You're moving to my house, aren't you?
What are you doing?
It's not a big deal.
Look at this.
Come here.
Don't you miss this?
Did you take a picture of this?
I took a picture of this.
When was this?
You're so young.
I'm going to wear this.
Your butt is the best.
It's amazing.
You're so cute now.
I was surprised when I saw this.
You were with her yesterday, weren't you?
Yes, I was.
You have a good taste.
Really?
Did you go out with her yesterday?
Yes, I did.
Did you?
Yes.
Did you get along with her?
Yes, we did.
Really?
Can I get along with you today?
Sure.
Let's get along with each other.
I want to.
Do you?
Let's do that.
Let's get along with each other.
Oh, you are sleepy.
I can't talk to her.
I don't know what to do.
Stand up.
Where is your nipple?
Where is it?
How long have you been wearing this?
I've been wearing it since today.
Don't you wear it in front of your mother?
I don't wear it.
Only today?
I don't know what to do.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Ahh.
Ay...
You're baby sleepy.
You want to wash your face.
I'm going to sleep.
Are you sleepy?
Yes, I'm sleepy.
You are very sleepy.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I can't.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
I can't.
Do you let her lick you like this?
She is not good at it.
Really?
She doesn't feel good at all.
I'll make you feel good.
Really?
I'll put this in your mouth.
Wow.
This is really good.
It's big, so it's painful.
Is it painful?
I feel good.
This is amazing.
I'm sorry.
I'll put this in your mouth.
I feel good.
Do you want me to touch you?
Please touch me.
Please spread your butt.
That's right.
You're mumbling a lot.
I feel good.
No!
Go!
I feel good.
Do you want me to do more?
No!
I feel good.
You're mumbling a lot.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
You feel good when you sleep with your husband.
Are you going to be so hard on your girlfriend?
I'm not.
Are you sure?
I'm not going to be so hard on my girlfriend.
I'm not a man like you.
I feel good.
You're mumbling a lot.
Do you want me to do more?
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
You really want me to do more.
You can kiss your husband.
No, I want to kiss you.
You want me to kiss you?
I feel good.
Which one do you like better, your girlfriend or your boobs?
Your boobs.
I feel good.
You like to kiss from behind.
Do you want me to do it?
You are really good at kissing.
Can I take off the pillow?
I feel good.
Do you want me to do it?
Ah, this feels so good.
Ah, no, no.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Ah, this is amazing.
Ah!
No!
I can't stop!
Ah!
Presentation of the area.
It's safe.
Taniguchi-san?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Well.
so baby-like
it's so nice
my booty's feelin' good
More! More!
More!
You are really sleepy, aren't you?
No! No!
Amazing!
More! More!
I feel great!
You are really sleepy, aren't you?
I'm sweating a lot!
You are sweating a lot, aren't you?
It feels so good!
Sumire-san, look at this!
It's a boob!
It feels so good!
Look at this!
You are really cute!
You are too cute!
You are so sleepy!
Amazing!
It feels so good!
It's going to reach your tongue, isn't it?
Umm?
Feelings!
Yeah?
It feels so good!
Mama, does it feel good ?
Good!
Do you want to pee?
Yes!
Show me your belly button.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I can't do it.
I'm going to die.
It feels good.
What are you going to do with the other person?
I'm going to sleep with my girlfriend.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Let me out.
I'm sorry.
I felt great.
I felt great, too.
Can you do me a favor?
What is it?
Do you want to do it again?
Again?
Don't you want to do it?
I want to do it, but...
Let's do it.
You said you felt great.
But you said you were exhausted.
That's why I was very exhausted.
You're still standing.
You're so erotic.
Push in the back of your pants.
You're full of energy.
You've done it.
That's right.
But you want to do this, don't you?
I want to.
I'll do it.
Hurry up!
How long are you going to stay like this?
I'm going to stay like this until the morning.
So, give me a lot.
Give me a lot.
Thank you for watching!