Thank you for your viewing.
Please subscribe if you like.
Excuse me.
Are you going on a trip?
I want to see Mt. Fuji.
Are you going to climb?
No, if I can see it up close.
It's nice here, isn't it?
I like it too.
Let's go a little closer.
It's a typhoon, so you shouldn't go.
Let's go to the hotel by car.
I haven't decided the hotel.
You haven't decided?
Really?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to the hotel.
Thank you very much.
There was a cancellation in my uncle's rental villa.
So I'm going to the hotel by car.
But it's okay.
I can't leave you alone.
I'm Kasumi.
How about you?
I'm Tatsu.
Let's go.
Follow me.
There's no one here, so don't worry.
I'm free today.
I'll explain the room to you.
This is the air conditioner.
Thank you very much.
Sit down.
I was working.
So I have to go back.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You don't look well.
I have a lot of things to do.
Are you depressed?
I'm fine.
I'm going back to work.
Really?
Yes.
Why did you go there?
I want to talk to you.
You don't look well.
Are you teasing me?
I'm not teasing you.
You don't look well.
I just did it.
I'm worried about you.
I have something to tell you.
Let's stay together a little longer.
You are kind.
I'm sorry.
Don't you want to go back to work?
I want to be healthy.
You are cold.
I'm fine.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm going to put a towel on your back.
It's comfortable.
You can't take it off by yourself.
I'm going to put a towel on your back.
Does your back hurt?
No.
I'm fine.
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
Then let's go to work.
Are you going to work?
Are you feeling better?
No.
Then let's go to work.
My legs hurt.
I'm going to put a towel on your back.
It's comfortable.
What are you doing?
I was wondering which one would be more energetic.
I'm going to put a towel on your back.
Do you like my neck?
It's comfortable, isn't it?
I'm going to put a towel on your back.
Do you like to be bitten?
I've never been bitten.
I don't know.
You don't know?
Your legs are moving.
I'm going to put a towel on your back.
I haven't told you what I'm going to do yet.
Don't get up.
Thank you.
I'm going to put a towel on your back.
It's big.
It's not a big deal.
I'm going to put a towel on your back.
It's hard.
Is it hard?
It's really hard.
It's hard.
It's a nice picture.
I'm going to put a towel on your back.
It smells good.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm going to put a towel on your back.
You're amazing.
You're so big.
You're just sleeping.
What's this?
You're sucking.
You're so erotic.
I'm embarrassed.
Where do you remember this?
You're so erotic.
I feel good.
I'm going to put a towel on your back.
You can't do that.
You're eating.
I'm going to put a towel on your back.
You can't do that.
It's so good.
Are you sleepy?
I'm so tired...
This is the last one...
This was really delicious alone.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
I can't eat it.
I can eat it.
I can't eat meat.
You can't eat meat?
You can't eat it?
Oh, my God.
I can't eat it.
You can do anything.
That's amazing.
I can't eat it.
I'm feeling better.
Thanks to you.
My back is moving.
I can't eat it.
You can do it.
You're getting softer.
You like my boobs, don't you?
I like it.
You look very happy.
You like my boobs, don't you?
I like it.
I'm getting softer.
You're trying to make me feel better.
I'm not feeling better yet.
I'm going to puke.
I can't.
Hang in there.
You can do it.
I can't breathe.
You don't have to come this far.
I want to do it.
Let's do it.
It's amazing.
You can do it.
I want to do it.
I don't want to do it.
You can't do it.
I can't do it.
You want to do it, don't you?
You can't do it.
Let's do it.
It feels good.
You're a man.
It's hard, isn't it?
Hang in there.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
You're very sensitive.
It feels good.
You can do it.
Are you okay?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's okay.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Are you going to sleep?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
How do you feel?
I understand.
It's hard.
It feels good.
It sounds like a dog.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
It feels good.
It's warm.
You've got a lot on your face.
You're not angry.
Why?
Are you angry?
I'm not angry.
I have to go to work.
I'm sorry.
There's one here.
Can I have some tea?
I want to drink tea, too.
I'm going back to work.
I have a lot of work to do.
I'll be back soon.
I'll buy you dinner after work.
Don't get sick until then.
Take care of yourself.
Be careful.
I'm home.
I bought you dinner.
I bought you a drink, too.
Thank you.
I don't think it's strong.
I like it.
Cheers.
It's peach.
It's delicious.
Do you want to eat more?
It's been a while since I ate it.
Why were you there?
I've been there a lot.
I'm walking around there.
Some people are taking pictures.
I'm disappointed in you.
I'll open this.
It's amazing.
It's in there.
It's cute.
Is it easy to drink?
It's delicious.
What?
I heard something.
Is that so?
I was wondering why you were there.
I don't know.
I want to do it anywhere.
What?
Not only at home.
I want to do it outside, too.
What?
It's erotic.
Is that the reason?
Why?
It's nice.
I did it in a strange place.
I don't think it's erotic.
Really?
It's erotic.
I'm in a bad mood.
I don't think it's erotic.
Have you ever done it?
Then, what is it?
What is it?
I've been drinking a lot.
I can't drink anymore.
I'm getting red.
It's on my stomach.
It's okay.
It's like a breast.
This is a real breast.
I don't know which one you feel.
Be careful.
Don't drink too much.
Do you like alcohol?
It's not erotic.
You're getting red.
Open your cheeks.
What are you shooting?
Do you want to take a picture with me?
You're getting red.
Cheese.
Your eyes are red.
You're getting red.
I'll send you to a strange place.
Don't erase it.
It's going to open.
I have something to take.
What is it?
Doburoku.
What is Doburoku?
It's sweet sake.
It's delicious.
It's not delicious, is it?
Your face.
You're biting.
It's delicious.
You don't lose weight at all.
You ate a lot.
I don't lose weight when I eat.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Be careful.
What?
Are you going to the bathroom?
Can't you go?
I can go.
What is this?
It's a break.
Here?
It's cold.
Which part do you bite?
I don't know.
From the right.
It feels good.
You have a lot of teeth.
I have a lot of teeth.
Left.
Which part do you bite?
Right?
It tastes good.
It's cold.
Your lips are warm.
My lips are warm.
Don't you go to the bathroom?
What?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
It feels good.
Which part do you bite?
I like both.
Do you like both?
You like both.
Your voice is erotic.
How do you feel?
I like both.
You sound like a queen.
Are you okay?
I like both.
Are you sure?
You sound like a queen.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You sound like a queen.
It's snowing.
Whoa, whoa, whoa ,...
Are you alright?
Oh, no, no...
Look,
It's hot.
What should I do?
I don't know.
I don't like it.
It's hot.
I like it.
I don't like it.
It's hot.
I like soft things.
I like it when it gets bigger in my mouth.
It's hot.
It's getting bigger.
It's okay.
I won't let you go.
You're still breathing, aren't you?
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
You like it, don't you?
It's hot.
You can lie down.
Your head hurts, doesn't it?
I'll give you a lot of medicine.
I'm going to get a shot.
I can't stand it.
It's hot.
You're about to cry.
I want to give you a shot.
I'll give you a lot of medicine.
It's hot.
I'll give you a shot.
My left hand is strong, too.
I'll do my best.
I think I'm strong.
It's hot.
I'm going to give you a shot.
Can I give you a shot?
Please.
What are you talking about?
It's dangerous.
Look at me.
I'm lonely.
It's hot.
I want to lick your buttocks.
No?
Please.
What are you talking about?
I want to lick your buttocks.
Please.
Me?
Yes, me.
That's amazing.
Are you okay?
I'm not angry.
It's okay.
I'll take responsibility.
Tell me if you don't like it.
It's hot.
Why are you moving?
You're a good boy.
You feel good, don't you?
Because I'm so close to you.
I feel good.
Do you know what it's called?
It's okay.
Let's do this.
Are you okay?
I feel good.
It's delicious.
It smells sweet.
Your butt is wet.
You're a good boy.
Look at me.
I love you.
Do you love me?
He fell asleep.
Are you okay?
Do you feel better with your eyes closed?
Please.
Are you okay?
You have a cute face.
Is this a video?
You're so shy.
Do you want to get up?
You're cute.
You're cool.
You've changed.
You're sleepy?
Did you like this side better?
You've got more confused, haven't you?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Hey, I'm the only one who's got a toothache.
Give it to me.
No!
What are you going to do? I haven't drunk it yet.
I drank a lot.
Where are you going?
It feels good.
I want to go out.
I want to go out a lot.
It feels good.
Give it to me.
It's my sister.
It feels good.
I love you.
Give it to me.
It feels good.
I'm drunk.
I'm not cute.
It feels good.
Give it to me.
I haven't drunk it yet.
It feels good.
Let's feel good together.
I want you to tickle me.
Please tickle me.
I want to go out.
I love you.
Good morning.
I bought bread.
Which one do you like?
Croquette.
I like yakisoba.
I don't eat sweets.
Is it the same?
Sometimes.
I'm curious about this.
I used to eat it when I was a kid.
Which one is the same?
A and B.
I hated cream bread when I was a kid.
Can I eat it now?
No, you can't.
It might be delicious.
I'll bring coffee.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
How is it?
I don't know.
I don't know what to say.
I want to eat it.
I think it's better than delicious.
Do I have to drink coffee?
I think it's just right.
What time is it now?
What?
I don't have a battery.
What's wrong?
I have to go.
Are you going to your girlfriend's house?
Can I stay a little longer?
It's a good sound, isn't it?
Don't get up.
Your legs are moving.
Your hands are moving.
You can't get up.
Are you checking yourself?
You're a good boy.
You're happier to be called a good boy.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
I have to go.
Don't do that.
Are you going?
Let me see.
Do what makes you feel good.
Here.
Here?
A little more.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Do you feel good?
It's hot.
I'm just touching you gently.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
Which one should I do?
This one?
If you lick my nipples, I'll go wild.
I'm afraid you'll go wild.
I'm not going wild.
It's hot.
Don't move your legs.
It's disgusting.
It's hot.
What's this?
It's disgusting.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
I was wondering what to do.
I was wondering how to take care of you.
Will you take care of me?
I'm taking care of you.
You're a good boy.
You have a lot of hair.
It's difficult.
I wonder if it'll get bigger.
It's hot.
Don't you like it?
Put your head on it.
You don't like it, do you?
I'll give you a body that you shouldn't have.
It's hot.
It's disgusting.
I'll give you a scalp.
Your scalp is disgusting.
It's hot.
Does your head feel good?
What did you do?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Concentrate.
There's something in your head.
There's something in my head.
I don't know.
It's hot.
It's embarrassing.
It feels good.
It's hot.
You have a lot of hair.
It's disgusting.
Do you want to be a girl?
It's hot.
Don't you forget me?
I can't touch you anymore.
Don't move.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Don't move.
I'll fall.
I'll get hurt.
Will you take responsibility?
I'm asking you.
It's hot.
I know.
You're in trouble.
It's hot.
You have a lot of hair.
What's that hand?
Are you embarrassed?
You have a lot of hair.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You have a lot of hair.
Does it feel good?
You'll feel better if I comb your hair.
You're about to die.
Hang in there.
Don't you touch your favorite nipple?
Why?
It's hot.
It's done.
It feels good.
I know.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
You wanted to get up, didn't you?
It's hot.
I think it feels good.
I'll give you a massage.
You really like nipples.
It's hot.
Look at me.
What are you going to do?
It's hot.
I know you don't have to touch your nipples.
I want to touch your nipples.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
I didn't touch your nipples.
It tickles.
It tickles, doesn't it?
It's delicious, isn't it?
Give me a kiss.
I can't help but kiss you.
Why are you trying to go without permission?
I'm closing my legs.
It's hot.
What are you going to do?
It hurts.
What?
What are you doing?
It's cute.
It's cold.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's delicious.
It's hot.
I love you.
It's cute.
It's hot.
I want to sleep.
Anything.
Anything?
Let's go to bed.
We're going home.
Open your eyes.
What?
What's wrong with you?
I want to sleep.
You don't want to sleep, do you?
I'm going to sleep.
If you sleep, you'll feel so good that you won't be able to go anywhere.
I'm not in the room yet.
I'm just checking the entrance.
What do you want me to put in?
Why are your eyes so hard?
You can't sleep.
Are you in there?
It feels good.
Why are you moving it?
It's amazing.
It feels good.
You're getting softer.
You don't want me to touch you?
You like the tip of my hand.
Hang in there.
You're acting like a baby.
Let's go down.
Do you want me to lick your ears?
Let me see your ears.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
You're big.
It's hot.
I'm so happy.
I feel good.
What?
You feel good, don't you?
Are you going to go?
It's like you're growing up.
It's not a kiss.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's like a baby.
It's hot.
I feel good.
I love you.
It's getting hot Seri's body was burning
have to lie down
Well let's lie down
And yesterday, we played back the video we took.
Why are you running away?
Don't touch anything. I'm just touch your butt.
Are you really going?
It's going to rain, so wear an umbrella.
Thank you for everything.
You can take a bath.
Well, thank you.
Thank you for watching.