For me, It's time to go.
Yuka is gone.
To the living room
Good morning
You're late.
What? I'm only five minutes late.
I'm going to tell you something special.
It's normal to be 15 minutes early on the first day of work.
I'm sorry.
You're the youngest, aren't you?
What?
By the way, you have a sweet tooth.
I'm sorry.
You're Yuuki.
I'll call you Yu-kun.
Yes.
What's your name?
Kaze?
I'm Kaede.
I'm Kaede Fuwa.
I'm Kaede. Nice to meet you.
I'm going to practice before I start my business.
Wait here.
Yes.
I'm going to practice before I start my business.
Do you often go to other restaurants?
No, I don't.
Then, I'll buy you a drink today.
I see.
Do you like alcohol?
Thank you very much.
It's hard for me to get in.
I see.
Then, please come to my restaurant again.
Thank you.
Whiskey has a deep taste because it is shaved with ice.
Is that so?
Yes.
Do you want to make the same whiskey?
I'll buy the same whiskey.
Yu-kun.
Yes.
How long have you been working here?
It will be two weeks soon.
Then, Yu-kun will make this order.
Me?
Is it okay?
Fuwa is good at reading whiskey while taking a break and making cocktails after closing.
Then, I'll do my best.
Thank you for waiting.
Your hands are shaking.
I'm sorry.
It's good.
Is that so?
I'm studying hard.
I see.
Yes.
Then, I'm leaving.
Thank you very much.
Hey.
Yes.
Can I have some water?
Sure.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
It's cold.
I'll wipe it right away.
It's a little wet.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
It's okay.
I'll wipe it.
You don't have to do it.
Okay.
It's a little wet.
I'll wipe it properly when I get home.
I'm sorry.
I'll wipe this side, too.
Thank you very much.
I see.
Yes.
I'll wipe this side, too.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
I'll wipe this side, too.
Okay.
I'll walk you to the exit.
Really?
Yes.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'll walk you to the exit.
Are you okay?
I'll walk you.
Kaede.
I'm really sorry for today.
It's okay.
Sometimes bad customers come.
Kaede is the same age as me, but she is an adult.
Yuu is too young.
There must be someone who is in a good relationship with Kaede.
But I can't leave a cute person like Yuu.
By the way, is there anyone who is in a good relationship with Kaede?
Fumiko hasn't been in a relationship for about two years.
If she is a senior, she will be confessed.
Then, will Yuu confess to me?
Don't make fun of me.
By the way, I'm annoyed.
Do you still have a grudge?
Of course.
I'm jealous of you.
Really?
Yuu is funny.
What?
Fumiko.
Your tights are torn.
What?
No way.
I don't want to take the train anymore.
Can I do something about it?
Please do something.
Can I do something?
I can't move this.
Can you open your legs?
I'm sorry.
I'm like a pervert.
It's been a while since I was touched, so I feel strange.
Let's go home.
Yuu, don't do that.
Fumiko, can I be spoiled?
Yuu.
I want to sit on your lap.
What's wrong?
Please let me go.
I'm embarrassed.
You're beautiful.
Don't look down on me.
Please don't look down on me.
I'm fine.
It tickles.
I'm sorry.
I smell something strange.
It doesn't smell strange at all.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
You have beautiful legs.
Do you like my legs so much?
I've never seen such beautiful legs.
You're a maniac.
No, I'm not.
Your legs are beautiful.
Your legs tickle.
I want you to play with me.
Do you want me to play with you?
It tickles.
Do you want to drink this?
Yes, please.
Don't smell it.
It smells good.
I don't want to smell it.
Yu-kun.
Look behind you.
Behind me?
Yes.
Like this?
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
You have beautiful hips.
No, I don't.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
My legs hurt.
Your legs?
Can I rub your legs?
What?
Where?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
How do you feel?
It tickles.
Yu-kun.
It tickles, doesn't it?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It tickles.
It's getting harder.
Here.
I'm sorry.
Behind you.
What?
Do you want me to rub your legs?
Yes.
It tickles.
It tickles, doesn't it?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It tickles.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It tickles.
Like this?
Yes.
It tickles.
Does it feel good?
My legs are shaking.
It tickles.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It tickles.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's getting harder and harder.
Senpai.
Did you have a heart attack?
No.
I'm sorry.
Senpai.
Your underwear is very sexy.
I'm embarrassed.
But I want to wear it.
Please open your legs.
I'm sorry.
You smell like Senpai.
Thank you very much.
No...
I can't get up.
Don't run away.
I'm embarrassed.
I can't get up.
It feels so good.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm crying.
I'll make you feel better.
Yes, I want you to do that.
It's hot.
Yes.
It feels so good.
I'll make you feel better with my feet.
How do you feel?
It feels so good.
You like my feet, don't you?
I love it.
My feet are getting harder and harder.
Does it still feel good?
Yes.
It feels so good.
Did you want me to do this all the time?
Yes.
Are you getting excited?
I'm getting excited.
It feels so good.
Yes.
Does it still feel good?
It feels so good.
I can't stand it anymore.
Do you want to do it?
Yes.
Can I do it?
Can I?
It's special.
I want to do it with your feet.
Please look back.
It feels so good.
Can I do it?
Yes.
It feels so good.
Can you raise your legs?
Yes.
It feels so good.
I can't stand it anymore.
Can you raise your legs?
Yes.
Can I look at your feet?
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels so good.
I can't stand it anymore.
I can't do it anymore.
It's okay.
Can I do it from behind?
No.
I can't do it anymore.
Yu-kun, hit me hard.
Too hard?
I understand.
I feel sick.
Do you feel sick?
It's too hard.
Help me.
I feel sick.
It's too hard.
Senpai said it's better to be hard.
I feel sick.
I can't do it anymore.
It's too hard.
I feel sick.
Yu-kun, I feel sick.
Senpai, you don't have to feel sick.
You don't have to feel sick.
I feel sick.
Help me.
I'll clean it up.
I feel sick.
The stocking is getting worse.
I'm sorry.
I wish I had a secretary like Fuwa-chan in my office.
Saotome-san, you play golf all the time.
Come to my office next time.
It's okay, but it's expensive.
Saotome-san, let's make a new drink.
Your new part-time job is going well.
Thanks to you.
You're after Fuwa-chan, aren't you?
If you touch him, I'll get angry.
He's still a baby.
I'll have a whiskey rock.
I'll have a cherry liqueur.
Thank you.
Yuu-kun, I think there's a cherry liqueur downstairs.
Can you find it for me?
Yes, I understand.
I'm looking forward to going to the condo with a new driver.
How much can you fly?
Saotome-san, you're good at it.
I have a day off at the end of the month.
You should go.
Really?
But Saotome-san, you have a girlfriend.
It's okay.
Are you sure?
I'll make time for Fuwa-chan.
Really?
How's the company going?
It's going well.
There's a lot I can't talk about.
That's great.
Is Yuu-kun here?
I'm sorry, I'll look for him.
It's a secret, but...
I'm making a reservation for dinner.
I don't have anyone to invite.
Are you inviting your friends?
No, I'm not.
Isn't there anyone nice?
I see.
I know a lot of people who are interested in Fuwa-chan.
Do you want me to introduce her?
Yes, please.
I'll tell her.
Okay.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I'm fine.
She's a really nice girl.
I think she's back.
She comes to my house a lot.
Is it okay if I don't go home yet?
It's over.
You're a strong drinker, aren't you?
I guess so.
How about you, Fuwa-chan?
I'm not that strong.
You seem to make a lot of mistakes.
I drink too much.
Isn't it dangerous if you drink too much?
What do you mean?
It's dangerous.
What are you doing tomorrow afternoon?
I'll take a rest at home tomorrow.
With your girlfriend?
I'm planning to get married soon.
That's great.
I'm wondering when I'll propose to her.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
It's hard to decide.
How about next month?
Next month?
What kind of proposal would you like to have?
Me?
I...
I don't know.
I want to have a surprise dinner.
A surprise dinner?
With a ring?
Yes.
Saotome-san is popular.
I'm sure your girlfriend is worried about you.
I've been with her for a long time.
We have a good relationship.
I see.
Is my house near here?
There are a few trains.
Is that so?
It's still okay.
Is there something on the floor?
Yes, it's a mess.
Don't worry about it.
Please bring your friends to this bar next time.
I will.
I've been talking a lot about you.
Please don't.
Everyone wants to see you.
I don't know what to do.
I like this atmosphere.
I want to be alone.
That's my request.
Please bring your friends.
I'll be in trouble.
I'll bring my friends one by one next time.
I'll bring my friends once a week.
Please.
What do you do on weekends?
Me?
I watch movies at home.
Movies?
Yes, movies.
Do you watch Japanese movies or American movies?
I watch Japanese movies.
Do you watch Korean movies or American movies?
I don't watch romantic movies.
Korean movies have the image of romantic movies.
There are many.
I think there are many other movies.
I think so, too.
I watch a lot of movies.
Please recommend me a movie.
Okay.
What's this?
You have beautiful fingers.
Nail polish?
It's cute, isn't it?
It's cute.
Don't you have a girlfriend?
I have a girlfriend when I go out.
I see.
Are you okay?
You look strange.
I didn't sleep well last night.
I'm sorry.
Don't you have a pet?
I'm thinking of getting a dog.
Do you like dogs?
I have a dog.
Do you?
I'm thinking of getting a dog.
It's cute, isn't it?
My legs are shaking.
I live in Melania.
Was it hard to clean the toilet?
You have to go to many places at first.
It was a little hard.
But I'm glad you remember it.
It's cute.
What do you remember about gay people?
Sit down.
Hello.
I'm sorry.
Yuki.
Don't come to the store.
Ayate will come to me.
What if she finds out?
I want to make fun of you in front of her.
You are distorted.
I'm sorry.
I was in front of you.
So what?
You were in front of me.
You were very wet.
Do you do that?
It's the same.
I'm sorry.
What if she comes back?
It's okay.
It's quiet.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
Senpai.
If you make a lot of noise, she will find out.
I want you to feel good.
I feel good?
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
I'm sorry.
Senpai.
Do you like this?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
Where is Fuwa?
I'm reporting the sales to the owner of the backyard.
I ordered a whiskey lobster.
Fuwa is making a backyard.
Please wait a moment.
Yes.
Senpai is doing it.
I'm sorry.
I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's
true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not.
I've finished the toilet cleaning.
Thank you for your hard work.
What are you doing?
Keep it a secret.
What's your secret?
Oh, I see. You're a man, right?
What?
Why did you find out?
What? Are you serious?
You found out.
What?
Are you really serious?
The other day, I asked Mr. Saotome to take me to dinner.
He introduced me to his co-worker.
He said he's a great guy.
What?
Are you texting him?
You're not allowed to use your cell phone during business hours.
You're so mean.
I got it.
I'll go check the bathroom.
It's clean.
What?
Have you been there all the time?
No.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Are you jealous of me?
No, I'm not.
You're cute.
Are you jealous?
No, I'm not.
Can I go out with him?
No, you can't.
You don't want to?
No.
You're cute.
What?
You can say that?
You're cute.
You're cute, so I want to tease you.
Tease me?
Yes.
Can I touch you?
No, you can't.
You have a customer.
I'm fine.
Really?
Don't you want to be alone with me?
No, I don't.
Okay.
You're standing up, right?
Yes.
Why are you standing up?
Because it's refreshing.
Can I touch you?
Yes.
Can I kiss you?
I want to kiss you.
You're cute, so I don't mind.
Okay.
Can I kiss you?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
I'll massage your mouth.
Okay.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Do you want me to massage your hips?
Hips?
Okay.
How do you feel?
It's hot.
Do you like my legs?
I love them.
Do you want me to massage your legs?
Yes.
How do you feel?
It's hot.
Do you like my legs?
Yes.
It's hot.
Do you like my legs?
Yes.
It's hot.
Do you like my legs?
Look this way.
This way.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
You're getting bigger.
It's hot.
Are you scared?
Yes.
It's hot.
You're getting bigger.
Do you want me to massage your legs?
Yes.
Do you like my legs?
It's hot.
Do you want me to massage your legs?
Do you like my legs?
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Do you want me to massage your legs?
Yes.
If you feel better, I'll think about it.
Okay.
It's hot.
It looks good on you.
It's annoying.
Can I massage your legs?
Can I?
It's hot.
You have beautiful legs.
Please show me your fingers.
It's embarrassing.
You've been to a lot of places.
It's hot.
You have beautiful legs.
Senpai.
I want you to massage my legs.
Do you want me to massage your legs?
Can I?
If you say so.
It's hot.
Do you want to be bullied like this?
Yes.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's hot.
It's getting harder.
Yes.
Do you want to be stepped on like this?
I'll step on you a lot.
It feels good.
Like this?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I got too excited when I looked at your face.
It's hot.
It's shaking a lot.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Does it feel good inside?
Yes.
Do you want to be stepped on a lot?
It's hot.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's shaking a lot.
It's hot.
I'm going to cry.
Did you say that to me?
I'm glad.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Do you like this?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Ouch!
Please don't go anywhere.
I hope you feel better.
I don't want to.
I want you to let me go.
Really?
Ouch!
I hope you get well soon.
I hope so, too.
Ouch!
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
Ouch!
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
Ouch!
You did it, didn't you?
Please don't go anywhere.
You're so cute.
I hope you don't go anywhere.
Okay?
Ouch!
Good morning, Senpai.
Good morning, Yu-kun.
Your outfit today is so cute.
I love girls who look good in that kind of outfit.
Is that so?
Senpai, if you have any worries, please tell me.
Oh, right.
When you finish your part-time job,
why don't you come to my room?
Yu-kun, actually,
I've decided to go out with you.
What?
Mr. Sawatome, who I told you before,
wants me to go out with him
on the pretext of our marriage.
No way.
So, I can't go out with you like I used to.
No, I can't go out with you anymore.
No, I don't want to.
I'll be back soon.
What's wrong?
I really don't want to go out with you.
Don't say that.
You're too strong.
Senpai,
I can't bear
to see you being
raised by someone else.
Senpai, please.
Yoshi-kun, please support me.
I can't, Senpai.
Hey, Yoshi-kun.
I'm sorry.
Senpai.
Hey, Yoshi-kun.
Yoshi-kun.
Hey, stop it.
Senpai, your beautiful legs.
Your soft thighs.
I don't want anyone
to touch these tights.
They're dirty.
Your legs
aren't dirty.
Do you like my legs that much?
They're normal, aren't they?
Your legs
are so beautiful.
I love them.
I'm sorry.
No one's here yet?
Are you okay?
I'm so happy.
Senpai.
Senpai's legs
are so beautiful.
Do you like my legs that much?
I love them.
Senpai.
Do you want me to hug you?
I want you to hug me.
I'm going to bed.
Okay.
Senpai,
my legs
are so comfortable.
Why are they so stiff?
Because of you.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels really good.
Do you want me to do it faster?
Yes.
Raise your head.
Senpai,
my legs are so comfortable.
Do you want me to hug you?
Yes.
I love you.
Your legs are so stiff.
Do you want me to lick them?
Yes, I want you to lick them.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Ouch.
Do you want me to do it faster?
Senpai.
Ouch.
It feels good.
Do you want me to do it faster?
Yes, I want you to do it faster.
Ouch.
Senpai,
please stand up and talk to me.
I can't help it.
Ouch.
Senpai,
your legs are so beautiful.
Ouch.
My head hurts.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Ouch.
I want to
take care of you.
Do you want me to do it faster?
Yes.
Ouch.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
That's enough.
Ouch.
It feels good.
I want you to do it faster.
Do you want me to do it faster?
Yes.
Your legs are so beautiful.
I can't help it.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Ouch.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Ouch.
Does it feel good?
Your legs are so beautiful.
I can't help it.
Wow.
Your legs are so wet.
Ouch.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Ouch.
I can't help it.
You can't?
It feels so good.
Ouch.
I can't help it.
Do you want to sleep?
Yes.
Can I?
Do you want to feel good?
Yes.
Do you want to sleep?
Ouch.
I can't help it.
It's quite hot.
I can't get it to go away.
Ouch!
Honey, ouch!
I have a burning sensation today.
Why did Senpai say such a thing?
I'm scared.
I want to fly to the earth.
I can't do that.
I'm scared.
I want Senpai to move too.
Ah, it feels good.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'm getting stiff.
Ah, Senpai.
Are you looking at it properly?
Yes.
Senpai.
It's the one that just came in.
Ah, Senpai.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I feel like I'm going to fly away in Senpai's legs.
It feels good.
Are you going to fly away?
I feel like I'm going to fly away.
You can't fly away yet.
It doesn't feel good at all.
It doesn't feel good.
Senpai is gentle.
It feels good.
It doesn't feel good at all.
It doesn't feel good.
It feels good.
I want to make Senpai feel good.
Senpai, make me feel good.
It doesn't feel good.
I'm going.
It feels good.
It doesn't feel good.
I'm going.
How many more days?
I'll tell you when I find out.
It's...
too soon.
I don't want to go to court.
It'll probably cure her.
I'm going to pretend to be sick.
Well?
I appreciate you.
Here you go.
It feels good.
The moon is shining.
It looks painful.
Let me go.
It hurts.
You have a lot of bruises.
Let me clean them.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It looks painful.
Senpai.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
I'm a boy.
If you decide...
It hurts.
Thank you for watching!