The next day
Excuse me
Please cool it down first
Do you want this one as well?
Then, I'll have the lunch set
Yes, the lunch set with tarako pasta B
I see
Please wait a moment
The next day
Nana-chan
Yes
Tarako pasta is on Tuesday, isn't it?
Is it Wednesday today?
It's Saturday today
Nana-chan, you are a student
You don't have lunch on weekdays
What should I do?
What do you mean?
I've warned you many times not to serve lunch on weekdays
You can't do that
Manager, please don't be mad at Nana
Nana-chan
Nana, are you okay?
Manager, it's too much to lecture in the store
Nana-chan, I'm sorry
It's my fault
Don't cry
Hey, Nana-chan
You are laughing
Don't imitate crying
Manager, your reaction is funny
Manager, you are underestimating me
Nana-chan, whatever it is
Please tell the customers about the menu
I see
Then
I can finally drink alcohol
If you take me to drink, I'll do it
Why?
It's your mistake
What about me?
It's all your fault
That's right
Why are you so arrogant?
I got it
Please tell the customers
I did it
It's your treat tonight
Please invite Takahashi-san
Why do we have to go together?
It's dangerous to go alone with Nana-chan
I'll go with you as a guardian
It's strange
I don't get paid as much as you think
I'm looking forward to the store
I did it
Thank you
The next day
We're tired
I want to go to a cake shop in front of the station
Let's go
Let's go together when the time is over
I want to go next year
I want to go
Wait a minute
Wait
I'm not in the mood
I see
Let's go to a cafe next time
Let's go on Saturday
Let's go
It's the same place
It's the same
Let's go together when the time is over
Let's go
What should we drink next?
I want to drink like you
I've never drunk this
I'll make it my own someday
What's this?
It's not ready yet
The alcohol is strong
It's sweet
I want to drink cream
Let's drink this
It's good
Manager
Can I drink this Malibu Pine?
You're drinking too much
It's my money
I want to drink alcohol
You're so cool
If you were a crow, I would have killed myself
Did you imagine that we were dating?
I'm scared
Manager
Don't get close to Nana anymore
Why are you treating me like this?
It's cheaper than a cabaret
That's right
I'm ashamed to be bullied like you
No matter how much money I spend on a cabaret, I don't get paid
Are you going to a cabaret?
Then pay half of the bill
I'm sorry
I only have 1,000 yen in my wallet
Why?
Manager
I don't have enough alcohol
There's more in the glass
Why?
You're so cute
It's my first time
I'm going to drink Malibu Pine
Drink it
What do you want to drink?
Can I drink champagne?
Please
Let's share
What should we do?
It's your treat
Yay
You're so cute
We drank a lot
You're the best
Thank you
Nana, are you okay?
Is she okay?
She had a fight with her boyfriend
That's why she drank so much
I see
That's why she was so excited
Maybe she was drunk
I'm going to go home
I'm going to go home too
What about you?
Please take care of her
Nana
Wake up
Do you want some water?
Nana
Wake up
I love you
Nana
Are you okay?
I'm so drunk
It's dangerous
I drank too much
I see
Nana
Can you go home?
I can't
You have a shift tomorrow
You should take a taxi
I don't have a taxi
How can you go home?
I can't go home
I have a shift tomorrow
I'm going to stay at a business hotel
Can I stay there for a while?
I'll go home in April
You have a boyfriend
That's not good
Did you imagine something strange?
I'm scared
You shouldn't have said that
Go home
I can't
Did you wake up?
Yes
I'm awake
You shouldn't drink too much
Have some water
Thank you
You're so kind
I'm not getting along with my boyfriend
Really?
We're the same age
He's a kid
He doesn't listen to me
He doesn't play with me
He invited me to the amusement park
But he didn't play with me
It's not fun to be with him
You're still drunk
You should sleep
I want to be spoiled by an older person
I want to date an older person
Don't you have a girlfriend?
I haven't had one for 2 years
Do you have a crush on her?
No
I'm not that kind of person
You're not confident
I've been asked out
You're cute
You can like me for 5 seconds
5 seconds?
Thank you for treating me
I don't get it
Here you are
What are you doing?
5 seconds to fall in love
Hey
Are you sure?
You always miss the chance to fall in love
Are you serious?
I'm sorry
Hey
You can't do that
I have a boyfriend
You said you wanted to break up
It's not decided yet
Hey
You can't do that
Are you satisfied?
Hey
You can't do that
I'm embarrassed
Let me see your boobs
You're so cute
You can't do that
Your boobs are getting harder
How about this side?
Does it feel good?
It's getting hot
I'm embarrassed
You can't do that
Does it feel good?
How about this side?
You can't do that
Wow
Does it feel good?
Let me see
You can't do that
I'm embarrassed
Let me see
Don't look at me like that
You can't do that
No, no, no.
Ah, the Vitriol is in your stomach
Damn it.
Ow!
Let's go for a walk
Oh!
Wow!
I'll take it.
Oh!
I'm sorry to my boyfriend.
I can't.
Oh, my!
I'll make him feel better.
Oh!
You're so wet!
It's embarrassing.
Oh!
You're so wet!
Ouch!
Oh!
You're so wet!
Oh, it feels so good.
I can't do it anymore.
Let's go.
Oh, it feels so good.
Can you touch me?
Touch you?
Yeah, touch me.
No way.
Your panties are getting bigger.
It's a little...
It's pretty hot.
Can I touch you?
No, you can't.
You can't touch me.
You were so wet.
You can't.
My boyfriend will get mad at me.
I'll do it with my mouth, so please bear with me.
Mouth?
I'll stop.
Oh, it feels so good.
Does it feel good?
Yeah, it feels good.
It's getting really hot and big.
Let's lick each other.
Lick each other?
That's right.
Turn your butt this way.
It's embarrassing.
Let me lick you.
I'm back.
Please don't look at me.
I'm embarrassed.
No, no, no, no.
One more time.
Did you fall asleep?
I'm sleepy.
No, you can't.
You were so wet.
I'll do it with my mouth.
No, you can't.
Hey.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, you can't.
No, you can't.
I'm going.
Oh, it feels so good.
No, you can't.
Oh, you can't.
I'm going.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, you can't.
I'm going.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, you can't.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, you can't.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Mm.
That's really cute.
Captain.
You are so cute, Ten-chan.
I can't help it, Ten-chan.
I can't help it.
It feels good.
Let's go.
I love you.
I can't help it.
I didn't think you'd be looking for me like this.
I feel sorry for you.
I'll keep it a secret from everyone.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
It's too late.
If my boyfriend finds out, I'll be in trouble.
My boyfriend is the champion of capoeira.
Is that so?
I'm scared.
Capoeira?
But I'm wearing a capoeira uniform for the first time in a while.
Let's keep it a secret.
I'm waiting for you.
Really?
It's hot.
Is it hot?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I just washed my hair.
It feels good.
Let's keep it a secret.
It's hot.
I'm getting hot.
I'm hot, too.
Really?
Yes.
It's hot.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I just washed my hair.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
It feels good.
I'm going to wash your butt.
My butt?
It's embarrassing.
You're drinking something.
You're drinking something, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
It's okay there.
I'm going to wash your butt.
You're not going to wash my butt?
It's okay there.
It feels good.
I'm going to wash your hair.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
It's okay there.
I'm going to wash your butt.
It's hot.
Look at this.
What's wrong with this?
I'm excited.
Are you excited?
I'm going to do it for the last time.
Do you want me to do it for you once?
I don't want you to do it.
Yes.
I'm going to cut it at the end.
Yes, at the end.
It's getting really hard.
Yes.
Does it feel good?
I just said it, but is it already this hard?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It's hard.
It's getting fun.
Yes.
You look cute when you bite.
Don't tease me.
Yes.
Does it feel good?
It's amazing.
Yes.
Does it feel good?
It's amazing.
Now that you feel better, let's sleep together until morning.
Yes.
It's amazing.
You're always being teased, but you're such a playboy.
Your boyfriend is young, isn't he?
But he doesn't listen to me at all.
When I was looking at my boyfriend's computer the other day, I saw a lot of sexy videos and photos.
Is that so?
Don't you ask him out?
Even if it's sexy, it's over soon.
When it's over, we play a smartphone game.
That's terrible.
I would do it with you every day.
Every day?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Are you getting wet?
I'm getting wet.
You're so wet.
It feels good.
I see.
I'm sorry.
You're very sensitive.
I want to make you feel better.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
You're so cute.
Touch me.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Can you touch me?
Together?
Yes.
You're getting bigger.
It feels good.
Do you want to kiss me again?
It's okay.
Do you want to kiss your boyfriend?
My boyfriend?
No.
I want to kiss you.
I think you feel better.
Really?
A little bit.
A little bit?
I told you many times.
You're good at it.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
You're excited, aren't you?
Let me see your eyes.
Do you want to see it?
Is it difficult?
Yes.
You're very wet.
I'm wet.
It feels good.
A little bit.
It hurts.
Look at my face.
You're very wet.
I changed my clothes.
It's difficult.
It hurts.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
It's embarrassing.
It's fun, isn't it?
Do you want to see it?
I can't stand it.
A little bit.
Just a little bit?
Just a little bit.
You were so wet.
I'm going to sleep.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Can I go?
I can't do it.
You went straight.
You're so excited.
Show me your butt.
My butt?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Does it feel good?
Show me your butt.
I can't do it.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Show me your butt.
I can't do it.
I'm hugging you.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Your phone is ringing.
At this hour?
Check it out.
Oh, no.
It's from my boyfriend.
No.
Oh, no.
Hello?
Nana?
What are you doing at this hour?
I'm sorry.
I wanted to apologize to you.
I didn't treat you well.
I'm not angry at all.
Really?
I'm sorry.
I want to see you after work tomorrow.
What?
Say it again.
I want to see you after work tomorrow.
Okay.
Really?
I want to make up with you.
Are you going to see me after work?
Yes.
I'm going to see you.
It's okay.
I'm not going to the store.
Will you come to my house?
What?
I'll go.
Really?
Yes.
I'll go after work.
I want to see you soon.
I want to see you, too.
I'm waiting for you.
Come to my house after work.
Okay.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
I'm scared.
You looked fine.
I'm sorry.
I'm better than you.
But...
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I feel sick.
Ah!
It's gross.
I can't do it.
Let's go.
It's gross.
I can't do it.
Let's go.
It's gross.
It's hot.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
You slept a lot.
It's already morning.
It's already this time.
I have to go.
Already?
Are you kidding me?
Let's go.
What are you going to do?
Let's go to the club.
I was happy to make up with you.
This is the last time.
Are you kidding me?
Aren't they coming?
They'll be here in 10 minutes.
10 minutes?
No, 30 minutes.
Is that okay?
Yes.
This is the last time.
I don't want them to come.
Let's wait until they come.
Until they come?
Let's go.
Are you going to do it in the store?
I'm scared.
It's nice.
It's amazing.
Are you excited?
I'm excited.
I can't help it.
What's wrong?
Are you going to take it off?
I'm glad you came.
If you can work, you can do it.
It's a trace.
I'm embarrassed.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's getting harder and harder.
I feel sick.
I'll help you.
It's hard.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
It's getting hot.
Is it okay to do it here?
I feel sick.
I'm scared.
I feel good.
Show me your butt.
I can't help it.
It's hard.
Don't look at me like that.
You're not nervous, are you?
You're lying.
You're excited.
I feel sick.
I feel good.
I can't help it.
It's hot.
I'm scared.
Your voice is creaking.
I see.
Can't you hear me?
I'm not coming, so don't worry.
I know you're shaking.
Look.
It's a scar.
Does it feel good?
Your face is hot.
It's a scar.
Does it feel good?
You're excited.
It's a scar.
I'm going to take a bath.
You're getting bigger.
Does it feel good?
Can I sit down?
I can't stand it.
Ah
Can you let me go?
This?
A little
Ah
It's hard
It's really not warm yet
Ah
It's okay
I'm going to sleep
Ah
I'm tired
It feels good
Ah
Ouch!
I can't get up.
Did you fall down?
Yes.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
I can't get up.
Ouch!
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
Ouch!
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
I can't get up.
Ouch!
I feel good.
I can't get up.
Let's go.
Ouch!
Can I do it from behind?
Look at me.
It's the best.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
I can't get up.
Let's go.
Ouch!
I feel good.
Let's go.
Ouch!
Did you fall asleep?
I feel good.
I can't get up.
Let's go.
You are shaking.
Sleep well.
I feel good.
I can't get up.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
I can't get up.
Ouch!
I feel good.
You have a lot of pimples.
Oh, no.
I have to change my clothes.
This is bad.
Oh, no.
I feel good.