But today is the last day of the Feature Work Moving.
I filmed this.
Here I am.
We're here.
This is the exclusive Went by S-1.
Today's the day of filming,
and I met the director for the first time today.
Oh god.
I was told to come here with a lot of luggage.
And I'm wearing a very strange costume.
I was looked at.
Is it okay?
I'm a little nervous today.
I wonder what kind of shooting it is.
Oh, are you the director?
Nice to meet you.
I'm going to shoot.
I'm Unpai from TikToker.
It's been a year or so since I started YouTube.
I'm still growing, so please take care of me.
I have a lot to absorb every day.
I'm studying.
I started going to acting school.
I went to acting school.
I don't have a lot of mood swings.
I can't get really angry.
That's why I'm studying.
Why?
It's better to study acting.
Isn't it bad?
It's a big school.
What? No way.
I thought it was a drama.
Yes.
What is a documentary about bleeding?
I can't do it.
I've never done anything right before.
It was difficult.
It looks fluffy.
I don't think viewers can imagine bleeding from poop.
What?
I've done a lot of things.
It's the first time I've done a drama last month.
Have you ever done a drama?
I don't think so.
I've never done a drama.
What is your favorite part of your body?
My virginity?
I love my virginity.
I really love my virginity.
I like my virginity.
What is your favorite part of your body?
I got it.
Well...
I like my face when I'm embarrassed.
I like my face when I'm not dirty.
And...
I like myself.
This is my favorite part of my body.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Yes, I do.
Before I became an actress,
I wrote on the self-introduction column of TikTok that I like virginity.
When I was an amateur, I thought I was looking for a virgin.
But now I'm an actress, so I can't find a normal virgin.
What?
I really enjoyed it.
But now...
I can't do it.
Actually, I don't have a girlfriend.
But, it's fun to have a girlfriend.
I love my virginity.
I love my virginity that much.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Yes, I do.
I have a boyfriend in private.
I told my friend that I like virginity.
My friend introduced me to him.
I was nervous.
When I came to his house, I asked him what I should do.
I said,
He grabbed my boobs like this.
It hurt.
But, it was still cute.
Exciting!
I'm so excited.
What kind of virgin will you have?
That's a secret.
I'm going to ask them to take a video with me
This is my bag
It always gets heavy
This and this
I always carry my clothes with me
This is a big bag
It's easier to take a video without this
I always bring a big bag
This is my business tool
I always bring it with me
I think I can take a video with my boyfriend with this bag
Can I take a video with this bag?
Of course
I brought a lot of stuff
I always bring a lot of stuff
It's heavy
Let's stay at your house
Stay at your house?
Yes
I'm going to stay at your house
Can I stay at your house?
Really?
At home?
That's great
I'm so happy
Look
Can I do that?
Really?
Did you understand?
Yes
That's why I'm standing on a narrow street
I'm so happy
Thank you
How do you train your butt?
I started to train my butt
I started to train my body
I want you to enjoy my body, boobs, and butt
I'm not aggressive
I'm like, I'm going to wrap you up
I want you to fall in love with me
What do you think?
I think it's great
Is it?
That's it
I'm going to show you my boobs
If you are a virgin, please send me a DM
What?
I'm an actress
Can I read it secretly?
I'm going to be scolded by S-1
I'm going to stay at your house
I'm at your house
I'm looking forward to it
I'm going to be surprised if you come to my house like this
Hello
Yes
Excuse me
Hello
Nice to meet you
I'm a virgin
Please come in
Can I?
I'm going to start here
I didn't prepare anything
Really?
You look beautiful
Do I?
Yes
I was surprised
Ta-da
Hello
Are you a virgin?
Yes
Really?
It's embarrassing
You're cute
I'm happy
What's your name?
I'm Koji
Koji
Nice to meet you
I really like virgins
Really?
Yes
So, don't worry
I really like virgins
Leave it to me
Nice to meet you
I was surprised
Was it too sudden?
No, it's okay
Are you okay?
Yes
It's like YouTube
It's like stairs
It's like this
Do you know me?
Of course
Do you?
I'm glad
I'm Kimu Naotomi
Are you a TikToker?
Yes
Thank you
I'm glad
Are you a TikToker?
Yes
I don't watch a lot
But, I've seen you on Buzz
I know you
Really?
Yes
I'm glad
I'm nervous to see you like this
You're cute
You're handsome
No, I'm not
I'm not
Are you really a virgin?
Really?
I'm not
Do you have a girlfriend?
No, I don't have one now
You don't have one now
Yes
How long have you been a virgin?
I've been a virgin for a year
Do you have a crush on someone?
No, I don't
Why?
I don't know
I haven't had a girlfriend for a long time
Until now?
Yes
I haven't had a girlfriend for a long time
So, I'm not confident
I'm not sure if I can do it
I see
You're lucky
I'll hug you gently
I'm sorry
I see
I'll bring you some tea
Tea?
Thank you
You're a grown-up
I'm sorry
I didn't bring anything
You look like you're living a normal life
Yes
You don't have many things
You look like you're popular
I'm not
I don't have many things
How can I say this?
I'm not good at talking
No, you're not
I was surprised by your room
I'll bring you some tea
Thank you
Can I?
Sure
Cheers
I'm sorry
You look like you're popular
I don't know how to deal with you
You're cute
I don't know
I love you
No
I'm glad
Are you sure?
Yes
I'm glad
I'm embarrassed
Because you said that to me
Let's keep a distance
Keep a distance?
I'm sorry
Well
What?
You can say it
I'm sorry
Can I get your autograph?
Sure
Can I?
Yes
I didn't know that
I'm sorry
I prepared it
Thank you
I'm glad that you prepared it
You're cute
Can I?
Yes
I'll draw it
Are you decorating it?
No
It's Koji
Yes
Thank you
I drew it
Ta-da
How is it?
You're good at drawing
You're used to it
I often draw this kind of thing at autograph sessions
I'm sorry
It's a valuable autograph
I want you to decorate it
What does it look like?
This is U, N, B
So, it looks like this
Wow
It's cute, isn't it?
It's cute
I can draw it right away
I love my autograph
This is...
This is a boob
It's cute, isn't it?
It's really cute
It's beautiful
Thank you
You're welcome
You're cute
Thank you
I'm going to stay at Koji's house
You're quiet
Am I?
I'm usually like this
Really?
Yes
In front of your friends?
When I'm with a man
You're noisy
No, I'm not
I touch my phone
Really?
Don't you have a game?
I don't
I don't think so
I play board games
Don't you have a board game or a trampoline?
I don't
I play it on my phone
Let's buy it
I'd like to buy it
Thank you
I'm bored
Do you want to have sex?
What?
Sex?
Yes
All of a sudden?
It's a long distance
I don't feel like we're getting along
I'm a little nervous
I'm nervous
I think we'll get along better if we have sex
All of a sudden?
Yes
I'm not ready yet
I don't want you to be ready
I want you to be ready mentally and physically
Like taking a bath?
Are you sure?
Yes
Are you sure you don't want to take a bath?
What?
Are you sure?
Yes
Don't you want to take a bath now?
I don't want to
You don't want to?
Let's do it
Come here
Yes
It's a little bright
It's all right
I'll turn on the light
It looks better when it's bright
It's all right
It's better when it's bright
You should look at my face
Yes
That's right
Come here
Yes
What do you think?
What?
I've never kissed you before
Really?
Did you feel good?
It's the first time
I was surprised
I'm sorry
Wait
I touched you
It's all right
Can I touch you more?
Yes
I'm sorry
Did you feel good?
Yes
You're cute
I'm sorry
Look at me
Yes
I'm sorry
What?
Are you all right?
I feel good
Yes
I'm sorry
I feel good
I'm scared
Men feel their nipples
Yes
Did you know that?
I feel good
Do you feel good?
Yes
How do you feel?
Your nipples are wet
Do you feel good?
Yes
You're cute
I feel good
Are you shy?
I'm shy
Yes
Are you?
I'm shy
What?
It's cute
Let's play a hide and seek
Hide and seek?
Yes
I'll too
I'm embarrassed
I can't see it.
Let's cover your eyes.
I'll cover your eyes.
How is it?
You can't see it, can you?
I can see a little bit of light.
A little bit of light?
It's cute.
If you cover your eyes, you'll feel better.
I'm a little bit embarrassed.
You feel better, right?
I'll cover your eyes.
How is it?
It's cute.
Don't you feel excited because you don't know which one will be touched?
I'll cover your eyes.
I'll make you a birdie today.
I'll make you a lot of birdies.
I'll make you a birdie.
Is this enough?
I don't know.
I'm a little bit nervous.
You can't see it, can you?
Hey.
I'm very nervous.
It's funny.
What should I do? I developed a nipple.
What should I do?
I'll make you a birdie.
How is it?
It hurts.
It's touching me.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'll take it off.
I'll make you a birdie.
How is it?
It hurts.
Take it off.
I'll make you a birdie.
Are you still embarrassed?
I'm sorry if it's dirty.
It's not dirty.
I'll make you a birdie.
You're training, so you have a lot of muscles.
Something is wet.
What's this?
You couldn't stand it?
Yes.
It's erotic.
I'm sorry if it's gross.
It's very erotic.
It's normal.
Do you want me to touch you a lot?
It's gross.
You can touch me.
You're cute.
I'm sorry.
Are you embarrassed?
I don't care.
Do you want me to touch you?
I'll take it off.
I'll make you a birdie.
Does it feel good?
Your waist is moving a lot.
I'll make you a birdie.
Don't do that.
I'm patient.
I'll make you a birdie.
Does it feel good?
I'll make you a birdie where it feels good.
Where it feels good?
Here.
Show me.
It's nice.
It's beautiful.
Does it feel good?
It's nice, isn't it?
I haven't licked your penis yet, but I'm licking your butt.
How is it?
I'll lick your penis as it is.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's harder than before.
I'm patient.
It's amazing.
There's a lot of juice coming out.
It's delicious.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Your eyes are shining. It's cute.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hard.
It's delicious.
Does it feel good?
It's hard.
I'll do my best.
How is it?
It's hard.
Does it feel good?
It's about to come out, isn't it?
It's hot.
Is it hot?
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
You're twitching again.
It's about to come out.
It's hard.
It's cute.
You've been through a lot.
It's hot.
It's hard.
Is it your first time to have a boob job?
Yes.
Your reaction is funny.
How is it?
It's hard.
Do you want to lick it?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
Is it good?
It's hot.
Is it about to come out?
Do you feel it?
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
It's about to come out.
I want to sleep.
I'm going to buy it.
What is it?
It's rubber.
Rubber?
I thought so, so I brought it.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's too big.
It's too tight.
Have you ever used it?
No.
Let's use it.
Is it this way?
Here you are.
Even I can't do it.
Wait.
How is it?
Is it okay?
Yes.
I'm going to put it on like this.
Does it hurt?
What are you doing?
It's tight.
Is it tight?
It's thin, isn't it?
But it feels good when I put it in.
It's almost 10,000.
Because it's so thin.
Can I put it in?
Yes.
Look at my panties.
It's so red.
Pink.
Yes.
Is it your first time to see my panties in front of you?
I've never seen your panties.
Have you?
I've never seen your panties in front of me.
I'm being patted.
Are you being patted?
Touch my panties.
Okay.
This way.
It's tight.
Can I touch your panties?
Aren't you a little wet?
You can.
How is it?
Is it good?
Yes.
Wow, your panties are getting wet.
Can I put it in?
Yes.
Do you want to put it in?
Look.
Your panties are getting wet.
Your panties are beautiful.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm going to put it in, so look at me.
How is it?
Thank you.
Your panties are getting wet.
I put it in.
Did you put it in?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to move it.
Is it warm?
Yes.
I'm going to put it in.
Is it wet?
Yes.
You have a warm stomach.
I'm going to put it in.
You have a lot of it.
Yes.
Oh, no.
Is it wet?
Yes.
Not yet?
No.
Hold on.
Yes.
You have a lot of it.
It's hot.
Eat it.
Is it hot?
Yes.
It's hot.
Not yet.
I felt good for a moment.
You're lying.
It's not hot yet.
I felt good for a moment.
I'm going to put it in from behind.
Look at me.
How do you feel?
It's hot.
Touch me.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Don't go ahead.
Can I do more?
It feels good.
How about my butt?
Do you like it?
I like it.
It feels good.
Don't go.
I'm going.
It's hot.
It was a good place.
It feels good.
Did you feel a lot?
It's hot.
Let's do more.
Let's do it here.
Here?
What?
I'm using this.
You don't like it?
It's not that hard.
Let's do it.
It's hot here, too.
It's hot.
How is it?
Do you feel good?
It feels good.
Let me move.
You can feel much better.
Look at this.
I can see you're sweating.
I can see it from below.
It's itchy.
Is your stomach warm?
Yes.
It's hot.
Let me move.
Do it harder.
Okay.
It's warm.
Are you okay?
It feels so good.
It's my first time to do it.
Do it harder.
It feels good.
I want to do it harder.
Let me do it again.
Do it again.
Do it harder.
Oh my....
Oh my...
You almost pooped.
When I'm with you, my stomach aches.
Why would she say you almost pooped?
How do you feel?
It's hot, isn't it?
You're sweating a lot.
Is it soft?
It feels good.
I'm glad you're licking me.
I'm sweating a lot.
Do you want me to touch you again?
You're cute.
Does it hurt?
It hurts.
It's not over yet.
You're holding back a lot, aren't you?
How do you feel?
It's hot, isn't it?
Do you want me to touch you again?
You're holding back a lot, aren't you?
What are you doing?
I'm holding back a lot.
Do you want me to touch you again?
How do you feel?
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're holding back a lot.
You can see it, can't you?
Look at me.
You're holding back a lot, aren't you?
It hurts.
Do you want to go home soon?
Get on my back.
Can you give me your hand?
You're good.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
The emperor's chin-up is the best.
Move your body a lot.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It hurts.
It's okay.
Do you want me to put your boobs out?
Can I have a boobs?
Can I try it?
It feels good.
Let's go together.
I feel sick.
I feel sick, too.
Let's go together.
I feel sick.
You didn't make it in time?
I'm sorry.
It was difficult.
You're cute.
I feel sick.
Why is the driver there?
I'm sorry.
I didn't make it in time.
Did you feel good?
I felt good.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Thank you.
Let's go to bed.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't bear it.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad you didn't have a big boob.
You were cute all the time.
I wanted to hug you.
I couldn't bear it.
You're cute.
I think I moved a lot.
I felt it, too.
I felt good.
You had a good sex.
You were very sexy.
You're the best.
I'm glad you said that.
I was excited.
I don't remember it well.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
Isn't it hot?
I'm sweating a lot.
You're not sweating much, are you?
I'm still nervous.
I want to take a bath.
Do you have a bath?
It's small.
I want to take a bath.
Let's take a bath together.
Do you want to take a bath with me?
Let's go.
It's very small.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
The next day
The rice is almost ready.
Chicken rice is ready.
Can I make it?
It smells good, doesn't it?
It looks delicious.
Can you make it?
I'll make it.
Be quiet.
It looks good.
Can you make it?
It's all right.
It's a little burnt.
You put a lot of ketchup.
What's wrong?
Wait a minute.
It's amazing.
I can't do it.
It's difficult.
It's a little burnt.
Be quiet.
It's getting hot again.
It's amazing.
It looks delicious.
It's a little burnt.
Do you want to feel good again?
I can't do it.
I'll put an egg in it.
It's a little burnt.
Are you all right?
I'm good at making omelet rice.
Can you mix it?
I can mix it.
Koji, mix it.
Mix it.
I can't concentrate.
I can't mix it.
I can't do it.
How do you feel about being touched so much in the kitchen?
It's terrible.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
I'm mixing eggs.
It's terrible.
I'm hungry, so I'll eat Koji's.
Can I?
I can't do it.
You can't do it?
It's good.
Koji's is really good.
I can't do it.
Can you mix it?
Yes.
Do you think you can do it?
It's stuck in my teeth.
Is it your first time?
It's hot.
How do you feel?
It came out a little, didn't it?
Eggs?
Do you want me to do it more?
Yes.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Are you mixing the eggs well?
It's funny.
It's hot.
Are you happy?
You can't do it.
It's hot.
It's getting really hard.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's okay.
Open your mouth.
It's hot.
I can't do it anymore.
You can do it.
I can do it.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Wait a minute.
It came out a lot.
It's hot.
Do you like it?
I'm sorry.
How was it?
Why?
It was delicious.
Really?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Let's eat.
You were hungry, weren't you?
I was hungry.
Are you okay?
It came out a lot.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to wash your face?
Yes.
Bye bye.
It came out a lot.
Yes.
It's like a cross.
Why did you give it to me?
Look at this.
I put it on your face very well.
It's coming off.
Isn't it good?
I can see it.
It's good.
Thank you for the meal.
Can I eat it?
It's a waste.
Right?
I have to eat it with ketchup.
Do you want to eat it?
It's good.
Is it good?
Yes.
Is it okay?
It's really good.
I'll do it for you.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I'll do it for you.
Okay.
Hurry up.
I can't do it.
It's hot.
Right?
It's good.
It's good, isn't it?
It's all over my mouth.
It's really good.
Is it enough?
No, it's not.
I'll put it in here.
Can I eat ice cream?
Ice cream?
Can I eat it?
Yes.
Thank you for the meal.
Isn't it cold?
I think so.
It's really good.
Isn't it good?
It's good.
Right?
It tastes like milk.
It tastes like milk, doesn't it?
I know.
I'm done.
Are you done?
Yes.
Don't you want to play something?
Well...
What is it?
It's amazing.
Why do you have it?
This is...
Do you play tennis?
My ex-girlfriend.
Oh, I see.
I used to play tennis with my ex-girlfriend.
I used to play tennis, too.
Let's do it.
Shall we?
Why don't we play a game?
A game?
Yes.
Well...
If you win the game,
do you want to have sex again?
What?
Can I?
I'd like to.
On the contrary, if you win,
can I have sex?
If I win,
can I be a slug?
I'm happy with both.
Are you?
Yes.
But I want to have sex.
Do you?
Yes.
Then, let's do our best.
Okay.
Well...
Like this...
I'll go up like this.
Like this?
Yes.
I'll go forward like this.
Okay.
I'll go around the wall and come back here.
The one who comes to me first wins.
Yes.
Don't drop it.
I got it.
Shall we?
Yes.
Ready, go!
I can't do it.
It's unfair.
I won.
Wait.
I did it.
It's unfair.
You dropped it a lot.
I got it back.
I won.
I did it.
I thought I won.
I'm tired.
I lost.
I won.
Thank you.
You won.
I won.
Let's have sex again.
Look at me.
Okay.
Can I do it now?
Yes.
Don't you want to do it now?
I want to do it.
Okay.
It tastes like soft cream.
It's sweet.
Hey, lick me.
I lost, but lick me.
Hey, let me do it.
It hurts.
I lost.
You did it.
I'm glad.
Sit down.
Okay.
You did it, too.
I'm glad you did it.
Are you glad?
Yes.
I'm glad.
I'll give it back to you.
Okay.
It's amazing.
It's too soft, but I got it.
It feels good.
I'm glad to feel like licking you.
Are you glad?
Yes.
I see.
It's the first time.
Yes.
I'm glad.
Don't you want me to lick you?
I want you to lick me.
I can't do it if you lick me.
Do you want me to lick you?
Yes.
Okay.
I'm glad.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
I'm glad.
Do you want me to give you a hug?
Yes.
You're sweating.
I'm sweating.
From the bottom.
Yes.
I'm glad.
Do you want me to give you a hug?
Yes.
Can I?
Can I do this?
Yes.
I'm glad.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
Yes.
Do you want me to give you a hug?
You're cute.
I'm glad.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I feel like I'm at home alone.
Yes.
I'm glad.
Right?
Yes.
I'm glad.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm glad.
I'm nervous.
Are you nervous?
You're cute.
I'm glad.
I feel good.
Touch my boobs.
My boobs don't float.
Don't they float?
No, they don't.
I'm glad.
Are you okay?
I feel good.
Touch my boobs.
Yes.
I feel good.
I'm glad.
I just did it.
Let's wash your clothes.
Okay.
My legs are painful.
It's painful.
Do you feel wide?
Yes, I do.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I feel it from my stomach.
My ears are weak.
My ears are weak because I was brushed.
Are they weak?
My ears are weak.
Is it your first time to do this?
Yes, it is.
I feel good.
How about this?
Let's wash your clothes again.
Okay.
I feel good.
It's good to take a bath, isn't it?
Yes.
Do you feel like a couple?
I feel like a couple.
I'll wash your body.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
I feel good, too.
How do you feel?
I feel better.
Do you feel better?
Thank you.
Do you want me to wash your hair?
I'll wash your hair.
Then, I'll wash your hair.
Thank you.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Do you want to play with me?
Around your neck.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
I'll wash your back, too.
Is that all?
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Do you feel ticklish?
Do you feel good?
Yes.
How do you feel?
I'll wash your back, too.
Look at me.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
Can I touch your butt?
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
You look healthier than before.
You look very healthy.
I'll massage your back, too.
How do you feel?
You'll feel much better if you practice.
It's hot.
It's very hot.
It's very warm.
It's amazing.
You're moving a lot.
Did you feel good?
Do you feel good?
My hands feel good.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
You're moving a lot.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
It's very good.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
It's hot.
I feel good.
You're moving a lot.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Did you feel good?
My mouth feels good.
Your chin-chin is delicious.
It's hot.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
It's hot.
I thought you felt bad.
Then, let's go to a more comfortable place.
Give me your butt.
What are you going to do?
Your butt.
It's hot.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm not embarrassed.
It's your first time, isn't it?
It's hot.
Are you embarrassed?
But I feel good.
I feel good.
Look at me.
It's hot.
It feels good to be hit by a lot of embarrassing things, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's getting hot.
It's my first time, but I feel like I can do it.
It's hot.
Look at me.
You've been through a lot, haven't you?
I've been through a lot.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
From now on, just say yes.
Look at me.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'll give you a lot of kisses.
You can get a lot better.
I can't breathe.
I'll do it with my breasts.
Did it come out?
It came out cleanly.
You put a lot in it.
I'm glad that your boobs are in the middle.
In the middle?
Yes.
In the middle.
Thank you very much.
What do you want to eat at the convenience store?
What do you want to buy at the convenience store?
Well...
Is there anything you want to eat?
I like croquettes.
Croquettes?
I'll buy it if you leave it at the convenience store.
I'll definitely buy it.
It's raining.
Hold this.
Are you going to hold this?
I'm a little embarrassed.
It's a souvenir.
Do you like it?
It's Mirai-chan.
Are you going to go?
Let's go.
I'm a little embarrassed.
But it's fun.
It's fun.
I'm hungry.
You're hungry, aren't you?
I think it's okay.
You're a genius.
Your face turned red.
What do you want to buy?
What?
What do I want to buy?
You like alcohol, don't you?
Yes.
I want to buy orange juice.
Orange juice?
Yes.
You look embarrassed.
It's 640 yen.
Thank you.
He bought it for me.
It's cheap.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It's the first time in my life that I feel embarrassed.
Really?
I'm glad that I came here like that.
I'm glad, too.
I'm home.
You looked very embarrassed.
I was very embarrassed.
It was fun.
I kissed you because it was you.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
You should be glad.
I'm sorry for being embarrassed.
I'm glad.
I've wanted to do this for a long time.
Really?
I'm going to sleep.
I'll do it.
PRESENT
This is awful.
What happened to me?
It feels so good.
It's so good.
I'm going to cry.
Look, it's so good.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
I'm going to throw up.
It's good.
It's good, isn't it?
It's been a while since I ate Takoyaki.
Really?
Is it still hot?
I added Tenkasu.
It must be good.
Tenkasu is good, isn't it?
It's creamy inside, isn't it?
Right?
Oh, right.
Look.
I'm going to put the camera here.
Like this.
Like this?
Are you going to take a video?
Yes.
It's popular to take a video with a couple.
But, it looks real.
I think you're going to forget that you're talking about your boyfriend.
How is it?
I often watch this.
Right?
Don't you watch couple videos like this?
You take a video like this.
It's popular, isn't it?
I think so.
I think so, too.
I'm going to eat one more.
Takoyaki?
Yes.
I think it's going to be popular if you take a video of it.
I think so, too.
Impact Takoyaki.
Takoyaki looks small, doesn't it?
I think so.
I'm going to put it here.
I think my boobs are big.
It's the same size as this.
It's the same size.
It's amazing.
It's so funny.
I'm going to eat this.
I think you're going to be banned.
Are you ready?
Yes.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Did I fail?
No, you didn't.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
I'm going to eat it again.
Is it hot?
It's hot.
It's burning.
I'm going to eat this.
It's messy, isn't it?
Can I eat this?
Are you okay?
I'm going to eat it.
Is it hot?
It was really hot.
Yes.
It's hot.
I didn't put any sauce on it.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Can you eat it in one bite?
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Yes.
It's delicious.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm glad you ate it in one bite.
It's delicious.
Right?
It was delicious.
It's hot.
It's really hot.
Ta-da.
Look at this.
I cosplayed for you.
I don't usually do this hairstyle, but I did it for you.
How do you like it?
Do you want to see me closer?
I look like an AV, don't I?
Touch me.
How do you like it?
Does it feel good?
I can't let you sleep yet.
Let's do something more fun.
How do you like it?
You're twitching again.
Right?
How do you like it?
Do you like it here?
You like it here, don't you?
Then, I'll do a lot of cosplay for you.
Which one do you like?
You like this one.
How do you like it?
You're twitching.
You're twitching a lot.
You look like a pervert.
Which one do you like, right or left?
Look at this.
You're twitching a lot.
Does it feel good to be touched from above?
Does it feel good?
It feels better to be touched from above.
You're twitching.
Why are you twitching?
Does it feel good?
I'll make you a fine lemon.
Why don't you make a sound?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Ouch!
What's this?
How many times did you do this today?
What's wrong?
You're amazing.
You're twitching.
Can I look at your twitching?
You're amazing.
Please stand up.
How do you feel?
I just made you sleep.
I want you to do it more.
What's this?
I'll lick you a little.
Do you want me to lick you?
I feel like I want to sleep more when I lick you a little.
I'm getting dizzy.
I'm getting dizzy, too.
Can you touch me?
Touch me with this finger.
I feel good.
I want you to touch me.
My pajamas are getting dirty.
Don't do that.
I feel good.
Can I lick you a lot, too?
Do you want me to put you in a toy?
Did you want to sleep forever?
I made you stay in my bed.
So it's going to feel good.
Get in, please.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, I can't do it.
I can't do it.
I can't.
Can I look at you and cry?
I'm going to cry.
I'm going to cry a lot.
It's really hard.
Ah, it feels good.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Ah, I can't do it.
Look at my butt.
Look.
There's a lot in there.
Look from this side.
I can't do it.
Ah, I can't do it.
I can feel a lot. Look.
I can feel a lot in your butt.
I can't do it.
This is...
This feels good.
I can't do it.
I love your face.
Look at me more.
It feels good, right?
I can't do it.
This feels good.
This is your first time, right?
Doesn't it feel good?
It feels good.
I can't do it.
When I think about having sex, anything feels good.
Is that okay?
I want you to have more sex.
I want you to have a lot of sex.
This feels good.
I can't do it.
More.
It doesn't feel good yet, right?
I'll make you feel better.
I can't do it.
I can do it.
It's still a hundred years early.
What is this?
Or do you want boobs?
How is it?
Isn't it sexy to do this costume?
Do you want me to put it here?
It's so sexy.
I'll take care of your posture.
Does it feel good?
You're moving your hips.
I'm going to take it off.
Do you want me to take it off?
Okay.
Take it off a lot.
Give it to me.
You're amazing.
You flew a lot.
I didn't know you could fly so much.
You flew on my face.
You're so cute.
I love you.
He's sleeping now.
I'm going to call him.
I was surprised.
Good morning.
What time is it now?
It's about 3 a.m.
I'm going home today.
That's right.
I wanted to do something with you.
I want to do it.
You want to do it?
I woke up.
Did you wake up?
I don't know.
I want to do more.
It's warm here.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Touch my neck.
It was good, wasn't it?
Yes.
It feels good.
You were sleeping until a while ago.
You're doing such a bad thing when you wake me up.
I want you to sleep in my arms.
My breasts are weak.
There's a lot.
It's the last.
Can I touch your breasts?
I want to feel good.
Do you want to lick each other?
Yes.
It feels good.
Let's cuddle.
Where are you going?
This way.
If you do this, you can cuddle.
I want to feel good with you.
This is the last kiss.
Let's sleep.
It's hot.
It's cold again.
It's salty.
Let's sleep.
It's cold.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Do you like me?
Do you want to be a pervert with me?
It feels good.
It's hard.
It's swollen.
It hurts.
I told you to be patient.
I'm sorry.
I'm a pervert.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
It's a million years early.
Is it early?
But it feels good.
You're a good boy.
Do you want to feel better?
It's the last one today.
It feels good.
You're feeling much better.
I'll feed you a lot.
I want to put kimchi in it.
No?
I want you to put kimchi in it.
I'll put it in.
Does this feel good?
It feels good.
It's almost 3 o'clock.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I'll feed you a lot.
You're a good boy.
Do you want to feel better?
It feels good.
Drink a lot.
You don't have to do this.
It feels good.
Stretch your back.
You don't have to do this.
I can't think of anything.
Can I sleep?
I love you.
Do you love me?
Let's sleep together.
It feels good.
I love you.
Do more.
It feels good.
I want to do more.
Your penis is mine.
I can't do it anymore.
You can't do it anymore?
You can't do it anymore.
Do you understand?
I can't do it anymore.
Do more.
Can you move?
Do you want me to move?
Yes.
Can you do it?
I'll do it.
Can I do it?
Yes.
Ah...
Ah, it feels good.
It fits perfectly.
It feels good.
Ah...
Ah, it's no good.
I can't do anything.
I can't do it.
I'm sleepy.
Ah, it's no good.
I was made to do a lot of things.
Ah...
It feels good.
I can't do it.
It's no good.
Ah...
It hurts so much.
I want you to do more.
Ah, it feels good.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Ah, it's no good.
I can't do it.
Ah...
Ah, it feels good.
It feels good.
I love you, little one.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Ah, it feels good.
It feels good.
I might have become your favorite child.
Really?
It feels good.
I want you to do more.
I can't do it.
I'm scared.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I can't do it.
It hurts a lot.
Hey, give me your tongue.
My tongue?
Give me your tongue.
It feels good.
Put a lot of it on my mouth.
Give me your tongue.
Give me a lot of it.
It hurts.
I put a lot of it in my mouth.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
It was cute.
It felt good.
I love you.
Do you love me?
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I took a video of your last impression.
My impression?
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's good.
Is it around here?
Yes.
It was in a blink of an eye.
I thought you were cute, so I loved you.
Really?
I didn't expect you to be so cute.
I'm glad.
We had a good chemistry.
Really?
I'm going to be more confident from now on.
You shouldn't be confident.
Only I can do that.
Really?
I won't do that from now on.
Then, let's sleep with a pillow.
I'm sorry.
Bye bye.
After that...
Is it good?
It's really good.
I'm glad.
I made breakfast for you.
Thank you.
Let me see what you made.
Ta-da!
Yes.
It's fried egg and salad.
It's really soft.
Yes.
You made it really well.
It's moving.
Is it moving?
I made it well.
It's amazing.
Right?
It's really soft.
It's good.
Do you want to eat over there?
Yes.
Do you want to go over there?
Let's eat together.
It looks good.
Do you want me to open it for you?
Yes.
Here we go.
Can you eat it?
Yes, it's good.
How is it?
It's good.
Is it good?
I'm glad.
Do you want me to open it for you?
Yes.
Open it.
Can I?
Let's eat at the same place.
At the same place?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Here we go.
Wait a minute.
Open it.
I'm sorry.
It's broken.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Thank you.
It's broken.
You might be lonely to go home.
It was a short time.
I want to stay a little longer.
Do you want to see me again?
Yes.
DM me secretly.
DM you?
Yes.
Can I?
Please.
Yes.
It was fun.
It was a lot of fun.
Yes.
I want to come here again.
I'm always waiting for you.
Yes.
I'll come here again.
It was fun.
Yes, it was.
We said good-bye to each other.
Thank you for bringing me here.
Is there anything I can do for you?
Can I take a picture of you?
Yes, you can.
Wait.
I haven't taken a picture yet.
I want to take a picture, but can I?
Can I?
I want you to take a picture of me.
Let's take a picture.
Yes.
It's a souvenir.
I'm happy.
I'll take a picture.
Thank you.
I'll take a picture of you.
I'll go home.
Yes.
I want to stay here for a long time.
I'm really happy.
It was a short time.
Yes, it was.
It was a long time.
Thank you.
See you.
I'll go home.
I'm home now.
I just got home.
I'm still excited.
I wanted to stay a little longer.
It's been a long time since I've been a virgin.
I'm in a good mood.
I'm overflowing with motherly love.
At the end of the video, I looked like Emo-kun.
I looked like Emo-kun.
It was so cute.
It was amazing.
It was my first time to look like Emo-kun.
So, I was nervous.
I might fall in love with Emo-kun.
What should I do if I fall in love with Emo-kun?
Yes.
How did you like my new video?
I'm waiting for your DM.
Please subscribe to my channel.