I'll do it...
The point of this project is
to encourage people with the talent you have
to grow your customers' expectations
Can I take a look at the report?
Oh, yes.
This is the report I handed out to everyone.
What page is it?
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's the 8th page.
That's enough. Who's next?
Hurry up.
It's tough, isn't it?
What should I do with all the projects?
You're going to work overtime and do it yourself, aren't you?
Oh, I see.
You're a typical working person.
You're right.
It's hot.
It's around 10 p.m., so the air conditioning in the building is off.
What's wrong with Director Yamada?
He's a tough guy, but he's in such good shape.
Damn it.
Team Yamada's sales in the second half of the year have recorded the highest in the past.
Let's continue to work hard as a team.
Cheers.
Congratulations.
It's good.
I'll have another one.
It's your first time drinking, right?
It's not a big deal.
You look strong.
It's good.
It looks delicious.
It doesn't have soy sauce on it.
I'll eat it now.
Excuse me.
Can I have some soy sauce?
Yes.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Where am I?
You're at a bar.
Everyone else went to a shorter bar.
I was told to meet you with the director.
He went home?
Yes.
He seems to be very drunk.
Excuse me.
Team Yamada's sales in the second half of the year have recorded the highest in the past.
Are you okay?
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm sorry.
I'll stay here.
I...
Yes?
Open the door.
It's painful.
Okay.
Is it painful?
More.
I'm sorry.
More?
Yes.
Okay.
Legs.
Legs?
Massage.
Massage?
Hurry up.
Okay.
Thank you.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
Yes.
I heard rumors. Are you a virgin?
No.
You seem to be a virgin.
Continue.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
You really can't work.
I'm sorry.
Hurry up.
Okay.
More.
More?
Not there.
Buttocks.
Buttocks?
Relax your legs.
Okay.
Hurry up.
I relaxed.
It's hard. Relax more.
Take off your skirt.
Okay.
Hurry up.
I'm sorry.
Are you excited just by looking at my underwear?
No.
Hurry up.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Put it higher.
Okay.
Don't touch anything weird.
There.
It's hot.
Press the button.
Hurry up.
I'm sorry.
How is it?
Do you want me to take it off?
All of them?
Yes.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'll take care of it.
What are you doing?
The director is coming.
I'll get angry.
But...
Okay.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
I don't know how to take it off.
The director is amazing.
I'm sorry.
Did you go to the director?
Yes.
You felt good, right?
I want you to feel good, too.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
What's that?
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
It feels so good.
It's so good.
It's okay, it's okay.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
It's so good.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
I can't take it anymore.
What's that?
It's okay.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
I can't take it anymore.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I can't take it anymore.
What's wrong?
I don't feel anything.
Let me have a look.
Ani, thank god!
Don't move!
I can't do it. I'm going to throw up.
I can't do it.
I'm going to throw up.
Ah...
Mike...
Mike!
Ah...
More...
To the buttocks...
Ah...
More...
Don't run away...
Ah...
No, no, no.
I'm so tired.
No.
Go, go, go.
I'm so tired.
I can't stop.
Let's go!
I don't like it.
No no no!
Go! Go! Go!
Go!
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
Why are you crying?
I want to pat your head.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Don't cry.
No, no, no.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
Are you okay?
It's hard.
No, no, no.
This feels good.
Chief.
I'm sorry.
I lied to you earlier.
I was a virgin.
But I'm not a virgin anymore.
I missed the last train.
Please stop today.
You must be tired.
I'll give you a massage.
I'll get you a hot bath.
I'll give you a hot bath.
You just want to touch my boobs, don't you?
No, I don't.
It doesn't feel good here.
My boobs are big.
It really feels good.
I'll do the upper part.
I'm sorry.
It's stiff here.
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Do you want to lick it more?
Was the massage good?
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Does it feel good?
Why does it feel so good?
Please, just stop!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Thanks!
I don't know what to say.
I think this is too much.
Excellent!
What the...
Chibita, did you just...
It's a bit of a stretch, but I think I'll be able to do it.
I'm not sure if I'll be able to do it, but I'll do my best.
Is that an issue?
Don't tell me...
You have to talk to him yourself.
I was at work.
So I guess I'll stop working for now and talk to you.
Let's have a tolerance test.
If you do something erotic and feel it, you lose.
But if you can concentrate on your work, I lose.
If you can concentrate on your work, I lose.
Good.
I'm going to put it in my mouth.
Don't you feel anything?
My legs are cold.
I'm going to put it in my mouth.
Don't you feel anything?
I haven't been able to work at all.
I'm going to put it in my mouth.
Please raise your foot.
I don't know what to do.
I'm sweating a lot.
Are you okay?
I can't sleep well.
Oh...
Oh, you're so cold.
Oh, you're so nice.
Oh...
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
It's hot.
It feels really good.
Wait a minute.
I don't want to make you sweat.
You don't want to sleep anymore, do you?
Are you okay?
You want to sleep, don't you?
No, I don't.
You can't.
It's hot.
I can't do it anymore.
You can't.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
You have a lot of things you want to do.
That's good, isn't it?
Even if you're nervous.
I'm sorry.
Hang in there.
You have to hang in there.
I'm sorry.
You're okay.
Phew...
Refrain it...
Done...?
Done...
It's very uncomfortable.
Your leg.
No, no.
I'll go if you push me too hard.
You'll go if I push you too hard?
I'm scared.
My face is in the way.
I'm going.
It's okay.
I'll be cool.
Come here.
Look at me.
I'll go if you push me too hard.
It's okay.
It's better to feel good.
I can't.
My legs won't move.
You can't move?
I can't.
It's not okay.
Go, go
Its really good. You can move around yourself
Look over here
I'm sorry.
Put your legs down.
It's okay.
What's wrong?
I can't.
One more time.
Ouch!
Oh, no!
No, no, no!
What should I do?
Ouch!
No, no, no!
Oh, no!
What should I do?
Does it feel good?
No, no, no!
Oh, no!
Do you want to lie down?
That's great.
Oh, no!
Ouch!
Does it feel good?
How do you feel?
It hurts more than before.
Oh, no!
No!
No, no, no!
Ouch!
Oh, no!
No, no, no!
What should I do?
Oh, no!
I can't, I can't.
I can't do this anymore.
It feels so good.
I can't, I can't.
I can't do this anymore.
Really?
I can't, I can't.
You can do it.
I'm so tired.
It feels so good.
I can't, I can't.
I can't.
What's wrong?
You can't do this.
It feels so good.
Keep going.
I can't, I can't.
I can't.
Keep going.
I can't, I can't.
I can't.
Keep going.
I can't, I can't.
I can't.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Good morning.
I knew it, it was work.
Yume was doing that kind of thing,
but she is good at switching.
It's hot.
You started to think of me as a man.
No.
Why don't you open the blouse button as usual?
You were seducing me unconsciously.
Like yesterday.
It takes an hour to get to the airport.
I know.
I'll let you in.
I'll open the button for you.
I'm sorry.
You're still the same as yesterday.
I'm a virgin.
You did it.
The manager said the L word at the office.
Monkey.
Have sex with a monkey at the office.
I wanted to work.
It's hot.
I want to drink.
What is this?
You're so mean.
You want to see me, don't you?
I want to see you.
You're so mean.
lick my feet
There's no more individuals who are taking this seriously
Although I know some people can take it seriously
There are so many ways to take care of yourself
Allevery people in our society
People who to secure just what they are doing
Speak up
To increase the centrum of human activity
I can't believe it.
, I can't believe it.
It feels so good.
wait
Ahh…
Your legs are so beautiful
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
It feels good here, too.
Does your buttocks feel good?
Show me your buttocks.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Show me your buttocks.
You have to show me your buttocks because it feels good.
Buttocks are scary when you work, but they are cute when you have sex.
Buttocks.
Is this okay?
It's hot.
What are you doing?
It's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
I'll do my best.
It's hot.
You're a pervert.
I'm a pervert.
You're a pervert, too.
You're doing this at work.
What are you going to do?
What am I going to do?
It's my line.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
You're a pervert.
What's going on here?
What's going on?
I'm not a pervert.
Can I check it?
It's hot.
Show me your buttocks.
It's slimy.
It's not slimy.
Can you hear the sound?
Show me your buttocks.
I'm not a pervert.
Are you sure?
Raise your legs.
Let's open this.
I'm not a pervert.
I like this part.
Show me your legs.
Don't close your legs.
I can see everything.
Raise your legs.
I'm not a pervert.
I like this part.
Do you feel good?
I feel a tingling sensation.
I'm not a pervert.
I want you to relax.
Do you want me to relax?
Yes.
I want you to relax.
I'm not a pervert.
I feel good.
What's wrong?
Do you feel good?
Yes.
I feel good.
My nose is burning.
It's getting harder.
Yes.
I feel good.
You have a lot of acne.
Yes.
I have a lot of acne.
I feel good.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to kiss me.
Do you want me to kiss you?
Yes.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
I feel good.
My nose is burning.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
Do you want me to kiss you?
Yes.
I feel good.
It's hot.
Can I throw up a little?
Do you want to throw up a little?
I'll fix it for you.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
I can't stand it anymore.
Why can't you stand it?
Can I throw up a little?
I want you to throw up a little.
I'll fix it for you.
It's hot.
I'm going to throw up.
I haven't moved at all yet.
Are you going to throw up?
It's hot.
I'm going to throw up.
Are you going to throw up?
I can't stand it anymore.
I want to throw up.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
It hurts.
I'm going to throw up.
Don't do that.
It hurts.
I'm going to throw up.
Don't do that.
It hurts.
I'm going to throw up.
Don't do that.
It hurts.
I can't stand it anymore.
Do you want to move?
Yes.
Please do not move.
Please be gentle.
I'm going to threw up.
Please don't move.
I can't stand it anymore.
Can I hold your back?
No, be gentle.
Be gentle.
Is it here?
No, no, no.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ouch, ouch.
Ohh!
Do you want me to give you a hand?
It's all right, it's all right.
I'm sorry.
No good.
It's going to break.
Go, go, go.
It's not moving at all.
It's going to break.
Hold it with your feet.
Hold it like that.
Just like that.
It's going to break.
It's not moving at all.
I can't.
This hurts.
It could be good.
No, no, no.
Let's go.
You're still standing.
You can still do it, right?
I can still do it?
Ah, I feel sick.
You can still do it, right?
You're still standing.
It looks like a butt.
Ah, I feel sick.
No, it's okay.
No, no, no, I'm fine.
So...
What?
So it was a lie?
So I...
Hey, Tetsuku,
This face is Satoru's.
I didn't mean to take you out.
I'm sorry.
Here?
Oh, no, no.
No!
No, no, no.
I can't take away her strength.
Oh, it relaxes really good.
You like it when I move, don't you?
I don't know what to do.
That's not good.
Good.
You still have your turn.
Ah, that feels good.
That feels good.
Don't worry. It's coming.
Come here.
It hurts.
No, no, no, no, no.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ouch, ouch.
Thank you for watching!