This is the first time I've ever seen such a thing, so I'm a little surprised.
I'm not sure if it's because it's my first time or because it's my first time.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
I'm sorry, but I'm busy.
I'm sorry, I'll fix it right away.
I don't have time, so I'll do it.
I'm sorry.
I'm busy, so I have to work more.
I'll be careful.
It's tough, isn't it?
I know you can work, but it's a little cold.
I want you to think about it a little more.
I'm sorry I made a mistake.
But if you say that, you'll be hospitalized.
But you're thinking about me.
You're a human being.
If I were you, I'd be mad at you no matter how beautiful you were.
Hey, you guys.
Don't talk and get to work.
This department has fewer employees and more work.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Why don't you give me an easel?
I don't believe you.
I do.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Do I have to talk to you now?
I think you'll talk to me face to face.
I'm sorry to hear that.
OK.
I'm sorry.
Then please take good care of yourself, and take care of yourself.
Are you done?
Yes, I've finished organizing the documents.
You're late.
I'm sorry.
I've prepared all the documents in the meeting room.
Are they all there?
Yes.
Here's your coffee.
Where's the sugar?
I didn't put it in.
Thank you.
It won't end.
I'll do my best.
What is this workload?
It won't end until the last train.
I have a lot of overtime today.
I'll do my best.
It might end if you don't pull your legs.
How long are you going to stand?
Hurry up and get to work.
Yes.
I'll do my best.
It's finally over.
It was a lot of work today.
I'm sorry.
It was a lot of work.
I wish you could do it more efficiently.
What are you looking at?
I'm sorry.
You were so beautiful.
What are you thinking about at work?
You're standing.
I'm sorry.
You're standing because you're not working seriously.
What were you thinking about at work?
I'm sorry.
It's not like that.
Why are you standing like this?
This is...
It's not good.
You're at work.
Do you always think like this?
No.
You were so beautiful.
I'm sorry.
I don't usually think like that.
You're not sexy at all.
That's not true.
I think you're beautiful.
I can't work because I think like that.
I'm sorry.
Show me.
Here?
Take it off.
I can't do that at work.
Take it off quickly.
That's why I can't work.
Hurry up and move.
I'm sorry.
You're late.
When did you get up?
I just got up.
Why?
I was looking at your body.
You're always standing.
No, I'm not.
You're not sexy at all.
I'm not sexy at all.
We were alone in the private room.
So I just stood up.
No, I'm not.
You're always like that.
I'm sorry.
I want to touch you.
Be careful.
You don't know who you want to touch.
I'm sorry.
I want to touch your boobs.
It's disgusting.
Be careful.
I'm sorry.
Do you think you'll feel better if you touch me like that?
Like this?
Make yourself feel better.
Is it okay if I touch you from above?
I'm sorry.
Don't you understand if I don't tell you?
I can't.
I want to touch you directly.
It's disgusting.
Be more intense.
Be more gentle.
Like this?
Be more intense.
Don't you want to touch me directly?
I want to touch you directly.
Touch me properly.
I'm sorry.
Make yourself feel better.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
Be more intense.
Like this?
Like this.
I'm sorry.
I want to lick you.
Can't you do anything without my command?
I'm sorry.
Make yourself feel better.
Okay.
Like this?
Like this.
I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
I can only touch your chest.
Don't you have anything else to say?
I want to touch your chest.
What are you talking about?
I can't help it.
Can you do it comfortably?
Make yourself feel better.
What are you doing?
I want to touch your chest.
I like it here.
Make yourself feel better.
I can hear you.
You don't have to say that.
Did you go?
I haven't gone yet.
What's inside?
I'm sorry.
You don't have to say that.
It's in the back.
Raise your fingers.
It's around here.
Are you feeling better now?
It seems like it.
What are you doing?
You're going to turn around, aren't you?
Yes.
Put your fingers in again.
Run around the back.
Yes.
Do it before I tell you to.
Here?
Yes.
Over there.
Here?
Yes.
Over there.
It sounds like it's going to explode.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to fall asleep.
I'm going to sleep.
You made the snack dirty.
Clean it up.
I'm sorry.
Harder.
That's right.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
That's right.
I'm going to die.
Lick me more.
If I hadn't told you, you wouldn't have been able to do it.
I'm sorry.
Did you feel good?
Thank you.
Do you want a reward?
I want a reward.
Reward.
I'm happy.
It's sweet.
It's gross.
I can't help it.
It's been a long time.
What should I do?
I'm sorry.
Sit down.
Here?
How long have you been taking it off?
I'm sorry.
Take it off quickly.
Quickly.
I'm sorry.
It's too luxurious for you.
Thank you.
I'm happy.
It's gross.
You're sensitive.
Yes.
I love it.
You're standing a lot.
You can't work because you're thinking about erotic things.
I'm sorry.
I'll be careful.
Be careful.
Have you noticed?
What?
You always have a pimple on your face at work.
It's coming out of your clothes.
I'm sorry.
I didn't notice.
It's because you're a female employee.
Is that so?
I'm sorry.
It's a bad reaction.
This pimple is bigger than before.
What?
Do you touch it yourself?
Only occasionally.
Hey.
Your stomach is slimy.
I'm sorry.
What's this?
It's a...
It's a scab.
Hey.
What are you trying to do?
You can't do that.
I'm sorry.
What are you going to do with this?
You made me stand like this.
I want you to do more.
What?
What do you want me to do?
You can't work because you can't speak your mind.
I'm sorry.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to lick me.
What did you say?
Do you want me to lick you?
You're disgusting.
Please.
Just a little.
Don't let it out of your mouth.
I'll do my best.
I can't help it.
Thank you.
Are you done?
Just a little more.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
I want you to lick me.
Just a little.
Please.
I can't help it.
It moved.
Do you feel good no matter who licks you?
No.
Just a little.
Have you ever been licked other than me?
No.
Really?
Yes.
What's wrong with you?
You're very wet.
I feel so good.
You're not going to let it out, are you?
I want to.
No.
Don't let it out.
I want you to kiss me.
Do you think you're the only one who feels good?
I'm sorry.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
I want to kiss you.
I want to kiss you so much.
Can you feel good about me?
I'll do my best.
Won't you do it right away?
Let me kiss you.
Please.
You're gross.
I want to kiss you.
Then feel good about me.
I'll do my best.
Don't go right away.
Move until I'm satisfied.
So I did.
Move more.
Woa, it feels so nice.
Here, I guess.
Yes.
Oh, it feels so good.
Senpai, do you feel good, too?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Then I'll do my best to make you feel better.
What is it?
It's a lie.
Oh, I see.
Move a little more.
Okay.
Why did you stop me?
Move your head.
I'm sorry.
There.
Here?
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Look at me.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I want to kiss you.
It's only been a month.
Here.
It feels good.
Stick to me.
Yes.
No.
It feels good.
That's right.
Keep doing that.
Do it harder.
Yes.
No.
I can't do it anymore.
Don't do it until I say so.
Yes.
It feels good.
That's great.
This is great.
It feels good.
Let me do it forever.
I'll get angry if I do it on my own.
Don't do it.
I missed the last train because of you.
I'm sorry.
But...
If I do it...
I don't know what will happen.
Don't say that.
It feels good.
Don't do it.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
It feels good.
It's great.
Why do you keep moving me?
Get up properly.
I'm sorry.
Hurry up.
Yes.
Get up properly.
More.
More?
It feels good.
I can do it.
No.
It feels good.
Can I do it?
No.
Let's go.
It's great.
Don't stop.
Yes.
Let's go.
Move me more.
Yes.
It feels good.
Move me more.
Yes.
It's great.
Hey.
I want you to move me more.
Yes.
Get up.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's still hot.
It feels good.
Support me.
Yes.
It feels good.
Touch me.
More.
More?
Move me more.
It's hot.
Yes.
You can do it.
Like this?
Yes.
Move me more.
Like this?
Yes.
Hurry up.
Move me more.
Like this?
Yes.
Move me more.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Yes.
Move me more.
There.
It's hot.
My legs are shaking.
Don't be afraid.
I'm sorry.
I'll be your support.
Don't pull me.
Yes.
It feels good.
Move me more.
It's hot.
Don't go until I say so.
Yes.
Move me more.
More.
Yes.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I can't stand it.
Move me more.
I can't do it.
I didn't say I can't do it.
I'm going to sleep.
Ouch!
I'm wet.
I'm so wet.
My clothes...
I'm sorry.
Ouch!
It's poisonous.
Hey.
Do you know?
My clothes are wet.
I'm sorry.
You know tomorrow, don't you?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Are you going to have a meeting?
Yes, from 2 o'clock.
It's an important meeting.
Yes, it is.
There will be a meeting of all the departments.
So, the atmosphere is heavy.
All the departments are strict.
By the way, did you finish the documents I asked you to do?
Yes, I did.
I finished 8 of them.
I think I can finish the rest.
Didn't you do it last week?
Couldn't you do it more efficiently?
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Yes?
I'm a little nervous this time.
What?
You'll be fine.
Come here.
I said I'd be fine.
I said it without thinking.
But you said it without thinking.
I'll be fine.
I said it without thinking.
Yes.
I'm so nervous.
Can you feel my heart?
No, I can't.
Touch my body with your bare hands.
Okay.
Don't you remember where I like?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm afraid someone will come.
Who?
Let me relax.
Relax.
Relax your back.
My back?
Like this?
Yes.
Hurry up.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, I got it.
Touch my favorite part.
Okay.
Like this?
Roll your body.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I can't do it if you don't tell me.
What?
I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry.
More.
I can't do it if you lick my nipples.
I want to relax.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
My back.
My legs.
Okay.
I can't relax if you touch my nipples.
What do you mean?
I'm afraid you'll make a noise if I touch your nipples.
I'm afraid you'll make a noise.
Let me relax.
Oh, I feel good.
No one is coming.
I can't.
I can't do it.
Don't say a word.
I can't.
Yeah.
You can walk
I feel sick
Teehe...
Hey!
You did well, Mom.
Thank you very much.
Do you want some coffee?
Yes, please.
Thank you.
How is it?
It's great.
Look at me.
Say cheese.
Ye!
I like you very much.
Thank you!
I have a question for you.
It's getting really hard.
This is almost like a company.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's just like this.
Oh, no.
It's so hot.
What?
This is no good.
You're doing too much.
Oh, no.
I'm going to throw up.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
It's a little before the meeting.
What if you can't speak?
I'm sorry.
It's delicious.
Well.
I was able to relax a little.
Maybe.
That's good.
Senpai.
Thank you for your hard work.
Nakano.
Did you finish the document I asked you to do?
I'm sorry.
I haven't finished it yet.
It's until 5 o'clock.
If you don't do it soon, it won't end.
Yes.
I'll finish it by then.
This is for today.
Good luck.
Thank you for your hard work.
You drank too much.
Did I?
You're pretty drunk.
Am I drunk?
I'm pretty drunk, too.
You don't like it, do you?
I don't like it.
Do you want to go again?
I don't want to go again.
Senpai.
It's rare.
What happened?
I...
Today...
It's my birthday.
What?
Really?
You should go first.
So...
Until the date changes...
I want you to go with me.
Can I?
Of course.
But...
Can I go with you?
I want to go with you.
Then...
Let's go again.
Yes.
Are you okay?
Hey.
You're going to drink a lot today, right?
Yes.
Zero.
I'm sorry.
I'm not good at drinking.
Are you hot?
Take this off.
Okay.
Touch my chest.
Hey.
Do you remember how to touch my chest?
Yes.
It feels good.
Hug me tighter.
Do you finally understand how to touch my chest?
Yes.
Okay.
Hey.
Touch my chest directly.
Okay.
It feels good.
My body is getting hot, isn't it?
Yes, it's hot.
It's hot.
It's because I drank alcohol.
I want you to feel better.
Otherwise, my body won't get hot.
Make me feel better.
Okay.
I feel good when you hug me.
You have a stiff neck, don't you?
Touch me.
It feels good.
I like this.
Touch me more.
It feels good.
I want you to hug me from behind.
I want you to feel better.
I'm getting used to it.
Hold me.
Look at me.
Make me feel better.
I want you to feel better.
I feel good.
I want you to hug me more.
It feels good.
I'm getting used to it.
You like being scratched like this, don't you?
Yes, I love it.
It's getting harder.
I'm getting bigger.
What do you want me to do with this?
I really like it.
Do you want me to do this?
It's getting harder.
You like being scratched like this, don't you?
I love it.
Does it feel good?
It's getting warmer.
What do you want me to do with this?
I want you to lick me.
You like this, don't you?
Does it feel good?
I can hear you.
It's harder than before.
I didn't do that to your boobs.
No.
You can't do that to my boobs.
I want this.
Me too.
Put it in my stomach.
Yes.
I put it in my stomach.
I like this.
It feels good.
I put it in my stomach.
Look at my face.
It hurts.
I'll put it in your stomach.
It feels good.
Don't look away.
Look at me.
My shoulders.
My waist moves on its own.
You like being with me, don't you?
I like it.
It feels good.
Don't stop me.
It's like a movie, isn't it?
It's big.
I feel like it's bigger than usual.
It's tight.
More.
It feels good.
Hey.
Did you see it?
Let's see it closer.
I like it.
I'm at my limit.
I feel like I can do it.
It feels good.
Thank you for being with me today.
Don't look at me too much.
I'm sorry.
What's up with you?
I only have 6 pages left.
You can't finish it at that pace.
I'm done with my work, so I'll go home.
Thank you for your hard work.
Midori, be nice to Nakano.
He's doing his best.
But it's not good for Nakano to be inefficient.
It's normal to do your best, isn't it?
I'm the guide, so don't say anything.
I'm sorry.
Nakano, Midori is strict, but do your best.
Don't quit.
I'm fine.
Thank you for your hard work.
Can I hold your hand?
Osawa may come back.
It's okay.
Even if he forgets something, he'll do it tomorrow.
Didn't Osawa say anything bad about me?
Midori is strict, but do your best.
Really? You don't like it?
It's not that I don't like it.
It's true that my work is inefficient.
You're doing it for me, aren't you?
I'm sorry.
It's hot, isn't it?
Yes, it's hot.
It's hot.
You're surprised from above.
I'm embarrassed.
It's hot.
Nakano, you love this place, don't you?
Yes.
You're purring.
Why are you like this?
Because you touch me all the time.
It's my fault, isn't it?
Yes.
It's hot.
I have to take the responsibility of making Nakano-kun's nipples dull.
Responsibility?
It's hot.
When I see your happy face, I'm getting hot, too.
Show me your nipples.
It feels good.
It's too big.
I'm sorry.
This side, too.
Yes.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You're purring.
Is this my fault, too?
Yes.
I have to take responsibility of this side, too.
I'm sorry.
Something came out.
It's hot.
There's a lot of liquid coming out.
I'll wipe it off for you.
Yes.
It's hot.
Does it feel good to be licked?
It feels good.
You like to be pinched by my boobs, don't you?
I love it.
I'll pinch you.
Yes.
It's hot.
You look like you're in a good mood.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's getting hotter and hotter in my boobs.
It's gotten bigger.
It feels good.
If you can't stand it, you can let it out.
It's okay.
It feels good.
There's a lot of liquid.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You look like you're in a good mood.
It's hot.
Let out a lot.
It's amazing.
It's in my boobs.
It's hot.
There's a lot of liquid.
I'll clean it up for you.
It's hot.
Are you done?
Do you feel good about me?
Yes.
It's hot.
I want to make you feel better.
It feels good.
I can't do this.
You like this, don't you?
I love you.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Do you want to drink this?
I love this.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Do you want to drink this?
I love you.
Show me a lot.
Make me feel better.
Yes.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's hot.
I can't do this.
I'm going to cry.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can't do this.
It's hot.
I'm going to cry.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Make me feel better.
Like this?
I'm going to sleep again.
It feels good.
I'm going to cry.
I want to cry.
I have to drink.
Are you ready?
I'm going to cry.
It feels good.
Hey, hey, hey.
Here
I'm going to die.
It's amazing.
I can't move.
I can't.
Here.
I'm going to die.
I can't.
It's amazing.
I'm going to die.
I'm so sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
I'm going to die.
Stack up one more...
Where's comfortable?
Does it hit?
It's hitting...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I can't stand it anymore
I'm fine
What is it?
I want to see your face
Are you okay?
No, I'm fine
I'm fine, too
Oh, it tickles
Wow
Wow, it's hot
Can you see me?
Yes
Oh
Wow
Hey
Your face is dirty
Oh
Let's continue at the hotel
What?
Are you still going to do it?
Yes
You can't change in this state, can you?
Yes.