This is the first time I've ever seen such a thing.
I'm not sure if it's just me, but I've never seen such a thing before.
Let me see.
What's this?
This box looks huge.
It's bigger than I thought.
That's right.
Let me see.
What should I do?
Osawa-kun.
Oh, there you are.
Osawa-kun, I've completed the report.
Oh, well.
What are you looking at?
Uh...
Do you have cellulite because you're looking at this?
Excuse me...
Do you remember that you have an important consultation in a month, Osawa-kun?
Ah, yes, of course.
It's with Professor E.S. Abe, right?
Yes.
Please sign up for that consultation.
I can't concentrate on my work because I'm being asked to do this.
What?
Listen, if you don't protect it properly, it will affect the assessment.
If you have the materials I asked for, bring them to me.
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
Good morning.
I'm with the president today.
It's nice.
But it's too stimulating for a muscle man.
Stop it.
When I think about the president, my body is starting to shake.
I don't know.
I think he's the one.
Do you want to stay at my house tonight?
He might invite me.
What?
That's impossible.
What's wrong?
Ouch.
That's impossible.
Osawa-kun.
Yes, president.
How long are you going to be in the office?
You haven't forgotten the consultation with the president, have you?
Yes, of course.
Don't forget it because it's at 20 o'clock.
What is it?
Do you keep your promise?
Yes, I do.
That's good.
I'm counting on you.
Osawa-kun.
What's this?
It smells so good.
I know.
I appreciate your customer service.
Thank you very much.
But my son is working at a company where you two work together.
You know what I mean, don't you?
But we've been working together for many years.
I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to president Nagi.
I know.
That's why my heart aches when I think about it.
It's really hard for me, too.
Right, Norika-chan?
It's all thanks to you.
If you say so, I'll do my best, too.
Let's drink.
Thank you.
Go ahead.
That's a good drink.
Let's drink more and more.
That's good.
Drink more and more.
That's a good drink.
Let's drink more and more.
Nagi-Kato, you're a good talker.
I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you, too.
Let's drink, Nagi-Kato.
Let's drink more and more.
Drink more.
That's a good drink.
Let's drink more and more.
Boss, are you okay?
You drank a lot.
I'm okay.
He's the worst.
He looked at my chest and touched my body.
He was a bad drinker.
I want to drink again at home.
Go out with me.
Now?
I don't want to.
I don't care.
But...
I want to drink again at home.
Boss, are you sure you want to drink again?
It's okay.
I'll give you a taxi.
Let's drink together.
Just a little.
I'm not a strong drinker.
Don't say that.
Let's drink together.
Okay.
Let's go home.
You're too aggressive.
You should be more aggressive.
Am I aggressive?
I'm not good at that.
If you're not good at it,
you're doing a good job.
Thank you.
You don't want to be repaid, do you?
You're a bad drinker.
Everyone doesn't know that.
So, you have to show off.
It's hot.
Stop it.
I'm going to be sick for a month.
I'm going to lose my mind.
Stop it.
It smells good.
I'm sleepy.
Your boobs are swollen.
I've always wanted to do this.
Your boobs were beautiful.
But I can't.
I can't stop it.
I'm going to be sick for a month.
It hurts.
It hurts here.
I can't do it anymore.
You can't do it anymore?
Don't do it.
I can't stand it anymore.
Stop it.
Don't lick it.
It's delicious.
Stop it.
You can't do it.
I'm not sick.
I can't get a job.
I'm sick.
It's okay.
It's delicious.
Stop it.
I'm sick.
I can't get a job.
Stop it.
You're sweating.
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are.
Show me your eyes.
No, I'm not.
Why are you crying?
I'm not crying.
I just spilled alcohol.
Stop it.
You can't spill alcohol.
Don't look at me.
Stop it.
You're sweating.
Don't look at me.
Stop it.
I told you not to look at me.
Don't put your fingers in my eyes.
I'm sweating.
Don't do that.
Don't put your fingers in my eyes.
My fingers are soaked.
Don't do that.
Don't move me.
What are you doing?
Kacchan.
Don't lick me.
I didn't take a shower.
It's delicious.
Don't lick me.
That's enough.
Can I taste it?
Don't taste it.
Let me lick you more.
Don't lick me.
Kacchan.
Let's do more.
Don't do that.
Kacchan.
Don't stop.
Why don't you stop?
Kacchan.
Don't touch me.
It's my fault.
It's my fault?
It's so tight here.
I'm sorry.
Don't let me out.
Kacchan.
Let me out.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Kacchan.
Stay still.
Don't do that.
Don't lick my nipples.
I don't blame you.
I...
Don't lick my nipples.
I did it for you.
I couldn't get a job while I was in the hospital.
I've been thinking about this all the time.
You've been thinking about this all the time?
Is that so?
That's not good.
That's not a job.
That's why I couldn't get a job.
Please take responsibility for this.
Kacchan.
Come here.
Please hold my nipples.
Is that so?
This is it.
Do you like this?
Yes.
It's getting harder and harder.
It feels good.
I'm getting sleepy.
Kacchan.
I licked your nipples.
Can you lick my nipples?
Nipples?
Don't you like me?
Are you satisfied?
I'm satisfied.
Please.
It's getting harder and harder.
It's salty.
I had a lot of water in my mouth.
Actually, I had a lot of water in my mouth when I was young.
Did you think about that when you were young?
I only thought about my mother-in-law.
Mother-in-law.
It feels good.
Are you satisfied?
Kacchan.
Can you lick my nipples?
My nipples?
It's getting harder and harder.
Please.
Are you satisfied?
I'm satisfied.
It's special.
Please.
You only think about this at work, don't you?
That's right.
It feels good.
You should be ready to quit your job.
I'll do my best.
I'm full of nipples.
It's soft and nice.
It's hard.
It feels good.
Are you satisfied?
It's getting harder and harder.
Kacchan, let me see your nipples.
It's hard.
It's all out.
It's like a lump.
Please clean it up.
There's still some left.
Are you satisfied?
I haven't cleaned my nipples for a month.
What are you going to do?
I can't be satisfied with my boobs alone.
What do you want to say?
Please let me see your nipples.
Don't do that.
I can't be satisfied with my boobs alone.
We are your boss and subordinates.
I can't stand it.
I'll do it again.
I have to see your nipples.
Don't do that.
Let me see your nipples.
It's been a long time since I've seen my nipples.
It's hard all of a sudden.
It feels good.
Don't do that.
I can't stop it.
It feels good.
Don't do that.
I can't be satisfied with my boobs alone.
It feels good.
Don't do that.
I can't stop it.
It feels good.
Don't do that.
I'll do it again.
It's hard all of a sudden.
Don't do that.
Can I put it in from behind?
Is it here?
Don't do that.
It's hard.
It feels good.
You like my nipples, don't you?
Don't say that.
Don't do that.
It's getting tight.
I can't breathe.
Don't do that.
Can you sit on me?
Me?
I just moved my hips.
Can you sit on me?
Can I sit on you?
Yes, please.
I don't know anymore.
It feels good.
Your nipples are shaking a lot.
It's really bad.
Don't do that.
I just moved my hips.
It hurts.
It's really bad.
I just moved my hips.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
It's getting tight.
Don't do that.
It feels good.
It's really bad.
Can I hug you?
I want to hug you.
I love you.
It's hot.
It feels good.
What are you talking about?
It's not over yet.
What do you mean?
I was on a one-month contract.
I can still do it.
I'm on fire, too.
I want you to go out with me.
You're amazing.
You're shaking your head.
I was on a one-month contract.
I can still do it.
Can you do more?
I'll give it a try.
It's harder than before.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hard again.
You're shaking your head.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
I love you so much.
You're amazing.
Does it feel good?
You like this.
It feels good.
You're sensitive.
It's hitting my stomach.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Do you know you're hitting me?
You're amazing.
It tickles.
Does it feel good?
You're amazing.
My cheeks are soft.
It's stuck.
It feels good.
I'll lick your cheeks.
It's hot.
Do you want me to do it?
Yes, please.
It feels good.
If you can't do it, you can do it anytime.
Yes.
Anytime.
I'm going to sleep.
It's sticking out.
It's sticky.
I'll clean it for you.
I have to take a shower again.
I have to go home.
What did you do?
I don't know.
It's okay.
It feels good.
It's hard.
It's getting harder.
Does it feel good?
I don't know what's going on.
It's getting hot.
Do you feel pain in your panties?
Yes.
I'm going to take this off.
Your voice is getting louder.
You want to do something more pleasant, don't you?
Yes.
Your buttocks are sticking out from the tip of your nose.
It feels good.
I'll lick it all off for you.
I've been on a one-month contract, so I can do more.
It's hard.
You've been looking at your boobs all this time, haven't you?
I'm sorry.
You really like it.
Do you want to be pinched?
Yes, I want to be pinched.
Then raise your hips.
You look happy.
You're cute.
Do you like being pinched so much?
Yes, I love it.
It's okay.
Feel good in your boobs.
You're making a lot of noise.
Why are you making such a noise?
I'm sorry.
Maybe the juice came out.
If you get pinched in your boobs, you'll get a lot of juice.
Give me more juice.
But you can't give me the white one yet.
It's getting bigger and bigger.
Can you stand it?
No, I can't stand it.
No, you can't stand it.
Was it dangerous?
It's going to come out.
You can't let it out so much.
I want you to feel good about me this time.
Make my boobs feel good.
Touch me as you like.
I like to be pinched.
Give me more.
It feels good.
My body is getting hot.
Tickle my nipples.
You can see that my nipples are hard, right?
It tickles.
I want you to pinch my boobs from behind.
I really like it.
I like it.
Give me more.
Like this?
How do you feel?
What do you think about my boobs?
It tickles.
It's wet.
Touch my boobs as you like.
I can't stand it.
It feels good.
Look at me.
Give me more.
Will you touch my boobs again tomorrow?
It tickles.
Look at me closely.
Rub my boobs a lot.
It tickles, doesn't it?
Make my boobs feel good.
I like it.
It tickles.
Make my boobs feel good.
It tickles, doesn't it?
I can't stand it.
It tickles again.
I made your boobs feel good, so I'll give you a reward.
It tickles.
You like it here, don't you?
I haven't touched your boobs yet.
I'll touch your nails first.
It tickles, doesn't it?
It feels good.
Your nails are getting harder.
It tickles.
Is it okay to make it so hard?
It's very hard.
My nails are as hard as your nails.
Do you want me to massage your nipples?
Yes, please.
It feels good.
Is this good?
How about this side?
Your nipples are trembling in your boobs.
Do you want me to touch your nipples?
I can't help it.
Does it feel good even if I touch your nipples?
I want you to tickle me.
It tickles.
Is this good?
Don't move.
I'm sorry.
It tickles.
I've been touching your nipples for a long time, and I want to tickle you.
It tickles, doesn't it?
Look at me when I tickle you.
I'm going to tickle you.
I've tickled all your nipples.
Do you feel good when I tickle your nipples?
Your nipples are getting harder.
It tickles.
I want to tickle your nipples, too.
I want to tickle your nipples.
It tickles.
Ah.
Take a good look at my face.
Ah...
I think I can win.
Check my face, okay?
Okay.
See?
You had a hard time...
Now Osawa will sit on top
Hurry up and close your mouth.
Ah, that feels good.
Hey, give me more.
Ah...
It feels good...
What's the matter?
You're almost there, but you can't do it yet.
I'll help you get to the top next time.
It can't be helped.
You can do it.
Make me feel better.
I'll do my best.
You want to do it again, don't you?
Yes.
You look like you want to do it again.
But you can't do it in your stomach.
Yes.
Do you want to do it in your boobs again?
It's so hot.
You can do it in your boobs again.
You can't do it?
I'll look at your face when you do it.
I want to do it in my boobs again.
It's so hot.
I'll clean it for you.
It's not soft, is it?
If you don't do it more, it won't be soft.
I didn't say that.
You've been on a diet for a month, so you can do it, right?
I want to do it in my boobs again.
You can do it in my boobs again.
It's so hot again.
I want to do it in my boobs again.
You can do it in my boobs again.
It's so hot.
I want to do it in my boobs again.
You can do it in my boobs again.
I can't do it anymore.
You can't do it anymore?
You don't know if you don't do it at work, do you?
Let's do something more pleasant together.
Let's go home.
I really have to go home.
I have to get ready for work.
You can go home from here.
If I work this hard,
It's okay.
I'll follow you.
It feels good.
You can't go home because you've grown up so much, can you?
That's...
I'll pour you a lot of hot water.
How do you feel?
Don't you want your boobs again?
Get up.
Do you want me to scratch your boobs?
You like this kind of thing.
Your boobs are too big.
It feels good.
It's stuck in your boobs.
Do you want me to put it in your boobs?
I'll put it in your boobs.
I'm nervous.
Use your waist.
It feels good.
It's soft.
I'll put it in your boobs.
It feels good.
It's stuck in your boobs.
It's hard.
Use your waist.
It feels good.
I can't get it out.
Don't get it out yet.
I'll put it in your boobs.
It feels good.
I'll do what you like.
Will you do it for me?
Can I take it off?
It feels good.
It's hard.
I'll put it in your boobs.
It's hard again.
You like being with me like this, don't you?
I love this.
This?
It feels good.
I love this.
It's harder than before, isn't it?
It's hard.
I'll put it in your boobs.
Please.
It's hard.
It feels good.
It's soft.
I'll put it in your boobs.
It's hard.
I'm sweating a lot.
Don't let it out yet.
Don't let it out.
You're sweating a lot.
But you can't.
I can't.
I told you not to.
I couldn't stand it anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's not over yet.
Be nice to me.
I'll put it in your boobs.
You have to kiss me.
It feels good.
Is it good?
It's good.
Your nipples are getting harder.
My nipples are getting harder.
It feels good.
I want you to feel better.
Come here.
Touch my boobs.
Be nice at first.
When you get used to it, it gets harder.
Does it feel good?
You really like boobs.
I'm so excited just by touching your boobs.
Let me touch your boobs.
Your body has changed.
It's soft.
Let me touch your neck.
Does it feel good?
Your neck is stiff.
Let me touch your belly.
Does it feel good?
I'm sweating.
Let me touch your belly.
Does it feel good?
I'm going to be a mess.
How was it?
Ah, this feels good.
Ah, it's going away.
It's going away.
Phew..
It feels good.
Is it good?
Phew, that was nice.
Hmm?
Ah...
I'm going to look back a little from the left.
Hmm...
Ah, I like that one.
Is that the one?
Yes, yes.
Ah, that's nice.
Ah, I'm going.
I'm going.
Ah...
Hmm...
Chief...
I can't sleep.
How are you?
You're hurting me, right?
Ow, it hurts.
Ouch.
Don't eat it.
No, no, don't eat it.
It was sour.
It was sour and disgusting.
I'm sorry.
I'll lick you as a reward for making me feel better.
Did you do this to me?
It's delicious.
It's disgusting.
Do you want me to lick you again?
Yes.
You really like it.
Look closely.
I can see that it's getting very hot.
Can you see that my nipples are wrinkled?
Yes.
It feels good to be wrinkled.
Do you want me to put it in your head?
I put it in your head.
It's very hard.
Are you going to sleep?
I'm going to sleep.
Give me a lot.
You're out again.
I can't help it.
I'll make you beautiful again.
You're making me sick.
Why are you out twice?
If you do that, I'll sleep.
I haven't gotten any better yet.
Can you kiss me?
I'll do my best.
Come here.
I'll put it in.
I'll make you feel better.
Mike...
Mike, I can be happy if I have you.
It's my turn now.
You shouldn't do that.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I won't forgive you if you do that again.
I'm sorry.
I feel like I won.
It feels good.
You shouldn't do that.
Do it more.
It feels good.
You shouldn't do that.
Do it more.
How is it?
You shouldn't do that.
Do it more.
I can't do this.
You shouldn't do that.
Look at me.
It feels good.
Do it more.
I can't do this.
It feels good.
Your father is amazing.
You should get some rest.
You shouldn't do that.
It hurts.
It's hot.
I can see where you want to go.
You shouldn't do that.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
You shouldn't do that.
Do it more.
It hurts.
It feels good.
You shouldn't do that.
You should get some rest.
Do you know how much I love you?
I love you so much.
You shouldn't do that.
Do it more.
It feels good.
You shouldn't do that.
Your butt hurts, right?
It's different from before.
This is bad.
Do it more.
You shouldn't do that.
This is bad.
You should do it more.
It hurts.
This is bad.
Do it more.
You should do it more.
It feels good.
Do it more.
You shouldn't do that.
You should do it more.
It feels good.
Do it more.
Can you hug me?
I'm scared.
I'm going to die.
I can't do it.
I want to do it while looking at your face.
Do it more.
Don't look at me.
I'm looking at you.
I can't do it.
I like you.
I want to hug you.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Why are you taking off your clothes?
I want to feel better.
Do you want to do it again?
I can't stand it anymore.
I'll squeeze you with my boobs again.
Do you want to do it again?
I'm sorry.
Did I hurt you?
You're sweating a lot.
I made you feel so good.
You're going to do something nice with me all day, aren't you?
Do you want me to think about it?
I'll do it until tomorrow's exam.
Do you understand?