What is this?
The numbers are totally different.
The numbers are so different. Why did you submit this?
I'm sorry.
It's not sorry.
Are you okay?
Did you review this?
I was in a hurry, so I didn't review it.
Don't submit it without reviewing it.
I'm sorry.
Can you make it in time for the meeting with this?
Make it again.
I'm in a hurry, so I'll make it again.
What made you angry today?
This is it.
Let me see.
What should I do?
How long will this take?
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Can you make it in time?
I think it'll be okay.
I'm in a hurry.
Thank you for your hard work today.
Thank you for your hard work.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm counting on you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Which one was this?
What should I do?
What was this?
This is too difficult.
I haven't used this when I had a heart attack.
What should I do?
What's wrong with you?
I'm fine.
I came to see how you were doing.
Really?
Thank you.
What should I do?
Change your clothes.
Okay.
It's starting to rain. Let's hurry.
Can you sit down?
Look at this.
It's starting to rain. Let's hurry.
It's done.
I thought I couldn't do it today.
You made a mistake from the first time.
All the numbers are wrong.
I'm sorry.
Why is it like this?
Let's go this way.
There's a warning sign.
What should I do?
The train has stopped.
It's like a blackout.
I don't think I can do it today.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to sleep here.
Do you want to sleep in the car?
I don't want to sleep in the car.
I'm going to sleep in the cafe.
Now?
If you sleep in the cafe tomorrow, you'll have to do it again.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to sleep in the cafe tomorrow.
I'm counting on you.
It's my responsibility.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
Come to my house.
What?
I'll be in the taxi in five minutes.
I'm going.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Get in the car.
I can't get in the taxi.
You can put your luggage down.
I'll get the towel.
Thank you.
Towel.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad I'm still close to my house.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I'll do it myself.
I'm going to catch a cold.
Are you...
a virgin?
How did you know that?
I knew it.
You're a virgin, so you know that.
Wipe it yourself.
I'll take a shower.
Can I take a shower?
Thank you.
Senpai.
What?
I...
Senpai, please.
What?
Wait a minute.
Calm down.
Senpai.
I can't stand it.
What are you doing?
Your boobs are so big.
I'm not stupid.
I'm worried about you.
That's enough.
I can't stand it anymore.
What are you doing?
Are you really stupid?
Senpai.
Wait a minute.
Show me your boobs.
No.
It's strange.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
Senpai.
It's hot here.
It's not hot.
Do you know what you're doing?
I can't stand it anymore.
I didn't ask you.
Senpai.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's strange that you're stupid.
Show me your boobs.
It's strange.
Wait a minute.
Senpai.
It's not something you can see.
It's strange.
What are you doing?
It's hot.
Wait a minute.
No, it's not hot.
You don't have to do it so fast.
I want to make you feel better.
No.
I can't do it.
It's over there.
Senpai.
No.
Wait a minute.
I don't want to do it anymore.
I'm sleepy.
Why did you let me sleep?
Can I look at you?
It's a big problem.
I want to see you directly.
I don't want to see you directly.
It's amazing.
It's big.
It's a big problem.
I want you to take this off.
Why am I the only one who is naked?
It's not a big problem.
It's amazing.
It's a big problem.
I'm sorry.
You have a very attractive boob.
Don't blame me.
I'm sorry.
I want to see you.
It's a big problem.
It's amazing.
Why are you looking at me?
It's a big problem.
You've touched me enough.
Do you want me to lick you?
It's a big problem.
Do you want me to lick you from above?
That's not what I want to do.
Wow...
Wow, amazing.
your display of affection is amazing.
I really like you.
Okay.
Not only that side.
Why don't we take off our clothes together?
Okay.
Why are you so rough when I take off my clothes?
What? I'm trying to take off my clothes gently.
I'm sorry.
You're not good at it.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
I'm sorry.
What about your tongue?
Don't you say sorry?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
This is mine.
What are you going to do?
I want you to touch me more.
Do you want me to touch you more?
Do you want me to whisper to you?
Yes.
Your hands feel so good.
Do you want me to touch you only with my hands?
I want you to lick my lips.
Your lips?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
It's getting harder than before.
It feels so good when you lick my lips.
You did it faster when I did it.
I'm sorry.
It feels so good.
I was surprised. I thought you were going to do it on your own.
It feels so good that I might go home soon.
Don't do that.
You touched me and licked me.
Are you done?
I want to have sex with you.
I'm going to pinch your boobs.
My boobs?
Yes.
Like this?
What are you doing?
It tickles.
It's okay.
It feels so good because your boobs are big.
It tickles.
I think I can bear it.
It feels so good.
It tickles.
It feels so good because your boobs are big.
That's because I'm touching you.
It feels so good.
I want to have sex with you.
You shouldn't do that.
I can't bear it.
You should bear it with your boobs.
You shouldn't say that.
It feels so good.
Wait a minute.
It tickles.
How can you move so fast?
It feels so good.
I know.
It tickles.
It feels so good.
A little more.
It tickles.
You know.
Why do you keep shaking your body?
Excuse me.
It tickles.
I'm sorry!
I'm telling you.
It hurts!
Are you listening to me?
I'm telling you.
It feels good.
Are you listening to me?
I'm telling you.
Why don't you know the limit?
It feels good.
I'm telling you.
It hurts!
It feels good.
I'm telling you.
It hurts again.
Are you listening to me?
I'm telling you.
It hurts.
I don't know anymore.
How long are you going to lick my clothes?
Can I lick you directly?
I don't know until you tell me.
Are you sure?
I'm telling you.
It feels good.
I'm going to take a shower.
You go first.
I'm going to catch a cold.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I can't get hot water.
Hot water?
I'm sorry.
I forgot to put a bottle in it.
I think I can get hot water with this.
Wait a minute.
Can I take it out?
Yes.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Don't get carried away.
I'm sorry.
Why are you standing?
Are you okay?
Your boobs are very big.
I'm worried.
You're standing.
I'm sorry.
Was it this hard?
No.
Your boobs are getting bigger.
I'm sorry.
Is it so funny?
It's soft.
I want to touch it forever.
I'm sorry to touch you forever.
Are you cold?
Yes.
I'm cold because I'm wet.
Can I take a shower normally?
You can take a shower as it is.
As it is?
Take a shower as it is.
Take a shower as it is?
It's warm.
You're wetter than before.
You're wet.
I'm sorry.
It's warm.
You're wetter than before.
I'm sorry.
You're great.
Can I get warm?
Aren't you cold?
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I think it's a good idea.
What did you do?
I did something erotic.
Can you tell me more specifically?
You licked me.
Where?
I want you to lick me.
But you won't touch my boobs.
I'm sorry.
I want to touch your boobs more.
Where?
You did.
I'm sorry.
I want to touch your boobs.
I am blue.
How do you feel when you touch my hand?
It's the best.
It's time for me to sleep.
Are you sure?
It feels so good.
It's hot.
Is it okay to be licked?
Well...
Well?
What?
I want you to feel good with your boobs.
With my boobs?
Feel good?
How?
I want you to pinch my boobs.
With my boobs.
Like this?
It feels so good.
It's getting hard.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels so good.
It feels so good.
What's that face?
You should feel better.
It feels so good.
Are you moving it by yourself?
You can move it by yourself, right?
Yes.
It feels so good.
Does it hurt?
No, it doesn't.
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels so good.
It feels so good.
I can't do it anymore.
Can you do it?
Yes, I can't stand it.
I can do it.
It suddenly became warm.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't stand it.
What are you doing?
I'm cleaning your nose.
Do you still want to do it?
No, I just took it out.
Don't you want to touch it?
I want you to touch it.
I don't want to.
I'll take a shower.
Don't you want to touch it?
Why?
Why do you want me to touch it?
In 30 words.
I don't want to do it.
It's warm.
How is it?
It feels good.
That's it.
Do you want to try it?
No, I don't want to.
That's not good.
What's wrong?
You're cute.
What?
You're very cute.
I'm going to sleep.
Are you hungry?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's hot.
Do you have a fever?
I have a fever.
I'm going to the store.
I'm going to buy some medicine.
It's raining outside.
I have a meeting tomorrow.
I'm fine.
I'm going to buy it.
I'm going to sleep.
You have a bad cold.
I'm sorry to bother you.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
You have a fever, don't you?
I'm fine.
What's wrong with you?
Don't move.
I'm fine.
You have a bad cold.
I like cold.
I don't care if you have a bad cold.
I'm fine.
I want to sleep.
I'm going to take care of you.
Take care of me.
You're fine even if you have a fever.
I feel great.
You're very hard.
You have a fever.
You don't have to say that.
I feel great.
I want to make you feel better.
Here?
Do you like my boobs?
I love your boobs.
Can I touch you?
Your boobs are the best.
Your fever will go up if you do this.
I want to touch you more.
Can I touch you?
It's getting harder.
Why do you always do your best?
I feel so good.
Your fever will go up.
I'm tired.
Can I sleep now?
I'm ticklish.
I feel so good.
I'm fine.
You look good.
It's hot.
I'm sweating so much.
My hands feel so good.
I can't stop breathing.
It's hot.
I feel so good.
I can't stop breathing.
Good morning.
I'm sweating a lot.
I feel so good.
That's good.
What's wrong?
You should go to bed.
No.
You're sensitive because it's morning.
You haven't done anything yet.
Why are you standing up?
You're sweating.
What's wrong?
I thought it was a good view.
Your boobs are the best.
What?
Your boobs are big and beautiful.
Did you wake up?
Let's go to bed.
Can I do this in a meeting?
Why?
If I do this, I can't concentrate during the meeting.
You can concentrate because you do this.
I'm bored.
You're excited, aren't you?
We both are.
I'm excited.
I'm sleepy.
I feel great.
I want to do this.
I can't do this.
I want to sleep.
I feel great.
I can't do it anymore...
It feels so good...
I'm sorry...
Are you okay?
Yes.