I see, an influencer's production company.
Yes, that's right.
Rather than booking an existing influencer,
I'm thinking of mainly recruiting new people and training them.
It's true that there are a lot of people who admire the super-famous influencer, Unpai-chan.
Above all, her social media buzz and know-how are different from others.
She's cute and talented.
I want to support those who want to be famous.
Then let me join you.
By the way, there's an event in Kansai next weekend.
There's someone I'd like to introduce to you.
Really?
She's strong in the entertainment industry, and she's also popular with famous influencers.
Let me introduce her to you.
I'd love to.
But the president is traveling abroad next week.
So I'd like to host the event myself.
Unpai-chan, are you coming?
Yes, I'm coming.
Takeuchi-kun, what are your plans for next weekend?
Next week...
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Where's he?
He's Takeuchi, a new employee.
Takeuchi-kun, say hello.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Nice to meet you. I'm Takeuchi.
Takeuchi-kun.
Takeuchi-kun, why did you join this company?
I'm a big fan of yours, and I wanted to work with you.
It's great that we can work together.
Yes, it's fun every day.
I see.
I think I'll be able to adjust it next weekend.
I'll leave it to you.
I'll be happy if you come.
Thank you.
See you next week.
I'll email you the details.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to next week.
See you.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I left my cell phone here.
Get a hold of yourself.
You just started the company, so your impression is important.
Yes.
Let's do today's shooting.
Can you do it?
Yes.
How is it?
Can you do it?
Yes.
Let's do it.
Okay.
How is it?
Can you do it?
Yes.
It's not good.
What?
Can you do it again?
It was good.
It's not good.
Let's do it again.
Okay.
I want to do it again.
Let's do it.
Okay.
It was good.
I'll change my clothes.
I'll give you the clothes.
Okay.
Let's do the next shoot.
Excuse me.
Hey.
What's wrong?
I...
I'm sorry. I just turned it off.
What? Why?
What do you mean?
Oh, it's gone.
I have to save it.
Do you want to go again?
I'm sorry.
Takeuchi-kun, it's okay because it's me, but if it's a client, it's over.
Next time it's okay.
Well, let's take a break and take a picture again.
Yes.
Takeuchi-kun, it's okay because it's me, but if it's a client, it's over.
Next time it's okay.
Takeuchi-kun.
What are you doing?
I'm checking the equipment.
Hmm.
Oh, that's right. Takeuchi-kun, who is in charge of Kansai next weekend, will also go with you.
Eh, me?
Yeah. I'll send you an email when I get the details, so check it out.
Make a reservation for a hotel with a Shinkansen ticket.
Yes, I understand.
It's an opportunity to expand your business, so don't miss it.
Yes.
See you.
Takeuchi-kun.
Yes.
You're tired, right?
I can't believe that two famous influencers signed a contract.
Yeah, but they were great too.
They got away with it.
Right?
But at a time like this...
Isn't it bad?
Yeah.
I'd like to eat something,
but let's check in at the hotel first.
Yeah, let's do that.
Oh, they're here.
Let's go.
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake in booking.
This is the only room available.
What?
You mean...
the other room?
I'm sorry.
But there's another room.
This way.
I'm sorry.
What's this?
Is this a love hotel?
No.
Every room is full.
This is the only room available.
I'm sorry.
Seriously.
I have to decide what to do tomorrow.
There's room service.
Let's eat in the room and have a meeting.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Can I have room service?
Yes.
I'd like a bottle of white wine.
I'm sorry.
Can I go home tomorrow?
I'll call you before I go to bed.
Bye.
I'm sorry.
You have a girlfriend?
Yes.
I promised to call you before I go to bed.
I'm sorry.
Isn't it bad to have a room service with me?
Well...
I want a boyfriend.
I'm sorry.
It's delicious.
I'm hungry.
So, I drink a lot.
You drink too much.
You have a strong tolerance for alcohol.
But I don't drink at all.
Drinking is very important in this job.
I'm sorry.
I don't drink much.
Do you have a strong tolerance for alcohol?
Do you think so?
You don't drink much.
And you don't have much sexual desire.
I don't drink much.
I don't have much sexual desire.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I just started dating.
I don't have a girlfriend yet.
You don't have a girlfriend yet?
I see.
I feel like I'm being watched while I'm shooting.
I'm a big fan of you.
You've been a fan of me before I started dating, haven't you?
Yes.
I've been a fan of you since I was a student.
Do you still like me?
I'm sorry.
Are you excited?
No, I'm not.
I'm kidding.
Are you a virgin?
You're blushing.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
It's late.
I'm getting sleepy.
I'm going to bed.
Senpai.
Are you really a virgin?
I'm going to bed.
Stop it.
What's wrong?
Did you invite me here?
I'm kidding.
Stop it.
Senpai invited me here.
What?
It was just a little spicy.
I know you well.
You know I've been a fan of yours for a long time.
And I know about the scandal with the president.
Wait, Takeuchi.
The picture at that time was secretly saved from the president's cell phone.
It would be terrible if that picture was on the Internet.
I'm going to bed.
Are you okay?
If you're nice to me, I won't tell anyone.
I'm sleepy.
Senpai.
I was kidding.
Stop it.
It's just a little spicy.
What's wrong?
Stop it.
Let me see it.
Don't do it.
Please don't do it.
Please.
Senpai, please be quiet.
Can I take a picture?
Can I?
I can't, right?
I'm sorry.
Let me go.
Don't do it.
I'm sorry.
I haven't taken a bath yet.
I'm fine.
Don't do it.
It's dirty.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I don't like it.
I'm sorry.
Don't do it.
Can I take a picture?
It's dirty.
It's not dirty at all.
I'm sorry.
Don't do it.
Do you feel good?
I didn't expect it.
Did you go to the bathroom?
No, I didn't.
Really?
Don't do it.
Don't you feel good?
You have a lot of pimples here.
I don't have pimples.
You have pimples.
Don't do it.
I don't have pimples.
I'll put my finger in your pimples.
Don't do it.
I'm sorry.
Wake up.
Please.
Don't do it.
I'm sorry.
You have a lot of pimples.
What is this?
Did you feel so good?
Don't do it.
I want you to lick my pimples.
Please lick my pimples.
I don't want to.
Don't do it.
If I lick your pimples, I'll end it.
What do you think?
I'm sorry.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Don't do it.
I'm sorry.
I want you to lick my pimples.
Don't do it.
If you lick my pimples, I'll end it.
I don't want to.
Please wake up.
Don't do it.
If you don't lick my pimples, I'll end it.
I don't want to.
Do you feel good?
It's hot.
I want you to lick my pimples.
I told you to lick my pimples.
Please take this off.
I didn't say I would take this off.
Please show me your pimples.
Do you feel good?
What is it?
It's hot.
It feels good.
I don't want to.
I haven't taken it off yet.
Please show me your pimples.
Do you feel good?
Please take this off.
I don't want to.
Can I put this in your mouth?
You're lying.
I didn't say I would put it in your mouth.
I didn't break my promise.
You just said you would put it in your mouth.
You're lying.
Can I put it in your mouth?
Don't say that.
I'm begging you.
I don't want to.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I'm begging you.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
I don't want to.
It feels good.
I'm fine now.
Are you sure?
I don't want to.
I want to do it again.
Can I do it again?
I'm sorry.
I don't want to.
Don't move.
Stop it.
I don't want to.
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
Did you leave?
Did you?
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
I feel bad.
Are you satisfied?
Not yet.
Yes.
I'm fine.
I got your contract.
Thank you.
Yes.
Takiuchi-kun is with me this time.
Did you go to bed?
Yes.
Thank you.
Really?
Yes.
When I go back to Tokyo...
When I go back to Tokyo, I'll get your contract.
Yes.
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Hey.
What are you going to do if they find out?
I'm not sleeping yet.
Don't lie to me.
You want to do more, don't you?
Idiot.
It's not like that.
I still want to do it.
What?
You just did it, didn't you?
I can still do it.
What?
When I do it alone, I do it five or six times a day.
Five or six times?
I still want to do it.
What?
Can you pinch me with your boobs?
Don't you watch too many movies?
Please.
I won't do it again when I go back to Tokyo.
Just today.
Okay.
Don't look at me like that.
Can I do it?
I still want to do it.
Is this okay?
Yes.
Why is it so hard?
It feels good.
Hey.
Don't do it again when I go back to Tokyo.
Okay.
Don't do it.
What's wrong?
Hey.
What are you doing?
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Don't do it.
Come here.
Hurry up.
What's going on?
I'm going to sleep here.
Don't do it.
What?
Lie down there.
Like this?
Please lie down.
That's right.
I don't know how to do it.
I've never done it, so I don't know how to do it.
But you're good at it.
Like this?
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Please lie down.
What?
I can't do it.
Like this?
It feels good.
Give me a break.
I can't do it.
I'll do it next.
Please lie down.
I'll do it.
I can't do it.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
You've done a lot.
I can't do it.
I really can't do it.
What's wrong?
Please do it again.
I can't do it.
Stop it.
I was very nervous.
I can't do it.
This is the best.
Do you feel good?
I don't feel good.
Stop it.
It's not enough.
Come here.
What's going on?
Why is it so hard?
I just did it.
What's going on?
I can't believe it.
It's not enough.
I can't do it.
Ouch!
I'm not done yet.
No!
I can't do it!
Ouch!
I can't do it anymore.
I'm not finished yet.
Ouch!
I can't do it anymore.
My whole body is moving.
What is it.
Do you want to go to sleep?
do you want to go to sleep?
I can not go.
Ah...
Oh...
Takeuchi-kun is too amazing...
I can't take it anymore...
He's too amazing...
Eh?
I can't take it?
Eh? Wait...
Eh? I can't take it anymore...
Wait a minute...
It's okay...
No...
Eh?
Um...
If you can't take it anymore...
Can I sleep with you?
Eh?
No...
I can't take it anymore...
Eh?
You can sleep with me from now on...
Um...
Ah...
Senpai...
Um...
Let's sleep together...
Wait...
Ah...
No...
Um...
Ah...
No...
What's wrong?
Ah...
It feels good, right?
Because you touch me a lot...
Ah...
Wait...
Yes...
Eh?
Ah...
Oh...
I cannot...
Yes...
My neck is cramping...
Ah...
Um...
Stop it...
Wait a minute...
Ah...
Okay...
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
I love you so much.
It's very sensitive.
I'm sorry.
I love you so much.
It's getting bigger.
I can't get up.
I love you so much.
It's embarrassing.
It's very sensitive here, too.
It tickles.
It feels good.
I can't get up.
It hurts.
Senpai.
You said you'd give birth to five or six babies a day.
I'm imagining you.
It's like a dream.
I can give birth to as many as I want.
It's too heavy.
I can't get up.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I can't get up.
It's embarrassing.
Does it feel good?
I can't get up.
Mom.
It's harder than before.
I can't get up.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I can't get up.
It's embarrassing.
You lick me a lot.
I don't do that.
Can I put this in your mouth?
Again?
Yes.
Can I put this in your mouth again?
I put it in your mouth.
Why are you standing like that?
It's amazing.
I can't get up.
Does it feel good?
It hurts.
I can't get up.
Does it feel good?
My hands are too stiff.
You lick me a lot.
I can't get up.
Your lower back is moving.
No, it's not.
Stop it.
Takeuchi-kun, stop it.
No, no, no.
You're slow.
You're getting stronger.
Takeuchi-kun, no.
No, no.
I'm going to go again.
No, no, no.
I'm going to go.
Your hands are moving.
I'm going to go again.
I can't get up.
I feel sick.
I've done a lot.
I can't do it anymore.
You've done a lot.
I've done a lot.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm going to go again.
I feel more sensitive than before.
I can't do it anymore.
It's over.
I ate too much.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm going to go again.
I can't take it anymore.
You're shaking yourself.
Come here.
You're short of breath.
I'm going to break.
It's strange that I can do this much.
That's true.
You're like a senior.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm going to break.
Are you going to break?
I'm sorry.
I can't move like this.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm sorry.
I'm out of breath.
I can't take it anymore.
Yes.
I'll be back at 3 o'clock.
You're going to shoot after that, right?
Yes.
I understand.
I think I can also report the example.
Yes.
Thank you.
That's right.
I understand.
Yes.
Ah.
That's right.
It's time to check out.
I'll call you again.
Yes.
Thank you.
Hey.
I can't.
Please.
One more time.
No.
I can't.
You're going to miss the bullet train, right?
I have to call you.
Hey.
You were a virgin until yesterday.
Yes.
This is the last time.
I can't.
I'm touching your butt.
Do you want to do it more?
Yes.
Are you okay?
Ah.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
...
Add oil with 0.1% salt
Are you disturbing me?
Are you sterilizing?
No, it's the feeling of nose.
It's the feeling of breath.
OH MY GOD
amoshakura
Are you calm?
I was watching this for a long time.
Woe
nice
ahh
this feels nice
let me l
so nice
Slept well, today?
Was that right?
You're still too big to go to the bathroom, so I'll wash you for you.
It's hard.
You are to be washed
Don't move.
It feels good.
Touch this side too.
It's getting harder.
I can feel it.
It feels good.
It's getting harder.
My butt.
It feels good.
I'll lick a lot.
It hurts.
Hey.
I'll lick a lot.
I was told to lick a lot.
It hurts.
It's getting harder.
Does this feel good?
It feels good.
I'll lick a lot.
It hurts.
I've licked a lot.
I'm about to fall asleep.
It's a strange feeling.
I want to get out of here.
I'm about to fall asleep.
I'm going to give you a lot.
You are amazing.
It's so nice.
No, no, no.
Hey, no.
I'm going to give you a lot.
Senpai.
Senpai licked me a lot.
I'm going to give you a lot.
Come here.
You are getting bigger.
Can I give you a lot?
It's so nice.
Do you like this?
You licked me a lot.
Let's play together.
Will you lick me?
You really licked me a lot.
Do you want me to put this in your mouth?
If you go back to Tokyo, you'll forget everything.
Yes, I understand.
I'm glad you're okay.
Are you okay?
I'm so glad you're okay.
I'm so grateful.
I'm so tired.
I feel so good.
Let's take a break.
I'm so tired.
Can I take a break?
Yes, you can.
This is the last one.
Do you feel good?
I know you feel good.
I feel so good.
Thank you so much.
I want to sleep, too.
I'm going to sleep.
It feels good.
Do you want me to sleep?
I'm going to sleep.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
I'm going to sleep.
My face is itchy.
I'm going to rub your face.
I feel good.
I'm going to sleep.
Are you going to sleep?
You like the back of my head.
I feel good.
You can do it.
Thank you very much.
I have a lot.
I can't do it.
It's hard.
The back of my hand is amazing.
I rubbed too much.
I'm going to die.
I can't do it.
I feel good.
I'm going to die.
I can't do it.
I have a lot.
I love this.
I'm going to kiss you a lot.
I'm good at it.
Why are you so good at it?
Because I love this place.
I feel good when I'm with you.
You are good at it.
I feel good.
It's been a long time.
I have a lot.
I feel good.
I'm in trouble.
I have a lot.
I told you.
I'm in trouble.
I have a lot.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm in trouble.
I have a lot.
I want you to clean up.
I'm in trouble.
I'll bring this video to the editing room.
Please.
I'm in trouble.
You promised you wouldn't do it when you got back to Tokyo, didn't you?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I already deleted that picture.
Well, do you want to go to a restaurant?
I'd like to go straight to the hotel.
Don't get carried away.
I'm sorry.