Good evening.
I'm refreshed.
I'm hungry.
This morning...
Hello.
Here...
Hello?
Yeah.
How's the contract going?
Really?
Okay.
I'll help you when I get back to Tokyo.
Yeah.
What?
Of course.
You know,
I have relatives in Obon.
Yeah.
What?
No, it's not like that.
By the way,
don't you have to do your homework?
What?
It's not over yet?
You should do it.
Even if you cry later,
I won't help you.
Yeah.
Okay.
It was hot outside.
Yeah.
You worked hard.
I had to take a break.
I'll be tired when I get back.
This is a souvenir for you.
Thank you.
I'm glad you didn't notice.
I'll make some tea.
Okay.
Where's your mom?
She went shopping.
I see.
Yuta.
Hi.
Welcome back.
Tsukasa.
It's been a while.
How have you been?
I'm fine.
Hello?
What happened?
Really?
You look busy.
I've been busy since this morning.
I see.
Can I help you?
Where can I find tea leaves?
Tea leaves?
You bought a lot.
Thank you.
I'm back.
You're back early.
I'll do it.
Please wait.
Thank you.
This is for you.
I'll go get changed.
Welcome back.
I'll help you with your luggage.
Thank you.
I'll put it here.
Are you going to college?
Yes.
It must be hard for you.
No.
It's hard for you, too.
Because you're my son-in-law's wife.
No, it's not.
Thank you.
Is he okay?
He's fine.
He's old.
Is he okay?
He's fine.
I'm back.
Did you get the beer?
Yes.
I hope you have soy sauce, too.
You have a lot of work to do.
I want to see your face.
You're right.
I'm a little late because I'm busy.
You didn't drink at all.
I'm fine.
You should drink.
You should drink, too.
I'm going to sweat.
Do you know where you're going?
Yes.
There's a lot of magic around you.
I'm going to sweat.
I'm tired of playing a good wife.
My third marriage.
I'm a married woman without children.
My father is busy with work and comes home late.
I sleep on my day off.
I've told my husband that I'm lonely.
But I can't help it because it's my job.
Even if I say I want a child, he doesn't listen to me.
I've been playing a good wife to support my husband.
But I'm tired of trying too hard.
Can this be solved?
Is there no choice but to divorce?
I'm going to sleep.
Is there a male partner?
Is your father going to sleep here?
I can't sleep.
I'm going to take a bath.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Yuta, what are you doing?
Can't you get a girlfriend?
I can't get a girlfriend.
Damn it.
You always bite your parents' back.
Here, drink it.
I'm not biting.
What are you talking about?
I can't drink this much alcohol.
I can't drink it because it's in my mouth.
No, you can't.
You have a lot of opportunities to drink.
I can't drink anymore.
Yuta, are you okay?
By the way,
I'm sorry, but I'm going to take him to his room.
Let's go to his room.
I'm sorry.
When I was your age,
I was much stronger.
Come here.
I'll change my clothes.
Here you are.
Drink up.
But...
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
You're sweating.
I don't want to.
I don't want you to do it.
You're drunk.
Listen to me.
But...
Tsukasa-san,
you're close to me.
Am I?
I'm just going to sleep.
I'm going to change your clothes.
What?
I'm ready.
Are you going to sleep?
No, I'm going to sleep.
What?
Tsukasa-san...
Wait a minute.
I can hear your voice.
But...
Tsukasa-san...
I didn't know you were this kind of person.
It's okay.
You don't have to be embarrassed.
Wait a minute.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you?
Are you this old?
No, I'm not.
Let me see.
But...
I'm your wife.
You've grown up.
Let me see.
Are you still embarrassed?
No, I'm not.
Wait a minute.
What?
You don't have to be embarrassed.
You've grown up.
Let me see.
Tsukasa-san...
You don't have to be embarrassed.
Let me see.
If you make a loud voice,
they'll find out.
Are you sober now?
No, I'm not.
Let me see.
Is my face close to you?
Yes.
Your face is close to me.
Wait a minute.
Tsukasa-san...
I'm going to sleep.
Let's break up.
I don't think so.
You don't have to worry about it.
Everyone is still drinking.
No, I'm not.
Do you feel bad?
Yes.
Let me see.
How can you sleep in this state?
You can't sleep, can you?
I'm sorry.
Don't touch me.
You have a sensitive body.
Let me see.
It's dirty.
It's not dirty.
Don't touch me.
Let me clean your face.
Wait a minute.
Why are you doing this?
Don't you like it?
It's strange.
You're cute.
Don't touch me.
I can't help it.
Put your hand here.
Wait a minute.
I can't help it.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
I can't help it.
Don't you like it?
Wait a minute.
I can't help it.
That's great.
You're out of breath.
You're ticklish.
I can't help it.
Listen to me.
What are you doing?
I just wanted to feel good.
I can't help it.
Why are you taking it off?
Please take it off.
You'll be scolded.
I'll tell you a good thing.
It's open.
Please take it off.
It feels good.
I can't help it.
Please take it off.
Don't you feel good?
It doesn't feel good.
If you take it off, you won't get pregnant.
Do you hate it that much?
I can't help it.
Do you feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
I can't help it.
Do you feel good?
Wait a minute.
I can't help it.
You seem to be fine.
Ouch.
Oh…
I don't know what to do
It feels so good.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
Open your mouth.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Hang in there.
It's too intense.
It's coming. Stop it.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
You're going to throw up.
Let me help you.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ouch, ouch.
It's too intense.
I'm glad you threw up today.
I'm sorry.
It's too intense.
Please sit down.
Thank you.
Good morning.
It's been two days.
I'm fine.
We're going to visit a grave today.
So, let's have breakfast and get ready for it.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
Hmm.
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry. I'll close the door.
Oh, wait. What if my sister finds out?
Should I tell her that Yuta did this to me?
Oh, no. Please don't.
Then I have to keep it a secret.
Can you keep it a secret?
What are you waiting for?
Oh, no.
You're looking forward to it.
Do you want to take it off?
What?
What if someone comes?
It's okay.
If you don't make a loud voice, no one will come.
Oh, no.
You can't escape anymore.
You've grown up.
Oh, no.
Take this off, too.
What?
Oh, no.
You're shivering.
You can't make a loud voice.
It'll be a big deal.
Oh, no.
You've grown up.
Have you ever done something like this?
No, I haven't.
Oh, no.
You're holding it in, aren't you?
Do you want me to do something?
No, but...
You're holding it in.
Oh, no.
This one, too?
What are you going to do if he notices?
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
My ears.
What should I do?
Oh, no.
Oh, it's hot.
Put your hands behind your head.
Oh, no.
Oh, it feels good.
No?
Oh, no.
Wait, Tsukasa.
Wait.
What?
I'm going to puke.
Stop it.
Show me.
Oh, wow.
You're still puking.
You puked a lot.
Oh, wow.
It's starting to hurt.
What?
Take responsibility.
Let's go to bed.
What?
Okay.
You're going to stand up again, aren't you?
I'll rub your butt.
It hurts.
It's okay.
Oh, it hurts.
Tsukasa.
Let me help you.
What?
I'll hold you.
It stings.
Let me hold you.
Do you want warm up your legs a little?
Let's move your body together!
That feels so good.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's tough.
oups
it feels so good
Oh god the bubbles
No worries
It's up to you.
What?
More, more.
More?
Yes, yes.
Do it.
Ah, that feels good.
Ah, ah, ah.
Do you like it?
What do you feel?
I can't do it
Wow
It's hard
I can't do it
Let's do something better
Ah
Does it feel good?
Yes
Let's do it again
Ah
It feels good
Ah...
You're awake.
Give me a kiss.
Okay.
I'll give you a kiss.
You're awake.
Give me a kiss.
Does it feel good?
Let's feel good together.
Don't do that.
Don't say that.
You said it.
Give me a kiss.
Ah...
I can't stop running.
My legs...
Ah...
Does it feel good?
I'm going to lose my voice.
You're going to lose your voice.
Ah...
If you say that, you're going to lose your voice.
I'm going to lose my voice.
Does it feel good?
I can't do it.
I can't.
Ah...
What are you doing?
Let's go.
Here you are.
Thank you.
It's beautiful.
Did you have a baby?
Not yet.
Not yet?
You're the son's wife.
You have to do your best.
I don't say that.
It's a gift.
Ah...
I don't think so.
What are you talking about?
Thank you.
It's been a long time.
You've become a man.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend yet.
You've become a man.
What are you doing now?
Ah...
I'm taking a break from college.
I see.
I was in the middle of a report.
I'm sorry.
Good luck.
You've become a man.
It's not good.
What if you run away?
You can't run away, can you?
It's not good.
You're shaking, aren't you?
You're shaking.
I'm sorry.
You're so cute.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to do it?
I won't do it.
You can't run away, can you?
Hey, Itsuka.
What are you doing?
Let's do it.
Yes.
I can't do it.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
It's not good to work too hard.
Take a break.
I'll try a little harder.
It's hard.
I can't do it.
I'll give you a massage.
Thank you.
You can continue.
What's wrong?
Am I in the way?
No, you're not.
I'm sorry.
I'll finish it by tomorrow.
Is it a massage?
Yes.
I'll give you a massage.
What?
It's not a massage, is it?
You're noisy.
Do you feel so bad?
I'll finish it by tomorrow.
But I want to finish it by today.
I want to finish it by today.
I'll finish it by today.
I'm sorry.
Let me take it off.
It's hard.
I can't do it.
Let me take it off.
Do you want to take a break?
Yes.
I'll take a break.
It's hot.
It's not a break, is it?
Don't you feel better?
I have to report.
I'm so tired.
I can't do it.
If you study all the time,
you'll get a headache.
But now...
I want to concentrate now.
My hands...
You have to concentrate.
That's right.
What?
It's hot.
What are you doing?
What's this?
It's a break.
I'm helping you.
Do you want to take a break?
You can't move like that.
You've grown up.
No, no, no.
You're a good boy.
Wait a minute.
Show me.
I'll show you.
Wait a minute.
No.
It's nostalgic.
Wait a minute.
Have you ever been in such an embarrassing outfit?
No.
No?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It tickles.
You've grown up.
No.
No?
Wait a minute.
You've grown up.
I have to report it.
Show me.
You've grown up.
Wait a minute.
It hurts.
It's sensitive.
Wait a minute.
That's dangerous.
Does it hurt anymore?
It doesn't hurt anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm going to eat it now.
Quick-my existence
I am in a hurry
Wait a minute.
No.
Wait.
Let me go.
Wait, let me go.
No.
I've done it twice. I can do it, can't I?
What? Not yet?
Please stop.
Please go back.
What are you guys doing?
I was going to make Yuta-kun a late-night meal, so I asked him what he wanted.
Then he said, please stop.
Yuta, you know, people's actions are to be taken honestly.
Oh, yeah.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I'm next to you.
I'm fine.
I'm taking medicine.
But you're so thin.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Why?
Why does it hurt?
It's okay.
It's not okay.
Really.
Don't make a noise.
No, I won't.
Wait, wait.
Did he wake up?
I'm sorry.
You're shaking.
What are you going to do when you wake up?
I'm sorry.
You've grown up.
Mr. Tsukasa.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
It's warm.
I'm going to touch you.
Does it feel good?
Come here.
You're wet, aren't you?
I see.
You're soaked.
There.
Touch me.
Does it feel good?
You should eat, too.
That's great.
Does it feel good?
Is it good?
I can't.
I can't speak.
It's hot.
You can't speak.
That's right.
Do it more.
Touch me more.
Does it feel good?
I'm going to touch you.
That's right.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'm going to touch you.
You can't do that.
Does it feel good?
Touch me.
That's right.
Does it feel good?
You can't do that.
I want to touch you.
I'm going to touch you.
Are you okay?
Please.
You can't do that.
I'm going to touch you.
Does it feel good?
Give me a pat.
Does it hurt?
Does it feel good?
I'm going to touch you.
Does it hurt?
Does it feel good?
I'm going to touch you.
Does it hurt?
What are you doing?
Does it feel good?
Does it hurt?
I'm going to do it gently.
Does it feel good?
You can do whatever you want.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to do it gently.
Does it feel good?
I'll do it gently next time.
New Year's Day
Please come again.
I hope I can give you a good report.
Thank you.
Does your calf itch?
It can't be helped. I'm busy now.
What are you talking about?
It's about work.
Tsukasa-san, you're a good wife.
Of course, I'm the son-in-law's wife.
But you're going to work for a long time, right?
I'm not going to work.