I'm sorry.
How do you feel now?
I can't believe it.
I didn't think I could win.
Please look at the camera here.
Thank you.
I didn't think I could win.
Maybe I said too much.
If you don't have confidence, you can't participate in Miss Con.
It's wrong to ask,
How do you feel now?
You have no choice but to answer, I can't believe it.
Huh?
She's the girl I see every morning.
She's wearing beautiful clothes today.
Is she going on a date?
Miss Campus Grand Prix
Did she win the Miss Con?
That's right.
She's beautiful.
But she seems to have a lot of pride.
I don't have a woman in my life.
Really?
My hand is on this beautiful woman's butt.
This is wrong.
I'm not popular.
I've decided not to participate in Miss Con.
I don't want to participate in Miss Con.
I don't want to win the Miss Con and be happy.
It's the worst.
What should I do?
But if I let go of my hand, I won't be able to touch her for the rest of my life.
Hurry up and let go of my hand.
It's really disgusting.
Oh, no.
I've set a time limit.
What am I doing?
My college friends.
Didn't anyone live on this expedition?
If I were you, I'd come to the station right away.
I guess I'll have to call for help.
It takes a lot of time to get a ticket.
What's wrong with this woman?
If you're going to call for help, you should speak up.
Maybe she's just having fun touching her.
When you get to the station, give me the money.
It's a so-called tsutsumotase.
It's disgusting.
Besides, there's no woman who can feel her butt.
My sexual organ is my nipples.
I'm sorry.
If I'm going to be beaten up when I get to the station,
I don't have time to touch my butt.
I'm a man of my words.
My father has always wanted to touch me.
I can't do anything about it.
What a bold man.
That's it.
I could have forgiven him if he was handsome.
But I can't.
I don't like this face at all.
The station is around here.
By the way, he's a great father.
Stop it.
But you're a coward.
Why do you follow me even though you're wearing my clothes?
You're a coward.
Hey.
Oh, no.
Why do I have to touch you?
I'm the most popular Miss Campus in college.
It's impossible for this face to touch my boobs.
But what's this?
You're good.
Oh, no.
I'm home.
Hello?
Well...
What floor is this?
Yes.
But it's okay now.
Thank you.
See you.
I felt it with my intuition.
It's the worst.
Hello?
Yes.
I'm home now.
From now on?
I'll stop.
I'm tired.
I won the Miss Campus.
Thank you.
What am I doing?
I've never kissed a woman.
Maybe I'm crazy because of my intuition.
See you.
I'll hang up now.
I love you, too.
See you.
You don't look good.
Why do I have to spend so much time with you?
I'm home.
It's not good.
It's the same car again.
I'm sure he's taking someone close to him.
It's not good.
He might beat me up.
I can't tell if he's taking someone close to me.
I'm worried about my boobs.
This is it.
I can feel his nipples.
No one is taking someone close to him.
I'll go to the next station.
I'm home.
I don't know what to do with myself.
I don't know. You felt good, didn't you? Don't blame me.
You're the one who made me feel good.
Please take responsibility.
Responsibility?
I'm going to school soon, but I can't wear a skirt like this.
I want to buy you clothes, but I'm going to bed because I have a hemorrhoid.
I'm going to bed because I have a hemorrhoid.
Then I'll forgive you for my voice today.
My voice?
I sometimes talk to other people on my way home.
Please protect me from that.
Protect you?
Please pick me up at school today.
Please take the train home with me.
Please pick me up at school.
I don't know what's going on.
She's beautiful.
She's pure and has the best boobs.
But she's so quiet that I'm getting excited.
Look at the sound.
I can hear the song.
I have to speak up.
I've never seen a man like me.
It's so fresh.
Don't speak up.
Go to your room.
Don't say a word.
Don't speak a word.
I don't know what to do with myself.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do
Oh my—
You can't catch anything.
Look.
I'm home.
Good girl.
Phew...
Phew, whew, phew
Phew
Yes!
Sigh
Uh!
It's okay.
Stop it.
Thank you.
It's okay.
It's nostalgic.
Are you excited to do this here?
No, I'm not.
I'm sorry.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah.
I can't believe I'm doing this to myself.
I can't believe!
I can't even dare to admit I'm doing this to myself.
What have I done to myself?
I'm doing this to myself!
I'm not at fault.
I don't know what to do.
Stand up.
Stick out your butt.
Open your mouth.
I'm going to put a little bit of coffee in it.
What? What? What? What? What? What?
It feels good. It feels good.
It's hot.
No, no, no, no.
Huh?
Ow, ouch.
Come on.
Here it is.
Ah!
That's my fanta.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
What should I do with it?
Wait a moment
It starts to get hot
Have a기
Oh my gosh
I'm scared
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh.
I don't really do what I'd expect a stalker to do
But...
...my intuition tells me it's fine
This is the end of this video. Thank you for watching so far.
See you next time with a delicious video 😊
Thank you for watching so far. See you next time with a delicious video 😊