Episode 1
An Old friend
Hmm, this is troubling.
It's only been a while since I've stopped by Uncle's place.
Why is she sleeping in her cousin's bed?
And why is she dressed like that?
Here's your tea.
Thank you.
Takashi, I'm glad you came.
I haven't been able to visit my relatives lately.
I'm glad to see you after a long time.
My uncle's house was close to where I moved.
So I thought I'd stop by.
Oh, it's close?
I see.
If it's close, come visit us again.
If Takashi comes, Monika will be happy.
I haven't seen Monika for a while.
I think I saw her when I was in junior high school.
That long ago?
Yes.
How's it going?
I just moved in.
But I haven't taken out all my stuff yet.
I see.
My cardboard box is in the way.
Huh?
Dad, you have a visitor?
Oh, Monika.
Monika?
It's Takashi. It's been a while.
Monika.
It's not just your dad.
Put a sheet of paper on it.
Oh, that's a hassle.
But you put out too much.
We're both men, so it's fine.
Yeah, but...
It's been a while, Takashi.
Yeah.
You haven't changed at all.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
You've gotten bigger.
What? I've gotten bigger?
Yeah.
I don't think I've changed at all.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Oh, are you talking about my boobs?
Huh?
You're so perverted.
Oh, I just remembered.
Monika has always been the type of girl
who doesn't care about her appearance.
She didn't care when she was little,
but now that she's grown so much,
she's become too stimulating.
Takashi, you're in trouble again.
No, I'm not.
It's not good to be a relative of your brother.
He's an actor, after all.
Huh?
Don't you have a red face, Takashi?
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I don't think so.
Keep it that way.
Huh?
Yeah.
Hmm.
Huh?
I feel like you're sleeping a little.
Oh, really?
Yeah, it's a little hot.
Yeah. Are you okay, Takashi?
Yeah, I think I'm fine.
Yeah, yeah.
What's wrong, Takashi?
Do you have a stomachache?
Oh, no, it's just...
Takashi, you seem to have a fever,
and you don't look well.
Huh?
Do you want to lie down?
Oh, no, not that far.
No, no, you don't have to sleep at a time like this.
Oh, no.
That's right, Takashi.
I'll use my bed, so you should sleep a little.
Oh, no, I'm really fine.
Really?
Come on, stand up.
I'll help you, so let's go to bed.
Oh, no, I'm really fine.
No, you don't seem to be okay.
You should sleep properly.
Because you're still hungry.
Let's go, let's go.
That outfit is against the rules.
It's almost time to go home,
so it's okay to get up.
Oh, Takashi, were you awake?
Oh, Monika.
That outfit...
That outfit?
I was just taking a bath.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
I fell asleep without taking a bath last night.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
I've finally calmed down.
Why do I have to take a bath at a time like this?
Takashi, are you feeling better now?
Huh?
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
Takashi, are you really okay?
Huh?
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
Yeah.
If you're really in pain, tell me right away.
Oh, yeah, if I'm really in pain,
I'll tell you, so don't worry.
Yeah.
Oh, by the way,
my dad's going out.
Oh, your dad's going out?
Yeah.
Huh? What's wrong, Takashi?
Huh?
Are you still not feeling well?
Oh, it still hurts a little.
Oh, it still hurts.
Yeah.
Oh, that's right. I'll pat your stomach.
Huh? My stomach?
Yeah.
Oh.
What's wrong?
Oh, no, it's nothing.
Takashi, are you okay?
Does your stomach hurt again?
Takashi?
Huh?
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
Takashi?
I'm sorry, Monika.
I can't help it.
But...
I'm naked.
It's Monika's fault.
With this towel...
I'm almost naked.
It's Monika's fault.
I can't tell him what I'm about to do.
You can't, Takashi.
You can't.
Let me go.
But...
You were so close to him.
Don't touch me.
I don't want you to get hurt.
You weren't this big when I first saw you.
I'm sorry.
I was being quiet.
Dad will get mad.
But it's best for you to stay quiet.
I'm sorry.
I don't want you to get hurt.
So stay quiet.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's different
Hmm
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
I'm sorry! I underestimated you!
What's going on?
Where did she go?
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Stop it.
She reacted like that.
I can't stop it.
I can't do this.
It looks like she's trying to get up.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't stop it.
She's reacting.
I can't do this.
That's amazing.
She's getting stronger.
I can't do this.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
That's amazing.
She was looking at her butt.
She's looking at her butt.
It's your fault.
I can't do this.
You can't do that.
It's dirty.
You were in the bath, weren't you?
It's okay.
I can't do this.
You were surprised again.
It must have felt good.
I can't do this.
I'm going to cry.
Don't take it.
Give it to me.
Don't.
Good boy, good boy.
Push him out...
It hurts!
I can't take it!
Ahh!
Onii-chan!
No!
No, no, no!
You can't do that!
No! No! No!
Onii-chan!
Ah! No!
No! No! No!
You can't do that!
No! No!
Oh no, what was that?
I told you earlier, didn't I?
He's not going out, is he?
It's okay if you keep quiet.
Please eat this.
It'll be over soon.
It's not your fault.
I'm sorry for making you sad.
It'll be over soon.
I'm really sorry.
It's hot.
It's really hot.
It's painful.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
I'll be back soon.
I'm sorry for making you sad.
Please cry.
Cry.
Don't do that.
I'll be back soon.
Cry.
Don't do that.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Big brother, let's end this. Let's end this.
No, no!
No! No!
No!
Big brother...
No! No!
No! No! No!
No!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
No! No!
Ah!
Let's end this. Let's end this.
Let's end this.
No! No! No!
Big brother, no!
No!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Don't go out with him like that!
No! You'll get sick! You'll get sick!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
No! No! No!
Ah! No! No! No!
Ah! Big brother!
Ah!
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
No! No!
Ah!
No!
Big brother!
No! No! No!
Ah!
I'm so embarrassed.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! No! No!
Big brother!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! No! No! No!
Big brother!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah!
No! No! No!
Big brother!
Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
No! No!
I said no.
Ah!
Big brother!
No! No! No!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Oh
Ono
Hmm
Ah
Not with you.
Oh, don't.
That's so gross,
You were feeling great.
No, no, I can't, no, no, no.
Dad is home!
You can't do that...
You are all in my way.
That's enough, enough!
Enougi, dirty girl!
I'll kill her.
My daughter!
No more, no more...
I'm sorry.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm really sorry.
I don't know if you'll forgive me.
I don't know what to do.
I'm sorry.
Brother.
Forget everything about today.
I'll forget it, too.
I won't tell my father.
Takashi.
Yes.
Are you feeling well today?
Are you hungry?
Yes, I'm fine.
That's good.
You left so soon.
You didn't even cook.
I'm sorry.
It'll take about an hour.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
A week has passed since then.
Monika didn't say anything to her uncle.
It was as if nothing had happened.
Monika.
Takashi came again today.
I wanted you to eat your father's food.
Yes.
Monika.
I'm really sorry about the other day.
You didn't say anything to your uncle.
Thank you.
A bug?
That's right.
I'm sorry.
Monika.
You didn't do anything terrible the other day.
You're still dressed like this.
I'm fine.
If I go home suddenly, my father will be worried.
I see.
But you're dressed like this.
Are you inviting your uncle?
What are you doing?
Stop it.
I'm not inviting him.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Your father will find out.
If you really don't like it, you can talk to your uncle.
You're inviting him, aren't you?
I'm not inviting him.
Really?
You're not trying to change your clothes at all.
I just don't want to show you.
I can see a little.
Stop it.
I just touched it.
It's hard here.
Stop it.
Your father will find out.
Are you having fun with your uncle?
I'm not having fun.
Really?
Stop it.
Why are you doing this?
You said you wouldn't do it again.
That's because you're dressed like this.
I'm not inviting him.
I'm not doing this.
Stop it.
Your father will find out.
You said you wouldn't do it again.
You must have been inviting him.
Don't touch me.
Monika.
Yes?
Do you want some tea?
No, I'm fine.
You don't want it?
No.
What about Takashi?
I'm fine, too.
Are you sure?
Thank you.
You're still holding it in.
You really wanted to do it.
Are you okay with spicy food?
Yes, I like spicy food.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'll make it a little spicy today.
Thank you.
Stop it.
I'm fine.
He'll find out.
Stop it.
I'm fine.
Monika, you have to speak up.
I can't hold back my voice.
I'm fine.
Stop it.
I just licked you a little.
You wanted me to lick you, didn't you?
I'm fine.
Stop it.
If you do this, he'll find out.
I'm fine.
Stop it.
I can't hold back my voice.
I'm fine.
Look at him.
Monika.
I was wondering what you were making.
You're looking forward to it, aren't you?
I'm looking forward to it.
You should learn how to cook soon.
I will.
I'll teach you next time.
By the way, what happened to Takashi?
Where is Takashi?
He went to the bathroom.
I see.
Monika, can you eat a lot today?
Yes.
I'm hungry, so I think I can eat a lot.
I see.
I'll cook for you.
Thank you for everything.
I can't eat any more.
You're making a lot of noise.
I'll cook for you next time.
I can't eat any more.
It's because of Monika.
It's okay.
You're making a lot of noise.
I'll lick you.
Then you won't make a noise.
You can bear it, can't you?
I can't eat any more.
I'm hungry.
Takashi, where did Monika go?
She went back to her room.
I see.
She was here a while ago.
I'm hungry.
You have to be quiet.
You like this, don't you?
I don't like this.
I'm hungry.
You have to be quiet.
You like this, don't you?
If you don't do this, Takashi won't let you eat.
You don't use your hands.
I'm hungry.
It's getting harder and harder.
Mi-chan, you can go now.
Is this okay?
She went out.
Mi-chan, you can go now.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Be quiet.
He'll notice.
It's dangerous.
Don't come in.
I'm sorry.
He'll notice.
Be quiet.
Don't move.
He's singing.
Why is it so hard?
It's because of your body.
It's all your fault.
I haven't washed you yet.
If you touch me, I'll scream.
I'm weak.
I know.
I'm going to puke.
Don't do that.
When they're in the spoon, Mary began to whine.
No, not now, please!
Try it later, Ok?
You're so itty-bitty.
You can't...
Mufui-chan, you got something on your face.
I'm just washing my face.
My butt is itchy, so I'll wash it like this.
Muneko-chan, you shouldn't go in front of my butt.
I'm sorry.
Muneko-chan, it's all my fault.
I'm going to go with you in such a hurry.
Muneko-chan, you're not moving your hips.
I'm not moving my hips.
I'm standing still.
Muneko-chan, it's all my fault.
I feel good again.
I'm sorry.
Muneko-chan, you look tired.
Is that true?
You're fine, right?
But my father's not here.
You have to say it out loud.
No, I can't.
You have to be patient.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I can't stop crying.
What is it?
What?
Do you want to take a shower?
Yes.
I want to take a bath before eating.
Do you?
Yes.
Have you eaten?
I'm going to eat.
Yes.
Did you know?
I'm hungry again.
It's really good.
I have no idea.
I'm going to take a shower.
I can't stop crying.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I
'm sorry
z L
I don't know what to do with myself, but I'm going to do my best.
I'm going to do my best.
What should I do?
Maybe...
Let me think.
Sister...
Okay.
Kani...
Haa... Haa... Haa...
Haa... Haa...
Haa... Haha...
Held it all up for 8 months...
I didn't have the strength to face things.
9 months later...
I'm going to make a hole in the center of the dough and put the dough in it.
I made a hole in the center of the dough and put the dough in it.
I'm going to bake it in the oven.
Monika.
Come in.
Okay.
Monika, your uncle really isn't here, is he?
No, he's out on a business trip.
I see.
He's not here?
No, he's not.
He really isn't here?
No, he's out on a business trip.
I see.
Monika, why did you call me today?
Well...
I just...
I just couldn't forget the time I spent with you.
At first, I had to force myself to do it.
But I couldn't forget you no matter how many times I did it.
So I wanted to do it again.
I see.
It wasn't my fault. It's all your fault.
I'm sorry.
Take responsibility.
It's all your fault.
It's all your fault that I became like this.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Give me a hug.
You don't have to be shy because your father isn't here today.
You're so aggressive.
Give me a hug.
I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I think it's true.
Sor borirmisch, fundamentals of the Gaia?
I'm not sure if I have a problem with that.
I'll fill it up for you.
I can't do it.
It feels so good.
It's so good.
Thank you.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
I wanted you to feel good.
It's too good.
I feel so good.
It feels so good.
Can I touch you?
I've been touching you.
It feels so good.
I know.
What?
You said you like this kind of thing.
I like it.
I'm always watching you because you're so cute.
It's because you've grown up.
Come here a little bit more.
How does this feel?
It feels so good.
Where did you learn this?
I watched your video because I wanted you to be happy.
That's why I learned it.
It feels so good.
It's because you've grown up.
I can't do it anymore.
You can't do it yet.
I'm sorry.
It's because you've grown up.
It feels so good.
I can't do it anymore.
It's because you've grown up.
It feels so good.
What are you doing?
Are you touching yourself?
Yes.
Touch me.
Here.
You're so wet.
Can I touch you?
Yes.
You're so wet.
It feels so good.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to dos.
You don't know what to do?
You have time?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, oh, oh, no, no,
oh, no, my grandchildren,,
Oh, son,
Will it be difficult for me to blush?
Should I stick my butt out?
I don't know what to do with myself.
Brother, you do more.
Hmm
I do not do.
You are not able.
Big brother, I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
Let me out today.
Really?
I'll let you out.
Let me out.
Ouch!
Big brother, you're trembling.
Come here.
Ouch!
Big brother, you can do it again, right?
I want to do it again.
Okay.
Ouch!
I'm going to fail because you're not here.
Okay.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I can't stop the pain.
It hurts.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can't do it anymore.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
It's hot.
Are you going to die?
I'm going to die.
Do you want to do it again?
I want to do it again.
Can I do it again?
Yes.
I don't want my dad to get mad at me.
It's none of your business.
It's hot.
I know there's a lot inside.
Get up.
It's hot.
You cleaned it up.
Let's do it again.
I can't do it.
I can't do it again.
I want to do it again.
You're the one who attacked me.
That's right.
You have to take responsibility.
Responsibility?
Let's do it again.
Get excited with my body.
It's hot.