Kacchan?
It's Kacchan.
Come in.
Oh.
The weather is still good.
Yeah.
I think Kacchan will be here soon.
The exam is next month.
Yuna doesn't move?
She does. She does.
She comes here sometimes when her husband is away.
What does her husband do?
Does he check the bridge?
Oh.
What bridge?
The bridge that crosses the river?
Yeah.
Oh.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It's hot because there's no air conditioner.
When should we stop?
No.
On the day off.
What?
Aren't you going to the wedding?
It's half a month ahead.
By the way,
why did you send the invitation to me?
Why do you know the address?
It's a secret.
Thank you for the meal.
I'm going back to Tokyo.
What?
What about the wedding?
I can't go out.
What are you doing now?
Oh.
I was in charge of the supermarket.
I'm waiting at home for a while.
Are you looking for a girl again?
No.
You're a fool.
I'm not.
Don't you want to eat ice cream?
I want to eat.
I only had one.
It's too much.
Yeah.
I ate too much.
Every house is beautiful.
I clean it once or twice a month.
Even if it sinks?
It's been a year since I bought it.
It's a memory.
But we're not memories yet.
It's all going to sink.
My house, my backyard, the park's toilet and the garage.
Don't arrange your memories.
It's not erotic.
It's love.
By the way.
When we first met.
You said you didn't like it outside.
There's no love photo around here.
You can't go home either, can you?
Yeah.
In the end.
You got into public relations and did it.
Then I did it again.
After all.
There are people who do it other than us.
But I was so nervous about that.
But I laughed.
Yuna.
It was tough.
You were so relaxed because you were crying.
But.
Yuna was trembling.
I was trembling, too.
It's been seven years since then.
Yuna will get married, too.
Yuna.
You don't have to hide anymore.
You can't cheat.
We're the only ones here.
We used to be ghosts.
I can't do it because you did it.
Yuna can't do it.
Hey.
Did I change?
Who did you touch?
Who is it?
Does it feel good?
Yeah.
It feels so good.
Let me touch it.
I put my tongue in.
Who did you touch?
It feels good.
My eyes hurt.
It feels so good.
I'm going to complain.
It feels good.
It's salty.
It's delicious.
You're shaking a lot.
I can't help it.
You're going to cry.
You're shaking a lot.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's delicious.
It feels so good.
It feels good.
Come here.
I thought you liked it.
I remember.
It feels good.
I'm going to cry.
You like this, don't you?
I like it.
I like this.
It feels good.
Let me touch it.
I'm comparing it with my husband.
It feels good.
Just stay here.
Are you going to go home?
Let's see the river.
The shape will change, right?
It's forbidden to stand up.
You can stand on the bottom.
Then I'll do it for free.
Aren't you going to get married?
I've been married before.
What about Reiko?
She's probably alone for the rest of her life.
It must be hard.
The translator was
hanging out with her sister.
But she said she wanted to go out with me.
What?
She said she was impressed with you
and wanted to see you.
She told me your address.
Why do you want to see me?
I don't know.
What?
You don't want to see me?
Last year,
my mother died.
I...
I didn't understand
what she said.
Reiko and I
have been together since we were little.
We've been a family since we started dating.
My fiancee
gave me a letter from Reiko.
But
I was afraid
and hid it in the room without reading it.
Could it be
that you came back to get it?
If I leave it like this, it will sink into the dam.
It's strange.
It's sinking.
It stinks.
How far can it sink?
It's up to here.
What's with that face?
What about here?
You're so sensitive.
Don't say that.
It stinks.
It can't be helped.
I walked for a day.
Did you become an old man?
What?
Don't treat me like an old man.
It's been seven years.
Right?
You haven't changed.
You're still cool.
Why so suddenly?
Are you popular with girls?
In Tokyo?
What kind of girls do you hang out with?
I don't hang out with girls.
What's with that face?
Is your wrist up?
It's up.
Who made it stand up?
Do you like being touched like this?
I like it.
Why?
It stands up quickly.
What are you doing?
Tell me.
What kind of girls do you hang out with?
I don't hang out with girls.
You're lying.
I'm telling the truth.
Then why do you take a break from work?
What?
You must be attracted to girls.
You said that earlier.
No.
I was lying.
You hung out with girls again, didn't you?
No.
You played with them, didn't you?
Wait.
You're wrong.
It's getting hot.
It's hot. Take it off.
I sleep when I sleep.
It smells like sweat.
It doesn't smell that bad.
It smells like you.
Are you a pervert?
I liked your smell.
Can I take this home?
No.
Why?
It's expensive.
I'll take good care of it.
Don't say that.
It's expensive.
Do you want to taste the takoyaki?
Yes.
It's delicious.
You're always annoying.
I'm not annoying.
Why are you kissing me?
It's normal.
It's not normal.
You're playing with me.
You're wrong.
Do it again.
It feels good.
Really?
Kiss me if you like me.
It feels good.
I said I like you.
What's wrong with you?
I really like you.
You're playing with me.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Do you want to kiss me again?
Why?
Are you asking me?
You don't have to ask me.
Then I won't kiss you.
I have to tell you.
I want to kiss you.
Do you want to kiss me?
Kiss me.
You're touching my butt.
Why are you touching my butt?
What?
I can't.
You're still strong.
You're touching me.
You're very sensitive.
Whose fault is it?
What?
Take it off.
Are you tired?
I'm tired because I walked today.
I'm tired.
Whose fault is it?
I'm sorry.
Don't write again.
I want to take this home.
T-shirt.
I'm sweating.
You're a good man.
What?
Are you happy?
You're honest.
Your body is getting hot.
I'm going to sleep.
What's with that face?
I'm sorry.
What?
I like you.
I see.
It's erotic to walk around in a comfortable place.
You too?
Are you listening?
Yes.
Don't touch me.
What about you?
I'm sorry.
You look like you want me to touch you.
I don't.
Hey.
Ouch.
I'll pull it out from there.
Stop it.
What's with that face?
What?
Are you honest?
I want to bully you today.
What do you mean?
I want to see your happy face.
You've changed in seven years.
Have I?
Seven years?
That long?
That's because you're in high school.
You'll grow up.
I'm doing the same for you.
I see.
That's a long time.
Have I changed?
In many ways.
What?
I won't do it for you.
Something's going on here.
It's not.
What if I sleep like this?
What's that?
What?
Can you sleep like that?
I can.
I can do it.
Right?
Even with this?
No.
It's going to be your pace.
What?
No.
What's that?
Hey.
Wow.
It's touching.
It's warm and hard.
Good.
It was mine.
Right?
What?
Oh.
It was yours.
Did you use this too?
Don't say that.
Your pants look tight.
Are you having a hard time?
I'm having a hard time.
Really?
You don't have to do it?
I was going to do it when I slept.
You're taking it off.
It's moving.
Wow.
What?
It's moving.
You're excited.
No.
Something happened.
What?
There's something I want.
Something I want.
What's that face?
Nothing.
It's standing up.
You were surprised.
What?
I was surprised.
That's good.
This.
It's moving.
It's touching.
It's amazing.
It's touching both sides.
It's moving.
It's over.
Really?
Stop it.
Are you sad?
No.
Do you want me to touch it more?
Try it.
If you ask me, I won't do it.
I wanted you to touch it.
I don't know if you're honest or not.
You're honest, aren't you?
It's moving.
Stop it.
What?
It's moving unconsciously.
Where?
Here.
It's moving on its own.
It's moving on its own?
I see.
It's moving.
Your pants are tight, too.
Whose fault is it?
Take it off.
What?
I'll take it off for you.
It's moving.
It's embarrassing.
It's amazing.
It's moving.
Try it again.
Stop it.
It's amazing.
Your face is close to mine.
Show me.
It's been a while since I've seen you.
I've seen you many times.
I want to see you.
Move your hand.
It's sweaty.
I've walked a lot.
It's smelly.
I'm going to get closer to you.
Really?
Look.
Wow.
It's warm.
You're sweating.
But it smells good.
Really?
Yeah.
I want to lick everything.
Huh?
What?
Nothing.
Say it.
Don't lick it.
No?
Say it.
I want you to lick it.
Huh?
I want to record it.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
Look at me.
Can you see?
Don't close your eyes if you feel good.
I know.
It feels good here.
It feels really good.
Close your eyes.
I won't do it if you close your eyes.
You opened your eyes.
That was a blink of an eye.
You're kidding.
Your face was like this.
I'll do it for you.
It feels good.
I didn't do it.
Do you want me to do it again?
I want you to do it.
You're calm now.
Let go of my hair.
Thank you.
It feels good.
Don't say it.
I'm in the mood to say it.
Why are you feeling good?
It's not like that.
It's not like that?
Don't say it.
Don't leave me.
This is a lot.
Is it the third point?
Who said that?
It's not like that.
I'm not a high school student.
I know that much.
That's right.
This is a quiz.
What?
Kacchan quiz.
Which one of us feels good?
That's not a quiz.
It's a quiz.
I want to know.
Do you remember the feeling of sex with your sister?
I remember.
What kind of sex did you have?
Don't say it.
Why?
Which one of us feels good?
Both.
Do you feel the same?
That's...
If you close your eyes,
will you know who I am?
Well...
I know that.
Really?
Really.
You have to memorize my body.
I'm standing like this.
I'm going to enter.
I'll take off my clothes.
Kacchan, please be a woman.
Why?
I've never seen it.
I'm embarrassed.
I want to see it.
Please be a woman without my nose.
What?
You said something great.
I often think of you.
Are you happy?
Well...
Will you do it?
Do it.
I'll take it off.
Separately.
Quickly.
Do you shake your left hand?
No.
What about your right hand?
Do it like you always do.
Are you touching Chikuri?
Well...
Do it.
Show me.
I'll show you Chikuri.
I took it off.
You rub it.
I'm rubbing it.
I think I feel better.
I'm younger.
That's because you're younger.
I like you more.
I was surprised.
I said I liked you, but you were surprised.
I'm coming in.
Did you remember?
It's unfair.
You did this to your sister.
I didn't.
You did.
I don't know.
You did something you didn't do.
Chikuri.
What about me?
Did you do this to your sister?
I didn't.
You have to answer.
You have to.
I have to.
I don't have to.
I don't want to.
It tickles when I think of you.
You were touching your sister.
It tickles.
Stop it.
Don't move.
It tickles inside.
Do you know?
I know.
It tickles.
Do you want to move it that much?
I want to move it.
Do you want to move it?
Can you come with me?
Come here.
Move it.
Why are you making me angry?
You didn't like it?
I wanted you to do this.
I wanted to do this.
Look at me.
Remember the shape inside me.
It tickles when I think of you.
Don't close your eyes.
I'm going to cry.
Stop it.
Did you cry?
Amazing.
I've never seen you cry before.
You're kidding.
I know you're crying.
Are you going to cry?
I'm closing my eyes.
I don't want you to leave me.
It's okay.
I'm going to cry.
Amazing.
What's going on?
I don't want to put in the baby's urine.
Stop it.
It's a waste.
What's with the face?
I'm satisfied.
Really?
It was a terrible farewell.
What is it?
Don't you remember?
No.
You were crying.
Yuna's uncle stopped me at the scene.
That's all I remember.
You remember.
I don't like that farewell anymore.
Forget about the letter.
The river was under the mud.
I don't think you'll find it.
As far as possible.
Yuna, go home.
Your husband will be back tomorrow night.
It's okay to take a taxi home, right?
Let's go home.
I've been walking for a lifetime.
Do you remember?
Again?
I've been thinking about it many times.
I haven't thought about it.
After the village sank into the dam,
will the memories left in the village reach the sea?
I was thinking about that while walking.
You're a narcissist, aren't you?
What kind of interpretation is that?
The village sinks.
It doesn't come to the sea.
What is it all of a sudden?
You're trying to keep your dirty memories clean.
That's what makes it easy.
I'm trying to spend it until it's easy.
It's easy not to marry anyone.
Do you love yourself the most?
What are you talking about?
Why don't you just come with me?
It's not good.
My husband will be back.
I'll be back soon.
It's not soon.
Why do you know the address?
The invitation to the wedding.
I can't come because I like it.
I wanted to say it from a distance, so I wrote down the address.
That's gross.
Come with me.
I've been waiting for a long time.
I've been waiting for seven years.
But I can't.
Come with me.
Stop it.
You've done a lot with me.
Why can't I do it now?
I can't.
I gave up on my mother.
What should I do?
I can't.
Come with me.
Come to Tokyo.
It's late.
Why?
It's not late.
Are you happy?
I'm happy.
I'll make you happier.
Come with me.
I can't.
You can do it.
You can do it again.
It feels good, right?
I'll make you feel better.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I know how you feel.
It feels good.
Will you do this for me?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Tell me it feels good.
It doesn't feel good.
If you're lonely, why don't you go with me?
I chose Yuna.
That's why I chose Yuna.
I didn't cheat.
I don't want to.
No.
Your father didn't notice.
I told him.
I wanted to test your mother.
I thought I could do it.
You can't.
I couldn't believe my sister cheated on me.
I'm sorry.
Damn it.
Add it.
I didn't say it's okay.
Eat more.
Yuna, eat more.
You can still do it.
This time, you have to eat while talking.
You can't see it.
Do it so you can see it.
I can't.
Open your mouth.
You forgot to speak.
Does it feel good to touch yourself?
What is it?
I can't see it.
It's good.
You can talk as much as you want.
Your eyes are closed.
The other side.
The balls.
Breathe more.
Look this way.
The upper layer.
Your eyes are closed.
Don't say that.
You closed your eyes yourself.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
I don't know.
Open your mouth.
Breathe more.
It feels good.
It's getting harder.
Open your mouth.
I can't believe I can save my life.
We can only say goodbye like this.
Take care.
Isn't this too flashy?
I wonder if my parents' impression will be bad.
Harumi?