A few days later
Mahiro-chan!
That's enough.
Can I call you back?
Yes, I got it.
A few days later
Hey, can you get me some gum syrup?
Come on, I'm not a salesperson.
A few days later
I'm sorry, I didn't see you before.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Here's my cell phone.
What?
You still play this game?
I still have a lot of it.
Wow, I miss it.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Are you Suguru?
What?
Who are you?
Were you born in Yamagata?
What?
A few days later
Are you Mahiro?
Wow, it's been a long time.
I know.
It's been 8 years.
No way.
Mahiro used to be so plain.
Did he change now?
At first, I didn't know who he was.
Did he change that much?
He changed a lot.
But he hasn't changed at all.
I feel like he hasn't changed at all.
Really?
He's still the same.
Yeah, you're right.
I want to talk to you more, but I have to go back to work.
I want to talk to you more.
Me too.
Has he changed?
Yeah, he's still the same.
I'll call you when I'm done with my part-time job.
Would you like to go out for a meal?
I agree.
I'll call you later.
See you.
Bye-bye.
What should I do?
What?
You're staring at me.
Do I have something on my face?
No, you don't.
You're different.
You're so different from the Mahiro I used to know.
You're so upset.
He hasn't changed. Are you praising him?
Yeah, I'm praising him.
Are you making fun of him?
No, I'm not.
To be honest, he's so beautiful now.
Do you mean he's cute?
Yeah, he's cute.
You're making fun of me.
I'm sorry.
I used to say he was like my little sister.
You're making fun of me.
No, I'm not.
What?
Why are you so nervous?
You don't have to be nervous.
Do you like alcohol?
Yeah, I do.
I like it so much that I often drink it.
I drank it until yesterday morning.
Really?
I'm nervous, so let's drink.
Yeah, let's drink.
Can you drink?
I can drink a little.
Really?
Yeah.
I wonder if there is such a thing.
Mahiro, you're strong.
Yeah, I'm strong.
How much can you drink?
120.
That's amazing.
Can you drink?
I can drink 150.
I don't understand.
You're lying.
Mahiro, you're lying, too.
Then I'll drink this much.
Can you drink wine?
Yeah, I can.
Really?
I can drink it.
I can drink it if I have a dry mouth.
I don't understand.
Anyway, let's drink.
Yeah, please.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Two wines, please.
Wait a minute.
What is this?
Two.
Two?
It's delicious.
It's the best.
Wine is delicious.
It's delicious.
Did you drink it already?
Yeah.
You're amazing, Mahiro.
I drank it all.
What happens to you when you drink?
I want to have sex.
Why are you saying that all of a sudden?
Don't you want to have sex?
It's not that I don't want to have sex.
Are you a virgin?
I'm not a virgin.
You've been a virgin for a long time.
Mahiro is the same.
We can't talk to other people.
Even if I have a boyfriend, I can't talk to myself well.
Really?
I really want to have sex, but I can't.
I know that.
Really?
I broke up with my ex-girlfriend.
Even if I try to have sex with her, I can't.
Is she strong?
She's very strong.
You're the same.
That's right.
Mahiro is interested in that kind of thing.
You're amazing.
Me too.
Really?
Why are you grinning?
Do you want to have a drink with me?
I don't want to.
Let's go to a hotel.
Let's go to a hotel and have a drink.
I did my best.
I did it.
I can't do it anymore.
Are you kidding me?
You're kidding me, right?
It's too much to talk about.
What are you talking about?
I didn't talk about it.
I only talked about pure sex.
What should I do?
I used it yesterday.
It's hard to walk home.
What are you looking at?
What are you going to do after this?
What?
After this?
I think you'll lose your last year.
That's right.
What should I do?
What?
What do you want to do?
I'm asking you.
It's hard to answer.
What should I do?
You go first.
What?
You should say it.
I'll say it.
What I'm thinking now.
You're cheating.
I'll say it.
Let's go to the hotel.
I knew you'd say it.
No, I just said what I thought.
You're cheating.
I knew you'd say it.
Don't you want to go?
What are you going to do?
Let's go.
I knew you'd say it.
Of course I want to go.
I'm finally here.
I want to lie down.
Let me take off my shoes.
I can't reach it.
Here you are.
Be careful.
I'm sorry.
Here you are.
I'm sleepy.
Give me a massage.
Okay.
Where do you want me to massage?
Back?
It hurts.
Was it strong?
Be gentle.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
I just touched you.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
What are you doing?
I'm taking a bath.
More.
More?
Down.
Down?
Here?
Yes.
More up.
More up?
Here?
More forward.
Forward?
Here?
More forward.
More down.
More?
There.
There?
Yes.
It's a massage.
It's a massage, so it feels good.
It feels good.
You're good at massaging.
Really?
Yes.
Is it hard to do with clothes?
It's a little hard.
Let me take it off.
This?
Yes.
Can you do it?
I'm trying to do it.
I can't do it.
You can't?
Yes.
How about this?
I can do it.
Like this?
Yes.
Raise your hand.
Put it all down.
Down?
Yes.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's okay.
I'll do it a little more.
What?
It's okay.
I'll do it again.
Mahiro.
Yes.
You're getting bigger.
Really?
Yes.
I don't know because I haven't taken off my clothes yet.
I'm the only one who's taking off my clothes.
Don't do that.
I know.
I wanted to try this.
Can you do it?
Yes.
Do you know how to do it?
This...
How do you do it?
Did you just do something?
No.
No?
I'm sorry.
What?
You don't have any impression?
I'm sorry.
I was so surprised that I said too much.
Surprised?
Isn't that a bad thing?
Really?
It's a word that gets stuck in my mouth.
Is that so?
Let me take it off.
I'll take it off.
Let me take it off, too.
It hurts.
Are you okay?
Be more careful.
You've been like that for a long time.
How about you?
You're too polite.
That's not true.
It doesn't make sense.
I've got muscles, too.
That's great.
You look like you have a way.
Do I look cool?
You look cool.
I'll be more cool.
Stop it.
Are you cool?
Yes, I am.
Here you are.
Thank you.
You've grown a lot.
It's still hot.
I'll give you a massage.
A massage?
Yes, a massage.
I'm embarrassed to do this to you.
I'm embarrassed, too.
Stop it.
Yes.
You smell like alcohol.
Because we drank together.
What do you mean?
You smell like alcohol.
Don't bite me.
Your lips are red.
Really?
My lips are soft.
Can you take off your clothes?
Take it off.
I took it off.
It's soft.
Is it soft?
Yes, it is.
I can't help it.
You look like a child.
Don't say that.
It's awkward.
We look good together, don't we?
I think so.
Really?
I don't know yet.
I'm going to go crazy.
What will you do?
I don't know.
I'm going to try it.
You're going to try it.
What's this?
I'm going to let you sleep.
Are you going to let me sleep?
Yes.
You've grown a lot.
Don't you want to sleep?
I can't help it.
That's great.
Smell it.
It stinks.
I'm kidding.
That's great.
Do you like it?
You've grown a lot.
You like it, don't you?
Do you like it?
That's great.
Your eyes are getting harder.
I feel sick.
Is that so?
Yes.
What?
Who will blame?
I don't know who will blame.
I want to blame.
Do you?
Who will blame?
I'm not blaming you.
I can't do it.
I'll do it first.
I'll do it from the bottom.
I'll do it from the top.
It's bigger than I thought.
Did you hide it?
I didn't hide it.
It smells bad.
You're lying.
I'm not lying.
You're spilling it.
I'm not spilling it.
It looks like it's going to explode.
Do you want me to lick it?
I can't do it.
It feels so good.
There's a hair on it.
It's a panty hair.
I can't do it.
It's very hard.
Can you stand this?
I can't stand this.
It feels so good.
Mahiro, when did you learn this?
It's a secret.
I can't do it.
It feels so good.
It looks like it's going to explode.
It's over.
Can you do it?
I can't do it.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
You're licking it a lot.
I'm not.
What's this?
I don't know.
You're licking it a lot.
Stop it.
I don't like it.
I'm going to put it on you.
How is it?
Does it smell?
It smells good.
How long are you going to sleep?
You're going to get in the way.
Open your eyes.
I'm embarrassed.
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
I don't want to.
Don't look at me like that.
Why don't you look at me like that?
I can't do it.
I feel like I'm going to pass out when I'm drunk.
I don't want to.
It hurts.
I can't do it.
I don't feel good.
Come here.
Bring it here.
Wait a minute.
The other way around.
I want to do this, but I can't say it.
I can't do it.
I've never done this before.
It hurts.
I can't do it.
I want to do this, but I can't say it.
It was so painful.
I can't do it.
Don't tease me.
Wait a minute.
I can't do it.
It's too hard.
Why is it so hard?
It's because your eyebrows are attractive.
Wait a minute.
It hurts.
I can't do it.
What?
Salt?
Do you have salt?
I don't have salt.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Move more.
I can't do it.
It hurts.
Wait a minute.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
It's too hard.
It's very big.
Make it smaller.
Can you do it?
I can't do it.
It feels good.
It's too hard.
I can't do it.
It's big.
I can see it.
Can you see it?
It feels good.
Don't move.
It came out.
I'm sorry.
Are you used to it?
It's too big.
Wait.
Where did you learn it?
It's a secret.
I can't do it.
Don't move.
Can you see it?
I can see it.
You like it, don't you?
I can't do it.
Wait.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Is it a good match?
It's definitely a good match.
It's just a little bit.
It feels good.
It's moving.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Hurry up.
Wait a minute.
I'm going.
I can't do it.
Why?
Why does it feel so good?
I can't do it.
What are you going to do after this?
I still have time until the departure.
I see.
Let me sleep in your house.
What?
What do you mean?
Can't I?
It's okay.
Can I?
Let's do it.
It was too far to walk.
My legs hurt.
You should have taken a taxi.
We didn't have anything when we took a taxi.
You wanted to have sex with me, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
Me too.
What?
I'm tired.
I'm sleepy.
Good night.
I'm going to sleep.
Good morning.
I'm ready.
Wait a minute.
You're still wearing these glasses.
Is it bad?
I'm wearing them all the time.
So, I'm calm.
What?
You're wearing too many clothes.
I'm wearing underwear.
What?
It's hot in this house.
You'll get dirty.
I see.
You're wearing too many clothes.
Isn't it hot in this house?
It's hot.
I haven't changed my clothes since yesterday.
You're right.
Cooking alone is delicious.
Cooking alone is delicious?
You're wrong.
Did I make a mistake?
Don't worry about it.
Cooking alone is delicious.
Really?
I'll take this.
This is my protein.
This is the source of protein.
This is delicious.
Did you eat this, too?
Yes.
Do you have time?
I have time.
I have to go to work after eating this.
I see.
Don't you have a job?
I have a job today.
Why are you laughing?
I don't understand.
I'm having fun.
I'm going to eat this.
Okay.
I'm coming.
I'm back.
What's wrong?
I'm close to my workplace.
Excuse me.
You think this is your house, don't you?
What are you reading?
This is an erotic manga.
What is this?
This is a masterpiece.
This is an erotic manga.
This is not an ordinary erotic manga.
Stop it.
You read this a lot.
All erotic manga are the same.
This is not the same.
I've read this many times.
What do you like about this?
Don't you know what I like about this?
You're an otaku, so you know.
I don't want you to tell me.
I'm an otaku.
That's a long time ago.
That's right.
This is an erotic manga.
This is amazing.
Are you excited?
Anyone would be excited to see this.
Are you feeling erotic?
I'm feeling erotic.
Are you standing up?
I'm standing up.
You're standing up.
Your clothes are wet.
Do you want to see it?
I want to see it.
What?
Your clothes are wet.
Tell me the truth.
What are you talking about?
Your clothes are wet.
Touch it.
Does it tickle?
I'm in pain.
You're sweating a lot.
I wanted to have a baby.
Did you know that?
You don't know that.
Hmm?
Let me kiss you.
Hey, I brought something good today.
Something good?
Can you take off your bag?
Huh? Oh, this.
I'm sure you'll like it.
What is it?
Can you tell?
Spray?
Yeah, you like this kind of stuff, right?
I love this kind of spray.
You want a maid?
Yeah.
Hey, wait a minute.
Isn't it great?
I'll make you a special public change of clothes.
Can I?
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
I just bought it, so I don't know how to put it on.
Wow.
I really like maids.
Really?
Yeah.
Wow, you're an otaku.
Okay.
Why?
You're not looking at me. You're looking at the maid.
I want to look at both.
Look at me.
I'm looking.
Okay.
My body has become so sexy.
What?
I don't think you saw it before.
You know what I mean, right?
You look like a woman now.
What are you doing?
Do your best.
Look.
Cosplay.
This?
What should I do?
Pants?
Put on the pants.
How can I do this?
Like this.
Close here.
Wait.
Isn't it loose?
Really?
Like this.
This.
This is a front hairpin.
Is this a front hairpin?
Isn't it?
Stop here.
Isn't it the other way around?
This is right.
Really?
I don't care.
How long are you going to wear the bra?
Mahiro told me to wear it.
Is this a pants?
No way.
I'm so happy to see people who wear this kind of clothes.
Really?
Yes.
Ero.
I'm going to attack you.
Wait.
I haven't put on the important headband yet.
Put this on.
It's done.
You look good.
Are you an otaku?
It's too big.
I'm going to put this on you.
Master.
Thank you.
Moe.
You are too aggressive.
I'm going to do anything for you.
Are you going to do anything for me?
Moe.
Are you dead?
I'm dead.
I'm in trouble.
What do you want me to do?
I'm going to die.
Don't I have to do anything?
No.
I want you to serve me.
Please sit down.
Please, master.
Okay.
Excuse me.
How do I look?
Don't I look like a priest?
I'm going to take off my socks.
Okay.
Take off your socks.
What?
Is it an order?
You are a maid.
Don't give me an order.
Take off your socks.
Are you kidding me?
I'm in trouble.
Excuse me.
Okay.
You like me, don't you?
You know I like you, don't you?
Really?
I'm excited.
You haven't changed at all.
I know.
Take off your socks.
Okay.
What?
I'm in trouble.
What do you want me to do today?
What did you do today?
I want you to feel good.
What?
You're using unfamiliar words.
Feel good.
And?
Do you get it?
Do you get it, master?
You're cute.
Do you have a weak neck?
Yes.
You hit me a lot.
I can't stand it.
I'll lick you.
No.
No?
I don't mean that.
What do you mean?
I want you to do it.
But you said no.
No.
Can I lick you?
No?
No.
I said no.
Can I lick you?
No.
Aren't you very excited?
I am.
It's dangerous here.
It's hot.
It's very hot.
Yes.
I'll give you a reward.
What is it?
Chocolate banana.
Chocolate banana?
I'm glad.
Excuse me.
Chocolate banana.
It's very hard.
It's big.
Can I lick you?
Yes.
Let's eat.
It's good.
It's dangerous.
It's very hard.
It's normal for you to do this.
It's dangerous.
I'm excited.
What is it?
Is it dangerous?
Yes.
It's dangerous.
Are you at your limit?
I'm not at my limit.
Let's do it again.
It's hot.
What?
I want you to make me feel good, too.
A maid who doesn't behave like this needs to be punished.
Is that so?
Wait a minute.
What is it?
What is it? Why do you have it?
It's a secret.
What is it?
Put this on.
I can't see it.
It's okay if you can't see it.
What are you going to do to me?
I'll punish you.
What?
Don't move.
You can't put it on.
Do you usually play like this?
No.
I just happened to have it.
It's not a coincidence.
It's a coincidence.
Is that so?
Is it a hobby?
It's okay.
What are you going to do to me?
What do you think I'll do to you?
You can move your hands freely like this.
No.
Please stop it.
It's a punishment for doing that to your husband.
Oh, no.
I feel sick.
I'm going to pass out.
I don't understand.
No.
Why?
It's a punishment.
I want to go.
I'll make you sweat a lot.
I feel sick.
Do you want me to hit your nipples?
I want you to hit my nipples.
I have to ask you to do more.
Please give me more time.
Please.
I feel sick.
Wait a minute.
Don't do that.
I feel sick.
I'll put this in here.
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
Please let me go.
Do you want me to let you go?
I feel sick.
Wait a minute.
Please let me go.
I feel sick.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to go?
I want to go.
Please let me go.
I feel sick.
Wait a minute.
Why?
I told you not to do that.
I feel sick.
Do you want me to let you go?
Please let me go.
I feel sick.
No.
I want to go.
Please let me go.
Yes, yes, yes
I'm counting on you
Please let me go
Okay
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
It feels so good! It feels so good!
AI-chan!
Yes, yes, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going
I told you I wanted you to go
But I can't, I can't, I can't
I'm going, I'm going
I want everything, I want everything
I want everything
It feels so good!
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going
I want everything
Please let me go
Ah! No, no, no, AI-chan!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
I want everything
Can I take this off now?
Not yet
Do you want me to put this on?
Yes, hurry up
Hurry up
Ah! Ah! Ah!
No!
It hurts, it hurts
Ah, it feels so good
My teeth feel so good
It feels so good
Tell me to keep going
Keep going
Ah! Ah! Ah! It feels so good
It hurts, it hurts
Ah! Ah! Ah! It hurts, it hurts
I want you to follow me from behind
Ok
Ah!
No!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
It feels so good
I want you to follow me
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah!
Wait a minute
What are you going to do?
I'm sorry
Stop it!
Ah!
It feels so good
Ah! It hurts!
Ah!
I'll hold it for you.
I can't do it.
You can do it.
Ah, it feels good.
It's so hot.
It feels good.
I'm going to go.
You can't do it on your own.
I can't do it.
My legs are moving.
Don't move.
I can't do it.
My stomach is getting sensitive.
Why am I so energetic?
I'm going to break this.
Really?
Are you glad?
This is great.
I can't do it.
Don't move.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Come on.
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Wait...
I'm going to die
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
You're sweating too much
Oh no
You're sweating so much
I'm sweating so much
Here
I'll give you a bath
Please
Oh no
It felt so good
I'm going to die
And then Mahiro
On the day I had a part-time job
He always came to my house
You're so scary
We meet almost every day
But I don't hate it
I'm here
I can't say I'm his lover
But I can tell that he doesn't want anything more
When we're together
You're feeling better now
It's because you licked me
Oh no
This relationship
This distance is the best
The washing machine is stopped
I can't do this
I'm going to die
Oh no
I'm going to wash you
Please
Now
I'm going to wash your mouth
Wait
My back is weak
I can't do it
I'm going to wash your back
I know
What?
This
Wash this
Wow
When did you know?
You washed my back
I can't put my mouth in
It's too big
See
It's too small
I'm going to wash your back
Oh no
Is it clean now?
Not yet
Not yet?
It's dirty
Yes
I know
What?
I'm going to wash your breasts
Breasts?
Yes
Like this?
I wonder if I can do it
Does it feel good?
Yes
Can you do it?
It feels good
Really?
Yes
Can you do it?
Wow
It feels good
Oh no
Let's stop
Why did you come closer?
I thought it would be easier to wash
Does it feel good?
Yes
How long is your neck?
It feels good
Sit properly
there we go
it's time for me to ask for your permission
I've done my best
can I ask you for your permission?
I wonder how long it will take
ok, then
come on, say your tongue
ok, I get it
You're right.
I'll make Mahiro happy.
Really? I'm not a slave.
I know.
Will you make her happy?
Yes, I will.
Ah.
You can put it in your mouth.
Can I?
Yes.
Ah.
Did it come out?
Yes.
Hey.
Yes?
It's a promise.
After this,
smile at me ten times.
More than ten times?
Yes.
Okay.
I'll make you feel good.
What?
I didn't tell you this, but...
I'm going home for a week from tomorrow.
What? Really?
Yes.
You're going to leave me, right?
I'm not going to leave you.
I'll be away from you for a week.
Really?
You don't look lonely at all.
It's too heavy.
I feel emotionless.
What? Are you happy to leave me?
I'm not happy.
Are you lonely?
I'm very lonely.
I'm with you almost every day.
Yes.
So, I'm just lonely.
Then, make a lonely face.
You don't look lonely at all.
You look sour.
You look like a sour man.
No.
I'm laughing because you're funny.
I'm very sad inside.
Really?
Yes.
Then, today will be the last night.
Why are you looking at me like that?
What?
I can't see you for a while.
I don't want to see you.
I don't want you to see me.
You should kiss me.
I don't want to see you.
What?
You should kiss me.
Yes.
I want to kiss you, too.
Let's do it for a week today.
I don't want to do it.
Yes.
I don't want to do it for a week.
I don't want to do it.
Let's do it for a week.
Yes.
It's hard, isn't it?
We haven't seen each other for a week.
It's a long time.
What?
I want to hug you.
Okay.
Sit down.
Raise your hand.
My hand?
Yes.
Raise your hand.
It's okay.
Did you tickle me?
No, I didn't.
You found out my weakness.
Ouch!
I didn't do anything.
You did.
Don't do that.
I don't want to do it alone.
It's good, isn't it?
No.
You're standing up.
I'm standing up.
It's good, isn't it?
I'll be lonely if I don't see you.
I'll miss you so much.
Let's do it for a week.
It's hard.
Oh, no.
Lie down.
Ouch!
Oh, no.
It's hard.
You're getting a lot of massage.
It's for a week.
Then,
I'll do something you've never done before.
What?
Come here.
I'll do something you've never done before.
Okay.
Oh, no.
Oh, no?
Ouch!
What?
You're standing up.
Ouch!
Oh, no.
I can't stand it anymore.
Ouch!
You're getting a lot of massage.
What?
You're trying to do it for a week?
I'm trying to do it for a week.
I have to do it all the time.
You're getting a lot of massage.
What?
Oh, no.
You're amazing.
Ouch!
You're doing it for a week?
Yes.
Oh, no.
You're getting a lot of massage.
Oh, no?
Hang in there.
Are you sure you want to do it for a week?
No, I'm not.
You're doing it for a week, aren't you?
Hang in there.
I can't do it.
Can you give me a massage?
Of course.
Sit down.
Can I sit down?
What?
Oh, no.
You're getting a lot of massage.
I can't feel my neck.
You can feel it, right?
No, I can't.
I can't feel it.
You can't feel it?
No.
Can I give you a massage with this?
Yes.
You were purring.
I can't feel it.
You can do it.
No, I can't.
I can't do it.
You can do it.
Here, too.
You don't usually do such a thing.
It's special.
I can't do it.
I can feel it.
Oh, no.
Let's go.
I can't do it.
You're getting a lot of massage.
Let me give you a massage.
Lie down.
I can't feel it.
You're getting a lot of massage.
I can't do it.
I can feel it.
Let's go.
I can't do it.
I'm wearing underpants, but I can't do it.
You're getting a lot of massage.
Lie down.
You're wearing underpants, aren't you?
I can't do it.
You're lying.
I don't know.
Let me check it.
No.
Before that, look at my back.
Your back?
Yes.
Are you sensitive?
I don't know.
I can't do it.
Lie down.
My back hurts.
I can't do it.
You're getting a lot of massage.
Let me check it.
No.
Raise your legs.
Hey.
What?
What's this?
I can't see.
You're sticky.
It's difficult.
You're eating.
Why?
I don't like it.
I can't do it.
Hey.
I gave you bread.
I can't do it.
Ai-chan.
It feels good.
Let's go.
There's something I want to do.
What is it?
It felt good just now.
Let me see.
Can I do it?
Yes.
I wanted to do it.
Drink it more.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Let's go.
I want to drink it.
Show it to me.
It feels good.
Let's go.
I'll make you feel good.
I'm going to go.
It feels good.
I want to put it in.
It's hard.
Look at me.
I want to put it in.
I'm a little sleepy.
I'm full of colors.
Ohh...
Ummm...
Wait...
Oh no...
I didn't go in the mirror.
Oh...
You're not gonna wake up.
Let's go.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It doesn't feel good at all, does it?
It feels good.
Do you like this?
Does it hurt?
It feels good, doesn't it?
No, it doesn't.
It's moving.
I want to move, too.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm going to go.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
I'm going, so I can't stand it.
Ouch.
I'm going, but I'm tired.
I'm going.
It hurts.
Show me your butt.
My butt?
Look at me.
I'm in trouble.
It hurts.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm in trouble.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm in trouble.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm sorry.
Show me your butt.
You're going to show me?
Yes.
It feels good.
I'm in trouble.
It's really hard.
What's going on?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
I'm in trouble.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Show me your butt.
I'm in trouble.
I'm going.
Let's go together.
I'm in trouble.
I want you to push me from below.
You're very energetic.
I'm in trouble.
It feels good.
I'm going.
I'm in trouble.
It's too fast.
It feels good.
I want more.
I'm in trouble.
I'm going.
Why is it so hard?
I'm in trouble.
It feels good.
I'm going.
I'm in trouble.
It feels good.
I'm going.
I'm in trouble.
It feels good.
It's not enough.
You can do it.
I'm going.
I'm in trouble.
It feels good.
I'm going.
I can't do it.
I'm in trouble.
It feels good.
I'm going.
Let me go.
I'm in trouble.
I can't see.
It's going to take a week.
I feel better.
I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
There is no more development with Mahiro.
At this time, I was so sure.
Well, it's okay.
Because I can do so many cute things.
Hey.
Aren't you hungry?
Are you hungry now?
Yes.
I want to eat grilled meat.
Do you want to eat grilled meat?
I want to eat garlic.
I want to do it again.
It's okay.
Let's go.
You have a lot of energy.
I can't see you for a while.
That's right.
What?
Hey.