I bought it without checking it, but what are you going to make?
Check it out?
Let's make stamina sometimes.
That's a good idea.
I still have to cheer up.
Do you think so?
I really think so.
I'm glad you say that.
I still have to put in nutrition.
Yuta.
Hibiki will make the meat you like today.
I hope you like it.
Hey, Yuta.
It's okay.
We've been married for six months.
I don't want to live like that.
It's okay.
I know how you feel.
I'm the one who's been rolling around.
I'm sorry.
Yuta.
This is Hibiki Natsume.
My father is dating this person right now.
He's thinking of getting married.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Hibiki Natsume.
My ex-husband died of illness and I was single.
After that, I continued to live alone.
I met my current husband, Mr. Satoru.
Mr. Satoru's ex-wife died of illness.
He was living with his daughter.
Mr. Satoru was in real estate management.
He needed a partner to take care of his son.
Four months later, we got married.
I'll be home early today.
Let's have dinner together.
Thank you.
See you.
Take care.
What's wrong?
Shut up.
What's wrong with you?
Calm down.
I'm married to my ex-husband.
That's not true.
I'm in trouble.
My father said so.
Shut up.
Yuta.
What's wrong with you?
You slept in your pants.
Don't look at me like that.
Shut up.
Stop it.
You're crazy.
Let go of me.
I don't care anymore.
Stop it.
Shut up.
Don't pretend to be angry.
I'll tell my father.
Tell him.
I'm angry.
Don't be angry.
You're cute.
Get out of my way.
Stop it, Yuta.
Or do you want to be born in this state?
I'm not a bitch.
You're my mother.
Do you sleep in your pants?
I don't sleep in my pants.
I can see it.
You slept in your pants.
Don't touch me.
I'm wrong.
What's wrong with you?
Let go of me.
You're a bitch.
Don't say that.
You wanted to do it.
I'm wrong.
I have to answer this.
Stop it.
Shut up.
You're a bitch.
Stop it.
You're cute.
You haven't touched me yet.
I haven't touched you yet.
What's the difference?
It's okay.
You can't stop in this state.
You can't do that.
Shut up.
Your hands are stiff.
You're excited.
It's okay.
Your hands are stiff.
Stop it.
It's okay.
You touched me.
Shut up.
Your hands are stiff.
It's okay.
Why don't you try touching it yourself?
You're wet, aren't you?
I can't touch it.
Then you'll have to check it yourself.
No, Yuta-san.
What?
We're family.
Stop it.
Get out of my way.
You're not wet, so you can see it.
I'm just checking if you're wet.
Stop it.
Get out of my way.
What is this?
Stop it.
It's so wet.
Don't look at it.
You're wet, so admit it.
I'm not wet.
You're saying it, but you feel like you're being attacked.
It's fine, right?
Not yet.
Say it to Satoru-san.
You still don't know what's going on, do you?
Before Satoru-san calls you,
you'll be able to protect this cute face.
Don't say that.
So be quiet.
I don't know.
Shut up.
Shut up and open your eyes again.
It's so wet.
Stop it.
What's with that voice?
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Open your legs.
It's easy for you to put your finger in it.
You're making such a loud voice.
I can't help it.
Stop it.
You're making such a loud voice.
You can't stop here.
If you keep doing that, you'll end up in Japan.
I won't, so stop it.
I'll show you.
What's in there?
It's so dirty.
Look at it.
Your son's finger.
It's all dirty.
Don't say that.
Why?
You'll be sad.
I won't.
You've come all the way here.
You can't stop now.
Look.
Your neck's been twitching.
Stop it.
What did you say?
I didn't say anything.
You did.
Look at this finger.
It's over.
Look at it.
It's twitching.
Did my finger feel good?
You're the only one who feels good.
Stop it.
You'll make me feel good, too.
Come on.
I haven't said anything yet.
Open your mouth and make me feel good.
Come on.
Eat it.
Don't stand up.
Don't let go.
I'm your mother.
You don't know?
What are you talking about?
Stop it.
You're the only one who says that.
It's not like that.
Come on.
Let's go back to our room.
If you make me feel good, I'll stop.
Come on.
Add it yourself.
Will you stop if I make you feel good?
Yeah.
You've been waiting for a long time.
Look at me, not at me.
It's not like that.
You can be more scared.
I don't think I can make you feel good.
Open your mouth again.
I licked it, so let's end it.
It doesn't feel good yet.
It's okay, right?
Come on.
Open your mouth.
No.
You can't do this.
Shut up.
Stop it.
I can still stop.
Come here.
Stop it.
Don't close your mouth.
I told you to stop it.
If you feel good, I'll stop it.
Stop it.
No.
Open your mouth again.
Stop it.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Do you want your hands more?
You're making such a loud voice with your hands.
If you're a chimp, you'll feel better.
I don't have anything to do.
Let me go.
Shut up.
This is good.
Open your mouth.
It's still wet.
Don't say that.
Every time you close your mouth, it gets wet.
It's wet, isn't it?
No.
It's still wet.
I told you to stop it.
I haven't told you yet.
I'll wait for you, so stop it.
Shut up.
It's still wet, isn't it?
I told you to stop it.
Shut up.
Don't you think it's bad?
It's still wet, isn't it?
Shut up.
Say something.
It's still wet, isn't it?
Stop it.
You're bleeding.
I'll kill you.
No, no.
No, don't.
I told you.
You've made a fool of yourself.
Have you ever made a fool of yourself with your father?
I won't say a word.
Hey, what's gotten into you?
Clean it up for me.
Come on.
That's enough. Stop it.
Shut up.
It's over.
What?
Hey, wait a minute.
It's not over yet.
It's over, isn't it?
Open your mouth.
It's not over yet.
Look at me.
I'm going to take a bath.
Wait.
It's not over yet.
Come on.
Open your mouth.
It's dangerous.
I'm going to take a bath.
It's over, isn't it?
Shut up.
I'm going to take a bath.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
It's not over yet.
It's not over, isn't it?
You're shaking a little.
It's not over yet.
No, I can't.
No, no, I can't.
Let me go.
Let me go, Yuta.
No, I can't.
Look, I'll clean it up.
Right?
Look, it's dirty.
Look.
Look, put it in.
I wanted to put it in again when it was lit.
Open your legs.
You know, right?
Open up more.
Look.
Come here.
Stop putting it in.
What should I do?
I can't put it in.
You've already done it twice.
It doesn't change.
It feels good, doesn't it?
What do you think?
How does it taste?
Look.
If I put it in more than this,
will I be able to have children?
You can have children with your mother.
I can't do that.
It's okay.
I'm your son.
I can't.
What should I do?
Your mouth is so big.
I told you to open your mouth.
I didn't.
I told you.
Stop putting it in.
I can't.
I'm your mother.
You can't.
I think it was good to have a mother.
It was nice to have a mother.
I've never been in any relationship with you.
I'm glad to have you.
This is the first time I'm talking to you.
I'll take a picture of you.
Show me your face.
This is a photo of evidence.
If you go to your father,
will you spread it on the internet?
You can take a lot of pictures.
Delete it.
No.
What's wrong, Hibiki?
It's so quiet.
Are you sick?
I'm fine.
It's not like that.
Is that so?
What's wrong?
What?
It's nothing.
Is that so?
It's itchy.
Yuta.
I don't want you to eat.
It's like a living room.
Stop it.
Didn't you feel it?
You didn't resist it.
And you closed it.
Satoru was next to me.
You said that.
You wanted to do it, right?
Come here.
Stop it.
It's dangerous.
It's not like that.
Stop it.
Don't say that.
I'll do it.
It's dangerous.
Calm down.
Yuta.
You didn't come here to do this, did you?
What did you come here for?
Stop it.
You didn't.
Shut up.
Your clothes will break.
You closed it.
It's not like that.
Do you miss me?
Shut up.
It's not like that.
You closed it.
Stop it.
Calm down.
You wanted this, right?
Stop it.
You didn't try to put it in.
If you want, you can do it a little more.
No, you can't do it with your mouth.
What are you doing?
Oh, what? Stop it.
It's a little wet, isn't it?
I can't touch it.
It's still wet.
Don't put it in.
It's so wet.
Put your finger in.
It's okay.
What do you want?
I don't have to do it.
Give it to me.
Oh, you don't have to put your finger in.
I don't want it.
I understand.
You want it, don't you?
I'll open it again.
You want me to do it, don't you?
You're feeling better now.
Let go of me.
Shut up.
What's wrong?
Does it feel good?
Shut up.
What's wrong?
You wanted it, didn't you?
I wanted it.
You can't do it with your head.
Stop it.
What's wrong?
I'm going.
Have a nice day.
Take care of yourself.
What are you doing?
Dad left.
Let's do something nice like this again.
What?
Don't do anything weird.
You felt it the other day, didn't you?
That's not true.
Stop it.
I didn't do anything like this.
You're such a bitch.
Don't say that.
Stop it.
You're always in a daze.
You're reacting every time you touch me.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Stop it.
From that day on,
like almost every day,
Yuta's forced sexual behavior continued.
I realized again and again that
it was still the return of Yuta's loneliness.
He lost his mother when he was young,
and his lonely days continued without a trace in his heart.
I was able to endure it.
I'll show you what a bitch looks like.
I can't do it.
I'm going to drink with my colleague today,
so please take care of Yuta.
I understand.
Don't come in without permission.
It's okay.
We're family, aren't we?
By the way,
my father isn't here,
so I'll make you feel better.
Yuta,
stop doing this.
What are you talking about?
Even though you were always on my side,
you really want to have sex with a young man, don't you?
That's not true.
Please stop.
Your body reacts a lot
even though you don't like it in words.
Why are you running away?
We're family.
Stop it.
Let's deepen our relationship.
Please go home.
Shut up.
You really wanted to be attacked
because you dressed like this, didn't you?
That's not true.
You can't forget my chimp, can you?
Please stop.
Look at me.
How long are you going to be like this?
You're so fast.
You always make a loud voice.
Your body is going to get sick.
Please go home.
No.
Let me have more fun.
What is this color?
It doesn't matter.
Show me more erotic clothes.
Stop it.
Come on.
That's enough.
When I saw you dressed like this,
I heard you were wearing a purple dress.
I don't know.
Stop it.
That's enough.
I told you to be quiet.
I'm going to make you feel good.
I didn't ask you to do that.
You're wearing an erotic dress.
You really wanted to be attacked like this, didn't you?
You have a very cute voice.
What's the difference?
Please go home.
No.
I'm going to make you feel better.
Stop it.
That's enough.
You've become very quiet.
You really want to be bullied a lot, don't you?
You have a good voice.
Let me hear more.
You've become like this just by licking a little.
Be honest.
You feel good, don't you?
I don't feel good.
Really?
You really don't feel good?
No.
What?
If you don't feel good,
let me ask you here.
Stop it.
If you don't feel good,
you're not wet here, are you?
No.
Stop it.
What's wrong with you?
You're wet.
You're wetting the bed by licking a little.
And you're wearing an erotic dress.
You can't complain even if you get attacked.
It's okay.
Can I stop here?
Really?
Yes.
Be honest with your body.
Even from the top of your pants.
You know you're peeing here, don't you?
It's my fault.
Your voice is coming out.
No.
Shouldn't you be honest?
Stop it.
Can I really stop it?
You're peeing so much that I can't convince you.
Can you hear it?
You're peeing from the top of your pants.
What's this sound?
You're wearing an erotic dress.
What's going on behind you?
Let me see.
What's this?
You can barely see your buttocks.
Don't hurt me.
Is this your type?
I don't have a type.
Do you like wearing an erotic dress?
I want to touch it.
Don't move.
The area of your pants is too small to see your buttocks.
Don't touch me.
It's sticky here.
You're really peeing, aren't you?
What did you say?
Stop it.
Unlike the other day, you stopped being quiet.
Let me see more.
Do it yourself.
I don't want to be killed.
Hold it yourself.
Let me see your buttocks.
Come on.
It's sticky.
Do you want me to touch it more?
You're peeing from the top of your pants.
I don't need it anymore.
Really?
Go home.
Do you like wearing an erotic dress?
It doesn't matter.
It has nothing to do with me.
It has nothing to do with you?
Do you have a reason to wear an erotic dress when your father is out?
It's normal.
You're going to be attacked.
You're glaring at me.
I'm not.
Are you embarrassed?
Do you want me to touch it?
Yes.
I'm not telling you to stop here.
Be honest with me.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Do you like to go home?
Are you satisfied with my fingers?
Yes.
You keep talking about yourself.
Please make me feel good.
Come on.
You're a bitch.
Come closer.
You're waiting for me.
You have a big penis.
You can't go deeper than that.
Do your best.
You're a bitch.
Why are you blocking me with your hands?
Don't touch me with your hands.
One more time.
What are you doing?
Are you satisfied with my penis?
I can't.
It hurts.
You have a big penis.
Please make me feel good.
Don't touch me with your hands.
You have a big penis.
It hurts.
I'm not telling you to stop here.
You're a bitch.
I can't go deeper than that.
You have a big penis.
You can't go deeper than that.
Open your legs.
You want my penis, don't you?
No, I don't.
You're a bitch.
You have a big penis.
I can't go deeper than that.
You're a bitch.
You can't go deeper than that.
You're moving your hips just by moving your hips.
I want you to move.
You're moving.
You're moving like this.
You're working so hard.
I peppers out...
You're moving like this...
You're moving so hard.
You were moving so hard.
Can I?
I put it out for you.
Clean it up.
Do you want more?
Do you want more in your mouth?
Or do you want more in your mouth?
You want more, don't you?
You're a bitch.
That's not true.
Stop saying that.
Be honest.
Look.
There's a mole here.
Be honest.
I told you to go.
I didn't.
Where is it?
I can't see anything.
Don't look.
Try to move in that position.
It hurts.
I told you to go.
I didn't.
Did you feel good about my massage?
I don't want to.
Be honest.
You feel good about my massage, don't you?
I told you to go.
Try to move in that position.
Your legs are shaking.
I told you to move in that position.
I didn't.
Your legs are shaking.
Try to move in that position.
You feel good about my massage, don't you?
I don't.
I told you to go.
Try to move in that position.
It hurts.
Your legs are shaking.
I said I didn't.
I did it for so many times so it's the same.
It's okay.
Try to move in that position.
You can do it because you're a bitch.
Let me see your hand.
I can't believe it.
You want more, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Be honest with me.
Your nipples are so flat.
I can't convince you.
Come on, lie down.
What's wrong?
You're closing your eyes.
You're overflowing with tears.
Why?
Give me some fresh air.
Let me wet your nipples.
You're getting used to it.
You gave me so much fresh air.
You want more, don't you?
Don't cry.
It looks delicious.
It's delicious.
What's wrong, Hibiki?
You haven't been sleeping well lately, have you?
No, I haven't.
You look sleepy.
Maybe I lack sleep.
You lack sleep?
Is there a problem?
It's not a big deal.
Let's eat.
Is there a problem with Yuta?
No, not at all.
He's being helped a lot.
I see.
That's good.
I have to go to bed early today.
That's right.
I'll go to bed slowly.
It's okay.
Dad will definitely wake up.
It's noisy.
Go home.
If I tell you to do it, you'll do it.
Be quiet.
You're standing here more than usual.
You're in a situation.
That's what I thought.
You're just tracing it.
You're soaking wet.
You're soaking wet, aren't you?
I was lucky because I was next to you.
That's not true.
You're having fun, aren't you?
Isn't it strange?
You're lying down in front of your dad.
You'll get dirty.
You're dirty.
What's wrong with your body?
You're crying like this.
Did you get that dirty?
To be honest,
What's wrong with your body?
Be quiet.
What do you want to do?
What do you want me to do?
Did you wake up?
Tell me what to do.
I'll wake up.
What do you want me to do?
Put your tail on my pillow.
Okay.
What do you want me to do?
Lick it.
Lick it clean.
What's going on?
You want me to push you more, don't you?
Oh, my God.
Take it easy.
Was it good?
But I'm going to get caught.
It's okay.
Look at me.
You're so cute.
There have been days where sex has been used,
And every time I'm served,
I feel inferior.
It's become the body that gets excited.
Now I'm hiding from my husband
I'm starting to enjoy having sex with my son.