Today, I'm going to make fried eggplant nampura hitoshi.
It sounds delicious just to hear it.
First, Saji-kun will cut the eggplant.
Yes.
First, cut the stem and cut the eggplant in half.
Is this okay?
Is the knife okay?
Put your index finger on the base of the knife and hold it here.
Yes.
Is it like this?
Please cut it in half vertically.
I think this is good.
Yes.
Next, cut it diagonally to soak the fire and the taste.
I will make a cut.
Yes.
Is it like this?
If possible, let's make the width narrower.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm nervous because everyone is watching.
If you get used to it, the speed will increase, so it's okay.
Yes.
It smells good.
It looks delicious.
Can I take this first?
Please.
I will eat it first.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's refreshing.
It's easy to eat, so I'm looking forward to it.
Let's eat.
Yes.
I will eat it.
It's delicious.
I'm glad.
It's easy to make, but it's a combination that I can't think of at all.
It's amazing.
I can't make complicated dishes.
It's easy to make at home, but I started researching because I thought it would be nice to have a little trick.
If you make it at home, your husband will be surprised.
Me too.
I'm glad.
Your husband is always happy to eat, isn't he?
Yes.
I'm jealous.
You can do what you like at work.
SNS is amazing because you don't know where it will be.
That's right.
I was really surprised when I got a message from Mr. Tanaka asking me to open a classroom.
The classroom will be popular soon.
That's right.
Mr. Sashi, do you think so?
Yes.
I think it will be popular soon.
It's delicious.
My friends are interested in SNS.
The number of members may increase.
I'm sad, but I'm sad.
I want you to teach me slowly.
I'm looking forward to it because there are so many people.
Thank you for helping me.
I'm good at washing dishes.
I used to work part-time when I was a student.
What kind of work do you do now?
I'm a web designer now.
That's cool.
It's plain.
Why did you decide to open a cooking classroom?
I have to research about cooking at work.
I searched a lot on the Internet.
I found out that Mr. Sashi's cooking looked very delicious.
I have an older sister.
When I was a child, I liked the food she cooked for me.
So?
I wanted to try the food I made.
There are many delicious foods in the world.
I would be very happy if I could make delicious food by myself.
That's great.
I had a lot of fun in the cooking class.
Can I come again?
Of course.
Thank you.
Welcome back.
I told you not to wait for me.
Do you want to eat?
I've already eaten.
I see.
You don't have to cook every night.
Do you eat nutritious food?
I'm fine.
I'm going to take a bath.
Thank you.
What?
Hello.
What are you doing today?
I'm sorry.
I'm not feeling well.
I'm going to take a break from today's class.
I'm in Melmaga.
Melmaga?
I'm sorry.
I forgot to tell you the other day.
Did you come?
Yes.
Are you okay?
It's 8 o'clock in the morning.
I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
Did you eat something?
I don't have an appetite.
But you should eat something.
Do you want me to make something?
What?
Here you are.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Good morning.
Do you want to eat something?
No, I don't.
I have to go to the cooking class.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't look good.
It's amazing.
Let's eat.
Okay.
Thank you.
How is it?
It's delicious.
Did you make this?
Do you know that?
Of course.
It's fun to prepare something like this.
Thanks to you, I can cook well.
I'm glad.
It's really delicious.
I'm happy that someone says it's delicious and eats it.
I agree.
I'm glad.
Thank you for today.
Thank you, too.
Can you eat my food again?
Okay.
I want to cook for you.
Saze.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
I'm going to make a salad, so I'll cut the water from lettuce.
Cut the water?
Is there a reason why you should cut the water?
If you cut all the water, the dressing will taste light.
That's right.
You can cut it with your hands.
I cut it with my hands.
Do you cut everything with your hands?
I think it's easier to cut it with a kitchen knife.
Why?
I cut it with my hands because the nutrients don't escape.
I didn't know that.
That's right.
Let's do it together.
Okay.
I'll make the dressing.
I'll help you.
The water is dripping.
It's easy to cut.
The teacher is kind when cutting the leaves.
That's right.
Is this size okay?
This size is fine.
I'll eat a lot.
I'm sorry I always do that.
That's not true.
I'm sorry.
See you next week.
See you.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
I'll make tea.
I can't.
I love you.
You had a hard time.
It is too painful......
Don't worry......
It's okay.....
Let's get married.
I can't stand it.
Please.
I'm sorry.
Please stop.
I can't stand it.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You're a good girl.
You're so beautiful.
It's okay.
You're amazing.
You're so beautiful.
It's okay.
Oh, my God.
It's fine.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm fine.
Hang in there.
It's okay.
Don't cry.
Creature.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay
It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
What?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Onishi-chan.
Wake up, Onishi-chan.
Are you all right?
Hey!
Misa!
Misa?
It's all right, it's all right.
I love you.
I love you, sis.
It's all right, it's all right.
It hurts, it hurts.
It's all right.
I love you, sis.
It's all right, sis.
Mizu.
Not too much.
seis.
It feels bad.
Mizu.
It feels so bad.
It feels bad.
Mizu...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Thank you.
And you too.
There you go!
Thank you.
Boil over medium heat for about 10 minutes
When it starts to boil, reduce the heat to low and simmer for another 10 minutes
After 10 minutes, turn off the heat and let it cool
Divide the dough into 8 equal parts
It's been a long time since I've had a cold, so I feel like I'm going to have a cold again.
I'm going to have to take a cold medicine.
I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to die if I don't eat this.
I know I blocked your sight, but I would like to ask you something.
I know you can't see, but you can't hear...
But you can hear something, and I need your help.
But you can't hear, and I need your help.
Thank you very much.
I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's true or not, but I'm not sure if it's
true or not.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay, it's okay.
Next time, please teach me how to make rice omelette.
Rice omelette?
Where?
At my house.
What?
That's weird.
Rice omelette?
Here you go.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
It's a mess.
You've cleaned up quite a bit.
Yes.
Thank you.
Where's the rice omelette?
Let's make it.
Is it good?
It's good.
Let's make rice omelette.
Let's make rice omelette later.
Okay.
Do you have a hangover?
You don't have a hangover, do you?
I've been awake.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, put him back.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh
Oh oh oh oh oh
He licks my back.
He licks my feet.
He licks my head.
He licks my back.
Don't lick me again.
Don't lick me.
You're so beautiful.
Don't look at me.
Get your hands off me.
I can't see anything.
Don't look at me.
You're amazing, Megwin.
I can't see anything.
Heavy.
Heavy on the hands.
That's it.
Let loose.
Slowly.
Good girl!
Thank you so much for visiting our salon and organising an iPLAY FESTIVLY!
This is the first time...
my son has read an autograph!
I'm going to sleep.
You're sleeping very well.
Meiji.
I'm sleepy.
You're sleepy, aren't you?
Meiji.
I'm sleepy.
Don't move like that.
Don't move.
I'm sleepy.
I'm so happy.
I've never been this happy.
It's warm.
I'm so happy.
It hurts.
Breathe in and out slowly.
I love you.
I love you so much.
It's my first time to hug you from the side.
I feel so good when I hug you from the back.
I love you.
I love you so much.
You're doing okay.
Is it that bad?
I don't know what to do.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I'm sorry.
What are you laughing at?
Welcome back.
I was talking to the students.
You look happy.
Thank you.
Do you want to eat?
I don't need it.
What is it?
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
I've been working since morning.
I'm glad to hear that.
What?
I'm going to put a shine muscat on it.
The color is beautiful.
It's gorgeous.
It's fashionable.
I'm going to put black pepper on it.
It's a marinade.
Black pepper.
It looks delicious.
It's done.
It's great.
It's fashionable.
It's like a feast.
Let's eat.
Yes.
Let's get ready.
I'm going to get ready.
It's done.
It's beautiful.
I want to eat it.
I'm going to get a drink.
Thank you.
I can't stand it.
Can I?
What?
Can I keep it a secret from you?
Why?
He doesn't like me.
What?
He doesn't cook for me.
He has been cheating on me.
Is that so?
If I were you,
I want to eat a lot of rice every day.
It's delicious.
I don't know why, but I think it's because I'm a deaf person.
Remembering is not good, do you know why?
Indeed, sometimes, no school is good,
because they seek hearing aid and support,
I don't know what to say.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh oh
Hmm
Oh
I mean what they really are
I have always been careful
I just wanted to show at the beginning
Am I too late?
You want to pass
Pretty
Nothing
Exactly
It's too late
No.
Damn it.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
I don't know if it's a good thing or a bad thing, but I think it's a good thing.
I think it's a good thing.
I'm sorry.
You came all this way just to kiss me?
Even though you are my brother, I really didn't like that.
I'm sorry.
It's good to get used to her who takes care of us
Especially Diva lucy
She's really good at her work
Oh my god
helped me overcome so many things
After I met her, I could see her real verse
I think it really helped me
That's why I'm very happy
Yuu
Are you okay?
It feels so good.
It's not going to come out.
I'm sorry.
I'm sweating.
Open the arms.
Father, please pull in.
Back.
Open the arms.
Open.
Are you okay?
Are you all right?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm so glad.
It hurts so much.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
I love you.
It hurts.
I'm going to die.
It's too disgusting.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What am I going to do with you?
Miso...
I love you.
I love you too.