How have you been?
I have a lot of overtime work.
Really?
Do you have overtime work?
Yes.
It's only in the morning.
I see.
It's hard.
Yes.
You haven't come back yet today.
You should come back soon.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
You don't worry about me, do you?
No, I don't.
I see.
You do.
I don't doubt you.
I see.
You don't doubt me?
You are late every day.
I didn't think so.
I'm a single mother.
I'm sad.
Really?
I only come back once in six months.
What do you do when you are a single mother?
Do you count me in?
Is it true?
Of course I do.
I'm true, but I'm too sad to be a parent.
I don't know if single mothers get overboard.
Aren't you a true parent?
It's true, but I tend to get overboard.
I'm so popular with other people that I feel difficult to overbear.
You're determined.
You're right.
You're lucky to have a husband.
I'm not lucky to have a husband.
No, you're not.
Don't you feel that way?
I do.
You do, don't you?
Yes, I do.
If you're lonely, you feel lonely even if you don't have a husband, don't you?
I do.
Really?
Can you sympathize with me?
But I haven't met him yet.
Oh, you haven't met him yet.
So I can't find a husband.
I see.
You haven't met him yet.
You look like you have a husband.
I want to know where he is.
I want you to introduce me to him.
Is it okay?
I can do it.
It's okay.
How do you feel?
Do you want to share it with me?
It's okay.
It's fun.
You look like you have a husband.
I haven't met him yet.
You haven't met him yet?
Yes.
You have a good body.
It's a waste not to play with you.
You're right.
But you're so delicate.
You're so delicate.
You're amazing.
You're right.
You're so delicate.
You're amazing.
I didn't know you were so delicate.
I'm the sexiest.
Did you aim for this?
Do I need to be delicate?
You're delicate enough.
I'm learning from you.
You're the most delicate.
I was surprised.
You have beautiful eyes.
I didn't expect you to be so delicate.
I'm going to use this.
Shiro.
Shiro's skirt is sexy.
I'm looking forward to it.
What should I do?
I have a good hobby.
Do you regret it?
I'll think about it.
I'm looking forward to it.
What kind of person are you?
I'm looking around.
I have to go up the stairs.
I have to pee.
I'm looking around.
I'm going to leak.
I'm going to buy a weapon.
It's the worst.
I found a key.
I left my cell phone.
I can't open it.
If I send this, there may be something.
I'll go.
I'm sorry I didn't notice.
It's okay.
I'm so glad you're okay.
You're welcome.
It's not normal to drop something like this.
It's not.
Thank you.
It happens sometimes.
I'll get you some sweets if you want.
No, it's okay.
No, no.
It's my gift for you.
Okay, I won't say anything.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It's my gift for you.
Where did I put it?
It's not here.
It's not here either.
Oh, here it is.
Do you like sweets?
Yes, I do.
I'm glad to hear that.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
I dropped it.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It's delicious, so please eat it.
Thank you.
I'll eat it.
Which one do you want to eat?
Well...
This one is delicious, too.
Is that so?
Yes.
Well...
You're getting bigger.
What?
No, no.
Well...
I want to thank you.
Me?
You know me well.
No, no.
Hey.
What?
I think you should take off your ring.
Oh, no.
My husband will come back.
No, he won't come back at this time.
It's okay.
What?
I thought you were looking at my butt.
Oh, no.
Well...
Do you like my butt?
Oh, no.
I don't like it.
No, no.
Well...
Isn't my butt attractive?
What?
No.
I think it's very attractive.
Which part?
What?
Well...
How can I say?
I can't say it.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
What should I do?
I want to thank you.
Oh, no.
Let me touch you.
What?
Can I?
No, I can't.
I'm sorry.
It's okay if I touch you a little.
Wow.
Can I touch you?
No, you can't.
Oh, no.
How dare you!
How do you like my butt?
I don't know what's going on.
I'm in a panic.
What?
If you do this, I can't stand it.
You don't have to stand it.
What?
My hands are warm.
Wow.
What?
It's transparent.
You're wearing such a dirty outfit.
I like being touched.
Touch me a lot and lick me.
Your butt?
Yes, my butt.
Wow.
I can see the hole in your butt.
It feels good.
Do you like being touched?
Touch me more.
Lick me.
Lick you?
Lick the hole in my butt.
The hole?
Yes.
Okay.
Here?
Oh, it feels good.
Is this okay?
Touch me more.
Oh, it feels good.
Wow.
You're so active.
Your butt is amazing.
This side, too.
Oh, it's scary.
I can't see anything.
Can I lick you a lot?
Lick me a lot.
Oh, it feels good.
You're so active.
Is this okay?
Touch me more.
Your butt is shaking.
Oh, it feels good.
Don't put anything in my butt.
What?
But you licked me.
Oh, it feels good.
Can I lick you?
I want you to lick my face.
Oh, it feels good.
You're really active.
Your butt is really big.
It's the best.
You can like me more.
Oh, it feels good.
I'm happy. You're getting bigger.
My hands are warm, so it feels good.
Are you okay?
Wait a minute.
I feel strange.
I was excited to see you from above.
Oh, it feels good.
I know you're excited.
It's a big complex.
That's great.
You don't have to feel complex at all.
My butt is shaking.
How do you feel?
Your butt is the best.
Do you like my butt?
I love your butt.
I've loved it since I first saw it.
Oh, it feels good.
Does this feel good?
It feels good.
Oh, it feels good.
Does your butt feel good?
It feels good.
Oh, it feels good.
Your butt is shaking.
Don't do that.
Oh, you're going.
Of course
Oh, my God.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm so excited.
Is this what happened to my butt?
Yes, it is.
There's something out there.
Oh, my God.
I'm so excited.
Are you pulling a string?
No, it's because you're so pretty.
I'm so happy.
Can I lick you?
Yes, of course.
Oh, my God.
I can't stop.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it's hot.
It feels good.
Do you feel good in your boobs, too?
Yes, I do.
Your buttocks and boobs feel good, too.
It's like you're a pervert.
Yes.
I'd like to rub your buttocks.
My buttocks?
Yes.
Can I rub your buttocks?
Like this?
Oh, it's hard.
It's hard all the time.
Yes.
Because I'm so excited.
I'm glad to hear that.
Try to rub my buttocks.
Oh, it's hard.
It's hard all the time.
Oh, it's hard all the time.
Can I rub your buttocks?
What?
I want to do something more pleasant.
Please touch me more.
Touch you?
Yes.
I can't do it anymore.
What do you want to do?
I want to touch your buttocks.
Can I touch your buttocks?
Oh, I'm nervous.
Oh, it's hard.
Please touch me more.
What?
Oh, it's hard.
Ouch!
I'm so surprised.
What do you think, mama?
It feels good.
Ah, it feels good to be absorbed in you.
Ah, it feels good.
Calm down for awhile.
That feels good.
Please...
It's too harsh...
You don't like this, do you?
Please press it higher...
Does it hurt?
Please!
Press it harder!
I feel leg pain.
It's okay.
It's better.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
I'm going.
I'm in a deep place.
It feels good.
I want it.
You want it?
I want something.
It feels good.
Make me stronger.
One more time.
It feels good.
I won't let go.
Not yet.
It feels good.
What do you want to do?
I want you to do the other side.
It feels good.
I can't stop.
It's deep.
I'm in a good place.
It hurts.
It feels good.
My hips are shaking.
I can't stop.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I'm in a good place.
It feels good.
Move as you like.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I'm in a good place.
I can't stop.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I can't stop.
It feels good.
It hurts.
I can't stop.
I want to do it while looking at your butt.
I like this.
Do you like this, too?
I like this very much.
It feels good.
I can't stop.
It hurts.
Why did you leave?
It feels good.
I can't stop.
Please tell me when you go.
I'm sorry.
I'm always at home at this time.
Please come and visit me again.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Please come here.
Didn't you see me?
No, I didn't.
I know you.
What did you do?
Let me see your phone.
No, I can't.
You took a video of me, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
I noticed it.
Please come here.
What is this?
You took a video of me, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
Really?
I saw you.
No, I didn't.
Let me see your phone.
No, I can't.
You took a video of me, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
What should I do?
Can I see your phone?
No, I can't.
I'm sorry.
You can't escape from the police.
What should I do?
I'm sorry.
Can you listen to me?
I'm quiet now.
Are you sure?
I won't tell anyone.
I don't have a lot of money now.
It's not just money.
Can I ask you?
I'll take off my clothes, too.
Thank you.
Can you take off your clothes?
What?
I said I'd ask you.
I'll take off my clothes.
I can't work in this.
I have to clean up.
I'll take this off, too.
Can I take this off, too?
Yes.
Is it dirty?
It's dirty.
I see.
I'll take this off, too.
You can take this off, too.
Which one?
Pants?
Are you cleaning the bath?
I'm not cleaning the bath.
Are you taking this off?
Can I take this off?
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
I'll take this off.
I'll take this off, too.
Can you take this off?
Isn't this a bath?
It's not a bath.
I said I'd ask you.
Of course.
What?
I'm not saying anything.
Can I take this off?
Yes.
I can't stand it anymore.
You were staring at my butt.
I'm sorry.
I was staring at your butt.
Can I look at your butt?
I'm sorry.
You were staring at my butt.
I can't stand it anymore.
What?
I want to look at your butt.
I'm sorry.
You're resisting, but your mouth isn't reacting.
That's not true.
What?
Can I look at your butt?
I'm sorry.
What?
All of a sudden?
All of a sudden.
I was surprised.
You're sexy.
What?
You wanted to see my butt, didn't you?
That's right.
You showed me your butt once.
What?
You're showing me your butt.
That's amazing.
Do you always show me your butt?
No, I don't.
I love your butt.
You're a pervert.
Am I a pervert?
That's amazing.
Your butt is big.
I touched your butt.
You're more active than I thought.
I'm sorry.
I love your butt.
I can't look at your butt.
You're a pervert.
I'm sorry.
What is this?
You don't think I'm sorry, do you?
No, I don't.
But I'm sorry.
What were you going to use it for?
I don't know.
What was it for?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'm glad you're doing this.
I didn't think this would happen.
How can I make you happy?
I don't know.
I like to be attacked.
I see.
Can you bully me?
Can I bully you?
Yes.
I'm not used to it yet, but I'll try.
Then,
I'll tap your butt.
Is that what you mean?
I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I can't take it anymore.
Isn't this what you want?
I like it.
Isn't it?
I'm sorry.
I can't take it anymore.
You're a pervert, aren't you?
Maybe I'm a pervert.
You're a pervert.
You're walking around like this on purpose, aren't you?
I'm not doing it on purpose.
You're doing it to make a man.
I just happened to wear it.
Really?
Yes.
You're doing it on purpose, aren't you?
Because...
What is it?
I haven't done it lately.
Husband and wife.
Then...
Did you want something?
Yes.
This...
This?
I can't take off my pants because I'm caught.
I haven't seen you in a long time.
It smells salty.
I didn't take a bath.
It's warm.
It's salty.
Do you hate it?
I'm excited.
I like it.
You like it?
Yes.
Please take a shower.
You're good at it.
I see.
Was it this kind of sweat?
Yes.
You were sweating.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Are you happy?
How do you feel?
I'm happy.
Are you happy?
Which one?
I'm happy.
Are you happy?
Yes.
Do you like this?
That's great.
You're a pervert.
You're lucky.
I bit you.
It feels good.
Really?
Yes.
I'll take a shower and come back.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
Yes.
You're wet.
It's not a little.
I don't want to.
I said it.
I'm a pervert.
I didn't expect you to be in such a bright place.
I'll put the towel in your clothes.
You wanted me to put it in your clothes, right?
Yes.
Thank you.
You're a man who doesn't know.
Thank you for giving me a nice kiss.
Come on.
Why?
I'm sorry.
I don't want to.
It feels good.
I just did it.
I didn't expect you to be in such a bright place.
Wait a minute.
Open your chest.
Shake it off.
Lie down.
I want you to sleep.
Where?
In my arms.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to have sex at all.
From now on, I'll talk to you a lot.
Really?
Please talk to me when you have time.
Give me your butt.
My butt?
I told you I like your butt.
My butt.
My butt?
I can't give you my butt.
Show me your face.
I'm sorry.
I want to do something pleasant.
Why?
I want you to do me a favor.
A favor?
Do you want me to give you a lot?
Yes.
Lick all the parts where you feel good.
How do you feel?
Can you lick more?
Can you lick the lower teeth?
Can you feel it?
How do you feel?
I've never licked my lower teeth.
You haven't?
This is the first time you've licked my lower teeth.
This is the first time you've licked a man's lower teeth.
I've never licked my lower teeth.
Then, lick my lower teeth.
You're still a pervert.
Does it feel good to be licked here?
I'm getting embarrassed to be licked.
I didn't know that.
Oh.
This is my whole body.
This is delicious.
Whole body?
Oh.
My whole body.
You licked my lower teeth.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
I want you to lick my lower teeth more.
I'll lick your lower teeth.
Oh.
Can you bring me my usual toy?
I want you to use it.
Can I?
Oh.
What's that?
This is it.
Wait a minute.
Do you always use it?
Yes, I do.
It's amazing.
It moves a lot.
I like this.
Do you?
Try using it.
I've only used it once.
Oh.
Can you lick my lower teeth again?
Again?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Can you lick my lower teeth?
Wow.
Put your hands together.
It moves a lot.
What's this?
Oh.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Wow.
It's better to use this, isn't it?
Yes.
It's amazing that you can use such a good toy.
Did you buy it yourself?
I bought it myself.
I see.
Do you feel embarrassed?
What?
There's a net.
I see.
Oh.
It's amazing.
It came out.
It was pushed out.
It's amazing.
It's amazing that you can use such a good toy.
Yes.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good to move.
Which is harder?
Is it hard?
Yes.
I can see the line.
It's amazing.
I see.
Do you turn on this switch?
Yes.
It moves when I turn on the switch.
I see.
Ah.
It's a vibration.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
What is this?
It's moving.
Which one do you feel better?
Really?
Can you move it?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It's moving.
I can't do it.
It's amazing.
It's moving.
Does it feel good?
It's amazing.
It's amazing how it moves.
It's amazing how it goes in.
It stopped.
It's moving inside.
It's amazing.
Try moving it by yourself.
By myself?
It's amazing.
Try moving it by yourself.
Try not to talk.
I can't do it.
It's moving.
Try moving it.
Did you see it?
What is this?
It's amazing.
It was moving a lot.
Please turn your butt this time.
My butt?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Show me your face.
You like to be touched, don't you?
Is it a toy?
Do you like the real one?
I like the real one.
I see.
Do you want me to put it in your mouth?
Yes.
Then,
don't drop it.
Don't drop it?
Do you want me to close your mouth?
It's amazing.
I can't do it.
If you try it, you can do it.
It's amazing.
You dropped it.
Did I drop it?
It's amazing.
Is it amazing?
Where is it?
I just licked your butt.
You licked my butt, so I have to give it back.
I've never been licked.
I'm sorry.
It's disgusting.
You look like you're in a good mood.
I'll take it off.
Do you want me to take it off?
It's disgusting.
Is it disgusting?
It was disgusting, wasn't it?
It's disgusting.
I can't do it.
What's wrong?
Are you going to go?
You can go.
What are you doing?
Go.
I can't go there.
It's disgusting.
I'll take it off.
Take it off.
I'll take it off again.
What's this?
You're in a good mood.
It's disgusting.
You don't like it, do you?
Do you hate it?
I hate it.
I can't do it.
You can't do it.
Explain what it means
OK?
Read the kanji
Can we try to put your seat belt in yourself this time?
YES
Do you want to put it in your mouth?
Can you put it in your mouth?
Can I put it in my mouth?
You can put it in your mouth.
I'll let you put it in your mouth.
Did you put it in your mouth?
Can you see it?
I can see it.
Look at it and do it yourself.
I'll let you put it in your mouth.
You're good at it.
You can go.
You can go if you want to.
Ah, I can't do this.
Huh?
Ah!
Ah, I can't do this.
What?
My head.
My head hurts.
Ah, I can't do this.
I can't do this.
It's terrible.
It feels good.
You have a lot of blood in your body.
You are so mean.
Yes.
Hey.
I got it.
You can't take it off.
What?
From your butt.
From my butt?
Yes.
You have to show your face.
Show my face?
Yes.
It's difficult.
Ah.
You are so mean.
It's good.
Wow.
It feels good.
I got it.
Does it feel good?
Ah, I can see it.
Yes.
Can you see it?
I can see it.
Okay.
Hmm.
Ah.
Here.
Hmm.
Ah.
Ahh.
Hmm.
Ah.
Ahh.
My younger sister, who is passing the prediction option, is really big your bowl, so she hits me a lot.
My brother and his sister, who is on the receptionist, may not slow down.
The pressure of my brother is too strongmother???
Are you okay?
You're blushing.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I think I'm going to die.
Are you sure you're going to die?
Oh, my God.
It's so hot.
I feel good.
I brought it in while looking at your face.
While looking at my face?
Do you like hot things?
I like it.
It's so hot.
I'll spread it out for you.
You're blushing.
Please put this in by yourself.
By myself?
It's so hot.
It's so slimy that I can't put it in.
I put it in.
You don't have to put it in.
I want to put it on your face.
My face?
You like it, don't you?
I like it.
My face?
I don't know.
It's so slimy that I can't put it in.
It's so slimy that you can't put it in.
I haven't put it on your face.
Please put it on my face.
It's so hot.
I'm going to put it in.
Are you going to put it in?
I can see it.
Does it feel good?
It's coming out.
It's coming out a lot.
It's amazing.
What's going on?
It's coming out a lot.
It's amazing.
It's in my belly.
Isn't it amazing?
Does it come out this much?
But my wife is a bad person.
It's amazing.
Is your wife drinking?
I put it in my mouth automatically.
Do you like it?
I like it, but I haven't been drinking lately.
Please put it all in your mouth and drink it.
It's amazing.
How much did it come out?
Can I help you?
I can't see it.
Can I put it in my mouth?
Open your mouth.
I ate it in my mouth.
Is it in your mouth?
Isn't it in your mouth?
I put it in my mouth.
You put it in your mouth.
It's amazing.
It came out a lot.
I can't put it in my mouth.
If my husband comes home now, I'll be in trouble.
I'm sorry.
It's about time.
Are you going home?
If my husband comes home.
It's still boiling, so it's okay.
Let's do it again.
I'll wash it.
Again?
It's still boiling, isn't it?
I don't know.
I think so.
Maybe I can do it.
This isn't a snack, is it?
What is it?
Isn't it sweet?
No?
Isn't it like a snack?
I'm sorry.
It's a little salty.
You didn't like it?
Don't worry about it.
Are you serious?
It's sweet.
I'm sorry.
My husband likes it.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
I prepared it for you.
It's dry.
That's all I could think of.
I'm sorry.
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
Do you like it?
I'm glad to hear that.
You're kind.
Of course I'm kind.
I'm glad to hear that.
You should give it to him.
I'll give it to him.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know what to do.
We drank a lot.
It's okay.
Please drink it.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Why did you say you didn't like it?
Please drink it.
I'm drunk.
You drank a lot.
Don't you feel sick?
I don't feel sick.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I like this sofa.
It's fluffy.
Do you want to sleep?
I don't want to sleep.
You can't sleep.
You're making a lot of money.
You're a beautiful wife.
You're so cute.
Please praise me.
You're not drunk.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm sorry.
You can eat ramen.
I'm full.
I'm angry.
You ate ramen.
There is a ramen shop near my house.
My ramen is the best.
Let's go together.
I'm already full.
If you're going to say that...
I got a lot of delicious food from you.
I'm so happy.
Let's do it again.
No, it's okay.
I'll go.
I'll wait in line for 30 or 40 minutes.
It'll take an hour.
It's okay.
Why?
I like ramen, so I'll go.
I'm going.
No way.
Are you going to leave us behind?
I'm sorry.
You're such a bad person.
I can't read the atmosphere.
You're always alone.
You're a bad husband.
Don't you think so?
Something's wrong.
We should go home.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Don't go home.
I don't want to be alone.
I don't think you'll be back for a while.
No.
Please stay.
I won't be back for more than an hour.
I'm lonely.
But...
Well...
Yes?
I've noticed something.
What is it?
You've been staring at my butt for a while.
Didn't you think I wouldn't notice?
No, I didn't do that.
Look.
The butt you were looking at is here.
No, it's just my imagination.
Don't you want to see it up close?
No, I don't.
Then, I'll get closer.
No, wait.
Wait.
How is it?
No, it's a little...
It's not good.
Look at your wife.
There's no husband.
No, wait.
Come closer.
Are you okay?
I like this.
Come here.
No, wait.
It's not good that you don't have a husband.
Come here.
Come here, too.
Touch me.
I'll touch you gently.
Is it okay for me to do this?
Please touch me harder.
No, it's not okay.
What?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm a man, too.
It's your husband's fault.
Look.
I like this.
No, it's not like that.
How is it?
No, it's great.
It's my butt.
You're cute.
Come here.
How is it?
It's great.
If you move like that, I'll bite you.
It's gross.
You, too.
Come here.
No, wait.
What's wrong with you?
It's not bad.
It smells bad.
Please taste it.
Okay.
Don't you want to taste it?
I'm lonely.
Please take it off.
I'll take it off.
You look like you want to take it off.
Why are you slacking off?
Don't slack off.
Don't sit here.
Okay.
What's wrong with you?
I don't know.
It's not bad.
Please tell me.
You don't need this, do you?
Why don't you hide it?
I took it off.
I already took it off.
Don't hide it.
It smells good.
It's good.
It's getting hot.
Your skirt is in the way.
Please take it off.
It's cool.
Please take this off.
It feels good.
You're more excited than usual.
How is it? Does it feel good?
How is it?
It's a secret from your husband.
You're so kind.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Your breath is getting hotter.
It's hot.
Is it good?
It's good.
Are you happy?
It's the best.
It's good.
Next, I'll lick your penis.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
Don't you want me to lick it?
That's not what I mean.
Please take it off.
This side, too.
Take it off.
It hurts.
Give it to me.
But...
It's okay, right?
Yes.
It's good.
It's cool.
It's amazing.
It's good.
It's cool.
It's amazing.
It's good.
It's cool.
It's amazing.
I can see your buttocks.
My buttocks...
Isn't it difficult?
It's hot.
No, it doesn't feel good.
It's amazing.
It's very beautiful.
You're panting.
It's amazing.
Is it amazing?
It's good.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I'm happy.
Let's lie down together.
Okay.
I have two.
I always have one.
It's a luxury.
What?
Really?
Do you want me to do more?
It's a mess.
It's good.
It's amazing.
You're drooling.
It's good.
I have a lot of drool.
Do you want more?
I can't stand it anymore.
I see.
It's good.
Can I put it in?
Do you want to put it in?
Yes.
I want you to put it in.
I want to put it in.
Put it in.
Come here.
Let's go.
It feels good.
Thank you.
It's amazing.
It's different from anything else.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I want more.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's good.
I'm sweating.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'm hot.
I want to take off my clothes.
Take off your clothes.
It's amazing.
I want to sleep.
Let's go.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I want more.
It's not enough.
It looks delicious.
I want more.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I don't need this anymore.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's good to look down on me.
I'm embarrassed.
I want to lick you.
I want you to lick me.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's delicious.
I want more.
It's amazing.
I want you to do that.
It feels good.
It's not good.
It's amazing.
It's good.
It feels good.
It's not good.
Let's look this way.
It feels good.
It's not good.
How is it?
It feels good.
It's not good.
I want you to do that.
No, no, no, no, no.
I want this kiss too.
Give it to me.
Is that okay?
I want you to kiss me.
I want a lot of kisses.
It feels good.
You can't move like that.
I can't stop.
This feels good.
This feels good, too.
It's amazing.
I can't stop.
I want you to kiss me.
Give it to me.
This feels good, too.
I can't stop.
It feels good.
I want more.
I want to touch you.
It's amazing.
Yes, big brother.
This feels good.
I want you to give me a kiss, okay?
It feels good, right?
It's amazing.
Everyone...
This way?
Get up.
I want to get up.
It feels good.
It feels so good.
I want more.
It feels good.
Give it to me.
It's okay.
It feels good.
It feels so good.
It hurts so much.
It feels good.
It feels so good.
It hurts so much.
It's so hot.
It hurts the bottom of my heart.
What did you do?
What did you do to be so cry?
It may be painful, so do not sleep so much.
It's like an escapist.
I'm surprised.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Do you like me?
I like you.
No.
Be careful.
Spread your legs.
It feels good.
No.
It's in my throat.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's in my throat.
I want to do it while looking at your face.
Are you going to put it on my face?
Look at me.
It feels good.
It's in my throat.
I was going to put it on your skin.
Can't I?
It's in my throat.
You can still do it, right?
I haven't put it out yet.
It's okay, right?
It's amazing.
That's a great way to put it on.
It's amazing, right?
It's amazing.
Come regularly.
It's okay, right?
By all means.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Let me taste more.
I want more.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Put it in from the front.
Give it to me.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
I want to put it out.
Put it in my face.
I want to put it in my face.
It feels good.
Help me!
I'm coming.
I think I can do it.
Help me.
Give me your tongue.
Speak clearly.
Can you speak loudly?
Speak loudly.
Squeeze it.
I can't touch it.
Give me your tongue.
Show me your tongue.
Open your mouth.
Can you see it?
Does it feel good?
Your face is covered with blood.
Can you be me again?
Of course.
I'm happy.
I don't mind if it's every day.
I'll keep it a secret from you.
Good evening.
Do you have time today?
Time?
What do you mean?
What?
You like butt, don't you?
Did you hear that?
What are you doing?
How is it?
I'm listening.
I'm not doing anything.
You have time, don't you?
Let's go.
Come here.
Lie down.
What are you doing?
You have time, don't you?
What do you mean?
You came here because you have time, don't you?
I talked about it the other day.
Is that true?
I heard it.
I was so excited.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
You're married.
That's why I'm okay.
Other men are attractive.
What should I do?
You like butt, don't you?
Our butt is heavy, isn't it?
You can do whatever you want.
Can I?
Look at this.
How do you like it?
It's amazing.
It's your favorite butt.
Yes.
Don't you want to touch it?
Can I touch it?
Please touch it.
How do you like it?
It's like a dream.
You like a big butt, don't you?
I think all men like it.
All men?
Yes.
I think all men like a big butt.
It looks good on you.
Anyone can like it.
You can get excited in this situation.
There's one more left.
You want me to touch it, don't you?
You're fast.
You can't stand it, can you?
Your nipples are tight.
If you like it so much, rub it on your nipples.
It looks good on you.
How do you like it?
I've never been told this before.
It's amazing.
I'll rub it on your nipples.
Your body temperature is rising.
You like a big butt, don't you?
I've never thought of that.
It's okay.
Please touch me more.
Would you like to smell my butt?
How is it?
It's amazing.
I'm so excited.
How do you like it?
It feels good.
I don't need this.
It's amazing.
It looks delicious.
Please touch other women's butt.
Can I touch other women's butt?
It's fun.
Next, I'll touch your butt.
It's amazing.
I won't let you rest.
It feels good.
I love it.
I don't need this.
I won't let you rest.
It's amazing.
Can I touch your butt?
It's okay.
I'll touch your butt.
It's amazing.
Can I touch your butt?
It's a pleasure to touch other women's butt.
It's amazing.
You're better than I thought.
I want to lick you, too.
Let's lick together.
It's amazing.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah ah ah ahh
me
That's right, your mother is a
digital
I'm going to take it out, too.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
That's right.
Don't touch it.
I want to touch it, too.
It feels good.
Is your mouth open?
It's open.
It's my turn again.
It feels good.
It's hot.
You love butt, don't you?
It feels good when I pinch your butt.
That's good.
It feels good.
It's hot.
My butt is hot.
I'm going to put something on your butt.
That's right.
It feels good.
It's messy.
I want to lick your butt.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
It felt so good.
That's great.
Let's drink together.
It's hot.
You're energetic.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're excited to lick my butt, aren't you?
You're excited.
You're a good person.
You found a good person.
It's still hard.
You look like you want more.
I have to lick you more.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'll lick your butt, too.
You look like you feel good.
I'll make you feel better.
Really?
How is it?
It feels good.
You like my butt, don't you?
I'll make you feel my butt.
Touch me.
That's right.
You look like you feel good.
My butt.
It feels harder than before.
You like my butt, don't you?
You're a pervert.
How is it?
It's great.
You can't stop licking my butt, can you?
That's right.
You like my butt, don't you?
You look like you feel good.
You're a pervert.
I can feel that you feel good.
You're licking my butt.
I'll make you feel my butt.
My nipples?
My nipples.
I can't stop licking your butt.
It's great.
I can't stop imagining it.
It's coming out.
No way.
Really?
It's coming out.
No way.
It's on my butt.
Look at this.
It's so thick.
Only this part is shining.
It's coming out.
I wanted to put it in.
It's a waste.
I put it out.
It's great.
It's coming out.
It's coming out a lot.
That's right.
You looked like you felt good when I put it in.
Can you bring me here again next time?
You have to put it in next time.
I want it.
Give it to me.
I want your genitals.