I will be in charge of it today, so I would appreciate it if you could change here as soon as possible and proceed if you are ready.
I will be in charge of the massage today, so I would appreciate it if you could change here as soon as possible and proceed if you are ready.
I feel like something is flowing.
Really? Did it warm up?
You said you would go to the massage, so it doesn't seem to be so stiff.
Really?
I want to be told that it is stiff.
I want to be loosened.
But I've never done anything that isn't stiff.
I see.
If you only do massages, don't you get stiff?
I'm often asked that, but I do get stiff.
I see.
I can massage my legs by myself.
You can do it by yourself?
When my body is warmed up, I can do it.
Do you use oil?
Yes, I use oil.
I have a stiff back.
You have a stiff back?
Yes.
I see.
Do you massage your back by yourself?
My legs are easy to massage.
Do you massage your scapula?
Scapula?
Scapula massage?
My scapula is stiff.
Do you feel uncomfortable?
No, I don't feel uncomfortable.
I want you to massage my scapula, too.
Do you massage your scapula?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Can I take off my panties?
What?
You can take off your panties.
Can I take off my panties?
My panties are too small.
Do you massage your neck?
Well.
do you massage your neck?
Do you massage your neck?
My neck is very pressed down.
It's hard for me to take off my panties.
Can you put it on my head?
Put it on your head?
Put it on your head.
No.
I'll put some oil on your head.
Could you close your eyes?
I can't close my eyes.
Could you touch me for a moment?
Just a moment.
A moment.
O.K.
Are you all right?
A moment.
I'll come again soon and show it to you, so please come again.
How soon?
I'll come again tomorrow.
You'll come again tomorrow and show it to me?
Yes.
Really?
Absolutely.
Absolutely?
What time will you come tomorrow?
What time will you be there?
I'll be there from 1 to 8.
Then, I'll be there around evening.
I'll make a reservation.
I understand.
I'll really come.
Please come.
I'll ask you to do something for me.
I'll come tomorrow.
You'll come tomorrow?
Yes.
You'll definitely come tomorrow.
Just a little.
Can I sit here?
Yes.
I'll come again.
I can see you.
I'll come again the day after tomorrow.
Can I rub you?
Rub?
What do you mean?
I don't know.
The day after tomorrow?
It's not realistic.
I'll come again the day after tomorrow.
The day after tomorrow?
I don't want you to come every day.
I don't know. I'll come every day.
Please come every day.
I understand.
I'll come every day.
Every day?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Like this?
How do you feel?
How do I feel?
It's very hard.
How do you feel?
How do I feel?
It's very hard.
Wait a minute.
You can't do that.
I can't?
Can I do this?
You're aggressive.
I can't do this.
I'm sorry.
I'll leave it here.
That's all for today.
Yes.
Please come every day.
Thank you.
I'll leave it here.
Yes.
I'll wait for you at the reception.
Thank you.
Yes.
Please come this way.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Please sit here.
Yes.
Thank you for coming today.
I'm Hachino.
Nice to meet you.
Is this your first visit?
Yes.
I see.
Are you tired today?
Yes.
Can I touch your shoulders?
Thank you.
Your shoulders are stiff.
I'll give you a massage.
Yes.
Is your lower body okay?
Can I touch your shoulders?
Yes.
Is your lower body okay?
Okay.
Let's get started.
Do you have any questions?
No.
Okay.
Please change your clothes.
Yes.
Please put your clothes here.
Okay.
Where should I change?
Here.
Here?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't look at me.
You're cuter than I thought.
Did I do something?
No.
I'm sorry.
Please call me when you're done.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Let's start.
I'll massage your shoulders.
Is your lower body okay?
Yes.
Then, I'll start massaging you with the oil.
Okay.
Please let me know if it's too hot.
If you'll excuse me.
Now, I'll massage around your shoulders.
Is it okay if it's quite strong?
Yes, it's okay.
Okay.
If you'll excuse me.
Is the pain okay?
Yes, it's okay.
Okay, thank you very much.
Hmm...
There's quite a bit of fat on your muscles.
It's quite easy to get stiff, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Do you do any sports?
No, not really.
I see.
I think it's good to walk a little.
Yes, it is.
It's embarrassing.
I'm also doing a lymph massage,
so please let me know if it's okay.
Okay.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Now, I'll massage your legs.
Okay.
I'll start with your calf.
Your legs are also full of lymph.
If I massage the back of your knees,
you'll feel much better.
How's the pressure?
It's okay.
Thank you very much.
If you'll excuse me.
Does it hurt anywhere?
No, not at all.
I'm sorry.
Please let me know if it hurts.
Okay.
I finished massaging the back of your knees.
Is there anything you need?
No, not at all.
Thank you very much.
Please turn around.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Isn't the water cold?
It's okay.
Okay.
I'll continue.
I'll start with your upper body.
If you'll excuse me.
I'll apply some pressure.
Does it hurt?
No, not at all.
Your belly is also full of fat.
Yes.
If you continue this massage,
you'll feel much better.
Is that so?
Yes, of course.
If you'll excuse me.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
Does it hurt?
No, not at all.
If you'll excuse me.
I'll massage your decollete.
If you massage here,
you'll feel much better.
You're sweating a little.
Is it hot?
No, it's not.
Are you okay?
It's a little warm.
It's getting warmer.
Yes, it is.
This oil has the effect of excretion,
so you'll sweat a little.
But it's a proof that you have a lot of decollete.
I see.
I'll start with your lower body.
Okay.
If you'll excuse me.
I'll continue.
Does it hurt?
No, not at all.
It feels good.
Okay.
If you'll excuse me.
I'll massage your lymph nodes.
Could you bend your legs a little?
Thank you.
Does it hurt here?
No, not at all.
If you'll excuse me.
It's easy to accumulate decollete around here,
so I'll focus on the squeeze.
If you massage here, your legs will be refreshed.
Okay.
Your right leg is okay.
I'll massage the other side.
I think it hurts a little here,
but please bear with it.
I'll start.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Wow.
It's amazing.
Many customers feel pain here.
It doesn't hurt,
but it feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'll focus on the squeeze a little more.
Okay.
Wow.
It's around here.
Yes.
It's tight here.
I'll massage around here.
Okay.
I'll massage harder.
I'll massage from the bottom,
and spread it up and down like this.
How is it?
Is it getting lighter?
Yes.
It is.
It's good.
I'll massage a little more.
Okay.
Wow.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It feels good.
Wow.
I'll massage here.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I was surprised.
It's okay.
Most of the customers will be surprised by the massage,
but don't worry about it.
Is it okay?
Yes.
Wow.
Is it really okay?
If the customers don't mind, it's okay.
This is a shop that normally doesn't care.
Well,
I'd like you to massage the part that's sticking out.
The part that's sticking out?
Wait a minute.
Is it the upper body?
No, it's the lower body.
Lower body.
Would you like to do it again?
No.
Not there.
Yes.
Is there anything missing?
I'd like you to touch here.
What are you talking about?
I told you it was a shop that normally doesn't care.
I'm sorry.
I'm not that kind of shop.
If you're going to do that, can you go home?
I'm sorry.
Please.
I'll give you a massage.
No.
Just a little.
Is it okay?
Just a little?
Yes.
If I give you a massage,
you'll tell someone else, won't you?
No, I won't.
I won't.
Can you promise me?
I promise.
Are you sure?
Then,
please remember what happens.
I'm sorry.
Is it here?
Yes.
Then, here, too.
Just a little.
Yes.
Is this okay?
Like this.
I'll give you a massage.
But, sir,
why are you so serious?
I just gave you a normal massage.
I'm sorry.
Then,
you should have been patient from the beginning.
I fell in love
with you.
Are you my type?
Yes.
You're a cute customer.
Then,
you gave me a massage.
Did you fall in love with me?
Yes.
Is that so?
Then,
you wanted me
to give you a massage, didn't you?
Yes.
Is it okay?
Just a little?
Yes.
Is it okay
to finish the massage?
Just a little.
You have 5 minutes left.
I'm sorry.
I want you to kiss me.
Are you sure?
I won't.
Then,
just a little.
Yes.
Kiss me.
Ah.
How is it?
The mouth massage?
It's good.
Ah.
I'm sorry.
Tell me
when you want to leave.
I'm sorry.
Then,
today's massage
is over.
Thank you very much.
Your clothes are here.
Please wipe the oil with this towel.
Yes.
Then, I'm leaving.
See you in the next video!
I'm going to
finish the work.
Yes.
You did a good job.
Thank you so much.
I thought you wouldn't come.
I'm half asleep.
Ah.
I'd like to ask you a question.
Is it okay if I do it four times?
Yes.
Like this?
My pants are in the way.
Please bear with it.
Please take off my pants.
I don't want to take them off.
Why?
You come here every day.
But this is not the kind of shop I come to.
I'm glad to hear that.
I heard that it's okay to do it four times.
The customers will say,
I took them off on my own.
I see.
Then it's okay.
It hurts.
Do I have to give you a massage?
You don't have to.
You are very energetic.
Thank you.
It feels good.
Isn't it hard?
No, it's not.
It's hard.
Can you massage my neck?
Your neck?
Can I massage your neck?
What?
Like this?
Yes.
It's hot.
It's big, isn't it?
No, it's not.
Can't you use your hands?
No.
How long is it?
I think it's easier to massage if I rub it.
It's easier.
It's not wet, is it?
I think it's wet.
I see.
It's okay if I rub it hot, isn't it?
I don't know.
I'll rub it.
It's better to rub it.
Yes.
Rubbing?
Oh, I see.
You remembered it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Congratulations.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Wait.
It's hot.
Please be quiet.
I don't have time.
I want you to rub it directly.
I see.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'm trying.
Are you trying?
Why are you trying?
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
Are you okay?
It's a secret.
It feels good.
I'm going to do it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Can you do it?
I can do it.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Can I do it again?
No, you can't.
I'm going to do it.
Are you going?
It's hot.
I'm going to cry.
Can I do it from behind?
It's hot.
I'm going to cry.
Don't cry.
It's hot.
I'll be waiting for you tomorrow.
Can you wipe my sweat?
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
Can I change my clothes here?
Sure.
Thank you.
It's hot today, isn't it?
Yes.
It was cool recently.
It was cold.
It suddenly got hot.
How are you feeling?
I'm not feeling well.
Are you not feeling well?
I'm fine today.
I'm going to change my clothes.
Thank you.
Please put your head here.
I'm going to start the massage.
Okay.
Are you tired today?
My lower body and thighs are a little tired.
Your lower body and thighs are tired?
Yes.
I started walking recently.
I see.
Walking is amazing.
Is it your hobby?
I'm trying to get rid of my lack of exercise.
I walk for about 1 to 2 hours a day.
That's a lot.
Is that so?
1 to 2 hours.
Isn't that a long distance?
I don't know.
It's about muscle pain.
It's because of my lack of exercise.
I see.
I'm going to start massaging your legs.
Okay.
Do you often get a massage?
Sometimes.
I get a massage once a month.
I see.
I feel good.
Really?
Isn't it too strong?
It's okay if it's stronger.
I see.
Please tell me if it hurts.
I feel good.
Really?
Your calves are full.
That's right.
I see.
I'm going to massage your back with oil.
Okay.
I'm going to massage your back.
I see.
Are you okay?
Yes, I feel good.
If you get a massage, you'll sleep better.
Really?
Yes.
Then, I'll sleep well tonight.
Okay.
Please turn your head.
I'm going to massage your back so that you can sleep well.
Okay.
Doesn't it hurt?
No, it doesn't hurt.
I see.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
I want you to give me a massage.
What?
This is not a massage shop.
Can you do it for me?
Can't you stand it anymore?
No.
Then, I'll give you a massage.
Really?
Is it here?
Yes.
Okay.
I'm going to give you a massage here, too.
It's very hard.
How long have you been doing this?
I've been doing this since I got a massage on my back.
Why?
Because you are beautiful and good at massaging.
Is that why you look like this?
I'm sorry.
That's amazing.
It sounds like you're in a bad mood.
Yes.
It feels good.
This side is also swollen.
Do you want me to do something better?
Yes, please.
How about this?
Ah.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Can you feel my warmth?
It's very hot.
It's harder than before, isn't it?
It's getting harder.
Yes.
It feels good.
I'm scared.
It tickles.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
It's coming out.
I don't know.
I can't stand it.
What?
Can I help you?
Does it come out?
Okay.
Oh, no.
It's coming out.
Did it really come out?
Yes.
It felt good.
Did it feel good?
Yes.
That's good.
That's all for today.
Is that all?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for coming today.
I'm here.
You didn't tell anyone about what happened last time, did you?
Of course I didn't.
And what I said last time is true.
What did you say last time?
I said I like you.
That's true.
Yes.
Can I be happy?
But first of all, I'll give you a massage.
Yes.
Are you tired today?
Are you tired at all?
Yes.
Then I'll give you a massage again.
Then I'll leave it to you.
I can't stand it anymore.
Please be patient.
I've been patient since last time.
You're a normal masseuse.
You know that, don't you?
I can't do it because you're too cute.
You're cute, too.
It's still hard around here.
Is your shoulder and lower body hard?
Yes.
You're a bad person.
You have a really cute butt.
It's embarrassing.
But you're happy, aren't you?
Does it hurt?
No, it's okay.
I'll do the other side, too.
It's not hard at all.
Are you tired?
Did you come here to feel better?
Yes.
So...
I told you, didn't I?
Don't come here with that kind of mind.
But my mind...
Please turn around.
Time will pass soon.
Excuse me.
It's not just the lower body.
It's amazing here.
Have you been sick all the time?
Yes.
Then...
Please wait a little longer.
Yes.
First of all, you have to warm your body with oil.
You can't feel good from the bottom of your body.
Yes.
Did you lose weight?
Did you go on a diet to meet me?
Yes.
You're kind.
But it's not over yet.
I like your cute belly.
Doesn't it hurt?
No.
I'm sorry.
I'm getting tired of using my breath.
I want you to do that.
It's hot.
How many days have you been eating?
One week.
Is it for today?
Yes.
Why are you so warm?
Then don't do anything today and go home.
Why?
I don't want you to feel good.
I'm sorry.
It's funny.
What do you mean?
You've been eating a lot.
But you can't cry.
That's good.
I don't want to.
You don't want to?
I'm sorry.
I'll massage you.
Yes.
Excuse me.
It's hot.
How is it?
It's warm.
Where?
I'm sorry.
I was right.
That's fine.
You're happy, aren't you?
Yes.
You're not clear.
I wanted you to do something cute.
Yes.
How is it?
Look.
You can see my panties.
You wanted to see my panties, didn't you?
I wanted you to touch my panties.
Yes.
I'll do a lot for you.
Like this.
But you have to be quiet.
Don't make a loud voice.
Yes.
I'm hot.
Can I take it off?
Yes.
What's going on in this uniform?
It's beautiful.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Don't touch me.
I'm just looking at you.
Did I say you could touch me?
No.
I'm just looking at you.
If you can't stand it, say it again.
I won't let you stand it.
I'll do it now.
Look.
How is it?
Do you smell my underwear?
Yes.
Does it smell good?
You can't stand it, can you?
Yes.
Can I touch your underwear?
Do you want to smell it?
Yes.
Smell it a lot.
You have to be quiet.
I want to stop it.
You're good at it.
How is it?
Does it taste good?
Yes.
I was in a daze, too.
I see.
I'm glad you came here again.
Me, too.
Did you like it?
Yes.
But I can't stand it anymore.
I want to touch you.
You can't stand it?
Where do you want to touch?
Your boobs.
I want to touch your boobs.
What should I do?
It's off.
Do you want to touch my boobs?
Yes.
Here?
It's beautiful.
I'll let you touch my boobs.
It's getting harder.
Do you like my boobs?
Yes.
I'll let you touch my boobs.
It's dangerous.
Do you want to touch my boobs?
I can't reach it.
Don't make a stupid face.
You'll make me laugh.
I'll let you touch my boobs.
Do you like it?
Do you like my boobs?
I'll let you touch my boobs.
Which one do you like?
I like that one.
Right?
Here you are.
Hold it yourself.
What do you mean?
It's in the way.
Don't make a stupid face.
I'm embarrassed.
Hold it yourself.
I'll let you touch my boobs.
Do you want me to touch your boobs?
Yes.
Don't do that.
I don't mind.
Don't make a stupid face.
You like my boobs, don't you?
I'll let you touch my boobs.
Really?
Okay.
Go ahead.
Do you want me to touch your boobs?
You've been holding it for a week.
Yes.
I won't let you touch my boobs.
I just want you to feel good.
Do you understand?
Go ahead.
Open your mouth.
You can't speak loudly.
I'll let you touch my boobs.
It feels good.
I'm satisfied with this.
You don't like it?
You're selfish.
I'll let you touch my boobs.
Be quiet.
Don't move your hips.
I'll let you touch my boobs.
I let you touch my boobs.
It feels good.
What?
You don't like it?
You can't put it in.
Stay still.
It's open.
Look.
Can you see?
Can't you talk?
It feels good.
Right?
How about this?
It's morning.
It feels good.
Right?
How about this?
It feels good.
Can I go?
Yes.
Let's go.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Your hair is red.
Does it feel good?
I don't want to go.
So I'm holding back.
Are you holding back?
If you move your waist a little...
Does it feel good?
You can't.
Let's go.
I want to go, too.
One more minute.
I told you not to move.
Do you want to go?
Yes.
Do you want to move?
Let's go.
It's open.
Can you go in 30 seconds?
You can't.
You have to hold back.
Come on.
You can touch me.
It feels good, right?
You can't.
You can't move like that.
Let's go.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It feels good, right?
Come with me.
Let's go.
You can't.
Did you sleep?
Yes.
For a week?
I slept.
Then...
I'll keep it a secret.
Will you come again?
Did you feel good?
Thank you for coming again.
Thank you.
I felt good.
Really?
Have you been walking recently?
Yes.
Really?
Do you feel your legs are stiff?
Yes.
I thought it would be okay if I got used to it.
But it's not like that.
It's not like that?
Did you sleep the other day?
I slept very well.
Really? I'm glad.
It's thanks to you.
Massage has the effect of making you sleep well.
Please tell me if I'm strong.
Okay.
Your shoulders are stiffer than before.
Is that so?
Yes.
Did something happen to you recently?
Well...
I was watching TV on my smartphone.
I see.
I can show you my daily time.
My average time of the day is about 13 hours.
13 hours?
That's quite a lot.
It's not that much.
My average time of the day is 13 hours.
I see.
Your shoulders are stiff.
I'll massage your feet as well.
Thank you.
I can feel that your feet are getting better than before.
Really?
Yes.
I think my muscles are getting stronger.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you.
Do you do any exercise?
Me?
No, I don't do any exercise at all.
My job is like an exercise.
I see.
I think I get tired easily when I do massage.
I think so, too.
It takes a lot of strength when you do it with a few people.
I'll use oil again.
Okay.
Do you play games on your smartphone?
Yes, I mainly play games.
I see.
What kind of games do you play?
RPG.
I see.
You can play it on your smartphone.
Yes, I can play it on my smartphone.
I see.
I've been playing it for a long time.
That's why your feet are getting stronger.
That's right.
I don't play games on my smartphone.
I play games on my computer at home.
I see.
I play games on my smartphone for 13 hours.
I don't know how many hours I've been playing games on my computer.
I see.
How many hours do you play games on your computer?
Your shoulders are stiff.
Don't your eyes get tired?
No, I've been tired for a long time.
Have you been tired for a long time?
I want you to make a screen that doesn't make my eyes tired.
I see.
Are your feet okay?
My feet feel great.
I see.
Are you tired?
I'm sorry.
Can you lie on your back?
Lie on my back?
I'll massage your feet.
I see.
Is this okay?
Yes, it's okay.
I'll massage the base of your feet.
I see.
Does it hurt?
No, I feel great.
I feel great.
Do you feel great?
Yes.
Is this okay?
Yes, it's okay.
I see.
I feel your feet are stiff.
Is this okay?
Yes, it's okay.
I'd appreciate it if you could focus on that part.
I see.
It's getting hot around here.
Is it because of the oil?
I think so.
It's a good sign.
I see.
It's not good to massage only that part.
Is that so?
No, it's not good.
Did it hurt?
No, I feel great.
I see.
How can I say?
What?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry for the last time.
Sorry for what?
If I massage only that part, it'll hurt again.
But you're moving your hips.
No.
You're moving your hips a lot.
But I feel great.
What?
You're just massaging.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to do it more comfortably?
Is that okay?
It's special.
Thank you.
It's getting hot again.
I feel great.
It's getting hot, isn't it?
Yes.
You just massaged.
You're moving your hips a lot.
It's strange.
I feel great.
It's hot again.
Do you want me to do it more comfortably?
Yes.
I want you to do it more comfortably.
Please turn around.
Okay.
It's hot.
I feel great.
You're moving your hips a lot.
I'll do it more comfortably than before.
Is that okay?
I'll do it only this time.
I feel great because it's warmer than before.
Do you feel better than before?
Yes.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
I feel great.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
I feel great.
It's hot.
You're moving your hips a lot.
I feel great.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
You're moving your hips a lot.
I feel great.
It's hot.
You're moving your hips a lot.
I feel great.
Do you feel great?
Yes.
Do you want me to do something more comfortable?
It's special.
It's hot.
You're tired.
Yes.
It's hot and I feel great.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
I feel great.
It's hot.
Do you feel good?
I feel great.
It's hot.
You're moving your hips a lot.
Do you feel good?
I feel great.
Yes.
Do you want me to do something more comfortable?
It's hot.
Move.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
It's beautiful.
It's hot.
It's comfortable.
I'll do it from behind.
It's hot.
Let me go.
You're sweating.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
That's all for today.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'll come again.
Please come again.
Thank you.