5 years later
Mei-san
Kurokawa-kun, what's up?
Are you done with your part-time job?
Yes, I am
You don't look well
Do I look like that?
Yes
Do you have any worries?
Worries?
Well, yes
If you don't mind, would you like to come to my house?
My house is nearby
I can serve you some tea
We can talk there
Your house?
Yes
Well...
5 years later
Thank you
I noticed that you don't look well
Did something happen?
You noticed?
Well...
It's just my imagination
If you don't mind, would you like to talk to me?
Kurokawa-kun may be a bit too much
Are you okay?
What do you want to talk about?
It's about my husband
Well...
It's hard for me to say
No, it's not like that
I'm just wondering if it's okay to talk to a man
I can listen to anything
Really?
I don't think I can give you any advice
I don't want to see a man who is not so energetic
Thank you
My husband and I...
He seems to be in a bad mood
I wonder if I'm not attractive
I wonder if there are other women
That's what I was thinking
I see
You're not that unattractive
I guess so
How long have you been with him?
About a year
That long?
I'm sorry to talk about this
Forget it
I won't make you feel lonely
What's wrong?
I love you
I won't leave you alone like my husband
Calm down
Can't I?
I don't know if I can make you happy
I love you
I can't stop thinking about you
I'm sorry
I can't do this
But I'm married
I know
Did you hear that?
My husband and I...
Forget about it
You're not attractive to anyone
You're very attractive
I wanted to kiss you
Just one kiss
You're beautiful
I love you
I'm sorry
Don't forget about us
I love you
You're beautiful
I can go back to the way I was
I'm sorry
Are you okay?
I'm not okay
Come to me
But...
From now on...
I want to kiss you
You're beautiful
I love you
Are you okay?
It's been a while since I kissed you
I love you
Don't you feel anything?
I don't feel anything
I'm sorry
Your panties are wet
I can't do this
Are you sure?
It's amazing
I never imagined this
I didn't know
I can't do this
I'm embarrassed
Your panties are wet
I can't do this
Where do you like?
Tell me
Here?
Wait
I can't
It's dirty
I didn't take a shower
It's nothing
I can't do this
It's dirty
It's been a while
It's warm
Does it feel good?
But
I can't do this
Ai-chan
I'm scared
When I see you like this
I'm sorry
It's hard
How do you feel?
Don't tell anyone
It's hard
It's warm
I can't do this
That's not good
It's warm
How do you feel?
It's not good
It's not like you're going to shut me up like this, are you?
I know, right?
I love you.
Ouch!
Wait.
You can't do that.
Ouch!
You're excited, aren't you?
Don't say that.
It's embarrassing.
Ouch!
It's not easy for you to get up.
Wait.
I can't.
Okay.
Ouch!
It's not like you're going to shut me up like this, are you?
Don't do that.
You can't do that, can you?
You can't stop me, can you?
But the ground...
It's not like you're going to shut me up like this, are you?
It's been a while.
Ouch!
Stop it.
I love you so much.
Ouch!
It's not like you're going to shut me up like this, are you?
Stop it.
I love you so much.
I'm sleepy.
I'm thirsty.
Are you awake?
I don't know.
I can't sleep.
Can you hear me?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
I can't do this anymore.
I can't stop going.
I love you more than anyone else.
But...
But I can't do this anymore.
Why?
I'm not wearing any rubber bands.
I can't do this anymore.
I want to cry.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
I love you.
I'm sorry for what happened earlier.
I'm sorry, too.
I'll wash my body.
Please wash my body.
Please.
I'm sorry for what happened earlier.
I'm sorry, too.
You are very beautiful.
Thank you.
Do you want me to wash your butt?
Yes.
How do you feel?
I'm sleepy.
I want to touch your butt.
Thank you.
I'll wash my body.
I'm sleepy.
What's wrong?
Really?
I'm sleepy.
You look like an angel.
I'm getting bigger.
I'll make you feel better.
I'm sleepy.
I'm getting bigger.
I'm just looking at your body.
I'm sleepy.
I want to sleep, too.
You're amazing.
You look like an angel.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
You look like you're in a good mood.
I'm glad.
I'm sleepy.
Do you feel good?
I'm glad.
I'm sorry.
I gave you a lot.
I have to wash it again.
Let's wash it again.
You don't have to go home.
It's already evening.
That's right.
Can I stay a little longer?
I don't mind.
Really?
I'm glad.
My husband is late today.
Is that so?
What?
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
What are you worried about?
Do you see me?
I'm embarrassed to hear that again.
Really?
Why are you touching me?
I want my husband to take care of me.
I remember this.
Do you remember this?
I want my husband to take care of me.
Is that okay?
Will you take care of me?
Of course.
I'm curious about how you take care of me.
Really?
Can I lie down?
Can I look at you?
I get excited when I look at this.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm getting excited.
Kurokawa-kun.
You're getting bigger.
I'm getting excited.
Let's pet Kurokawa-kun.
Can you look at me?
It feels good.
Can you hear the sound?
I want to look at you.
I'm sorry.
Don't look at me.
Do you want to look at my butt?
I can't help it.
Do you want to cut my butt?
Come closer.
Closer?
It's cold.
Look at me more.
I'm sorry.
It's painful.
Are you a deaf?
No, my brother told me.
You've had a surgery twice today.
You've grown up.
Do you want me to clean your ears again?
It's just a little sticky.
Does it feel good?
Do you like it?
I'm sorry.
Kurokawa.
Hey.
Can you do more?
I'm sorry.
I was surprised.
Are you okay today?
Let's go inside.
I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
I don't know. What's wrong?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
You've grown a lot, haven't you?
Yeah.
You've grown up so much in such a short time.
You're heavy.
It's hard, but I'm very excited.
Are you excited?
What's wrong?
It's good.
Is it good?
Let's feel good today.
What's wrong?
How do you feel?
Are you sick?
It's good to be in a place like this.
Do you want to stop?
I don't want to.
Are you sick?
You're sick.
It feels good.
It's hard.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
It's hard.
It hurts.
It hurts...
I'm sorry.
Give me a breather.
Ah, I'm tired...
1, 2, 3...
Turn around...
1, 2...
I feel better now.
Ah ah ah ah ah
Ah ah ah ah
Let me go, let me go
Let me go
Ah ah ah ah
You're doing real good
Go easy on it