Iori-san, I'm sorry for stopping you suddenly.
Isn't it cold today?
If you don't mind, would you like to take a break at my house?
You had a hard time with your part-time job today, didn't you?
Iori-san is always working hard, so I thought you might be a little tired.
Kojima-kun, who works at the same store, always cares about me like this.
My husband doesn't listen to me at all.
Then, I'll listen to you.
Is that okay?
Then, this way, please.
Please.
I'm sorry.
It's a mess here.
Can I do it here?
Here?
Yes.
Here you are.
Thank you.
It's dirty.
I'll bring you a drink.
It's warm. Thank you.
It's really cold today.
I'll turn on the heater.
You'll be warm soon.
Thank you.
If I had gone home like that, I might have collapsed because it was cold.
No, it's nothing to thank me for.
You're kind, Kojima-kun.
Thank you.
Iori-san.
Actually, I've liked you for a long time.
What?
I'm sorry.
But, I'm serious.
But, I...
I know it's wrong.
But, I can't control my feelings anymore.
So...
Kojima-kun.
Iori-san.
Is it wrong?
Kojima-kun.
Iori-san.
Your lips are so soft.
I want to kiss you more.
Can I?
Iori-san.
I'm sorry.
You don't like it?
Kojima-kun.
I want you to kiss me until the end.
Iori-san.
Kojima-kun.
I'm going to look at you.
My hands are shaking.
Kojima-kun.
I'm sorry. I was nervous.
You're so big.
Iori-san.
Kojima-kun.
You're so beautiful.
I didn't know you were so big.
I want to look at your boobs.
Can I turn around?
Iori-san.
Wow.
This is good, too.
Are you embarrassed?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I can't take my eyes off you.
Wow.
I'm embarrassed.
You're so beautiful.
Wow.
You're so soft.
I love you.
Wow.
I'm so happy.
Don't hide it.
Does your boobs feel good?
Yes.
I feel good.
Well, then.
I want you to feel a lot better.
Wow.
I want to see more.
I want to see everything about you.
Is it okay?
Yes.
Wow.
Wait a minute.
Your boobs are so big.
You're so sexy.
I want to see more.
Show me your butt.
Wow.
It looks good on you.
You're so cute.
Wow.
Your butt is amazing.
I'm sorry.
Don't you hate it?
I don't hate it.
Wow.
It's melting.
It's so hot.
Can I see here?
Yes.
Wow.
Can I see here?
I'm sweating.
Wow.
It's so hot.
It smells so good.
Wow.
It's so hot.
I'm embarrassed.
Wow.
Let me see.
It's so beautiful.
Yes.
Wow.
It's so soft.
Do you like being touched here?
Wow.
It's so hot.
Didn't it hurt?
No.
It feels good.
Wow.
It's amazing.
It's really beautiful.
It's getting bigger.
It's true.
It's amazing.
I can't believe I'm being touched by Ibusa.
It's getting bigger.
Yes.
Can you see it?
I want you to see a lot.
Wow.
It feels so good.
It doesn't taste weird.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
No, it doesn't.
If you touch me.
Yes.
It feels so good.
I'm so happy.
Wow.
I can't stand it.
I want to be with you.
Yes.
Again.
Show me there.
Wow.
It's so soft.
Yes.
It's amazing.
Wow.
Yes.
Can I touch you like this?
Wow.
It's amazing.
It's so soft.
It feels so good just by doing this.
I'm going in.
Yes.
It hurts.
Wow.
It's tight.
It's amazing.
It's so soft.
It feels so good.
Really?
I'm so happy.
It's amazing.
It feels so good.
It's so soft.
It's my first time.
It feels so good.
It's amazing.
It's so soft.
It feels so good.
Show me how you feel.
You're so cute.
You can feel how soft I am.
There you go.
You're sweating a lot.
It feels so good.
Show me your face.
It's amazing.
It feels so good.
It's so good.
You're sweating a lot.
Your back, too.
It feels so good.
It's amazing.
Your back.
You're sweating a lot.
You can rub your back.
It feels so good.
It's amazing.
You're sweating a lot.
Your back.
Your butt.
I love your butt.
It's amazing.
It feels so good.
It's so nice.
I can't.
You're moving a lot.
It feels so good
No, no, no
Inside
ミロさんごめん急いで中に出ちゃった
すごい出てる
Can I borrow a shower?
It's this way.
Excuse me.
We only have men's shampoo and body soap.
Feel free to use it.
Okay.
Bye.
Wait.
Let's take a shower together.
Can I?
Yes.
I'll wash your hair.
Okay.
How is it?
It's okay.
I'll wash your hair.
Thank you.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
My heart is pounding.
It's hot.
I'll wash your hair.
Okay.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I'll wash your hair.
Okay.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
I didn't know it was this hot.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Your skin is so smooth.
I'm happy to hear that.
Can I rub your butt?
My butt?
Yes.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Your butt is so smooth.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Your skin is so smooth.
I'm embarrassed.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Your butt is so smooth.
It's hot.
Can I do this?
Yes.
I feel good.
I'm sweating.
Can I do this?
Yes.
Let me do this.
I feel good.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I washed my hands.
It's okay.
You sweat a lot.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
Thank you.
Do you need anything?
Do you have alcohol?
Yes, I do.
Do you want something sweet?
Yes.
Can I drink this?
Thank you.
It's hot.
Cheers.
It's good.
I'm glad.
By the way.
Are you free today?
Yes.
I can't go home because I'm late for work.
I'm free.
I'm glad.
I didn't want you to go home.
I admired you.
You are good at your job.
You are kind to everyone.
You are beautiful.
I'm embarrassed to hear that.
I'm embarrassed.
I'll stay here tonight.
Please stay here.
Hiyori.
Come here.
Show me your body.
I'm embarrassed.
You are looking at me.
Like this.
Show me more.
You are beautiful.
Why are you so beautiful?
I don't know.
I didn't do anything.
You are amazing.
What?
You are surprised.
Are you excited to see me?
Maybe.
You have a pure image.
Do you do it yourself?
Do you do it?
I don't do it.
You don't do it?
You do it a little.
Just a little.
Can you show me a little?
Can you show me?
Here.
How do you do it?
As usual.
But...
You are amazing.
I'm embarrassed.
Do you touch only your boobs?
What else?
My tongue.
You are amazing.
That's how you do it.
You put on underwear.
If you are embarrassed, you can turn around.
Turn around?
I'm embarrassed.
Show me a lot.
Can I show you?
I'm embarrassed.
How do you look now?
Turn around.
You are amazing.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm talking to you.
I want to see your face.
I'm embarrassed.
You are amazing.
Your chest hair is red.
I'm embarrassed.
You are amazing.
I want to see you more.
I'm embarrassed.
You are amazing.
Can I do it with you?
I'm embarrassed.
You are amazing.
Can I lick you?
I'm embarrassed.
You are amazing.
You are cute.
I'm embarrassed.
You might pee again.
Do you want me to wipe?
You want me to wipe?
I'll wipe.
It was so good.
There's so much.
It felt so good.
I'm sorry. I got you dirty again.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Iori-san.
I might not be able to touch you yet.
Can I touch you until tomorrow morning?
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh, Uta-san.
You're here.
Come in.
Please sit down.
I'm so happy.
Would you like something to drink?
I'll go get it.
I'd rather have sex with you than drink.
Uta-san.
Yes.
I can't stand it anymore.
Uta-san.
Are you okay?
Uta-san, I want to touch you.
You're amazing.
Thank you.
You're wearing a cute underwear.
You're sweating a little.
Let's take this off.
You're amazing.
It looks really good on you.
Thank you.
Let's take this off, too.
Wow.
You're amazing.
Your nipples are already standing.
Thank you.
It's really hot in here, too.
Can I look at you a lot?
Yes.
I can't stand it anymore.
Thank you.
You smell really good.
Uta-san.
I can't stand it anymore.
Let me see your nipples.
Like this?
Yes.
I see.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed, too.
You're really beautiful.
I can't stand it anymore.
Let me see your nipples closer.
It's good.
I can't stand it anymore.
You're amazing.
Let me see your nipples closer.
I see.
It's really good.
I can't stand it anymore.
Your nipples are already standing.
Can I look at you from the front?
I see.
You're amazing.
You're so soft.
I can't stand it anymore.
Let me see your nipples closer.
I see.
I can't stand it anymore.
You're amazing.
It's hot.
Let me see your nipples closer.
You're amazing.
Can I look at you from the front?
I can't stand it anymore.
You're amazing.
Let me see your nipples closer.
Can I look at you from the front?
I can't stand it anymore.
You're amazing.
You're so soft.
I can't stand it anymore.
Let me see your nipples closer.
You're amazing.
I can't stand it anymore.
You're so cute.
You're amazing.
I can't stand it anymore.
Do you like it?
Yes.
I can't stand it anymore.
You're so soft.
Can I put this in your mouth?
Yes.
Let me see your nipples closer.
I can't stand it anymore.
You're so soft.
Let me see your nipples closer.
I can see your nipples.
I can't stand it anymore.
Let me see your nipples.
You're so soft.
I can't stand it anymore.
Let me see your nipples closer.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
Are you okay?
Let me see your nipples.
I feel good.
You're so soft.
Let me see your nipples.
I feel good.
You're so soft.
I can't stand it anymore.
Here.
I feel so good.
I felt it deeply.
Ha!
Haa.
Haaaaaaaaaaaaaa...
Goddess, you are the best.
Ahhh.
III
Goddess,
you are amazing!
You have such a big bum!
You make me feel into dancing.
What?
Drop...
Don't move.
Kosei, open your mouth
Oh...
Can you hear the noisy sound?
Oh, no...
What is it that you want...?
Umm
Ah…
No~~
That's too rough.
Woah
You better come home.
You have to come home.
This plant is in your way.
Ah
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
itself
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah Ah ah
Ah ah ah ah ah ah
Plus
Ah ah
Hmm
Ah ah ah ah
I feel great
Hmm
Haa
Ha
Hmm
I'm getting more and more tired.
It's amazing.
It's hard. I feel sick.
It's hard.
It's amazing.
It's really amazing.
My stomach is growling.
It's amazing.
It's really amazing.
I feel so good.
I can't stand it anymore.
If I tighten it this much, I'll go.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I can't stand it anymore.
I feel like I'm going.
Let's go together.
I can't stand it anymore.
It feels good.
I felt so good.
I felt so good, too.
I'll eat it for you.
Really?
It feels good.
It's pink because I just ate it.
It's pink.
Do you have time today?
Let's do it again after taking a shower.