I heard that you got a girlfriend in 7th grade.
Oh, really?
That's great.
I want a girlfriend soon.
What do you think?
I...
Well...
I think so.
I think so, too.
I want to make a girlfriend soon.
I want to graduate anyway.
I see.
Is it just us?
Is it just us in the class?
I don't know.
What do you think?
Everyone says they have a girlfriend.
That's right.
It's about time.
I see.
I don't want to say it.
Well...
I see.
Do you have any experience?
What?
Are you a virgin?
Well...
I'm a virgin.
I see.
I want to graduate as soon as possible.
But I can't help being impatient.
It's just us, isn't it?
I don't think so.
I'm impatient.
I think I can do it someday.
I want to do it soon.
I want to do it.
I see.
Toshiya is a virgin.
I wonder what it's like to have sex with a virgin.
I'm very interested in it.
I want to graduate as soon as possible.
I'm sorry.
I have a favor to ask you.
Can you buy me some milk?
I don't want to.
I have to prepare dinner.
I'll go.
Thank you.
Toshiya.
I asked you a while ago.
Are you still a virgin?
Did you hear that?
I see.
Are you so embarrassed to be a virgin?
Well...
I want to graduate as soon as possible.
Why don't you try it now?
Really?
Promise me you won't tell anyone.
I promise.
I haven't done it recently.
I was lonely.
So I'll tell you a lot of things.
Are you sure?
Can you kiss me?
Can you come closer?
Can you do it?
Yes.
What?
Is it a tongue?
Is it okay?
It's okay.
It's a practice.
Wow.
It's very slimy.
I was surprised.
Are you nervous?
Yes.
You don't have to be nervous at all.
I'm nervous.
But I kissed her.
Touch where you want to touch.
Where do you want to touch?
I don't know where I want to touch.
It's okay.
Can I touch your boobs?
Yes.
I'll touch your boobs.
Please do it like this.
Like this?
Yes.
That's right.
Like this.
It's amazing.
It's elastic.
Is it amazing?
It's soft and big.
I see.
Is it here?
Yes.
How is it?
It's soft.
It's better to touch it gently.
Gently?
Yes.
I think it's comfortable.
That's right.
Gently.
It's difficult.
It's soft.
I'm impressed.
Really?
That's right.
More.
Yes.
Can I touch more?
Really?
Yes.
Can you show me?
It's big.
Touch it.
Your boobs are in front of me.
Is it okay?
Yes.
It's okay.
How is it?
It's soft.
It's amazing.
My boobs are shaking.
Yes, your boobs are shaking.
It's amazing.
Does it hurt?
No.
It's just right.
It's okay.
It's gentle.
Yes.
I want to see inside.
Do you want to see?
Yes.
Do you want to take it off?
You've never taken it off, have you?
No.
It's okay.
Can you take it off?
No.
I can't.
Can I take it off?
Yes.
Did you take it off?
It's amazing.
How do you feel?
My boobs.
It's amazing.
It's beautiful and big.
Really?
Is it soft?
Yes.
My boobs are amazing.
It's amazing.
I want to see your boobs more.
Do you want to see?
It's okay.
Is it okay?
Yes.
It's amazing.
My boobs are amazing.
Can I lick your boobs?
Can I?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It's delicious.
Is it alive?
Yes, it is.
It's amazing.
I want to lick your boobs.
Really?
It's amazing.
I'm glad that I could lick your boobs for the first time.
Do you want to see?
I want to see.
Can I?
Yes.
It's amazing.
How is it?
What's inside?
Do you want to see?
Let me take off your clothes.
Can I see?
Yes.
Do you want me to take off your clothes?
Can I?
Yes.
It's amazing.
How is it?
It's in front of me.
I want to see more.
Can I see?
Yes.
I want you to pull my hair.
How is it?
It's like this.
Can you see?
I can see very well.
It's like this.
Yes.
What should I do?
Do you want to touch it?
Where should I touch?
Touch here.
Like this?
Yes.
How should I touch?
Touch gently.
I'm sleepy.
Are you sure?
Yes.
It's slimy.
Do you want to put your finger in there?
My finger?
Yes.
It's slimy.
Here?
Yes.
It's slimy.
Did you put your finger in there?
Yes.
Doesn't it hurt?
It feels good.
It's difficult.
It's good.
Really?
Yes.
It's good.
It feels good.
It's very...
It's very hot.
I'm excited.
Are you excited?
Yes.
What should I do?
Do you want to do something?
Can I lick you?
Yes.
I'll lick you.
Did you lick me?
Yes.
It was good.
Really?
Yes.
I licked you on YouTube.
It was very good.
I want you to do something.
Okay.
What should I do?
Should I lie down?
Yes.
Lie down.
Can I lick you?
Yes.
I'm embarrassed.
Can I lick you?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Can I lick you?
Yes.
You're standing up.
I was excited.
It's my first time to be licked.
Do you want to drink something?
Can I lick you?
No.
It's okay.
It feels good.
Can I lick you?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
Can I lick you?
Yes.
It feels good.
Can I lick you?
Yes.
It's hot.
Do you want to sleep?
Is it really okay?
Yes.
It's okay.
Finally, I'm going to graduate.
I'm going to sleep.
Yes.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I feel so good that I feel like I'm going to pass out.
Really?
Can I move?
Yes.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
Yes.
It's hot.
Can I lie on your butt?
It's hard.
It's hot.
It feels good because it's different from my body temperature.
Really?
Yes.
It's hot.
I want to move.
Yes.
Can I lie on your butt?
Is it here?
Yes.
It's here.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Can you do it?
Yes.
I can do it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Can I do it again?
It feels good.
Does it?
Yes.
It's hot.
Can I kiss you again?
Yes.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm going to puke.
It's okay.
Is this okay?
Yes.
I'm going to puke.
It's okay.
Let it out.
I'm going to kiss you.
It's hot.
Sex feels so good.
Yes, it does.
It felt good for me, too.
It's a secret.
I know.
It's hot.
I'm home.
I came to visit Toshio.
Welcome home.
I'm home.
I'm tired.
Have a seat.
I had a hard time today, too.
It was hard.
I didn't have a chance to visit you.
But, if I didn't clean up, I wouldn't have been so angry.
I was about to talk back.
I put up with it.
But, you didn't help me at all.
You didn't help me at all.
It's a part-time worker.
Hello.
I'll have a drink.
Okay.
Is that mine?
I don't know.
I'll have a drink, too.
I can't forget what happened the other day.
Can I do it again?
No, you can't.
Calm down.
Please.
Toshio graduated at the same time as you, didn't he?
Please do it one more time.
I can't do it.
It may be mine.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
I can't forget it.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
Can I do it again?
Okay.
I'll do it again.
Please.
Can I do it again?
Okay.
I'll do it again.
I can't do it.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it without you.
What should I do?
Yes.
I'm busy.
Are you busy?
Yes.
I can't do it.
If you leave it to me...
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I see.
What should I do?
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
I see.
I'll go get it now.
Please.
I'm sorry, Toshio.
What?
I forgot something at work.
Can I go get it now?
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Bye.
Shun left.
It's okay, right?
No, but...
Please.
What?
This is the last time.
Toshio, this is the last time.
I know.
Okay?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It's so soft.
I can't hold it with these boobs.
I see.
Are you okay?
It hurts.
It's okay.
It's so beautiful.
I'm so happy.
It smells so good.
Why is it so hard?
It's nothing.
You're excited.
Does it hurt?
It doesn't hurt at all.
It's hot.
I've been studying a lot of things lately.
What did you study?
Things like this.
I'm good at it.
You're good at it.
It's hot.
Why are you surprised?
Because I'm being touched.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's hot.
You just said it.
I'm happy.
It feels so good.
It's okay.
It's hot.
It's hard.
It feels so good.
I want you to massage my shoulders.
It's hot.
It feels so good.
I want you to massage my shoulders.
Okay.
Juanita crab...
The taste is a bit spicy
and Fanta's crab is more crunchy
Their meat is really nice
Also the meat is way cheaper than normal one
One more is too much for me.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's good.
Is it good?
Yes.
It feels good.
It might be a little bad.
Is it bad?
It feels good.
I can't get up.
You can't get up?
Can I get up?
Yes, you can.
It's hard.
You slept a lot.
I want you to make it clean.
Okay.
It's clean now.
It felt so good.
It's the last one.
Yes.
Did you like it?
It felt so good.
But I wanted to do it until the end.
What?
Toshiya.
Toshiya, who just learned how to have sex, came to me many times like an animal with a collar.
Toshiya, who is getting better at having sex, kept me alive many times.
Now I'm looking forward to Toshiya coming to me.
Toshiya.
It's hot.
Does it make you feel good?
Of course.
Your cup is the best.
Thank you.
I want to hear a lot of pleasant sounds.
All right.
It's getting very hot here.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
It's getting very hot here.
It's because it's big.
It's hot.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I was very surprised.
You've gotten better.
Do you want to see my breasts?
I'm glad.
It's really beautiful.
No matter how many times I see it, it's beautiful.
I'm glad.
It's hot.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
I love you.
These breasts are the best.
I'm glad.
If I do this, I'll be very surprised.
You'll be surprised.
It's hot.
It's getting harder and harder.
It's all round.
It's embarrassing.
Open your breasts.
It's like this.
It's hot.
You're crying a lot.
Look at me.
I prepared this.
Why?
I wanted to use it.
Did you bring it?
Can I use it?
I'll use it.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'm sure this feels better.
I think so.
Do you want me to press it?
Press it.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
Can I press it harder?
It's okay.
How about this?
It's strong.
It's hot.
Are you going to go?
I want to see it.
I'll show you.
It's hot.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Do you want me to take this off?
My body is getting hot.
It's hot.
I want you to make me feel better.
I want you to look at me.
Does it feel good?
No.
It's hot.
It feels good.
My body is getting hot.
Already?
It's true.
It's amazing.
I want you to let me sleep.
It's okay.
I'll let you sleep.
Can I sleep?
Of course.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'm going to move my body a lot.
It's hot.
I want you to let me sleep.
It's okay.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's hard.
My nipples are hard.
I want you to rub my nipples.
It's hard.
It's hard, isn't it?
My nipples are shaking.
It's amazing.
It's hot.
I can't stand it anymore.
I want to sleep.
Do you want to sleep?
It's okay.
I'm going to sleep.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It feels good no matter how many times I do it.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
I want you to rub my nipples.
I was surprised.
I was surprised, too.
Does it feel good?
I'm going to rub your buttocks.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
Yes.
I want you to rub my buttocks.
It's hot.
Can I rub your buttocks?
Wait a minute.
Rub my buttocks.
Okay.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Wait a minute.
It's hot.
It feels good.
How's my buttocks?
It's hard.
It feels good, but it's about to come out.
Is it about to come out?
Okay.
I'll rub your buttocks again.
It's about to come out.
Is it about to come out?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Can I rub your buttocks more?
Can I?
Yes.
It's about to come out.