A few days later
Come in
Sorry to keep you waiting
I'm sure you know her
She's Ayumi, the doctor
We were going to get married
Ayumi is going to have a new mom
You have to get along with your mom
I never imagined my dad would marry Ayumi
I'm sorry, Yuta
Let's get along
Sorry to keep you waiting
It's okay
Really?
Yeah
It must be tough
If anything happens, help me
Of course
I'm happy
Let's help each other
Yeah
You're a good cook
Yeah, I used to cook by myself
I want you two to eat
I can't wait
My dad remarried Ayumi
Ayumi was a nurse when I was in the hospital
Yuta, how tall were you?
39.8 cm
Let me see
You're a bit tall
Let me measure your pulse
39.8 cm
Your pulse is normal
Are you feeling better?
Yeah
I'm glad
I should have gotten along with Ayumi before my dad
I should have...
Yuta, what's wrong?
Ayumi...
Oh, it's your mom
Are you used to living here?
Yeah
I've never heard about it
But my dad and Ayumi have been living here for a long time
I see
It must be tough
Yeah
I've never heard about it
But how did you get along with your dad?
Well...
Yuta was in the hospital
My dad came to visit me a lot
At that time
Why did you want to get married?
Well...
My dad came to visit me a lot
I thought he was a kind person
So I fell in love with him
I see
But I like Ayumi more than my dad
What's wrong?
You like Ayumi, don't you?
No
You've liked her since you were in the hospital
Ayumi, I love you
Calm down, Yuta
I can't
But it must be tough for your dad to live here
It's none of your business
No, Yuta
Calm down
I can't
Yuta
Calm down, Yuta
Calm down
Yuta
I can't
Calm down
It must be tough for your dad to live here
I can't
I told you I can't
Calm down
I can't
I told you I can't
Yuta
I can't
Calm down
Yuta
I can't
I'm scared
Oh no....
Be careful..
Wait..
Oh no!
Please don't...
Don't...
Don't open that place...
Don't do that...
It's not good to be seen by your father.
Just a little more...
It's not good...
Compared to your father...
No, it's not good...
It's better to be seen by me, isn't it?
No...
It's not good...
You look like a nice man.
Thank you.
Good girl.
I'm going to sleep now.
Do you want me to pinch your boobs?
No, I don't want to.
I want you to do it.
I'm going to sleep now.
Don't do that.
Don't wake me up.
I'm going to sleep now.
Why are your hands so hard?
Don't talk about me.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
I can't do this.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
How do you feel?
Are you relieved?
Don't say that.
You're very quiet.
I can't do this anymore.
You feel good, don't you?
Don't do this to me.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm sorry...
No.
No, no.
Agh! Outta my way!
Oh, no.
Itchy...
Ugh...
How far are you going to drag me?
This far?
I can't take it anymore.
Yuto-kun.
What did you do inside?
I don't know.
I won't tell my father.
Yuto-kun.
Oh, it's cold.
I'm home.
You're early today.
I wanted to see you early, so I came home early.
I'm glad.
I wanted to see you.
I've been thinking about it all the time.
Really?
I was surprised because you came early.
I finished my work right away.
I'm glad.
What's wrong?
It's not fair to my father.
No, it's not.
I'll do it for you.
We can't do this.
No, it's not.
I'm cold.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
It's not good.
I'll fix it.
I can't take it anymore.
Mom, what should I do?
Mom, you look the most attractive in this dress.
Yuta.
I'll make you feel better today.
I can't take it anymore.
I feel sick.
Yuta, don't do this.
I can't take it anymore.
It doesn't hurt, does it?
Yes, it doesn't hurt.
There are a lot of things here.
I'm sorry.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,interspection
This is so relaxing.
Ah...
I can't do it.
Don't spread your legs.
It's painful.
It's painful?
That's great.
Wow, amazing.
Yuta-kun is amazing.
Is Yuta-san amazing?
Don't ask such a mean thing.
Tell me.
Yuta-kun is amazing.
I want you to have a lot of breakfast.
A lot?
Good morning.
Yuta-kun is amazing.
I know Yuta-kun is amazing.
I want you to keep wearing your undergarments.
Do you want me to keep wearing my undergarments?
Good morning.
I want to kiss you.
Do you want to kiss me?
I want you to keep wearing your undergarments.
Yuta-kun is amazing.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh It hurts
it hurts
Hah
Hmm
That is all I can do for you for the remaining year.
Please stop!
Please stop.
That is all.
Hurry up.
How's this?
What's happening?
It's okay.
Ouch!
It's fine.
It's a little hard.
I can't do it.
Oh no!
Oh my god!!
It hurts!
It's not good.
I can not
Kemio-chan
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my goodness
u
You are deep.
I feel like scaring you.
You are so soft that I just don't want to.
I think so.
Don't move me.
Does it feel good?
I feel so good.
I love you.
Thank you.
I'm so tired.
Thank you so much.
I feel so good.
I love you.
I can't sleep.
I'm so tired.
I feel so good.
I can't sleep.
I'll clean your back.
I love you.