Look at if you are studying at night.
I say you are studying well.
You have been getting a lot of grades lately.
Can you come and see me a little?
Oh what are you doing?
Just look at that.
I want to come as much as possible.
by
What are you doing.
Oh well mother.
My father was angry.
What to do.
If you’re angry, I don’t like to talk long.
Did you not study and play?
No, I just took a break.
Sinai, Sinai, where are you going?
Where did you go? - Shiny
Oh, Shane, who is this?
I am not watching.
I was playing, don’t study.
Go in, the grade.
Not anything any.
I just play so much, no.
It is true.
What to do, from now on.
Can you change your school beautifully?
Which school is it.
I’ll let your father handle it.
I do not know well.
There is a new school in front of the station.
Yes, it looks good.
You know, is it?
It looks like a complicit hospital.
Oh yes?
How long does the train take?
I hear it is quite expensive.
Oh is?
is high?
Good luck, I will look at you and make a specific review.
It is.
Be careful with your mother.
Yes of course.
So to say, mother.
I was a friend of Suzuka at night.
Yes Mr Suzuki.
Oh well Mr Suzuki.
He probably had crossed the line.
But I am sure.
At the same time, right?
Maybe it is with friends.
He cannot stand that he is alone.
What happened?
Is it okay?
Yes it is okay.
Hasn’t it been down for a long time?
In such a time, maybe it might be.
I shall see.
Is it okay?
Yes it is okay.
Because I just look.
Tell me if something happens.
Yes to.
The sound stopped.
It seemed like something was broken under the shell.
Did he fall, is it okay?
Do you not sound?
Fix the foodstuffs now.
Sorry, was it noisy?
Did you help me something?
OK is OK.
Because you shouldn’t do this.
Oh, and what about school?
Yes, it is okay.
What is OK? what is OK?
Their grades are getting better.
Is it getting better?
I do not think so.
I am studying a little.
If you don’t study, you won’t be a good person.
He is doing well.
You don’t seem to be doing better than your father.
Maybe they are hiding behind it.
Yes, in the recent time.
I have had a cell phone in the school recently, so it’s hard.
What is it?
You’ll be serious about studying, so you’ll be serious about it.
You do it well, so it is okay.
If not, I will take your phone or phone.
I understand.
Turn off the phone, you.
You cannot concentrate on studying.
Oh, that is it.
When you do something, you turn your phone.
I think I’ve been studying on my phone lately.
I can’t tell you, but you can’t watch your phone all year round.
I understand.
My dad also has a lot of medication.
If my mother were like that,
Maybe it’s the second time, but maybe not.
A little bit, I can’t believe it.
Because there is a constant weight.
Yes
Stay tightly targeted.
You have to work hard.
I know.
Let’s go to the toilet.
Oh well sir.
No to no.
No to Mr. No.
Daddy will come back from the toilet.
by Chen
Oh is
and more
It is Tys.
That is?
Shine is?
I told you to study something, and sooner.
Oh is?
It seems to be back in your room.
Oh yes?
Yes
by
It is okay to leave.
No to?
No more, I am going to.
Yes yes
Oh well okay?
The heart comes out.
Sorry to
Why is it.
Sleep by
Do not go.
by
Just a little.
I finally came, stay here.
Oh, you finally came.
Is that your mother?
Oh yeah.
Was it not there?
Yes to.
Where did you go?
I want it.
I told you you went back to the school.
Because I haven’t eaten enough yet.
really is?
I will get a cold from you.
Study well.
I went, Dad.
Because my father went out.
Come here and come.
What happened?
It was a little cold.
It is cold, so open it.
Yes
thanks to