The next day
Mr. Nagawara
Yeah?
Koichi's grades seem to be falling recently.
I guess so.
I don't know.
Don't tell me you're studying.
Really?
You're always on the phone until late at night.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Aren't you concentrating at night?
I don't know. I'm going to take a look.
I'm hungry.
This is a good drink.
This is the best.
Koichi.
What are you doing without studying?
What are you doing?
I'm angry.
Are you playing with a student?
Where did you get this?
I don't know.
Are you a person?
He doesn't even know how to study.
What were you doing?
Were you watching TV?
What should I do?
What are you talking about?
He was studying.
He used to be a good concentrator.
You're not like Koichi.
Really?
Yes.
I'm telling you.
I don't know.
You can play sports.
You don't have to study.
You don't have to play sports.
Really?
You're studying now.
He doesn't play sports.
You're right.
What's wrong with you?
It's nothing.
Listen to me.
I'm talking for him.
Please listen to me.
Recently, some people make money by playing games.
Yes.
But they can't make money by playing games.
They can make money by eating.
I want to make him a public servant.
A public servant?
It's difficult.
What's wrong with you?
It's nothing.
I'm just curious.
Do you want to go home?
No.
Koichi, let's go home.
You're right.
I'm going home.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Sometimes, it's important to take a bath.
I don't know.
It's not a bath.
It's early in the morning.
Where are you going?
I'm going to buy coffee.
I see.
Here you are.
I'm sorry.
Ugh...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I
'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I
was glad to meet with the P- repetitive even I Saraparo
I excited to see the first walk
you
professional
I am not going to believe it
Hey, do you have time?
Oh, I see.
Alright, I'm going home.
When I get home, I'm going to give him a big lecture.
Take care.
See you.
How was it?
It was good.
It was good!
It was good, alright!
It was great.
It was good!
It was good.
preservation, observation and safe keeping.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
is
son
Hmm
Uh-huh
Ah ah 2015
tan
Four
I'm sorry.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm saying this for your future.
I know you're noisy.
You know that I had a hard time because I couldn't make good friends.
I don't want you to have the same painful feelings as my father.
I'm telling you to study.
You know that, right?
I know.
Mom said something.
I think it's good to do what you want to do.
If you know what you like, it's easy to do it.
Study for the time being.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to do it.
I have something to do next week.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Where is Koichi?
He went to his room.
What is he?
You don't have to say that.
I don't know what to do in the future.
I'm worried about what Koichi wants to do.
I don't know what Koichi wants to do.