I still sigh That's a great body.
I wish I could get married to someone like you in the future.
Thank you.
By the way, do you think you can find a room?
I'm looking for a lot of things, but I can't find a good one.
Take your time until you find a good one.
Thank you.
By the way, is your uncle still on a business trip?
Yes, he is.
He seems to be busy.
He said he was going to leave next month, but he said he was going to leave again.
I see.
Take your time until you find one.
Thank you.
It smells good.
Satoru?
It's you.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
Raise your head.
What?
Are you excited about my underwear?
I'll let you smell more.
It smells good.
I'm glad you were excited about my underwear.
It's hard, isn't it?
It smells good.
Satoru.
This room is small.
Let's go to your room.
Satoru.
You can smell more.
Can I smell more?
You like it, don't you?
It's your underwear.
I'm glad you smelled it.
How is it?
Is it still hard?
Do you get so excited?
Satoru, you're a pervert.
Are you okay?
I'm glad.
Look at me.
It's embarrassing.
It's okay.
Look at me.
It's embarrassing.
Do you want to smell more?
I'll smell it.
Smell it.
It's embarrassing.
It's amazing.
I can feel Satoru's nose.
It's warm.
How is it?
I'm so excited.
I'm so excited to smell your underwear.
It's embarrassing.
I'll give you a massage.
I'll remove the smell from your underwear.
How is it?
It's amazing.
You're so excited.
It's hot.
Let me touch you.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's warm.
I'm glad.
It feels good.
You should have done something more pleasant.
It's embarrassing.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
It's embarrassing.
You're sweating a lot.
It's hot.
It's hard.
I've never done this before.
What are you doing?
I'm licking you.
Doesn't it feel good?
What would you do if I found out?
You look so painful.
It's painful.
It's hot.
Do you want to smell it?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Stop it.
I want you to lick me more.
Okay.
It's hot.
It feels good.
You're sweating a lot.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
I'll put it on the spot where it touched.
Here.
How is it?
It's hot.
Stop it.
It's dangerous.
Touch my boobs.
Your boobs are so soft.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Your boobs are so soft.
Lick my boobs.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
Touch my boobs.
You're sweating a lot.
Does it feel good?
Touch my boobs.
It's hot.
Here.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
It's warm inside.
I'll rub it with my fingers.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
Here?
There.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Come closer.
It's where I put my underwear on.
Here?
There.
Lick my boobs.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Lick my boobs.
What are you doing?
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
Do you want me to put it in your pants?
Yes.
Come here.
Do you want me to put it in your pants?
It's a woman's pants.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
I'm sweating.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
I'm sweating.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
I'm sweating.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Are you okay?
Do your back.
It's hot.
It smells.
Do you like my panties that much?
It's hot.
It hurts.
I cried.
I want to do more.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah…
Oh, it feels so good.
You're getting smaller.
Hang in there.
You can't help it.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh.
Welcome back, Satoru.
You're early today.
I wanted to see you as soon as possible, so I got up early.
I'm glad.
But you don't have to try so hard.
Oh, yeah.
I'll give you a massage.
Hey.
No, it's okay.
It's not a massage.
No, it's more than that.
What?
What's more than that?
Can you show me your underwear?
Then the fatigue will blow away at once.
It's a little embarrassing.
Hey, please.
Please show me.
Please.
But...
Please show me your underwear.
Please.
Just a little.
Oh, yeah.
Like this?
What?
I can only see a little.
A little more?
Can you show me a little more?
I can't help it.
Then...
Like this?
Wow.
It's like a string.
What?
It's a little thin, but...
It looks great on you.
It's embarrassing.
Wow.
What?
I don't know what it looks like.
Wow.
What's going on behind you?
Behind me?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, behind me...
It's embarrassing.
Hey, show me.
What kind of underwear is it?
What?
Please.
Behind me...
Wow.
What?
It's a T-bag.
Don't look at me like that.
It's embarrassing.
Show me, show me, show me.
A little more.
Lift it up.
Yes, lift it up more.
Like this?
Yes.
Wow.
It's a T-bag.
Yeah.
Wow.
Are you done?
A little more.
Show me a little more.
What?
You've seen a lot.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm getting excited.
It's amazing.
What?
It's stiff.
Wow.
It's already stiff.
Hey.
What should I do?
It's amazing.
I want you to squeeze it with your panties.
Squeeze it?
Yes, please.
What?
Then...
I'll take off my panties.
Yes, yes.
Wow.
I'll take it off.
Yes, like this.
Like this.
Hey, hey.
Please, please, please.
What?
Like this?
I want you to wrap it in your panties.
Wrap it in my panties?
Yes.
I want you to wrap it in your panties.
Please.
Like this?
Yes.
Oh, that feels good.
It's warm because I just took off my panties.
Don't be shy.
That feels good.
It's very stiff.
Oh, that feels good.
Like this?
Yes.
Oh, that feels good.
Does it?
Yes, it feels very good.
Oh, it's very stiff.
Is it?
Is it stiff?
Yes, it is.
I'm getting excited.
Wow.
Doesn't it hurt?
It feels very good.
Really?
Yes.
Oh, it's very stiff.
I can't take it anymore.
What?
Can I take it off like this?
Take it off like this?
I want to take it off like this.
Oh, no, no.
It's coming off.
Did it come off?
A lot.
It came off a lot.
It's very sticky.
Thank you, ma'am.
I'm tired all of a sudden.
Do you feel better?
Yes, I do.
Let's take a bath and get refreshed.
Okay.
Satoru.
This is our secret.
Yes.
Of course.
Hey, ma'am.
Can I stay like this until my uncle comes back?
Satoru, are you okay with me?
Yes.
Because I've always admired you.
So I want to stay like this a little longer.
Okay, ma'am?
Yes.
Thank you, ma'am.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I do.
Thank you, ma'am.
How do you feel?
It's cold.
Thank you, ma'am.
You're so wet.
It's hot.
Thank you, ma'am.
What?
It's getting harder and harder.
Let's do it one more time.
Please.
It feels good.
Let me lick you.
I'm getting full.
It's amazing.
It's in my stomach.
It's tasty.
Ma'am.
You can't take the video?
It's in my stomach.
I'm gonna throw up
Wow
You threw up a lot
I threw up a lot
Satoru
Ma'am
Don't call me ma'am
Call me by my name
Yui
That feels good
Yama-san
Tell me everything
Tell me everything.
I feel good when you touch me.
Touch me a lot.
Hm...
Wau!
Ah...
Waii!
Huh?
Ha...
Here we go.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh.
Ah!
Ah.
Got it soaking in.
Nnnn ...
ah.
Nor mincing...
Ah.
Hmm...
Makes me excited.
Yes very much.
Ahh ...
Hmm mundo ...
And ...
Touch me.
It doesn't feel good.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
It doesn't feel good.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't lick me.
I'll lick you a lot.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
Ouch!
It doesn't feel good.
It's amazing.
I didn't know my belly was this big.
It doesn't feel good.
Even though I'm wearing underwear.
It's amazing.
You have a lot of belly fat.
I'll take it off.
You look happy.
I'm very happy.
I'll make you feel better.
It doesn't feel good.
It's amazing.
My hand.
It doesn't feel good.
It's getting harder.
Let's lick together.
It doesn't feel good.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'll give you a lot of kisses with my underwear.
It doesn't feel good.
I can't do it anymore.
Do you want me to do it?
Yes.
Hurry up.
I can't breathe.
It smells good.
It's hard.
I can't breathe.
It doesn't feel good.
I'll move.
Go ahead.
I can't breathe.
It's hard.
Ahhhhhh
Ah!
Ouch!
Ouch, I'm tired.
I'm tired.
You love panties, don't you?
Ouch!
More.
Stay there.
Hold my hand.
Ouch!
It's hot.
Give me more.
Ouch!
It smells good.
Wow!
Ouch!
It's hot.
It's hot!
Ouch!
Please!
Please, it hurts!
Zzzzzzzzzzzz
Oo!
Yuichi.
I'm sorry.
Zzzz
Ah, please save me
Soekarno-san.
Stop eating.
Get up.
I'll go inside.
Ouch
Please, give me a hug.
Oh, my god!
I'm hot.
I can't do it.
Yui.
Help me.
I can't do it.