Today, I'd like to review the previous test.
The result is...
Nakahira-kun, the best student of the year.
You did your best.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
The exam is coming soon.
I hope you all learn from Nakahira-kun and study hard.
Yes.
Nakahira-kun, I'm going ahead.
What should I do?
Should I go ahead?
I'm hungry.
Where should I go after this?
Nakahira-kun, you're doing your best.
Yes.
I have high expectations of you.
Yes, I'll do my best.
If you're in trouble, just tell me.
I'll do anything for you.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you.
Be careful on your way home.
Yes, I will.
You still don't know how a woman reacts.
You have an excellent gene, but you're still cute.
The time limit is 40 minutes.
If you're done early, please sit down and wait.
Let's start.
The time limit is 40 minutes.
If you're done early, please sit down and wait.
Thank you.
You were wearing underpants, weren't you?
Not only study
You're interested in women, too, aren't you?
You're interested, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
You can tell that my boobs are touching yours, can't you?
Don't tell me that you're already in love with me.
No, I'm not.
You're so cute.
I'm graduating soon.
I can graduate from high school, but I can't graduate as a bachelor.
I'll tell you when I graduate from college.
I'm a little embarrassed.
I forgot my bag in the classroom.
What are you talking about?
I'll go get it.
I'm going ahead, so come back soon.
He's stupid.
I'm a virgin after all.
Nakahira, congratulations on your graduation.
You're a graduate from a prestigious university in April.
Your teacher is very proud of you.
It's all thanks to your guidance.
Thank you very much.
But...
Nakahira, the top student of my high school,
said,
I'm worried about you going to college.
I see.
I have a lot of things to tell you before I go to college.
Why don't you come to my house today?
Your house?
There are a lot of bad temptations at college.
I want to talk to you about that.
Okay.
This is my teacher's address and contact information.
I'll pick you up when I get close.
Call me.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Come in.
Sit down.
Come on.
Are you nervous?
Yes.
Is this the first time you've been in a woman's room?
I've never been in a woman's room before.
I knew it.
I'm sorry.
I'm worried about you.
What?
You're still a virgin, aren't you?
No.
That's good.
There are a lot of temptations at college.
I've seen a lot of examples where a pure and excellent girl like you goes crazy as soon as she goes to college.
So...
Before you go to college...
I want you to know a woman...
because this is your last class.
Teacher.
Yes.
Is this your first kiss?
It's good.
By any chance...
Did you just kiss me?
Don't hide it.
I'm embarrassed.
Did you leave me something?
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
I'm embarrassed.
You've never experienced anything like this before, have you?
I told you.
I want you to know a woman.
That's great.
It's good.
I'm glad you're so happy.
Teacher.
Lie down.
I'm sorry.
That's great.
It's hot.
How do you feel in your mouth?
How do you feel?
It's hot.
Teacher, don't do that.
Don't do that.
It's hot.
Did you feel good?
I don't know.
You're still big.
I just told you.
You're still hard.
It feels good.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm going to sweat again.
Again?
It's okay.
Let me see.
That's great.
It's hot.
You're sweating a lot again.
Let me see.
That's great.
Are you shaking?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Nakahira-kun.
Yes?
If you say it with your mouth and hands, you can't say you know a woman.
Is that so?
I'll tell you more.
Look at me.
You've never seen a woman naked before, have you?
Yes.
That's great.
Just look at me.
What should I do?
You can do whatever you want to do.
For example, something like this.
You've been standing like this for a long time.
That's cute.
Touch me.
It's soft.
What kind of boobs do you like?
I don't know.
Do you like boobs?
Yes.
What do you want to do with this big boob?
I want to lick it.
Okay.
I didn't expect that.
You lick me well.
I'm sorry.
Did you...
Did you watch a lot of my videos?
Yes.
Really?
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
Doctor.
You've become a pervert.
Don't you want to see what's going on now?
It's warm.
Do you want me to help you?
Yes.
Okay.
Come closer.
It's close.
Touch me.
Lick me.
Check me.
It's soft.
It tickles.
Is that so?
Did you do it on purpose?
I'm sorry.
I don't think so.
I can't.
Please.
Lick my tongue gently.
Sometimes I stop your tongue.
Lick my tongue.
That's right.
Good.
Keep going.
That's great.
Touch me.
Check me.
It tickles.
How do you feel?
It's warm.
Right?
It tickles.
Lick my tongue gently.
Lick my tongue.
Is that so?
Yes.
It tickles.
Touch me.
Yes.
That's right.
It tickles.
I should feel it at the same time.
Do you know what I mean?
Yes.
It tickles.
Ah!
Ah! I'm going to fall!
Help!
Ah!
Wow!
You're shaking.
Ah!
When a woman cries,
You know what happens inside, right?
Wow!
I'm sorry I'm making you feel better.
No, no.
Come here.
Yes.
Ah!
Mmm...
Ahh...
I know you were really excited while licking my belly and putting your fingers in my mouth.
This juice is really salty.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Mmm...
Ahh...
Oh, no.
Hmm?
It's coming out.
Mmm...
Oh, no.
Ahh...
Mmm...
Ouch...
Mmm.
Oh.
Hmm.
Mmm.
Oh.
Ah!
Did it come out again?
Give me the last one.
You're amazing.
You don't seem to be getting smaller at all.
Hey.
Yes?
Do you want me to put it in your ear?
Yes.
Is it okay?
I'm glad.
I'll teach you how to do it.
Thank you.
Look at me.
Yes.
I'm going in.
It's all in.
Yes.
It's warm.
I'll move slowly at first.
Yes.
What's wrong?
It comes out soon.
I'll move a little faster.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Ah!
I can feel your passion.
But it's not like this.
Yes.
Ah!
I can feel your energy.
I can do it as it is.
Ah!
Yes.
How about rubbing it like this?
Something hits me.
Yes.
Ah!
When the position changes,
The place to hit also changes.
Ah!
It feels good in many places.
Yes.
Ah!
Oh!
Rub my bias.
Yes.
Ah!
It's all right.
Can you sit a little deeper?
Yes.
I'm going to sleep.
Let's go again.
Go to your favorite time.
I'm going to sleep.
Come here.
You can do it, can't you?
Next time, move yourself.
I'm going to sleep.
From behind.
Can you put it in properly?
Make sure you put it in.
Slowly.
There.
I'm going to sleep.
Don't you know where to go?
Not really.
Close your legs.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm moving to support you.
I won't move.
Do it like you're doing now.
It feels good.
I'm getting used to it.
Does it feel that good?
That's good.
I'm going to sleep.
Make yourself feel good.
Don't move yet.
Keep going.
I think I can do it a little more.
I'm going to sleep.
Can you do your best?
There.
It feels good.
I'm getting used to it.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to clean your bed.
Please clean my bed.
I'm going to sleep.
Why are you getting better so soon?
I'm sorry.
If I see you like this, I'll want to do it more.
How do you feel?
It's very good.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm sleeping.
You can put out a lot.
You can put it out.
Ouch!
Apahiro...
Aren't you a good daughter?
I do have a misunderstanding
I think he needs some time
Are you sure?
She's only pregnant
What seems to be the problem?
Please, do more.
You did it from the back, but this time from the front.
Can you do it?
Yes.
You did a good job earlier.
It's a little awkward, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
It's like a woman's forehead is facing her belly button.
It feels good.
You did a good job.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Please stay in the doctor's office.
It feels good.
Don't leave yet.
Please stay in the doctor's office.
It feels good.
Are you sleepy?
I'm sleepy.
Do you know a little about women?
Let's take a break.
You're tired, aren't you?
I'm sorry.
I wanted to make it with something, but I could only make this.
No, it looks delicious.
Please eat.
Thank you.
It looks delicious.
It's delicious.
Really?
I'm glad.
It's really delicious.
There's more, so you can exchange it.
Yes.
It's delicious.
It's spicy and delicious.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Hey.
I'm eating curry now.
When I saw you eating deliciously, I wanted to prank you.
Prank?
Oh.
You can eat curry.
I can't eat curry.
Why?
I'm not eating curry.
I'm eating your penis.
What?
Oh.
Hey.
I'm still eating curry.
Oh.
I want to eat your penis more than curry.
Is it okay?
It's not delicious at all.
What are you talking about? It's delicious.
Oh.
It's getting bigger.
The bigger the penis, the more delicious it is.
Is that so?
Oh.
It's delicious.
It's amazing.
Oh.
It feels good.
Do you feel good in your boobs?
Oh.
It's so good.
Curry was spicy, but boobs are sweet.
What are you talking about?
Oh.
Did you have time to say that kind of joke?
I'm so happy.
Oh.
It's so good.
Teto.
Oh.
It's so good.
Teto.
Yes.
Let me see your mouth.
Oh.
Aw.
Ew...
Ugh...
Rrr.
You're out.
Alright, so what do I write here?
Bitter!
You don't feel like writing any more?
I'm not a good brother.
I'm sorry.
But it's not fair that you always feel good first.
You're not a virgin anymore.
You have to be a man who can make women happy.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Get up.
Yes.
It feels good.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to put my dick in there.
Yes.
I have to make it wet.
I can't do it until I become a virgin.
It feels good.
I'm going to put my dick in there.
Yes.
It feels good.
It's a little tight to put my dick in there.
Yes.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I want to do it more.
What's wrong?
It's hot.
You want to do it, don't you?
Yes.
Keep doing it.
I can do it.
It hurts.
I can't do it yet.
I can't do it.
It hurts.
Let's sleep more.
Yes.
I want to sleep.
It hurts.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It hurts.
Do you want to sleep?
Yes.
It's hot.
It's overflowing.
It's pure white.
It's amazing.
It hurts.
Let's feel good together.
I can't do it.
We were having a meal.
We were.
It's cold.
Let's have a meal.
Yes.
Let's continue later.
What's wrong?
I want to pee.
I see.
Did you wake up because you want to pee?
Do you want to pee?
Yes.
I want to pee.
Do you want to pee?
Open your stomach.
Why are you so stiff?
Because I want to pee.
Do you get stiff when you want to pee?
Yes.
Do you get stiff like this?
I've never seen anyone so stiff when they go to a hotel.
Yes.
You can't pee if you're so stiff, can you?
Hold here by yourself.
I'm going to pee.
Are you going to pee?
Really?
Yes.
Ah.
Do you want to pee here?
No.
Why?
Because it's the entrance.
Do you want to pee?
I'm going to pee.
What?
I feel good.
Do you want to pee here?
Yes.
Which do you want to pee?
I want to pee.
Wow.
You pee so fast.
Do you feel good?
I need to go to the bathroom.
Yes.
Wow.
Do you want to pee?
Yes.
Come here.
Slowly.
A few days later.
You are so young.
You grew up so much in such a short time.
I'm sorry.
It's OK.
You don't fall down even if I touch you.
You are great.
You have a lot of hair.
But you have a lot of hair.
Huh?
You don't get up.
Did you get up?
What are you doing?
Good morning.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Why?
When I wake up, I see you like this.
You are great.
Because it's morning.
Well, teacher.
Yes.
I feel good.
You are great.
I feel like I'm going to puke.
Are you going to puke?
It's OK.
Let it out as it is.
You are great.
Look at you.
You have a lot of hair from the morning.
Did you feel good?
Yes.
But my head still hurts.
My head still hurts.
Let it out as it is.
Let it out.
I feel good when you open your stomach.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It was great.
I'm going to sleep again soon.
It feels good.
Are you going to sleep?
I'm going to sleep.
Okay.
It's hot.
You've been very energetic since this morning.
You're still big.
Do you want to do it again?
Yes.
You can do it, can't you?
This is my manko.
This is your manko.
Does it feel good?
It still tickles a little.
Does it tickle?
I'll move it slowly.
It feels good.
Does it tickle?
You're amazing.
It feels good.
It tickles.
Do you want to do it again?
You can do it again.
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep again.
It's okay.
Wake up.
I can do it.
You're amazing.
It tickles.
You're in my manko.
I was nervous.
It tickles.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Let's have breakfast together.
It tickles.
Do you want to do it again?
Help me.
It tickles.
Wake up.
It's okay.
I'm going to sleep again.
Help me.
It tickles.
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep again.
I love you.
It's okay.
It tickles.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
Do you want to sleep?
Do you want me to kiss you?
I can't stand it.
I'm going to kiss you.
It tickles.
I'm sorry.
You can still do it, right?
Yes.
Not only me.
Do you want me to kiss you?
Yes.
It tickles.
It feels good.
Don't stop me.
It tickles.
Let me go to the doctor.
Good morning.
What did you say?
Yes.
I'm ready.
You know the station, right?
Yes.
I'll send you my address again.
About 5 or 6 boxes of cardboard.
Do you have furniture over there?
Yes.
But I want to bring only the washing machine.
The washing machine is heavy.
I don't want to carry it.
Can you carry it?
Yes.
I can't carry it alone.
Really?
It's heavy.
Yes.
What?
I'm drinking water.
Are you drinking water?
Yes.
You make a strange sound.
I don't make a strange sound.
I'm done.
Do you have something to do?
I just wanted to talk about moving.
I see.
If you don't have a problem, I'll do it.
What's wrong?
I didn't do anything.
I can't hear your voice.
Because I just woke up.
You have a bad breath.
What?
Do you have a problem?
Maybe.
You can't move suddenly.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
No.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
No.
What?
I'm fine.
I don't know.
Grilled meat.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
I'm alone.
I'm going to sleep again.
I'm going to sleep.
What?
I don't know.
I'll tell you next time.
Okay.
If you're out, let's meet up.
I'll hang up the phone.
Wait.
No.
Are you going out again?
What?
I feel good.
Did you want me to come?
No.
I said no.
You said no.
Why did you say no?
I'm going to sleep.
I feel good.
Don't say that.
I'm on the phone with my friend.
You have to say something.
Okay.
I'll hang up the phone again.
Let me hang up the phone.
Ai.
I feel good.
I'm not done yet.
Okay.
Can you make me feel good?
Make me feel good.
Okay.
I feel good.
Use your fingers.
Okay.
I feel good.
Ai.
Use your fingers.
I'm not done yet.
Ai.
I feel good.
Oh, it feels great
Two, one...
Hey!
I got more like him.
It's so good!
It's so good.
Look at this.
It's in my neck.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
I can do it many times.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
It's still hard.
Please lean on my back.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
I want to do it more.
I can't stop.
I'm sorry.
It feels so good.
It's so good.
I'm slipping.
It feels so good.
I want to do it more.
I'm slipping.
Let me out.
Let me out in your arms.
It hurts.
It's so good.
I can't stop.
I'll make you beautiful.
Make me beautiful, too.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
Over there.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
I want to live with you.
I want to be with you.
I can't take it anymore.
It's so good.
We were together at the end.
Yes.
Did you feel good?
I felt so good, too.
That's all for today.
Yes.
Nakahira.
Good luck in college.
Yes.
Thank you.
After that, Nakahira came to take my class.
My class is more important than any other famous teacher's class.
It felt so good.
That's all for today.
It's the teacher's job to teach until the students are satisfied.
This relationship is not over yet.