Yes, please.
Sakura-kun.
Yes?
I'm done here, so please clean up.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you.
Um...
Is Sakurai-san...
having...
a tea break today?
What?
What are you talking about?
Well...
I didn't get a reply from Panty,
so I was wondering if that was the case.
That's disgusting.
Do you really say things like that?
Please stop.
Yes.
Hey.
Can you stay at my place tonight?
Are you going to stay?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Of course.
It's been a while.
I know.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll make you a cup of coffee.
Really?
I'll make it.
That's fine.
Thank you.
Damn it.
I always make a fool of myself.
If I drink this...
I'll make you a cup of coffee.
Can I go to the bathroom?
Okay.
I'll wait here.
Thank you.
Shit.
I don't like it.
It's sticky.
I can't take it off.
What should I do?
I don't like it.
Aya.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Let's go.
You need to go to the bathroom.
I'm fine.
Let's get ready.
I'll cook for you again.
I'm happy.
I love your cooking.
You like my cooking?
I made a mistake.
I'm happy.
I love your cooking.
By the way, you're going to take a bath, aren't you?
Yes.
I'll prepare a bath for you.
Thank you.
I'll take a bath while you're cooking.
I'm happy.
I'm going to take a look at the contents of the box.
When I look for a hidden box, there's no boxes with
What is it?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I took a bath.
I'll be right back.
I'll get ready while you take a bath.
Thank you.
I'm going to take a bath.
Ta-da!
How is it?
It looks delicious.
I prepared this for you.
I love crab.
This is a good crab.
It looks really delicious.
Cheers!
Which one should I eat first?
Let's eat.
Don't hesitate to eat.
Try this.
That's right.
How is it?
It's delicious.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Don't hesitate to eat.
It's delicious.
It wasn't delicious.
It's difficult.
It was delicious.
Can I eat one more?
Yes.
It's difficult to eat crab.
How can I eat crab?
Can you help me?
You are a man.
Thank you.
You are good at peeling crab.
I'm not good at it.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
I'm going to eat this.
Go ahead.
It's hot.
I can't eat this.
What are you doing?
I can't eat this well.
It's not difficult to eat.
Crab is delicious.
It's delicious, isn't it?
There are still a lot of crab.
Can I eat this?
Yes.
Thank you.
It was fun.
I didn't think it would end like this.
Thank you.
It was fun.
Let's watch a movie.
I can't watch a movie today.
Why?
It's dangerous.
You don't have a gun, do you?
I don't have a gun.
I'm fine.
I'll shoot you with my mouth.
Can you bear it?
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I feel good, too.
I feel good.
I feel better.
My body is shaking.
I'm glad.
Don't look at me like that.
What are you talking about?
You're looking at me, aren't you?
I feel better.
It's amazing.
I'm fine.
I'm so excited!
Thank you so much!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, on, on, injoked
me
wel
b
Hmm...
Oh, ah...
Ah...
Oh...
Aah...
Ah...
Aaarooo
Oh, ahh...
Oh, ooh...
Hey...!
Oh...
Oh, oh...
Oh, my God.
I'm going to die.
You've had a lot.
You may have been more excited than usual.
Did you feel good?
Yeah, I felt good.
I'm glad.
I mean,
You really wanted to meet her, didn't you?
What did you do?
You screamed a lot.
I don't know.
I think I've changed.
Is that so?
Do you mean you've become sensitive?
Well, maybe.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God
I don't know why, but I can't help but cry when I think about it.
Feels good!
......
It's painful....
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Hmm
Yeah
At
some point
E
Old man.....
It's so hot.
What is this poison?
What is this?
I'm sorry.
You were drinking?
Yes.
I didn't want to wake you up.
It's hard to work on a day off.
Yes. I'm holding back my business trip, so I don't have time to get ready for work.
Thank you for your hard work.
Let me know if there's anything I can do.
Thank you.
I'm going.
Have a good day.
Thank you.
What is this?
It's bitter.
It's dirty.
I don't like it.
What is this?
Am I so greedy?
It's an alien.
What is this?
It's warm.
It's very hard.
What is this?
I'm getting sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
It's warm.
It's really hard.
What is this?
It's getting hotter and hotter.
What are you doing?
I can't stand it.
Boss.
You always make me angry.
What are you talking about?
I'm not feeling well today.
I have a fever.
Can I go home?
I have a stomachache.
Why are you avoiding me?
You always make me angry.
What is this?
I have to take care of you as a company.
I have to check with the Ministry of Health and Welfare.
If you have any problems, please let me know.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Get back to work.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Thank you.
Can this make it back online?
Yes, definitely.
Yes.
Can you put your name on it?
I'm going to show you how to do it.
What happened to you?
This must be a dream.
We're fine.
I'm going to show you how to make it.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong, Sakurai? Are you not feeling well?
I'm sorry. I'm not feeling well either.
I'll go upstairs first.
Oh, I see.
Excuse me.
Where are you now?
How are you doing?
You've been acting strange lately.
What's wrong?
Maybe I'm working too hard.
Is that so?
I'm not working too hard.
I see.
Have you been eating?
Yes, I have.
I'm worried about you.
Thank you for worrying about me.
I want to see you right now, but I can't.
I know.
I can't see you right now.
I'm lonely.
I'm lonely too.
I really want to see you.
I'm fine when I see you at times like this.
I've been working so hard lately.
I'm not in a good mood.
I'm having a hard time.
I know.
Are you feeling well?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm fine, but...
I need someone by my side.
I know.
I'm really lonely.
Are you lonely?
Yes.
I was lonely.
I'm lonely when I'm alone.
What's wrong?
When I heard your voice, I felt lonely.
Really?
Do you miss me so much?
Yes.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
I know.
What's wrong?
When I heard your voice, I felt lonely.
Really?
You have something in your pants.
You're making a lot of noise.
You say the same thing as me.
What?
Because...
I'm sweating a lot.
You're making a lot of noise.
That's amazing.
Do you feel that way?
It's strange.
My body is sensitive.
Is that so?
I don't know why.
Are you lonely and sensitive?
I haven't seen you for a long time.
Where are you now?
I don't feel anything.
Really.
Is it because of your voice?
Do you feel that way?
I was excited when I heard your voice.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
What's going on?
What?
I'm ready.
Let me hear your voice.
It's a good voice.
I'm ready.
I'm sorry.
I got a call from the company.
No way.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Call me when you're done.
Okay.
I'm going to the bathroom.
See you later.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Why does it feel good?
I don't know what to do with myself.
I don't know what to do.
Why do I suddenly have a stomachache?
What should I do?
What?
Something is rubbing against me.
Again?
What should I do?
What?
Everything is fine.
I don't want to see this.
omg
come again
wait
my ab noise
i smell
it
i don't just go
jaki
like
the
i want to
open
my
door
i want to
What should I do?
Ai-kun!
Why are you doing this to me?
What should I do?
It feels so good!
Ai-kun!
What should I do?
My body feels so good!
It tickles!
It's getting bigger and bigger!
It's getting hotter!
Mommy?
What should I do?
I'm sorry. I was embarrassed earlier.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Sakurai.
You have a tea bag in your room.
What?