It's a little rotten.
That's enough.
And what about Taichi?
I asked him but he's not answering.
You're late!
It'll be fine. Of course he'll be late.
Do you want bread for breakfast tomorrow?
What would I make with just cucumbers?
Here, I made him a cucumber abura-age yesterday.
But it's thin...
And the Davao?
I only have cucumbers.
Taichi, do you want to eat bread tomorrow?
I don't need it.
Don't worry about it.
I'm just embarrassed to have a mother suddenly.
I'm home.
Izumi, that's my item.
You're stupid.
By the way, isn't Mr. Chidami here today?
I don't know. Maybe he went shopping.
He should be back by now.
Why do you hate him so much?
Did he do something bad to you?
He didn't do anything bad to me.
Then you should be normal.
What?
We live together.
It's better to be comfortable with each other.
You're an adult.
You're too childish.
By the way, what's going on with your mother at school?
Who are you talking about?
I'm talking about Ryoko.
She checks your homework.
She folds your gym clothes.
She's like your mother.
I'm not your mother.
Don't be angry.
What do you think of Ryoko?
Maybe I like her.
I want to be honest with her.
She has a good personality.
She thinks of me as a woman.
I'm sorry.
I was going to turn the washing machine.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
That's mine.
Wait.
Give me a break.
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
Don't do that.
It's okay if it's just my mouth.
That's not the problem.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Don't do that.
It's hot.
Don't tell my father.
I won't tell him.
Don't do that.
It's hot.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good, but...
It's hot.
Hang in there.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's big and hard.
It's hot.
It's so big.
I want to put it in.
But we're parents.
So I can't.
It's hot.
It's a great day.
It's getting bigger.
It feels good.
It's hot.
You're so kind.
You know,
Can you stop doing this?
Can you stand it?
Yes, I can.
Can you stop doing this?
I'm going.
See you.
Aichi.
Can I have dinner with fish?
I don't need it today.
I'm going to Izumi's house.
I'm not saying I don't like your cooking.
I was just talking to Izumi.
Really?
Yes.
Can you stand it?
No, I can't.
Did you get excited because I came?
No, I didn't.
I told you to be patient.
I'm patient.
You have a lot of earwax.
It's only today.
That's great.
You have a lot of earwax.
What should I do?
Ah, shh...
Don't do that...
What are you doing?
It's so big.
Ah, it's hot.
It's hot.
Hmm...
It's so big.
It's so sensitive.
It's so hot.
It's hot.
Ah...
Don't do that.
It's hot.
Ah...
Release tension
Itchy
Your toe is moving
Very nice
That's pleasant...
It's okay.
It's so hot.
Taichi.
Yes?
Have you ever had sex with a woman?
Just today.
It's so hot.
I'm sorry.
Let me see your tongue.
More.
It's so hot.
Why are you so nervous?
Why are you so excited?
I'm so excited.
Is this your first time?
Hey.
Do you want to see my body?
What?
Let me take it off.
Do you want me to push you?
Do you want me to take this off?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Up.
Up?
Yes.
Can I pull you more?
Can I?
Have you ever touched your boobs?
No.
No?
I'm sorry.
Slowly.
Why?
Is that so?
It's so big.
It's soft.
Is it soft?
Yes.
It's soft.
It's so hot.
Put your tongue out.
Tongue?
Eye.
Use your tongue.
Ah, it feels good.
Good job.
The other side.
Ah, it's good.
Wow, you're good.
Do you want me to do something better?
More?
More.
Do you think so?
What do you mean?
Does it feel good?
I'll show you something good.
Have you seen this before?
No, it's my first time.
Your first time?
Yes.
This is the eardrum.
It has a great shape.
Can you look closer?
Can I look closer?
Yes, yes, yes.
Can you see it?
Wow.
It's pink.
This is the clitoris.
This is the hole.
It's wet.
Give me your hand.
Ah, it's good.
Try putting it in your nose.
Slowly.
Put it in.
Put it out.
Wow.
How is it?
It's very warm.
Is it warm?
Yes.
It's pressed.
It feels good.
Wow.
Don't push it too hard.
Do it slowly.
Slowly.
Yes.
You're good.
This is good.
It feels good.
My back is moving.
It's moving.
It feels good.
Wow.
You're good.
It feels good.
Really.
Ah.
I want to sleep.
Next.
My shoulders are getting bigger.
Really.
You're very sensitive, Tachi-kun.
It's good.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Is it because your tip of the tongue is weak?
Don't lick your tip of the tongue.
I know because you're licking your tip of the tongue.
It's getting bigger.
Wow.
It's amazing.
It's good.
You're good.
It feels good.
It's good.
Don't lick your tongue.
You're going to lick your tongue from now on, right?
No.
I don't want to lick my tongue.
It's really not good.
I know.
I don't want to lick my tongue.
It's good.
You're very sensitive.
Then I'll put it in.
Do you understand?
I'll put it in here.
There?
Here.
Here?
Huh?
A little more.
A little lower.
Lower?
That's not it.
It's a little difficult.
I can't get in.
It's here.
A little more.
A little more to the right.
It's hot.
Is it difficult?
I don't know.
I'll put it in for you.
What should I do?
Lie down next to me.
Ah.
Does it feel good?
How do you feel?
What's going on in there?
Ah.
What's this?
Oh, my God.
Did it come out?
It's throbbing.
Ah.
That's a lot.
You should say,
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
But you still want to do it, right?
I want to do it.
What do you think?
You can still do it.
You still can do it.
Ah, I can.
Ah.
Do you get it now?
You get it now, right?
Yes.
I'll give it a try.
Do your best.
It's here.
Here?
Yes, slowly.
Yes.
Ah!
Try moving it slowly.
Slowly.
Move it back and forth.
Yes.
Ah!
Yes, very good.
Yes.
Ah!
Try moving it as you like.
Yes.
Ah!
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Taichi, you're doing well.
Ah!
It feels good, right?
Yes.
Ah!
You have to say
you'll do it next time.
Yes.
Ah!
It feels good.
Yes.
Do it while kissing.
Ah!
Put your tongue out.
Oh!
Ah!
Are you okay?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Move your body more.
It feels good.
Don't stop.
I want to do more.
It feels good.
More, more, more.
More.
I want to do more.
More, more.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
What?
More, more.
It feels good.
Don't stop.
It's too fast.
It feels good.
It's hot.
He's gone.
It's too fast.
I have to go.
Are you going?
You don't have to hurry.
I have to go.
It's just for today.
I know.
What should we do?
We have no choice.
Let's pray.
TEMPTATION
This isn't M. Isn't it M?
TEMPTATION?
That's right.
TEMPTATION
Wait, what are you doing?
You asked me to do it, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
What are you doing?
You're lying.
You two get along well.
Hey, why don't the three of us go somewhere?
What do you mean?
I want to go on a family trip.
I'm sorry I haven't been able to take you anywhere.
I'm sorry. I'll never do it again.
What?
I'm going to study over there.
Call me if you know where to go.
Okay.
TEMPTATION
By the way, where do you want to go?
Me?
Onsen...
I don't think Aichi can enjoy it.
Where should I go?
Where do you want to go?
Is onsen a bad idea?
I don't think so.
Isn't there a natural place?
Like a boat or something?
There's a kudai.
I see.
You want to go to onsen, don't you?
I want to go to onsen.
There are many places to relax.
I think it's near here.
I see.
Oh.
I'm going to Saitama.
What?
Isn't it close?
Yes, it is.
Oh, that's why you can go there so soon.
Yes.
It's about an hour and a half on foot.
I see.
But I want to experience the feeling of traveling.
I want to travel a little more.
How about going to Yamanashi?
But isn't Yamanashi a place where you can buy fruits?
Like grapes.
What about hot springs?
There are hot springs.
There are, right?
But I don't go there often.
I see.
I want to go there.
I want to eat something.
I see.
How about grapes?
Oh, I like grapes.
Then, let's go to Yamanashi.
Yamanashi.
But I'm a little depressed now.
Let's walk a little more.
How about going to Nagano?
Oh, that's a good idea.
That's a good idea.
Nagano.
Kanto is quite far from here.
It's quite far from here.
Let's walk a little more.
Oh, we flew all of a sudden.
I want to go there.
Do you want to go there?
But it will be an airplane.
I want to go to Shinkansen.
Oh, Shinkansen.
That's a good idea.
Then, let's go to Hachinohe.
Hachinohe.
Hachinohe?
Kyunohe?
Jyunohe?
Have you ever heard of Kyunohe?
No, I haven't.
Is that a mistake?
Have you ever heard of Ichinohe?
Is it from 1 to 8?
I don't think so.
But isn't it 4?
Isn't it okay to have 4?
Like bad luck.
No, it should be 4 of happiness.
Isn't that just a four-leaf clover?
What's that?
It's a four-leaf clover of happiness.
Oh.
It's usually a four-leaf clover.
I don't think so.
It's a little far from here.
Is it better to be a little closer?
On the contrary, it's warm.
How about Kyushu?
Oh, that's good.
How about Shikoku?
The food is delicious.
But isn't there a hot spring over there?
No, there should be.
Is Beppu over there?
Where is it?
Isn't Beppu hot spring better?
What prefecture?
Isn't it Oita prefecture?
Oh.
It's a good prefecture.
It's very famous.
Let's go to Beppu.
But in the Kanto region, there is a place called Gunma.
Gunma.
Let's look for it.
Kusatsu, Kusatsu.
The inn is in a pinch.
There aren't many places to play in the hot springs.
I want a place to play.
I want to play in Taichi.
Where should we go?
I don't think there is a place to play in Osaka.
I think Hakone is a good place.
Hakone?
That's a good place.
It's a little rusty.
Is it rusty?
Isn't that Atami?
Is that Atami?
I think it's Atami.
What is Hakone?
It's a museum.
Where is the museum?
Museum?
Wait a minute.
Museum.
Isn't this Gunma?
It's Gunma.
There aren't many places to play in the mountains.
It's not a bad thing to do it alone.
It's a bad idea.
Can't Taichi see that?
He can enjoy it.
That depends on how you look at it.
It's like a museum.
Is it like a museum?
What is this museum?
It's a toy museum.
Toy museum?
It looks fun.
There is also an experience section.
Let's look around here.
There are Gunma and Ibaraki.
Is this okay?
You can experience Kirie.
That's good.
It looks like it's close to a hotel.
Taichi will enjoy it.
This is good.
The hot spring is small.
Is a hot spring like a family bath good?
A family bath is good.
Let's go there.
The restroom is gorgeous.
There is a room that these girls will like.
This is a science fiction style room.
I see.
This room seems quite spacious.
But it doesn't have to be that spacious.
If it's a big room...
I heard that you can get skin care.
Skin care?
Yes.
That's nice.
I heard that your skin will get whiter.
What?
If it gets whiter than this...
What should I do?
Your skin might get tanned.
You might not be able to see me.
That's a good thing.
It's interesting.
Do you want a beard effect?
Of course I do.
I see.
I think this area is good.
What should I do?
I should get a beard effect.
Do you have any particular meal you want to eat?
I want to eat fish.
Fish?
I don't know.
I want to eat sardines.
Sardines?
This is good.
Where is the bathroom?
Bathroom?
I don't know if it will take a long time.
I don't think so.
I hope it won't take too long.
This is good.
Do you want to go to the bathroom?
I don't think so.
This is good.
By the way, what's wrong?
Nothing.
I heard that bears can eat this.
Bears?
Bears.
It looks smelly.
Is it smelly?
It looks like a bear.
That's not good.
Bears are not good.
Wild boars are the same.
This is good.
Where is this?
This is a bear.
This is good.
This is not good.
Do you think so?
Fluffy in the nose.
By the way, TAICHI wouldn't think so.
This is not good.
That's okay.
Do you put this here?
It's a little low down.
This is dangerous.
The view from the top of the mountain is beautiful, isn't it?
Well, I'll take this one.
Oh, but it's a little hard to make a reservation here.
Oh, really?
I wonder if it's the same place as before.
The reservation for the previous place is still open.
I see.
You can experience the previous place, too.
Oh, I see.
But the current season is a little hard to make a reservation.
Oh, that might be better.
I think it's better to make a reservation for the next three years or so.
Then it's easier to make a reservation.
That's true.
This week and next week.
Let's make a reservation for the third year.
Oh, it's open.
Are you going to take this?
I'll take it.
Then I'll take it.
Well, I wonder if I can take this.
Oh, I see.
I can choose what to eat.
Japanese food or Western food?
Oh, Italian food.
I don't like Italian food.
No, it's not Italian.
Then...
Japanese food?
Do you want Japanese food?
Yeah, I like Japanese food.
Okay, Japanese food.
Okay, I'll make a reservation for Japanese food.
And I heard there's a hot spring.
I can make a reservation.
I heard I can make a reservation.
I'd like to make a reservation.
But I don't have time.
What time is good?
What time is good? About 7 o'clock?
About 7 o'clock?
If it's open at 7 o'clock...
Oh, it's not open.
Oh, it's open?
Yeah.
And I heard I can choose the size of the room.
Is it better to be wide?
Yeah, it's better to be wide.
Oh, it's about 10.
I'll take this.
If I put it like this...
And...
Is this Genku?
It's painful.
Then I'll choose Genku.
Genku is...
Oh, it's this one.
By the way, what's wrong?
Oh, it's okay. It's nothing.
I can choose the check-in time.
What time is good?
Is it okay to make a reservation with this?
10 o'clock...
5 o'clock...
I'll make a reservation at 5 o'clock.
Okay.
3 o'clock...
10 o'clock...
5 o'clock...
Okay.
Taichi.
Are you studying?
It's too difficult. I'm tired.
What? Do you want me to see it?
Oh...
But I don't know what this is.
What's this?
The handwriting is dirty.
I think so.
What's this?
What are you doing?
Stop it.
You don't have to be patient.
I'm not patient. What are you doing?
You don't have to be shy.
I'm not shy.
Stop it.
I said stop it.
Why?
A girl in my class asked me out today.
I want to go out with her.
Why?
You said you like me, didn't you?
When did I say that?
I'm sorry.
I heard you talking to Izumi.
Look.
You said you wanted to go out with me.
Oh, that.
It's not about you.
What?
It's about my classmate, Yoko.
It's about your misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
Yes.
So, I can't go out with you.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm home.
Anonymous
COVID-19
Can I help you?
Hello
Taichi ?
Mr. Azuro suddenly disappeared
I'm sorry, but can you eat it by yourself?
By the way...
You don't want to be alone with me, do you?
I'll go home in the morning.
Coco is approaching the kitten
I let him sleep on the scratches.
It seems that Shima is sad because bad hair grew on her face.
I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to die if I don't do something about it.
I'm going to die if I don't do something about it.
I feel like I'm going to die if I don't do something about it.
There, there's something wrong.
I don't know why, but I feel like I'm going to die if I don't do something about it.
You have a nice body, don't you.
Let's have breakfast now
Ah, over there
Ah, that feels good
Hum, Hum, Hmm.
I can't take it anymore.
Oh, my God.
I'm like a dog.
You're so cute.
Give me your mouth.
No tongue.
I can't take it anymore.
Oh, my God.
Let me see.
I can't take it anymore.
You're so cute.
You're like a skeleton.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm so sensitive.
You're like a skeleton.
You'll be fine.
What's wrong?
I can't take it anymore.
Don't do that.
Don't do that until I say so.
I can't take it anymore.
You're so sensitive.
Don't do that.
You're like a skeleton.
You're so sensitive.
I can't take it anymore.
Don't do that.
You're so sensitive.
You're drooling.
I can't take it anymore.
What's wrong?
You can't take it anymore?
I can't take it anymore.
I'm so sorry.
I want to go, but I can't.
I'm not satisfied.
You're so sensitive.
I can't take it anymore.
I want to go, but I can't.
Look at me.
You're so sensitive.
I want to go, but I can't.
Can I go in?
I can't take it anymore.
It's so hard.
What's this?
I'm getting bigger.
Can you see me?
Yes.
Look at me.
I'm so sweaty.
I feel so bad.
What's this?
How do you feel?
It's so good.
It's so hot.
My back hurts.
It's so good.
It's getting more and more sweaty.
It's so hot.
It's so good.
It feels good.
Ah
From behind
Put it in
Ah, it feels good
Look
It's amazing
I'll put it in
Ah
It's amazing
Ah, it's here
Ah
Slowly
Like this
Ah
Bang, bang, bang
It feels good
Ah
It's getting bigger
Ah, it feels good
More, more
More
Ah
More, more
Ah, it's amazing
Ah
Ah, it feels good
Look
I'll clean it up
Give it to me
It's okay
Ah
Like this
It's hot.
I can still see it.
It's embarrassing.
It's hot.
If you do this, you won't be able to stand it anymore.
You're getting bigger.
What are you going to do?
What do you want to do?
The rest of your face is coming out.
It's hot.
You're getting weird.
That's right.
You're looking at my face.
Open your eyes and look at my face.
What are you doing?
You're going to go again?
I just got this skeleton.
You can't do that.
You can't?
I want to do it again.
You want to do it again, don't you?
I know.
Not yet.
I need you to clean my skeleton.
It's hard, isn't it?
Put your tongue out.
You look happy.
It feels good.
You're sucking up a lot of your blood.
Lick it properly, please.
I'll lick your buttock.
Stretch your tongue out.
You're good at that.
It's so itchy!
I want to lick you more!
More! More!
Ah! Ah! Ah! It feels so good!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
No!
It feels so good!
What are you doing?
I can't?
Then I'll do something better for you.
Something better?
Yes, something better.
Raise your hips.
Look.
There's a pimple.
You can see it, right?
If you do this,
you'll feel so itchy.
You'll feel so itchy.
Look.
There's a pimple.
I'll do something better for you.
You like the pimple, right?
It's so itchy.
Pimple.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Your boobs are starting to feel good.
Ah! Ah!
Your boobs are rubbing.
Your boobs and pimple are rubbing.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
It feels so good!
Ah! No!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Your boobs are getting bigger again.
Ah! Ah!
I just took them out.
That was close.
Your nipples too.
Ah! Ah!
I want to rub your nipples.
Ah! It feels so good!
Ah! Ah!
It's so slimy.
Your nipples are getting bigger.
Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! It feels so good!
Ah! Ah!
I want to rub your nipples too.
Ah! Your nipples are getting bigger again.
Ah! Ah!
Don't do that.
I want to rub your nipples.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm going to rub your nipples.
I'm going to make you feel better.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Look at your nipples.
Look at them.
Ah!
Ah! It feels so good!
It's amazing!
How is it going in here?
It's amazing.
It's moving.
Ah!
It looks good.
I'm going to rub your nipples.
Ah!
Here, drink up.
Ah! It feels so good!
Ah!
It's amazing.
It's getting bigger again.
How big will it get?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Open your eyes.
Look at my face.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Ah!
It feels good.
Ah! It feels good!
Ah!
It's amazing.
Ah! It tickles!
Ah! It feels so good!
Ah!
Ah! It feels good!
Ah! It's amazing!
Ah!
Ah! It feels so good!
It feels so good!
Ah!
ah
don't fall
you are doing it again
you doing it again
you doing it
you doing you doing
aah
you doing it
ah
ah don't stop
move it
it up
ah
feels good
aaah
ooh
ah
ahh
ahhh
don't
any longer
it's
going
Good boy!
Please work slowly.
Yeah, a bit more!
More!
Good boy!
It feels so good!
Doesn't it feel good?
Aah, it's so hard to shore!
More more!
Do more!
Shake it!
Shake it, shake it!
Does it feel good?
I want you to look at me!
It's so good
Does it feel good?
It's good, isn't it?
I can't stand it.
I'll take it out.
Take it out.
More.
Oh, my God.
Don't take it out.
Take it out.
Oh, my God.
I'll tickle you.
It's still okay, isn't it?
I don't know what to do.
Go to sleep.
I'm going to sleep.
Close your eyes.
I just said it, but it's getting so big again.
It's heavy.
Like a baby.
A lot of boobs.
Breathe in a lot.
Make it feel good.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I can't stand it.
You can't stand it?
Then you don't have to stand it.
I can't stand it.
I knew it.
It feels so good.
Come on, breathe in more.
Drink it.
Breathe in a lot.
How many times do I have to breathe in?
You can breathe in a lot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
That's great.
From now on, I'm your girlfriend.
What about my father?
Your father is your husband.
Taichi is your boyfriend.
Okay.
I did it.
Isn't my build amazing?
Why did you dump Ryoko?
Ryoko was crying.
I'm dating Chinami.
What?
Welcome.
Mizumi.
Thank you for playing with Taichi all the time.
Chinami.
Are you dating Taichi?
I told you it's a secret between us.
You are cute.
I want to be proud of you.
What?
I can't.
Why?
Because Mizumi is here.
You want a reward, don't you?
What?
I can't.
To be continued.