I'm so bored.
I don't have anything to do.
Hello? Mom?
I'm home.
Mom?
I'm free now.
Can you come to my room?
Yes, I'm coming.
Yes, please.
Nice to meet you.
What are you doing here?
I ran out of money.
Money again?
I just gave you money the other day.
I don't have that much money.
I want to go out and play.
I don't have money.
Tell your father.
I want to go to the bathroom.
What?
I don't have money.
I want to go to the bathroom.
I'm stupid.
I don't have money.
If you don't have money,
Mom?
What?
You always do it.
Be quiet.
I don't have enough money.
What?
Please.
I don't have enough money.
What?
What should I do?
Please.
If you don't have money,
let me play with you.
Please.
If you don't have money,
let me play with you.
I'm sorry.
One more time.
Let me play with you.
Please.
What should I do?
My shoulders hurt recently.
My legs are swollen.
If you're good at massage,
I can think about it.
I'm the same age as you.
Please.
I'll massage you.
My legs are swollen.
It feels good.
How do you feel?
It's annoying.
I've never had a massage before.
How do you feel?
I don't know.
I've never had a massage before.
I'm doing my best.
I'm tired.
I want to work.
I want to play.
What's up?
Please work.
I'm in my 30s.
I can't.
Let's get married when we get divorced.
Don't do that.
Don't tell my dad.
I wish I could do something like this.
It feels good.
I want to do this too. I'll be serious.
It's from the hip joint.
It seems that your legs are getting tired.
Don't you think it's erotic?
Are you serious?
Massage me properly.
I've never heard that erotic massage can relax your body.
What did you say?
I'm sure it's true.
Are you serious?
It feels good.
I'll massage your lower back.
It seems that your muscles are getting tired.
You're right.
I have a muscle that supports my spine.
What's that?
It seems that I have a muscle that supports my spine.
Are you serious?
It seems that I have a muscle that supports my spinal column.
I'm stupid, so I can't remember it.
Isn't it amazing?
Where did you learn this word?
I don't know.
It seems that I have a muscle that supports my spinal column.
It seems that I have a muscle that supports my spine.
What's that muscle?
It's a trapezius muscle.
Trapezius muscle?
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
You're really good at it.
Do you need a massage?
It should be a hard work.
Are you sure?
It seems that it's a good sound.
No, it's not.
It's not Gori Gori.
It's Gori Gori.
Does it feel good?
Mom, you're doing well.
It's good.
It's a little crazy.
What? Are you going to do this side, too?
I'll do this side, too.
Thigh, too.
Oh, that's good.
This is good.
The lymph is flowing.
I want to let the lymph flow.
It tickles a little.
Does it hurt if you don't like it?
It tickles.
This side, too?
My hands are in my skirt.
What?
It's not in there.
It's in there.
It's really not in there.
I can't put my feet on it.
It tickles.
Can I give you a mouth massage?
I don't like that place.
Are you going home from work?
Does it smell?
I don't like it.
It tickles.
It's important for your stomach, too.
Warm up your stomach.
Let's purify it.
It tickles.
I'll give you a boob massage.
Does it hurt?
It tickles.
I feel better.
Be quiet.
It tickles.
I'm scared.
It's getting hot.
I'm getting hot.
It tickles.
It's difficult.
Don't move.
It tickles.
Let me take a picture of you.
I don't want to.
Don't move.
What do you want to take a picture of me?
A story?
I'll give you money for the bath.
You don't have to do that.
Don't put me in a strange place.
It's okay.
Look at me.
I don't want to.
I'm posing for you.
I'll take a picture of you.
I don't want to.
I'm posing for you.
Look at me.
I can't do it.
You can do it.
You're so cute.
Why did you marry my father?
My father was cool.
Are you sleepy?
Look at me.
I don't want to.
I'm posing for you.
Look at me.
I don't want to.
Are you still posing for me?
I'm posing for you.
I don't want to.
When I look at you,
I want to tease you.
I have something good for you.
I don't have money.
Did you buy it?
Yes, I bought it.
Isn't it cute?
Do you know what this is?
It's called a rotor.
You have a strong heart.
I have a strong heart.
My nose is twitching.
Don't tease me.
You have a strong heart.
Don't hit me.
I'm sleepy.
Very well...
My heart has dropped...
This is terrible...
My bottom...
ねえ!
あきさんきて!
おいでおいで
おけおけ
あの
ちょっと待って
練師さん
ちゃんとやってね
Oh, my.
I'm so embarrassed.
You can sleep here.
You must be tired.
There is a bed here.
Are you okay now?
Yes, I'm fine.
Did you buy something?
Yes, I did.
I bought it because you gave me money the other day.
Who did you use it for?
This.
I used it for you.
I'm serious.
I didn't use it for anyone.
Only my mother decides to have sex.
Oh, my.
Wait a minute.
It's been a long time.
I feel like I'm going to die.
Oh, my.
Is this your neck?
Yes, it is.
Did you put your own feet on it?
No, I didn't.
I've never seen you like this before.
Stop it.
Don't say that.
I'm sorry.
It's comfortable here, isn't it?
I'm having a period.
You're having a period.
Are you sure?
I'll be gentle.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I'm so excited.
Don't look at me.
It's hot.
I'm tired.
It feels good...
My voice is gone...
I love you...
Why?
I want you to stop...
It feels good...
My stomach is growling...
I'm going to give you a lot of massage...
From the top of the punch...
My punch is getting dirty...
It feels good...
I want to kiss you directly...
I love you...
Let's lick slowly
If you make a loud noise, they'll find out
Okay
Somehow
I'm getting used to it
Kure-chan, look at my face
Don't look at my face
I'll make a loud noise
Ah!
What's this?
My head is...
I'll give you
Kure-chan
Ah!
It feels so good
It's getting bigger
Kure-chan
You're cute
You surprised me
Kure-chan
Amazing
How about here?
Kure-chan
I'm going to give you a gentle massage
Put this.
Delicious.
One more.
Poochoo! Poochoo! Poochoo!
Poochoo!
It looks like you're brushing your teeth.
It's good!
It's amazing!
The juice is...
If you lick your mouth,
the poo will be...
really wet.
It's good!
Look, the poo is wet.
Let me smell it.
It's good!
It smells like the juice.
Let me lick your neck.
It's good!
The poo is hard.
It's hard!
It's really good!
It's good!
Let me...
Do you hear it?
It's hot.
Do you like it here?
I put a lot of salt in it.
Does it feel good?
Is it hot?
It's good!
The golden egg on the right is on top.
Do you like it here?
Do you want to try a deep throat?
What is it?
It's so hot!
It's so hot...
I can't breathe...
My face is so hot...
Do you like it?
It's so hot...
You pinched me.
I want to do it myself.
It's so hot...
I'll do it myself.
What are you filming?
It's so hot...
It's so embarrassing.
But it feels good.
It's so hot...
I want to do it myself.
This is erotic.
It's like you're crazy.
What do you want to say?
It's so hot...
Make me feel good.
Can you do it?
It's so hot...
Do you like this?
I don't know if I'm drooling.
It's so hot...
This feels good.
It's on my underwear.
It's okay.
It's so hot...
My body is so hot.
You can put me into the hot water.
Take a shower.
What are you doing?
It's late, so I made it myself.
Is it hard?
I was about to go.
What?
I'm lonely.
What are you talking about?
I thought you wouldn't come.
If you like it so much, show me more.
What?
Hurry up.
I'm embarrassed.
No, show me your smile.
I'm not smiling.
I don't have a chance to see your smile, so I'm looking forward to it.
Are you going to sleep?
It's embarrassing.
Do you want me to massage your neck?
When I'm with you, I hit my own neck.
I bought it.
It's very embarrassing.
Don't say that.
My neck hurts.
I'm doing my best, but it doesn't hurt at all.
I'm not used to being looked at.
Are you lonely to be alone?
I'll go out with you.
Look at me.
I'm just looking at you.
Your neck is getting harder.
Do you understand?
It's tickling.
This side, too.
It tickles my neck, too.
It feels good.
I'm moving a lot.
Do you want me to do a lot of things for you?
It's tickling.
It's delicious.
My tongue is getting numb.
It tickles.
Look at this panties.
It tickles my neck.
It tickles.
It's getting harder.
Don't touch me.
I'm just looking at you.
Your nipples are like this.
It's slimy, isn't it?
You can smell it.
I'm out of breath.
It feels good.
I'm rubbing your face.
Are your hands moving well?
I'm going to make you a woman.
It feels good.
It's getting harder.
I'll give you a countdown.
Are you going to sleep?
It's zero.
I knew it.
I feel sorry for you.
Were you preparing to sleep?
I'm sorry.
You're so slimy.
I feel sorry for you.
I'll just make a countdown.
Are you going to sleep?
I'll make a countdown.
Did you make a countdown?
Don't talk yet.
Show me more.
I don't know what you're talking about, can you hear me?
I'm mumbling.
I'm sleepy.
I'm sorry.
I'm just looking at you.
I'm going to puke.
My fingers are going to puke.
I thought I was puking.
I thought I was puking in my stomach.
Can you hear me?
I didn't know you were going to say that.
I'm going to close my stomach.
My stomach is very wet.
Is this the result?
Is it delicious?
I'm going to stick my tongue out.
I'm hungry.
It feels good.
I'm going to puke.
Look where you're going.
I'm the only one who can go.
Do you understand?
I understand.
I'm going to puke.
I can't.
Look at me.
I'm going to puke.
I'm going to close my stomach.
I can't stand it.
Do you want to puke?
Do you want me to puke?
I want you to be hot.
I want you to puke a lot.
You're so pure.
It's hot.
It's a waste.
I spilled it all.
It's hot.
Come here.
This is not the end.
It's hot.
I want to puke more.
I kissed your whole body.
It's hot.
It feels good to be angry.
Do you lick me to that extent?
It's delicious.
It's hot.
I'm sweating.
You're so kind.
I'll lick you.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's cold.
Do you like to be kissed on your mother's body?
I love it.
I'm glad.
You're a good boy.
It's hot.
Do you lick me to that extent?
It's delicious.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Do you like to be angry?
Is it painful?
Do you like to be kissed on your mother's body?
I can feel your throat.
It's cute.
It's hot.
You're a good boy.
Do you like to be kissed on your mother's body?
I love it.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I love it.
It feels good.
It's painful.
It's hot.
Do you like to be kissed on your mother's body?
It feels good.
I love to be kissed on your mother's body.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I was attacked.
It's hot.
I'll kiss you.
You like to be kissed on your mother's body, don't you?
Yes.
Why do you like to be kissed on your mother's body?
I want to melt everything.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's painful.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
It's painful.
I can't breathe.
My chest is out of breath.
It's hot.
Do you want to sleep?
I'm alone.
I'm out of breath.
It feels good.
My chest is out of breath.
I don't want to sleep.
I'm out of breath.
My fingers are moving.
It's hot.
If I drink so much, I'll get a pimple.
I'll get a pimple.
I haven't put it in my house yet, but it's still there.
It's hot.
It's still there.
I'll get it all out for you.
But it smells bad.
It's hot.
It's delicious.
It's a pimple.
I didn't expect it to be this hard.
It's in my boobs, too.
It's a soft pimple.
It feels good.
It's in my boobs.
What do you want to do?
Are you okay?
I can't do it.
I put it in here.
Can you touch me?
I can't do it.
It tickles.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
No, you can't cry.
You'll cry.
I'm sorry.
You can't cry.
I'm so sorry.
I've cried a lot.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I got hit in the stomach.
I can't.
I'm getting bigger.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm such a fool.
I can see you're panting.
I just took a shit.
You're so stiff.
You're a bad boy.
I can't do it anymore.
My hips are moving.
It's so intense.
It's so frustrating.
I can't do it anymore.
Can you still see me?
I can see you're panting.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I can't do it anymore.
Come here.
You're so stiff.
I can't do it anymore.
It feels good.
Naka!
Naka, what's wrong?
I told you not to do it!
Why did you do it?
Because I couldn't stand it.
Naka!
I can't forgive you for making me so pale.
Can you do it more?
Come here.
It's so hot.
It hurts so much.
It feels so good.
I can't stand it.
I can't stand it anymore.
Stop it!
It hurts so much.
Does it feel good?
He's licking his eyes.
It feels so good.
It's so hot.
I can't stand it anymore.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's so dirty.
It's so hot.
I can't stand it anymore.